<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Piracy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/piracy/</link><description>Recent content in Piracy on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/piracy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The US has published the 2016 Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</guid><description>The Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR) has released its annual Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets report. The 2016 review calls attention to online and physical marketplaces around the world that reportedly engage in or facilitate significant copyright infringement and trademark counterfeiting.
USTR Michael Froman emphasized the problem of piracy and counterfeiting in online markets, saying that governments need to address these issues throughout the supply chain to protect consumers from unsafe products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>60% of software installations in APAC are unlicensed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-software-installations-in-apac-are-unlicensed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:44:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-software-installations-in-apac-are-unlicensed/</guid><description>In 2013, the Asia Pacific region had the world&amp;rsquo;s highest rate of unlicensed PC software installations at 62%, resulting in an estimated US$21 billion in lost revenue, according to the BSA Global Software Survey.
The Middle East and Africa followed closely with a rate of 59%, mirroring Central and Eastern Europe. Latin America also reported 59%, while North America and Western Europe had lower rates at 19% and 29% respectively. Globally, the average rate of unlicensed software installations was 43%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-software-installations-in-apac-are-unlicensed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-software-installations-in-apac-are-unlicensed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The expense of utilizing unlicensed software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-expense-of-utilizing-unlicensed-software/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 08:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-expense-of-utilizing-unlicensed-software/</guid><description>The recent 2018 Global Software Survey from BSA | The Software Alliance, titled Software Management: Security Imperative, Business Opportunity, supports the findings of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Asia PC Test Purchase Sweep. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s study revealed that a significant number of PCs in Asia, approximately four out of five (83%), are equipped with pirated software.
Tarun Sawney, the Senior Director for Asia Pacific at BSA, highlighted the persistent issue of unlicensed software. Globally, unlicensed software constitutes 37% of all software installed on personal computers, marking a 2% decrease from 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-expense-of-utilizing-unlicensed-software/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-expense-of-utilizing-unlicensed-software/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>