<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GetResponse on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/getresponse/</link><description>Recent content in GetResponse on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/getresponse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GetResponse introduces its email marketing platform in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>GetResponse, an email marketing platform, has officially launched in the ASEAN region. The company enhanced its cloud-based platform earlier this year to include support for Chinese, Malay, and Thai languages. This move has contributed to a significant 41.6% surge in new account registrations. GetResponse has observed a 35.8% year-over-year growth in email marketing activities within ASEAN.
Source: GetResponse website.
Simon Grabowski, CEO of GetResponse, emphasized the significance of email marketing, especially for small and medium-sized businesses working with limited budgets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>