<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Glassdoor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/glassdoor/</link><description>Recent content in Glassdoor on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:13:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/glassdoor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glassdoor has released a list of the top 10 workplaces in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</guid><description>The job and recruiting website Glassdoor has revealed the winners of its annual Employees’ Choice Awards, which included a category for Singapore for the first time.
These awards recognize the Best Places to Work in 2020 across nine countries, including Singapore. The rankings are determined by the input of employees who anonymously share their experiences through company reviews on Glassdoor. This feedback encompasses their job, work environment, and employer over the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>