<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Connected on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/connected/</link><description>Recent content in Connected on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:30:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/connected/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intel Security has released a list of the holiday gifts that are most vulnerable to hacking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</guid><description>· A survey indicates that 80% of shoppers are anticipated to make purchases online this year.
· While 85% of consumers begin utilizing connected devices within a day of obtaining them, a mere 45% report taking the appropriate security precautions.
· Despite acknowledging the significance of device security, nearly half of consumers (46%) are unsure if they are implementing adequate protective measures.
Intel Security has released its second yearly McAfee Most Hackable Holiday Gifts list, aiming to spotlight potential security vulnerabilities linked to popular gift items this holiday season.</description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay.</description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway.</description></item><item><title>Helping Your Business Achieve Hyperconnectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It took a whole generation to connect the entire world to the internet. Now, get ready for an even bigger change: we&amp;rsquo;re moving towards hyperconnectivity, and it&amp;rsquo;s happening fast.
Everything, Everywhere, All at Once
Hyperconnectivity means that anything and anyone who can be connected will be connected all the time. We&amp;rsquo;ve already shifted from logging in to having always-on internet for our computers and phones. The next step is to let our devices communicate with each other without us.</description></item><item><title>China Telecom is conducting a trial of a connected car concept in partnership with Gemalto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</guid><description>Gemalto, a digital security company, and China Telecom, a major Chinese mobile operator, are collaborating on a connected car project. They are using Gemalto&amp;rsquo;s LinqUs On-Demand Connectivity (ODC) subscription management solution.
The companies recently demonstrated at Mobile World Congress Shanghai how remote provisioning can securely connect mobile devices. They plan to apply this ODC solution to vehicles. This would allow China Telecom&amp;rsquo;s automotive clients to provide their customers with instant in-car connectivity.</description></item></channel></rss>