<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SSL on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ssl/</link><description>Recent content in SSL on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ssl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Different Types of VPN Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 04:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</guid><description>You prioritize the privacy of your network, but what happens when you need to connect to the outside world? Do you let anyone and everyone in, or do you secure your network across the distance using a private or virtually private network?
Before Virtual Private Networks (VPNs), there were private networks, and they still exist. Some situations demand such high security that the only way to guarantee control and prevent intrusions is through dedicated, point-to-point private lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Private Network Definition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</guid><description>While everyone understands the concept of a network, the meaning of a virtual private network (VPN) can be a bit unclear. Essentially, a VPN is a real network that utilizes technology to make its privacy seem virtual. For instance, the internet is inherently public, but methods exist to enhance the privacy of online communications, making them &amp;ldquo;virtually&amp;rdquo; private.
A genuinely private network necessitates stringent access control. Only authorized individuals and devices should be granted access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>