<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AEC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aec/</link><description>Recent content in AEC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The ASEAN Economic Community has the potential to be a goldmine for B2C businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, has published a white paper outlining a strategic framework for marketing to ASEAN consumers.
The establishment of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in December 2015 will unify the ten ASEAN member states into a single market and production hub. This development is anticipated to draw significant attention from multinational corporations that have traditionally focused on China and India. Euromonitor suggests that the AEC is on track to become a global economic powerhouse due to its projected robust economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new executive board of the EU-ASEAN Business Council has been elected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (EU-ABC), the leading advocate for European companies in the ASEAN region, recently selected its Executive Board for the next two years. The election took place at their annual general meeting in Hanoi, Vietnam, on June 1st.
The new board members are:
François Guibert, Executive Vice-President, President, Greater China and South Asia Region, STMicroelectronics (Chairman) Donald Kanak, Chairman, Prudential Corporation Asia (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Theodoor Bakker, Partner, ABNR Law, Indonesia; Executive Board Member, European Chamber of Commerce, Indonesia (Chamber Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Martin Hayes, President, Robert Bosch SEA (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Treasurer), and Jan B...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB discusses its regional strategies for participating in the ASEAN Economic Community</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. Chairman of CIMB Group, YBhg Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Nazir Razak (right) and Director, Southeast Asia of The Economist Intelligence Unit Justin Wood showcasing the special report Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia.
CIMB partnered with the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) to publish a report titled Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia. This independent management brief, co-sponsored by CIMB and Baker McKenzie, aims to equip companies for the upcoming launch of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) on December 31, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EY identifies obstacles that are impeding the effectiveness of the AEC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</guid><description>Political, legal, and organizational difficulties, regulatory burdens, and a lack of standardized trade regulations among ASEAN nations are hindering the progress of the 2007 ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) Blueprint. This plan aims to achieve regional economic integration by 2015, according to EY.
A recent EY report, &amp;ldquo;Trade Secrets: ASEAN economic community and inward investment,&amp;rdquo; examines the AEC&amp;rsquo;s development from a business standpoint, specifically focusing on obstacles to conducting business within ASEAN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>