<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CoS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cos/</link><description>Recent content in CoS on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking Providers Want Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 12:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>The telephone industry is undergoing a transformation. Previously, businesses typically relied on in-house PBX systems to manage their phone networks and utilized ISDN PRI trunk lines for external calls. However, this is changing rapidly.
Two significant trends are emerging: cloud-based hosted PBX telephone systems and SIP trunking. While these technologies complement each other, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to implement SIP trunking without cloud services.
A telephone trunk consists of multiple phone lines grouped together, either physically or electronically...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transforming the WAN Into The Smart WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</guid><description>People tend to think of WAN connections as basic channels for data, similar to how Senator Ted Stevens once described the internet. However, with the shift from on-site data centers to cloud-based systems, VoIP, and video streaming, our needs have outgrown this simple model. This is where the concept of a Smart WAN comes into play.
Instead of treating all data equally, a Smart WAN prioritizes different types of data through a system called Class of Service (CoS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should You Buy VoIP as a Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</guid><description>Cloud-based services, including Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), have been around for a while. What&amp;rsquo;s becoming more popular now is the trend of large businesses connecting their different locations using SIP Trunks and all sizes of businesses choosing to outsource their PBX functionality. This can be considered VoIP as a Service.
Many home and small business users adopted cloud-based VoIP early on to cut costs. They did this by replacing their traditional phone lines and using their broadband internet connection for both high-speed internet and phone service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs EoC vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</guid><description>Not long ago, businesses seeking a dedicated, symmetrical bandwidth line had only one option: T1. However, the landscape has changed with the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and SIP Trunks. While options like DSL, Cable, satellite, and 3G wireless offer shared and asymmetrical bandwidth, and DS3, SONET, and Ethernet over Fiber provide higher bandwidths at higher costs, they fall outside the scope of this comparison.
Similar to their copper-based counterparts, Ethernet over Fiber, DS3, and SONET are higher bandwidth alternatives to EoC, T1, and SIP Trunks, respectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>