<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call Centers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call-centers/</link><description>Recent content in Call Centers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:11:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call-centers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud vs Premises Contact Center Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</guid><description>Lots of small businesses can get by with just a local or toll-free number for customer calls. But as companies grow, they usually dedicate staff and resources to handle customer interactions, creating a dedicated department known as a contact center. While contact centers are important, they can be expensive to run. Is there a way to reduce the cost?
Until recently, outsourcing to different locations was an option, but that often led to issues with language barriers and inconsistent service quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Services Proliferate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</guid><description>The increasing need for bandwidth in the business world has driven the rapid expansion of high-speed voice and data services. While T1 lines were once considered high-end, businesses now have a variety of options, including various DSx copper and fiber optic connections, wireless broadband, and even point-to-point laser technology.
DS3 is gaining popularity as companies find their T1 connections inadequate. Upgrading from a DS1&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 Mbps to DS3&amp;rsquo;s 45 Mbps accommodates more users and allows for dedicated internet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet DS3 Bandwidth Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has grown continuously since T1 lines became the norm for dedicated internet access and private point-to-point connections. If you currently use DS3 bandwidth services or are thinking about an upgrade, comparing your wide area network (WAN) bandwidth choices is essential.
DS3, a 45 Mbps service, represents the traditional high-bandwidth network connection and is equivalent in speed to a T3 line. These days, most DS3 services are delivered via fiber optic cables, with a copper handoff point at the demarcation point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why, Oh Why, PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</guid><description>You might know the terms PRI, T1 PRI, Telephone PRI, PRI Trunk, or ISDN PRI, but what do they actually mean, and why choose this service?
PRI stands for Primary Rate Interface. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN or Integrated Services Digital Network and is a step up from BRI or Basic Rate Interface. Simply put, PRI is a digital line connecting to your PBX phone system. It combines numerous phone lines into a single digital line, leading to cost savings on monthly phone bills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reducing Call Center Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 23:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/</guid><description>Running a call center, whether onshore or offshore, comes with inherent costs. While labor is a significant factor, telecommunications expenses shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be overlooked, especially with larger centers. These expenses can quickly escalate due to high call volumes and data usage.
Fortunately, there are ways to reduce these costs without compromising service quality. Many assume they already have the best deals on voice and data services, especially with high usage. However, this might not be the case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Telephony Has Many Flavors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</guid><description>Initially designed for high-volume call transfer between telephone exchanges, T1 technology has evolved into a leading digital phone solution for businesses. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering T1, understanding the available options is crucial.
T1 is a digital standard supporting voice, data, video, or a combination thereof. Originally, it carried 24 separate calls on individual channels called DS0s, collectively forming a T1 line or DS1. Each DS0 transmits digitized voice, call control, and signaling information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How AI is Helping to Improve Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Customer service calls are increasingly frustrating due to rising costs and labor shortages, negatively impacting both customers and companies. Tech expert David Pogue, in a CBS News report, suggests a blend of human agents and AI as a solution.
One such AI, called Grace, can handle customer interactions independently. However, AI like Grace can falter in complex situations, necessitating a transfer to human agents. While some of the best agents are located internationally and may have accents, this can be a hurdle for some US customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Centers Move To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems are gaining popularity as a replacement for traditional phone systems. Businesses are recognizing the benefits of moving their phone systems to the cloud. So why aren&amp;rsquo;t call centers embracing this technology?
Actually, some call centers are already using cloud-based systems. Smaller and geographically dispersed call centers are more likely to transition from physical to cloud-based phone systems. Larger call centers face more challenges in adopting this technology because their needs extend beyond basic phone functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>