<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Center on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-center/</link><description>Recent content in Data Center on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Infrastructure as a Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</guid><description>Cloud computing is widely understood to have three main levels: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS). The most fundamental of these is IaaS, which forms the basis for the other two. IaaS essentially refers to providing basic hardware and operating system software over the internet.
Infrastructure is fairly self-explanatory: it&amp;rsquo;s the foundational hardware and software needed for computing. When considering cloud infrastructure, the comparison is often made with having your own data center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When It Comes to Computer Networks, Trust No One and No Thing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security is a major concern for businesses today. One might even miss the days of isolated computers, unconnected to any network.
However, even those isolated computers weren&amp;rsquo;t entirely secure. Malware could still spread and confidential files could be copied through physical transfer of files using floppy disks. The challenge today is that modern networks, encompassing local networks, data centers, multiple cloud platforms, and the internet, make it incredibly difficult to track who is accessing the network and their intentions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Neutral Connectivity at Colocation Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses struggling to find enough bandwidth might be overlooking a simpler solution. Instead of waiting for carriers to come to them, companies can benefit by going where the carriers already are.
Colocation Centers: A Hub for Connectivity
Carriers are drawn to locations called colocation centers, or colos, and carrier hotels. These large data centers are designed to accommodate multiple tenants, unlike typical data centers that serve a single company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Diverse Connections For Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</guid><description>The reliability of data connections is crucial for data centers and colocation facilities to ensure service availability. Having multiple separate network connections is not enough; you need multiple diverse data connections from different providers that take different routes to your facility.
Simply having multiple connections from a single provider offers limited protection because a catastrophic failure could take down the entire connection. This risk is amplified in your own facility, where a single connection runs for miles and is vulnerable to disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Types of Clouds You Should Know About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud-based IT services might leave you wondering if you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. To help you decide, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the three primary cloud types and which applications are well-suited for cloud environments.
These days, it seems everyone is offering cloud services, primarily based on three architectures: public, private, and hybrid clouds.
The most common is the public cloud, a specialized data center owned and operated by a provider serving numerous paying customers concurrently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Booming For Telx Interconnection and Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</guid><description>Despite the current economic downturn, data center provider Telx is experiencing a surge in construction at their main Chicago facility. This might seem counterintuitive during a recession, but it makes sense considering the ongoing technological transformation in business and finance.
Companies have shifted from manual processes to computer-based systems, leading to a client-server model that boosted efficiency and productivity. Now, forward-thinking companies are seeking new strategies for a competitive edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Concentric Cloud Solutions Virtualizes Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been bombarded with information about virtualization, unsure if it can help control unpredictable business expenses. You might feel overwhelmed about the process of deploying virtualization. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry, Concentric can guide you through it.
Initially confined to local data centers, virtualization has migrated to the cloud. The fundamental concept is maximizing hardware performance. This is achieved by making a single server function as multiple servers, or transforming a cluster of smaller servers into a powerful computing unit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth For Remote Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</guid><description>Businesses need to have a solid plan to safeguard their important data. While basic backups on disks or tapes can help with minor issues like a crashed computer, they are inadequate for major events like natural disasters. Offsite backup is crucial in these situations.
The key is choosing a location geographically distant from your primary site to avoid shared risks. Backing up data across regional offices, separated by significant distances, enhances data protection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting With a Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve considered cloud computing as a potential solution for your business but hesitate due to the investment and commitment. Now, a free trial for cloud hosting presents the perfect opportunity to explore its benefits.
Cloud hosting is a practical step for businesses exceeding their shared hosting capacity and considering VPS or dedicated servers. Cloud hosting surpasses these alternatives by offering flexibility and cost advantages.
VPS and dedicated servers eliminate the need for capital expenditures and infrastructure management associated with running a data center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefit From The Great CAPEX to OPEX Migration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world, moving away from traditional capital expenditures (CAPEX) towards operational expenses (OPEX). This change, although seemingly subtle, represents a fundamental shift with far-reaching implications for businesses of all sizes.
Businesses incur both capital and operational expenses. Operational expenses are the costs of daily operations, like utilities, supplies, and salaries. Capital expenses, however, are long-term investments, such as purchasing buildings or major equipment. An example of this is an in-house PBX telephone system, which might soon be replaced by an operational expense alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Demand a SAS 70 Type II Data Center?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-demand-a-sas-70-type-ii-data-center/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-demand-a-sas-70-type-ii-data-center/</guid><description>When choosing a cloud or colocation provider, prioritize data privacy and security, especially in regulated sectors like healthcare and finance. A facility with SAS 70 Type II compliance can offer this assurance.
SAS 70, based on the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA) Statement on Auditing Standards No. 70, Service Organizations, involves a rigorous audit of a company&amp;rsquo;s data handling practices by an independent firm. This audit results in a comprehensive written report...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-demand-a-sas-70-type-ii-data-center/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-demand-a-sas-70-type-ii-data-center/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes High Frequency Trading Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</guid><description>Computerized trading, including high frequency trading, is now the norm in the stock market. As seen on CBS News, algorithms can automatically execute trades when specific conditions are met.
A key challenge of automated trading is ensuring fairness by synchronizing timing for all participants. The New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) addressed this by creating a data center that standardized access time to 65 microseconds for everyone. However, this only applies to trading within the NYSE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Computing In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computing-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computing-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud computing&amp;rdquo; has become ubiquitous, but what does it entail and what are its advantages over traditional data centers?
Initially, cloud computing provided access to a network of computers for tasks that exceeded the capabilities of individual resources. A prime example is the SETI@Home program, which harnesses the idle processing power of countless personal computers connected through the internet to analyze radio telescope data in search of extraterrestrial life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computing-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computing-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantage of Colocation Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</guid><description>Companies frequently grapple with the decision of whether to handle a product or service internally or outsource it to a specialized vendor. This dilemma extends to telephone and computer services, demanding a careful evaluation of the most advantageous approach.
The optimal choice concerning technical services hinges significantly on your specific circumstances at any given moment. It is advisable to reassess these decisions periodically, perhaps annually. While the merits of internally managing your telephone and computer systems might be clear, it&amp;rsquo;s equally crucial to understand the upsides of outsourcing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>