<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/solar/</link><description>Recent content in Solar on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 04:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/solar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Green Hosting Reduces Environmental Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-hosting-reduces-environmental-issues/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 04:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-hosting-reduces-environmental-issues/</guid><description>World Environment Day encourages us to consider how we can lessen our environmental footprint. While this often evokes thoughts of making sacrifices, what if there were ways to gain advantages while simultaneously addressing environmental concerns? Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be an appealing approach?
Getting more for less is universally desired, and thankfully, we can achieve this by being discerning about the companies we support. Choosing environmentally conscious businesses doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily equate to higher costs; in fact, many responsible companies share the cost savings from their efficient practices with their customers.</description></item><item><title>Holy Guacamole, It's Green Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</guid><description>The internet&amp;rsquo;s days of excessive energy consumption might be ending. Websites and online businesses contribute to environmental issues, but we can&amp;rsquo;t just abandon the technology we rely on. We need a more sustainable solution: eco-friendly hosting.
The demand for electricity is increasing while clean energy sources are limited. Traditional power sources like coal are harmful, and even with reduced emissions, they still contribute to climate change. Renewable energy is becoming a viable solution.</description></item><item><title>Concentrating on Kickstarter: Making Solar Power Accessible to Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 10:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</guid><description>Spor Solar Charges aims to make convenient solar-powered battery charging accessible to everyone. Their product, Spor, is a portable battery charger for USB devices that can recharge itself using solar energy. It can also be powered up using a standard AC outlet. The company claims that Spor can charge multiple devices simultaneously and replenish a phone&amp;rsquo;s battery almost as quickly as a wall outlet, according to their Kickstarter page.
Source: Kickstarter.</description></item></channel></rss>