<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Performance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-performance/</link><description>Recent content in Network Performance on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:12:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High Reliability VoIP Phone Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</guid><description>The days of traditional phone lines, even ISDN PRI, are fading. Cloud-based systems and computer networks offer more adaptable, feature-rich, and cost-effective voice communication solutions. To tap into these advantages, adopting packet-based phone service, also known as VoIP, is key.
People&amp;rsquo;s feelings about VoIP as a replacement for traditional phone service are mixed, ranging from enthusiastic support to staunch opposition. This spectrum of opinions stems from individual experiences with the technology and when they first used it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Need for Low Latency Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</guid><description>When discussing network performance, bandwidth is often the primary focus. Higher bandwidth is equated with faster speeds, allowing for quicker file transfers and increased productivity. However, another crucial aspect of network performance, latency, has gained significant attention recently.
Latency refers to the time delay within a network, specifically the time it takes for data packets to travel between nodes. While it might seem related to bandwidth, latency is a distinct characteristic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Bandwidth Can Affect Productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</guid><description>Businesses are grappling with decisions about bandwidth allocation, often facing costs calculated per Megabit per second (Mbps). While strategies exist to maximize Mbps per dollar, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to first understand the correlation between network bandwidth and employee productivity.
If your bandwidth is primarily used for non-work activities, reducing it might seem like a productivity booster. However, most businesses rely heavily on internal and external network connectivity for operations. So, how do you determine the appropriate bandwidth level?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.0 Fiberizes Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Cable companies have been envious of Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS fiber optic service because it surpasses the broadband capabilities of coaxial cable. However, a new upgrade to the DOCSIS cable broadband standard might change that. This upgrade boosts digital download speeds to rival those of fiber optic connections, all without needing a fiber optic line to the home.
DOCSIS, which stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification, is the standard for cable modems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>