<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SMS Audio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sms-audio/</link><description>Recent content in SMS Audio on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sms-audio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>