<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Syria on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/syria/</link><description>Recent content in Syria on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:42:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/syria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The program in the European Union that allows Syrian refugees in Turkey to seek humanitarian admission.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</guid><description>Laura Robbins-Wright
PhD Candidate in Government, London School of Economics and Political Science
On December 15, 2015, the European Commission put forward a suggestion for a program to offer humanitarian entry to Syrian refugees residing in Turkey. This proposal follows earlier EU initiatives, including a plan to relocate refugees within the EU and a program for resettling refugees from other countries. It also builds upon an action plan from October 2015 and a more recent decision to give €3 billion to a Refugee Facility designed to better coordinate aid for Syrian refugees in Turkey.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening and weakening the legal standing of individuals granted subsidiary protection under European Union law – the ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union in the case of Alo and Osso.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</guid><description>Dr. Louise Halleskov Storgaard, Assistant Professor, Aarhus University
Can a country that offers subsidiary protection (a form of protection similar to refugee status) restrict the movement of those beneficiaries within its borders if they receive social security benefits? This is the central question addressed by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Alo and Osso case on March 1, 2015. The CJEU’s answer is notable, innovative, and potentially contentious as it reinforces the influence of the Geneva Convention on subsidiary protection standards but also raises questions about the applicable non-discrimination standard.</description></item></channel></rss>