<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notebook on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/notebook/</link><description>Recent content in Notebook on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/notebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lenovo issues global recall for Thinkpad batteries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</guid><description>Lenovo has expanded a battery recall that was first announced on March 27, 2014. This recall now includes all affected lithium-ion batteries globally. The batteries, as announced in late April 2015, were manufactured for ThinkPad notebook computers shipped between February 2010 and June 2012.
Lenovo stated that they are offering free-of-charge replacement batteries for all recalled batteries in the interest of public safety.
The batteries were sold with new notebook computers or as optional or replacement batteries for the following models:</description></item><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration.</description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new laptops and monitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</guid><description>Dell Singapore has launched new laptops and a monitor for consumers.
The XPS 12 is the first 2-in-1 laptop with a 4K Ultra HD display. The Inspiron 11 3000 series offers an affordable and portable laptop option available in three colors. Dell also released their first 4K consumer monitor, the Dell 28 Ultra HD 4K Monitor.
&amp;ldquo;Consumers have increasingly diverse needs. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a student or a professional, size, power, design, and price all matter.</description></item><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series.</description></item><item><title>The ASUS EeeBook X205 is now available for purchase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</guid><description>ASUS has introduced the EeeBook X205 to the Indian market. This 11.6-inch ultraportable laptop is designed to offer a user experience similar to a smartphone and is well-suited for young professionals.
The EeeBook X205 features &amp;ldquo;connected standby technology,&amp;rdquo; allowing for near-instantaneous wake-up from sleep mode and continuous social connectivity, even in standby. Equipped with a quad-core Intel Atom processor, the laptop comes with Windows 8.1 with Bing and is offered in four colors: dark blue, white, gold, and red.</description></item><item><title>HP's Elite business PCs excel in performance, productivity, and security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 22:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</guid><description>HP has introduced its latest Elite business PCs, including the exceptionally thin and light HP EliteBook 705 series, an all-in-one (AiO) model, and a refreshed desktop lineup featuring the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest business-class desktop.
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the demand for high-end Elite notebook innovation to be extended to a wider range of employees and devices. HP&amp;rsquo;s response is the Elite 705 and 800 Series PCs, which bring sleek design, enhanced collaboration features, and robust security to mainstream business devices.</description></item><item><title>HP introduces the thinnest laptop in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</guid><description>Every Spectre accessory has been designed to provide a luxurious experience.
The CNC machined aluminum body is as sleek as an AAA battery at a mere 10.4mm. Enjoy exceptional performance with Intel Core i5 and i7 processors. Immerse yourself in the vibrant visuals of a full HD 13.3&amp;quot; edge-to-edge display complemented by Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen sound. HP claims to have developed the slimmest laptop globally, meticulously refining every detail to provide an unmatched user experience and peak performance.</description></item><item><title>HP Stream notebooks include a complimentary one-year subscription to Office 365 and OneDrive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new notebook PCs to its HP Stream line of lightweight, cloud-based Windows devices. HP emphasizes affordability, offering these thin and light notebooks at a lower price point than typically seen.
Source: HP. The HP Stream notebooks come in horizon blue and orchid magenta.
“Consumers today want mobile devices that reflect their style and empower them to work and play from anywhere,” says Serena Yong, General Manager for Printing &amp;amp; Personal Systems at HP Singapore and Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>HP updates Pavilion features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pavilion PCs, including convertibles and notebooks, designed to be stylish and powerful. The company aims to provide customers with a range of options to suit their needs and budgets.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that HP understands customers&amp;rsquo; diverse needs, with some prioritizing portability and others seeking performance. The redesigned Pavilion PCs cater to both, offering affordability and style.</description></item><item><title>Huawei will be offering laptops for sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore customers can purchase the HUAWEI MateBook 13 and MateBook X Pro starting May 30, 2019.
The HUAWEI P30 Pro in Amber Sunrise will be offered for models with 512 GB of storage.
The Huawei Consumer Business Group Singapore has revealed its plan to expand its product lineup in Singapore beyond smartphones and smartwatches to include laptops. This new laptop selection features the latest HUAWEI MateBook 13 and MateBook X Pro.</description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure.</description></item><item><title>Acer introduces new convertible notebooks, the Aspire R 13 and R 14</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</guid><description>Acer has introduced two new convertible notebook lines, the Aspire R 13 and Aspire R 14 Series, both capable of transitioning between various notebook and tablet modes. These notebooks are designed for users seeking the functionality of a traditional notebook with added flexibility.
Source: Acer. The R 13 in one mode.
Acer&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Jason Chen, stated that their objective is to exceed expectations with their products at every price point. He believes these Aspire convertibles are ideal for users who require both portability and productivity.</description></item><item><title>HP has released a variety of mobile solutions to enhance business productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</guid><description>HP has introduced a suite of commercial mobility solutions aimed at boosting workplace productivity. The offerings include eight new mobile devices and accessories designed to simplify business processes.
Anneliese Olson, HP Asia-Pacific and Japan VP and GM of Personal Computing, highlighted how these products address evolving workplace dynamics, workforce trends, and work styles, ultimately reshaping workflows.
HP has developed a comprehensive mobility solution catering to diverse businesses, including those in specialized sectors like education, field service, healthcare, public safety, and retail.</description></item><item><title>The Apple Macbook is revolutionizing the laptop industry with its numerous innovative features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apple-macbook-is-revolutionizing-the-laptop-industry-with-its-numerous-innovative-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 02:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apple-macbook-is-revolutionizing-the-laptop-industry-with-its-numerous-innovative-features/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The new MacBook is offered in three aluminum finishes—gold, silver, and space gray. Its thickest point measures 13.1 mm.
Apple has introduced the redesigned MacBook, a new notebook lineup representing the thinnest and lightest Macs to date. Every aspect of the new MacBook has been meticulously redesigned to achieve a remarkably thin and light profile, weighing a mere two pounds and measuring a mere 13.1 mm thick.</description></item><item><title>Acer unveils three convertible notebooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</guid><description>Acer has expanded its line of 2-in-1 notebooks with the new 11.6&amp;quot; Aspire Switch 11 series and a new Switch 10 featuring a 1080p Full HD 10.1&amp;quot; display. The Aspire Switch 2-in-1 series combines a Microsoft Windows notebook and tablet in one device.
Source: Acer. The Aspire Switch 10.
The Aspire Switch series is thin, lightweight, and durable, designed for work and travel. It supports four modes: touch, typing, viewing, and sharing.</description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights.</description></item></channel></rss>