<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Email on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-email/</link><description>Recent content in Business Email on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:32:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A New Cloud In IT Managed Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</guid><description>Many businesses are seriously considering migrating their IT infrastructure to cloud-based managed solutions. The key question then becomes: which cloud platform is the right fit? One compelling option is the &amp;ldquo;new cloud.&amp;rdquo;
NewCloud Networks, a managed service provider established in 1988, offers comprehensive solutions ranging from voice and data services for small businesses to intricate national and international networking solutions.
NewCloud differentiates itself by providing bespoke solutions tailored to specific client needs, rather than forcing a one-size-fits-all approach.</description></item><item><title>UK Domains and Web Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-domains-and-web-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-domains-and-web-hosting/</guid><description>Network Solutions, a leading provider of domain registration and web hosting, offers a wide range of services tailored for users in the United Kingdom. These services extend beyond .co.uk domain names to include web hosting, email hosting for businesses, SSL certificates, and design and marketing solutions, catering to both UK-focused and global businesses.
](http://www.tkqlhce.com/click-1726600-10868378) While .uk is the UK&amp;rsquo;s designated country code top-level domain (ccTLD), registering a .uk domain differs from registering a .</description></item></channel></rss>