<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vr/</link><description>Recent content in VR on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The future was examined at the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>The second day of the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong brought together over 50 prominent figures from various industries to discuss the future of living. The event, which ran until March 24th, featured experts, business leaders, and creatives sharing their insights with attendees from around the world.
With a focus on the prediction that 70% of the global population will reside in urban areas by 2050, the festival examined the implications for how we live, eat, travel, and interact with the natural world through panels and demonstrations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HALCYON VR murder mystery from Syfy will soon be accessible on the Samsung Gear VR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</guid><description>Source: Syfy. HALCYON investigates a VR murder.
Syfy, known for its imaginative entertainment, will debut its unique hybrid virtual reality (VR) series, HALCYON, on September 22nd at 10 pm. The series is a creation of Secret Location, a multi-award-winning content studio specializing in cutting-edge platforms.
Set in 2040, HALCYON centers on Julie Dover, a detective in the Virtual Reality Crimes Unit. She tackles the first-ever murder within virtual reality, a seemingly impossible crime, and unravels the hidden conspiracy behind it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Keppel Land enhances marketing strategy with virtual show suites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</guid><description>Keppel Land is the first developer in Singapore to utilize Oculus Rift technology to create 360-degree immersive virtual reality (VR) show suites for its Highline Residences property. These two digitally rendered suites complement the three existing physical show suites at the Highline Residences showroom in Singapore.
The new VR platform, a collaboration between Keppel Land and visualisation firm VMW Group, features virtual tours of these new unit layouts. It also allows for a virtual exploration of key landmarks in the trendy Tiong Bahru neighborhood where Highline Residences is located...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience cutting-edge VR gaming at Bugis Junction and Bugis+, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</guid><description>This Halloween, shoppers at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bugis Junction and Bugis+ malls can participate in an immersive virtual reality (VR) gaming experience. This event marks the first time malls in Singapore have hosted a VR experience of this magnitude.
The &amp;ldquo;Time Zombies&amp;rdquo; competition invites shoppers to assume the roles of time-traveling detectives. Their mission: to stop the nefarious Dr. Virago, a mad scientist attempting to unleash a zombie apocalypse. This competition utilizes cutting-edge Arctic Fox wireless technology, allowing players to move freely within the virtual world using a wireless headset, eliminating the need for cumbersome cables or backpack computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover Emirates aircraft in 3D</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates pioneers VR experience on its website.
Emirates has become the first airline to use web-based virtual reality (VR) technology. They&amp;rsquo;ve added 3D seat models to emirates.com.
This 3D model shows a 360-degree view of the inside of their A380 and Boeing 777 aircraft. It allows customers to view the Economy, Business, and First Class cabins, as well as the onboard lounge and shower spa on the A380...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Windows device will soon enhance your creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The possibilities of Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, sketched on a Microsoft Surface by Michael Mindflyer.
Microsoft has launched the latest version of its operating system, the Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, offering it as a free upgrade to current Windows 10 users globally. This update, the fourth major one for Windows 10, prioritizes creativity. It aims to make mixed reality and 3D design accessible to Windows users, leading to improvements in gaming, audiovisual content, and mixed reality experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>