<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Movement of Persons on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-persons/</link><description>Recent content in Free Movement of Persons on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-persons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What impact could Brexit have on the younger generation? EU Referendum Briefing 2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A UK exit from the European Union, or &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; could have significant implications for young people, impacting their education, travel opportunities, and economic prospects.
Education
The EU does not control educational content or matters like tuition costs. Instead, its involvement lies in cross-border educational aspects, including promoting student and teacher mobility through initiatives like the Erasmus program. Established in 1987, this EU law-based program facilitates student exchanges across various educational levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Brexit Causing the British Mind to Close? The Impact on EU Academics and Government Guidance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Brexit vote is often seen as an attack on both academic expertise and EU citizens in the UK, whether accurate or not. These two issues intersect in a recent dispute involving the Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO) and the London School of Economics (LSE). The FCO allegedly barred EU citizens from advising the government on Brexit, though the details are unclear.
The LSE reportedly informed staff that the FCO no longer sought Brexit advice from EU nationals, sparking a controversy that made its way to social media and prominent news outlets like The Guardian...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the free movement of people in the European Economic Area (EEA) distinct from that in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Karin Fløistad: PhD Candidate, European University Institute; practicing lawyer at Norwegian law firm Simonsen Vogt Wiig
The UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit relationship with the EU often involves discussions about the free movement of people, with the EEA Agreement frequently cited as a potential model. This piece will analyze two key distinctions between the EEA Agreement&amp;rsquo;s approach to the free movement of people and that of full EU membership.
The EEA Agreement integrates the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market with three members of the European Free Trade Association (EFTA): Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>No Longer Negotiable: The Rights of EU and UK Citizens Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 04:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
This post examines the findings of a British Future inquiry into the post-Brexit status of EU citizens in the UK. It outlines the inquiry&amp;rsquo;s key recommendations concerning EU citizens residing in the UK after Brexit, proposes recommendations for UK citizens in the EU after Brexit, and analyzes the concept of &amp;lsquo;associate citizenship&amp;rsquo; for UK citizens post-Brexit. The latter two points, while outside the inquiry&amp;rsquo;s scope, are addressed in parallel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it appropriate to question the credibility of research conducted by academics whose institutions receive funding from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 08:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Some Eurosceptics suggest that research should be disregarded if the academics involved or their institutions have received EU funding, especially if that research contradicts Eurosceptic viewpoints. This tactic has been used against both recent research on the positive impacts of free movement of EU citizens and me personally. While it&amp;rsquo;s tempting to ignore these accusations, they are frequently used to discredit objective evidence supporting pro-European arguments, particularly in the context of a potential referendum on British exit from the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An important Irish ruling on compensation for violation of EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) affirmed the right of individuals to sue Member States for damages resulting from breaches of EU law over two decades ago in the Francovich case, most subsequent lawsuits have been initiated by businesses seeking compensation for financial losses. The CJEU has yet to address a case involving damages claims related to the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is this the beginning of the end for citizens' rights in the Brexit 'Sufficient Progress' deal?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent joint report on Brexit negotiations, along with accompanying documents, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of discussions. This phase will center around a transition period and the framework for the future relationship between the UK and the EU.
Although a political rather than legal document, this report holds significant practical relevance for the withdrawal agreement. It outlines agreed-upon details concerning citizens&amp;rsquo; rights, the Irish border, the financial settlement, and concluding rules...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Questions &amp; Answers about EU Free Movement Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We shouldn&amp;rsquo;t create a misleading impression of the law.&amp;rdquo;
(Measure for Measure, 2.1.1)
Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School, University of York
Laurent Pech, Professor of European Law, Jean Monnet Chair of EU Public Law at Middlesex University London
This article clarifies common misunderstandings about EU free movement rules, often found in British media. We believe much criticism targets a distorted view of the actual system.
The UK shows a desire to restrict EU freedom of movement, yet misinterpretations about these rules persist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement Analysis 2: Transition Period</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Now that a revised Brexit withdrawal agreement is available, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to revisit my prior analyses of the initial agreement. This post, updating my spring 2018 analysis, focuses on the transition period outlined in the agreement. (The revised agreement includes changes to the Irish border protocol and the political declaration on the future relationship.) This post will provide context for the transition period and then break down the text...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a 'fast-track' Treaty amendment on the free movement of workers with the Cameron express?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Experts in EU law see Treaty amendments as a monumental event. After the Treaty of Lisbon, significant changes to the Treaty seemed improbable in the near future. However, this prospect is becoming more likely due to David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s push to renegotiate free movement regulations within the EU, a sentiment somewhat shared by the UK Labour party.
This brings us to the crucial question of what form such a Treaty amendment would take...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The historical context of the Dano judgment: Free movement and social benefits for economically inactive EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 12:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Géraldine Renaudière, Trainee at the CJEU, within the cabinet of the Court Vice-President, Koen Lenaerts. (This post reflects the author&amp;rsquo;s view only).
The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s recent ruling in Elisabeta Dano and Florin Dano v Jobcenter Leipzig revisits the sensitive issue of national laws that prevent economically inactive EU citizens from receiving special non-contributory benefits, even though those benefits are available to nationals in similar situations. Issued a year after the controversial Brey decision, this judgment aims to clarify the connection between Directive 2004/38, which concerns the free movement of EU citizens, and Regulation 883/2004, which deals with coordinating social security systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ensuring the Smooth Movement of People: Emergency Brake (Part 3)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-smooth-movement-of-people-emergency-brake-part-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-smooth-movement-of-people-emergency-brake-part-3/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
*Both authors work at the University of Cambridge and receive funding from the ESRC&amp;rsquo;s UK in a Changing Europe program. A more detailed examination of some of these points can be found in Barnard and Fraser Butlin&amp;rsquo;s article, &amp;ldquo;Free movement v. Fair Movement: Brexit and Managed Migration,&amp;rdquo; published in the Common Market Law Review (2018) 55 Common Market Law Review 203.
Introduction
The first two entries in this blog series (available here and here) introduced our concept of &amp;ldquo;fair movement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-smooth-movement-of-people-emergency-brake-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-smooth-movement-of-people-emergency-brake-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU’s Patients’ Rights Directive in practice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</guid><description>Tamara Hervey, Professor of Law and Head of Law School, University of Sheffield
As Europe focuses on the immense refugee crisis, discussing other migration matters can seem trivial. However, this week also saw the release of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s report on the &amp;ldquo;Patients&amp;rsquo; Rights Directive.&amp;rdquo; This report reveals that the directive&amp;rsquo;s name is misleading, as its primary goal appears to be safeguarding national health systems instead of patients&amp;rsquo; rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's judgment on divorce and free movement law poses a problem.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Singh case tackles a crucial question: what happens to a non-EU spouse&amp;rsquo;s residency rights when their EU citizen partner, who moved to another EU country, leaves that country after their marriage ends? This case highlights a conflict within the EU Citizens’ Directive, where rules concerning divorce and departure clash. Unfortunately, the court chose a simplistic interpretation, aligning with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s prior suggestion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union rejects benefit tourism by EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant ruling in the case of Dano, which dealt with the ability of EU citizens to access social welfare benefits when they relocate to another Member State. The Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the laws in this case (and other rulings earlier this year involving EU citizens with criminal histories) suggests a stricter approach, possibly reflecting the ongoing political discussions regarding the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CS and Rendón Marín: Are Union Citizens and their Third-Country National Parents Experiencing a Revival of the Ruiz Zambrano Ruling?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</guid><description>Maria Haag, PhD Researcher, European University Institute (Florence, Italy) &amp;amp; Michigan Grotius Research Scholar, University of Michigan Law School (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
Background
Five years ago, a significant ruling in the case of C-34/09 Ruiz Zambrano was delivered by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The court found that national measures that hinder EU citizens from genuinely enjoying their rights as citizens are prohibited under Article 20 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial stances on the status of UK and EU citizens in the Brexit negotiations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Introduction
A crucial Brexit issue with potentially significant consequences for many is the fate of UK citizens in the EU and EU citizens in the UK post-Brexit. Addressed early in Brexit negotiations, both sides have established positions: the EU through a Council decision outlining the mandate for Commission negotiators on May 22, and the UK through a government proposal on June 26. Despite claims to the contrary, the UK&amp;rsquo;s proposal didn&amp;rsquo;t precede the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Love triumphs in the CJEU: Equal Marriage and EU Freedom of Movement Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling on same-sex marriage within the framework of EU free movement law in the case of Coman. This case involved a Romanian citizen, Mr. Coman, who married his American husband in Belgium while residing there. When they attempted to return to Romania, the Romanian government, which does not legally acknowledge same-sex marriage, refused residency to Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gathering of EU citizens residing in their home country: Understanding the Surinder Singh and Carpenter rulings for family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
This article examines when an EU citizen residing in their home country can assert rights under EU law for family members to join them. This analysis stems from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressing judgments in the Surinder Singh and Carpenter cases. These cases involve family reunification for EU citizens who return to their home country after residing in another Member State and for EU citizens who provide services in another Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it fair for EU citizens who relocate to still have the right to vote in their home country?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 02:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently issued a communication and recommendation addressing the loss of voting rights for EU citizens who relocate to other Member States. The Commission acknowledges that national identity grants Member States the right to determine voter eligibility. However, they urge Member States to consider if their policies on disenfranchisement hinder political participation. The Commission argues that many citizens maintain an interest in their home country&amp;rsquo;s politics, staying informed about political developments is easier than ever, and there&amp;rsquo;s a growing trend towards allowing expatriates to vote...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 4: Immigration in the EU Referendum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
How does the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the European Union (EU) affect immigration and asylum? This piece examines this complex topic, focusing on migration to the UK by both non-EU and EU citizens.
Non-EU migration
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between non-EU and EU migration in the Brexit referendum discussion for two key reasons. Firstly, while EU migration is inherently linked to the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership, non-EU migration is not...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The immigration issues in the UK renegotiation deal have been finalized.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
David Cameron has successfully negotiated a deal regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the EU. This post, the first in a series about the deal, focuses on &amp;ldquo;EU immigration&amp;rdquo; or, in terms of EU law, the free movement of EU citizens. I will delve into other important matters (competitiveness, Eurozone relations, sovereignty) and the legal structure of the deal later.
The deal comprises seven legal documents: a Decision by the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government (the &amp;ldquo;Decision&amp;rdquo;); a Statement from the Heads of State and Government (an agreed Council Decision); a Declaration by the European Council (representing the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government); and four declarations by the Commission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Following the Dano ruling, under what circumstances can unemployed EU citizens be deported?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Dano case focused on benefit applications, not deportation. Therefore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly affect deportation. However, due to the Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the EU citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive, it might indirectly impact deportation.
Earlier this year, I published a blog post about when unemployment could justify deporting or banning EU citizens. This post expands on that analysis, considering the Dano judgment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British lawyers have made a significant impact on EU (migration) law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk, Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen, Netherlands.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) acknowledged the significant contributions of its British members to European integration and legal precedent. This recognition prompts reflection on the impact of British legal professionals on EU law, particularly in the areas of migration and free movement.
British judges and advocates-general, with their common law background, played a key role in shaping the CJEU into a more transparent and adaptable institution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Alice Gross case: Examining EU law implications of allowing murderers to freely move within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British readers of this blog are likely aware of the case of missing teenager Alice Gross. A Latvian man, Arnis Zalkalns, is a person of interest in her disappearance. What makes this case more complex is that Mr. Zalkalns had a prior murder conviction in Latvia before relocating to the UK. He has since vanished, possibly returning to Latvia.
This raises several questions: how was a convicted murderer able to enter the UK undetected?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are the new proposals for simplifying Schengen visa applications for third-country national family members of EU citizens comprehensive enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU citizens with family members who are non-EU citizens often face obstacles to free movement, especially when those family members are from Asia, Africa, or the Caribbean. Traveling outside of the Schengen area with these family members often requires obtaining visas, adding complexity to their trips.
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent proposals on visas, if adopted, could bring some relief. One proposal focuses on revising the existing &amp;ldquo;Schengen visa&amp;rdquo; rules, which permit travel across Schengen countries for three months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Handbook on Marriages of Convenience by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
In September 2014, the Commission introduced a Handbook designed to guide Member States in addressing marriages of convenience between EU citizens and non-EU nationals. The goal is to combat these marriages without unduly restricting the free movement rights of EU citizens. The Commission emphasizes that the guidelines, developed in collaboration with Member States, are not legally binding and don&amp;rsquo;t supersede existing EU law or its future interpretations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is equal treatment possible in the fair movement of people? (Part Two)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
The authors are both at the University of Cambridge and funded by the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme
Introduction
This blog post proposes a UK/EU migration policy based on &amp;ldquo;fair movement&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;free movement.&amp;rdquo; This system would require work permits for genuine employment or self-employment and a simplified registration process like the one used for Croatian migrants.
The authors suggest limiting the principle of equal treatment for work and benefits, using existing restrictions within the Citizens’ Rights Directive 2004/38 and the Brussels New Settlement Agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anticipating the ECJ Decision in Coman: Progressing Towards EU-wide Recognition of Same-Sex Marriages across Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Photo: Mr Adrian Coman (right) with his spouse, Mr Claibourn Robert Hamilton (left)
(picture from PinkNews http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/29/romania-goes-to-court-over-whether-to-recognise-gay-couples-marriage/)
Introduction
The question of legal recognition for same-sex relationships has become a major topic in recent decades, sparking intense discussions globally in legislative bodies, courts, and the media, with strong opinions on both sides. This complex and delicate issue intersects with human rights, religious beliefs, moral perspectives, traditions, and constitutional principles like equality, personal freedom, and inherent human worth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Free Movement in Europe Unusual? The Recent Open Borders Policy in South America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 01:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</guid><description>Dr Diego Acosta Arcarazo, Lecturer in Law at the University of Bristol, and member of the research project Prospects for International Migration Governance (MIGPROSP)
While the freedom of movement within the European Union (EU) faces criticism and limitations from certain political and media outlets, other areas of the globe, such as South America, are embracing similar systems. This highlights that the EU model isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual, contrary to some opinions. Examining these different regional approaches offers valuable insights for refining existing legislation and policies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The lives of UK nationals living in other EU Member States have been significantly altered by Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah McCloskey and Tamara Hervey, Sheffield Law School
Following a string of significant political shifts, many can relate to the feelings of unease and worry stemming from the resulting instability. Currently, those hit hardest are individuals who have exercised their right to free movement without fear of it being revoked. This is the essence of Brexit: a source of discontent for some, a daily news item for others, but for EU citizens in the UK and UK citizens residing in other Member States, it holds the power to drastically alter their lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The case of V.M.A. v Stolichna obshtina, rayon 'Pancharevo' and the rights of rainbow families to freedom of movement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 06:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Linguist agent at the European Commission and honorary fellow European Union law at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Introduction
Advocate General Juliane Kokott, in her opinion, highlights the unfair burden placed on children of same-sex couples due to differing societal values among EU member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Putting an end to uncertainty: advocating for the protection of the rights of EU27 and UK citizens post-Brexit - including a suggested draft.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent draft of the Brexit withdrawal agreement might encounter obstacles and potentially fail to gain approval due to conflicting viewpoints on the Irish border or other matters. Should this occur, the question arises: what will happen to the provisions concerning EU27 citizens residing in the UK, and UK citizens residing in the EU27, prior to Brexit?
To provide maximum assurance regarding their immigration status, there is a compelling rationale for separating these provisions from the main withdrawal agreement and ratifying them under a distinct agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on domestic violence and the free movement of EU citizens is disgraceful.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU freedom of movement laws don&amp;rsquo;t directly apply to non-EU citizens. Instead, they gain rights through family ties with EU citizens. This poses a problem in domestic violence situations where the abuser is an EU citizen and the victim is not. Leaving the abuser could lead to expulsion, forcing victims to choose between their safety and remaining in the country, potentially separated from their children.
EU law attempts to mitigate this risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gazing into the Void: The Future of Citizens' Rights in the Event of a No Deal Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 03:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
After resisting guarantees for EU27 citizens&amp;rsquo; rights in the UK for over two years, the UK government has finally issued a plan outlining the treatment of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 in a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit scenario. This comes as the UK Parliament prepares to vote on the withdrawal agreement and after the European Commission published its own position on this matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who should have control over the 'emergency brake' on benefits for EU citizens: the Commission or the Council?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
During the UK&amp;rsquo;s negotiations to leave the European Union, a key point of contention arose: the process for enacting an &amp;ldquo;emergency brake&amp;rdquo; to restrict EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to in-work benefits. Should a Member State have the authority to implement this measure independently, perhaps with a requirement to inform the Commission and Council? Or should it be required to submit a request, leaving the decision of authorization to the Commission and/or Council?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the European Union a cause worth sacrificing for? Contemplating the future of Ukraine and the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</guid><description>There were many reasons to criticize the Yanukovych government in Ukraine, but the protests that led to its downfall were sparked by Yanukovych&amp;rsquo;s refusal to sign an agreement with the European Union. This strong desire for EU membership among some Ukrainians raises important questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s future.
The first steps after the planned elections would be straightforward. A pro-European government would likely ratify the association agreement, which connects Ukraine to EU law more closely than previous agreements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is CJEU case law on EU citizenship normatively consistent? Unlikely! - An answer to Davies' 'Has the Court evolved, or have the cases?'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 02:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</guid><description>Alexander Hoogenboom, PhD, MSc. LL.M. Senior Policy Officer at the Dutch Healthcare Authority and associate researcher at the Institute for Transnational and Euregional cross border cooperation and Mobility, Faculty of law, Maastricht University. The opinions presented in this paper are solely those of the author.
Introduction
Some have interpreted recent Court of Justice rulings on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits as a restrictive shift compared to earlier decisions, possibly influenced by rising populism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's 'emergency brake' preserving or abolishing the free movement of people?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Steve Peers
If British pro-Europeans could travel back in time, their priority should be returning to 2004. They should focus all efforts on persuading the then-British government to reconsider granting immediate free movement of workers from new EU member states. While economically advantageous, this decision has severely damaged public support for EU membership in the UK, as well as for the UK Labour Party.
Today, the free movement of people is often framed as a fundamental flaw within the EU, prompting calls for the UK to either leave or renegotiate its terms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unemployed EU citizens may benefit from the CJEU's decision, potentially complicating David Cameron's renegotiation strategy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ability of EU citizens to move freely between Member States, often referred to as ‘immigration,’ has sparked significant political debate, particularly in the UK. Access to benefits for these individuals remains a point of contention. The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has an opportunity to provide clarity on key aspects of this issue in the upcoming case of Alimanovic. An Advocate-General recently issued a non-binding opinion on this case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Farewell, harsh world: will there be visas for holidays post-Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Previously, I maintained that British citizens needing visas for short trips to the EU after Brexit was highly unlikely. I even disagreed with some &amp;ldquo;Remain&amp;rdquo; supporters who feared this outcome. The EU consistently lifts short-term visa requirements for wealthy nations (like the USA, Canada, and Japan) if they reciprocate for EU citizens. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t envision those on the &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; side supporting short-term visa requirements for EU citizens visiting the UK post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU law and its impact on minority languages in court proceedings: exploring the potential and constraints.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-its-impact-on-minority-languages-in-court-proceedings-exploring-the-potential-and-constraints/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 23:18:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-its-impact-on-minority-languages-in-court-proceedings-exploring-the-potential-and-constraints/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), through its judgment in the Ruffer case, reinforced and broadened its stance on using minority languages in legal processes.
The case involved Mrs. Ruffer, a German citizen residing in Germany, who was injured in a skiing incident in Bolzano, Italy, a region where German is commonly spoken. She held Ms. Pokoma, a Czech citizen living in the Czech Republic, responsible for the accident and filed a lawsuit against her in the Italian courts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-its-impact-on-minority-languages-in-court-proceedings-exploring-the-potential-and-constraints/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-its-impact-on-minority-languages-in-court-proceedings-exploring-the-potential-and-constraints/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Imbalance in the Right to Free Movement for European Union Citizens: A Focus on Students</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia*, Connor Brown**
*Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
** LLB Law European and International, University of Sheffield
This post reflects the preliminary results of a research project conducted as part of the Sheffield Undergraduate Research Experience programme (SURE). It also builds on a presentation at the International Society of Public Law (ICON-S) annual conference in New York on 2nd July 2015
INTRODUCTION
Growing concerns about limited public funds, diminished international cooperation, and declining support for a more unified Europe have cast a shadow on a key principle: the free movement of people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A revival of the Brexit negotiations? Theresa May's address in Florence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s recent speech was largely seen as an effort to jumpstart the Brexit negotiations, which have hit a roadblock, particularly regarding financial matters. The question is whether her speech will be successful, or if its underlying goal of appeasing Leave voters in the UK, especially those in the cabinet and the media, will undermine its effectiveness. Additionally, it prompts questions about the future relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union provides clarification on the Singh and Carpenter rulings for EU citizens' family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Typically, EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant residency rights to non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in their own home country. However, recent court rulings have clarified two key exceptions to this rule, albeit with unexpected outcomes. These rulings stem from Advocate-General Sharpston&amp;rsquo;s December 2013 opinion, as discussed in a prior blog entry.
The O and B case: Revisiting Singh
In 2007, O, a non-EU citizen, and their Dutch partner, sponsor O, moved to Spain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>No one will know his name...: An analysis of the CJEU ruling on the use of names acknowledged by other Member States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-one-will-know-his-name-an-analysis-of-the-cjeu-ruling-on-the-use-of-names-acknowledged-by-other-member-states/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-one-will-know-his-name-an-analysis-of-the-cjeu-ruling-on-the-use-of-names-acknowledged-by-other-member-states/</guid><description>Jacques BELLEZIT, Université de Strasbourg
A primary criticism of the European Union is its tendency to involve itself in matters that initially appear outside its defined powers, as outlined in Articles 3 to 6 of the TFEU.
The principle of attributed powers is embedded in EU law and acknowledged as legally binding to ensure the EU operates as a &amp;ldquo;rule of law&amp;rdquo; entity (Les Verts judgment). However, this has not prevented the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) from broadly interpreting its jurisdictional authority concerning EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-one-will-know-his-name-an-analysis-of-the-cjeu-ruling-on-the-use-of-names-acknowledged-by-other-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-one-will-know-his-name-an-analysis-of-the-cjeu-ruling-on-the-use-of-names-acknowledged-by-other-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has upheld the temporary free movement rights of third-country family members of EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent ruling from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the McCarthy case addresses a crucial question about EU free movement law in the UK: can the UK restrict the ability of family members (who are third-country nationals) of UK (and other EU) citizens to visit the UK?
The case involved a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual British and Irish citizen)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>