<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Right to Privacy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-privacy/</link><description>Recent content in Right to Privacy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU makes a ruling on data protection laws and home CCTV: Bringing Data Protection to Your Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Law, University of Essex
A recent decision by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ryneš v. Úřad pro ochranuosobníchúdajů addressed whether EU data protection law applies to home CCTV cameras. The CJEU agreed with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s earlier opinion on the matter, though it avoided addressing some of the more complex issues.
This judgment is significant for two reasons. Firstly, its implications extend beyond stationary surveillance systems and could impact how recording devices are used in public areas, even by private citizens.</description></item><item><title>Workplace Privacy: The Strasbourg Grand Chamber Provides Clarity on Legal Standards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Background
The Bărbulescu case examined the permissible extent of employer monitoring of employee communications, including internet usage, particularly when private conversations might be mixed with work-related ones. An employee, dismissed for violating a company policy prohibiting personal use of work equipment, sued his employer in Romania. He lost and appealed under Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), which protects privacy rights, arguing that his employer&amp;rsquo;s monitoring of his communications violated the precedent set by Copland v UK.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU missed an opportunity to address mass hacking and fundamental rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Hugo Partouche, a Paris Bar Attorney-at-law (avocat), and Chloé Berthélémy, a Senior Policy Advisor at EDRi, collaborated on this piece.
Photo credit: hacker-silhoutte, via Wikimedia commons
*This article initially appeared in French in Actualité Juridique (AJ) Pénal, Dalloz Revues. You can find it here.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on the ‘EncroChat’ case on April 30, 2024.
This case arose from large-scale European police operations targeting organized crime.</description></item><item><title>Is the UK's new data retention bill in violation of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Despite the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidating the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive in April, the UK government is pushing for continued data retention authority. This piece examines whether the proposed law aligns with EU law and if it violates the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.
The connection to EU law lies in Article 15(1) of the EU&amp;rsquo;s e-privacy Directive. This article allows Member States to restrict certain rights concerning communication confidentiality for safeguarding national security and other serious matters.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the Big Brother Watch case: part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
(These observations on the judgment follow part 1 of the analysis, which explained the Court’s reasoning).
The Big Brother Watch judgment can be interpreted in two ways: as confirmation that mass surveillance is permissible (para 314) or as an acknowledgment that the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act (RIPA) framework was inadequate. This implies that the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA), which inherited some of RIPA&amp;rsquo;s shortcomings, is also lacking.</description></item><item><title>Has workplace privacy become obsolete? Thoughts on the Barbulescu ruling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The question of when employers can access employee emails, texts, or internet usage is crucial for both parties involved. A recent judgment in the case of Barbulescu v Romania tackled this issue, but unfortunately, misleading headlines like &amp;ldquo;EU court allows employers to read all employee e-mails&amp;rdquo; have emerged. This is inaccurate for two reasons: the ruling originates from the European Court of Human Rights, not an EU court, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant employers unrestricted access to employee emails.</description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations.</description></item><item><title>The Tele 2 and Watson case: Human Rights and National Data Retention Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The Advocate General recently issued an opinion on two cases referred by national courts. These cases stem from the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in Digital Rights Ireland, which invalidated the Data Retention Directive. Both cases examine whether the mass retention of communications data aligns with EU law, raising a critical question: can such broad data retention ever truly comply with human rights?</description></item><item><title>Schrems II and the Transfer of Personal Data: You Were Only Meant to Blow the Bloody Doors Off!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued its highly anticipated decision regarding the legitimacy of standard contractual clauses (SCCs) for transferring personal data outside the European Union. This decision is part of a larger effort to challenge the “surveillance capitalism” model employed by many online businesses. While this case significantly impacts SCCs and Facebook&amp;rsquo;s operations, it also reveals the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s stance against mass surveillance, a recurring theme in European jurisprudence.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ ruling in Joined Cases C-203/15 and C-698/15 Tele2 and Watson (Grand Chamber) on data retention and national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent court decision examined the legality of national data retention laws from a human rights standpoint. These laws remained in effect even after the Data Retention Directive was struck down in the Digital Rights Ireland case due to its disproportionate impact on Articles 7 and 8 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (EUCFR). This judgment clarifies the interpretation of Articles 7 and 8 within EU law, particularly in the context of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Directive, and may impact the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU post-Brexit.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on police powers in relation to mobile phone theft and EU eprivacy law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ministerio Fiscal contributes to the understanding of the ePrivacy Directive, specifically Article 15, which allows Member States to make exceptions to the confidentiality of communications for certain purposes. This article played a role in the legal framework surrounding the mass retention of communications data from the Digital Rights Ireland case, where the CJEU established that data retention is justified only in cases of &amp;ldquo;serious crime,&amp;rdquo; as per the Tele2/Watson case.</description></item><item><title>Doctor U? The CJEU balances the right to a name with passport security.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many individuals possess a flexible understanding of their personal identity, this concept clashes with the perspective of law enforcement agencies. These organizations aim to establish a fixed identity for each person they gather information on to ensure absolute certainty.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently addressed these contrasting viewpoints in a case involving an individual identified as &amp;lsquo;U.&amp;rsquo; This case was among several during that week where plaintiffs were identified solely by letters, a practice the author suggests moving away from in favor of using pseudonyms for clarity and ease of reference.</description></item><item><title>The GDPR's right to erasure (also known as the right to be forgotten) - a potential risk of "rewriting history" or an opportunity for individuals to move on from the past.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gdpr-s-right-to-erasure-also-known-as-the-right-to-be-forgotten-a-potential-risk-of-rewriting-history-or-an-opportunity-for-individuals-to-move-on-from-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 06:23:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gdpr-s-right-to-erasure-also-known-as-the-right-to-be-forgotten-a-potential-risk-of-rewriting-history-or-an-opportunity-for-individuals-to-move-on-from-the-past/</guid><description>Ketevan Kukava, PhD Student in Law, Tbilisi State University
In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, where information is readily stored and accessed, managing one&amp;rsquo;s personal data is a complex challenge. Completely removing data from digital platforms, especially once it&amp;rsquo;s publicly accessible, is technologically and practically difficult. The lasting impact of past actions, preserved online indefinitely, raises concerns in the present.
The internet and digitization, while offering unparalleled access to information and content creation tools, present a significant drawback: the loss of control over personal data and the right to be forgotten.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions regarding consent for cookies in accordance with data protection laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A significant ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the use of cookies and the interpretation of consent under the e-Privacy Directive was issued last week in the Planet49 case. This ruling holds implications for comprehending cookie requirements under both the existing and forthcoming data protection regulations.
Judgment
At the heart of the matter was an online lottery requiring participants to provide their name and address.</description></item><item><title>Is privacy prioritized over transparency in CJEU cases?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</guid><description>Peter Oliver, Barrister, Monckton Chambers; Visiting Professor, Université Libre de Bruxelles
Having a name is essential, as not having one can lead to problems. This is why courts in Strasbourg and Luxembourg have acknowledged a person’s fundamental right to use their own name.
The Court of Justice has traditionally used initials to protect the identities of vulnerable individuals like asylum seekers and children involved in sensitive litigation. However, in a recent announcement, the Court stated its intention to partially overturn this long-standing practice.</description></item><item><title>Is it an early Christmas gift or a disappointment? Examining data retention and the leaked ePrivacy Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
The leak of a draft ePrivacy Regulation on December 12, 2016, has sparked discussions about its implications for data retention. This post will examine this aspect of the draft regulation.
The Article 29 Data Protection Working Party (A29DPWP) had previously advised against introducing new European data retention requirements. This recommendation, reflecting concerns about the existing ePrivacy Directive&amp;rsquo;s allowance for national data retention regimes, is echoed in the leaked draft Regulation.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Human Rights highlights the significance of encryption in the case of Podchasov v. Russia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip &amp;amp; Frederik Zuiderveen Borgesius*
*Both authors work at the iHub and the Institute for Computing and Information Sciences, Radboud University, The Netherlands - mattis.vantschip[at]ru.nl &amp;amp; frederikzb[at]cs.ru.nl
Photo credit: Gzen92, on wikimedia commons A February 2024 ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Podchasov v. Russia highlighted the crucial role of encryption in safeguarding privacy rights. This judgment comes at a time when encryption is at the heart of many global legal discussions.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's confusion on biometric data and data protection law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Growing concerns about the protection of biometric data have led the EU to propose a data protection regulation classifying such data as sensitive, thus providing it with a higher level of protection. However, until this proposal is enacted, existing EU regulations address this issue, although not always effectively, as demonstrated by the recent CJEU ruling in the Willems case, which falls short in its application of existing regulations to biometric data.</description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts.</description></item><item><title>Protecting data and smart meters: GDPR and the EU clean energy law's 'winter package'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giulia Pizza, FratiniVergano, European Lawyers - a Brussels-based law firm specialising in European and international law
Introduction
In late 2016, the European Commission introduced the “Clean Energy for All Europeans” legislative package to modernize Europe&amp;rsquo;s electricity market and encourage cleaner energy solutions. This push for &amp;ldquo;decentralization&amp;rdquo; is seen as a way to drive innovation and shift the focus to a demand-driven energy policy. The goal is to give consumers the tools they need to actively participate in this change.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item><item><title>Is the Passenger Name Record Directive legally valid? Thoughts on the upcoming CJEU case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-passenger-name-record-directive-legally-valid-thoughts-on-the-upcoming-cjeu-case/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-passenger-name-record-directive-legally-valid-thoughts-on-the-upcoming-cjeu-case/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, a legal expert in human rights and data protection, believes the EU Court of Justice should examine whether the PNR Directive aligns with the Charter of Fundamental Rights. This follows a similar inquiry by Belgium&amp;rsquo;s Constitutional Court.
Korff suggests that any large-scale surveillance, such as that under the PNR Directive, needs to meet two criteria. First, there should be strong proof from the European Commission and EU member states that these measures genuinely help combat crimes related to PNR.</description></item><item><title>The ECHR provides clarification on the use of hidden cameras in relation to human rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Bremner v Turkey provides clarity on the use of hidden cameras by journalists and potential human rights violations. The case involved an Australian citizen, Bremner, who was secretly filmed in his apartment discussing Christianity for a documentary about &amp;ldquo;foreign peddlers of religion&amp;rdquo; in Turkey. The program aired footage of Bremner with his face unblurred.</description></item><item><title>The UK is now part of the Schengen Information System, bringing the Panopticon Home.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The idea of a &amp;ldquo;Panopticon,&amp;rdquo; a prison where guards could potentially see any inmate at any point, was conceived over two centuries ago by British philosopher Jeremy Bentham. He believed that the constant threat of observation would motivate prisoners to act appropriately. This concept is now often used to illustrate contemporary patterns in widespread monitoring and societal control.
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) initial move in this direction was the establishment of the Schengen Information System (SIS) during the 1990s.</description></item></channel></rss>