<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Implementation of Directives on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/implementation-of-directives/</link><description>Recent content in Implementation of Directives on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:38:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/implementation-of-directives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What are the reasons behind the ineffectiveness of the Blue Card Directive for highly-skilled workers, and what solutions can be implemented to improve its functionality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 2009, the EU introduced the ‘Blue Card’ Directive to attract highly qualified individuals from non-EU countries. As part of a broader strategy for legal immigration, this Directive is crucial. However, a recent Commission assessment suggests that the Directive has not effectively reached its goals. This raises the question of necessary revisions for improvement.
Implementing the Directive
While all EU Member States obligated to implement the Directive have done so, the actual impact has been underwhelming.</description></item><item><title>Close partners: The highest courts of member states and the enforcement of EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Two high courts in France and Spain recently issued significant rulings concerning how lawyers and domestic courts should apply EU law. Although dealing with distinct issues, both decisions are important for properly implementing EU law. As noted a few weeks prior, national high courts are becoming crucial in EU law, a trend the Court of Justice should encourage.</description></item></channel></rss>