<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Network Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3x3 Mbps Ethernet Doubles Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t benefit from additional internet speed? Websites, software, and files continue to grow larger, but unfortunately, technology budgets haven&amp;rsquo;t kept pace. Imagine doubling your internet speed without increasing your current expenses – an appealing proposition, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
It might sound illogical to suggest that doubling your internet speed wouldn&amp;rsquo;t cost more, especially since internet providers aren&amp;rsquo;t known for giving things away for free. The secret lies in adopting newer, more cost-effective technology instead of simply replacing your existing service with an identical one from another provider.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections.</description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds.</description></item><item><title>Replace T1 Line With 10 Mbps Fiber at Same Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</guid><description>Are telecommunications companies pushing you to replace your outdated T1 line? See this as a positive change! You might be able to upgrade from a 1.5 Mbps T1 line to a 10 Mbps fiber optic service for about the same price. Moreover, fiber optic allows for easy bandwidth increases as your needs grow.
What&amp;rsquo;s Happening to Traditional Phone Lines?
Bell Labs created T1 lines as the first digital telecommunications service to carry multiple phone calls.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking Providers Want Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 12:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>The telephone industry is undergoing a transformation. Previously, businesses typically relied on in-house PBX systems to manage their phone networks and utilized ISDN PRI trunk lines for external calls. However, this is changing rapidly.
Two significant trends are emerging: cloud-based hosted PBX telephone systems and SIP trunking. While these technologies complement each other, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to implement SIP trunking without cloud services.
A telephone trunk consists of multiple phone lines grouped together, either physically or electronically.</description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>Eliminating the WAN Choke Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 02:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</guid><description>The speed difference between LANs (Local Area Networks) and WANs (Wide Area Networks) is often significant. This becomes apparent when accessing the internet or transferring files, as actions that are near-instantaneous within a local network can take much longer externally. This is known as the WAN choke point.
Visualize this by comparing a highway exit onto a crowded street during rush hour or trying to fill a pool using a garden hose connected to the main water supply.</description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Cable Gets Limber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 05:38:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</guid><description>Fiber optic and copper cable are competing to be the main wiring used in communication setups, whether for renovations, improvements, or brand new projects. However, fiber is already recognized as the superior long-term option. Copper persists due to its widespread implementation and compatibility with existing switches and routers.
A significant installation obstacle has hindered the widespread adoption of fiber optic cabling: limited fiber bending flexibility. Exceeding this limit not only risks snapping the delicate strands but also creates functional issues.</description></item><item><title>Content Delivery Networks Transformed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth is steadily growing, largely due to the rise of IP video streaming, downloads, and more sophisticated websites with larger graphics and interactive features. To keep up with this demand, networks and websites themselves need to change.
While increasing WAN bandwidth is a given, it&amp;rsquo;s not a complete solution. Despite significant growth in WAN bandwidth, internet traffic congestion persists, leading to the emergence of Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) as a bypass.</description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning.</description></item><item><title>The LAN WAN Connection Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 18:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</guid><description>Local area networks (LANs) are standardized and consistent, making them easy to understand and work with. However, connecting to a wide area network (WAN) introduces a new set of telephone company standards that can be challenging for network professionals familiar with LAN technologies.
In the past, connecting to a WAN required specialized knowledge of complex technologies like DS channels and SONET multiplexing. This often involved significant effort to bridge the gap between LAN and WAN environments.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds.</description></item><item><title>Will 2013 Be Your Year of the Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing was a major trend in 2012, with numerous vendors offering a wide range of solutions. Cloud services are no longer limited to powerful supercomputers; they&amp;rsquo;ve become accessible and practical for everyday resources, often surpassing the benefits of in-house solutions. This raises the question: will 2013 be the year you transition to the cloud?
For many businesses, the answer is a clear &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Cost-effectiveness, support, and accessibility are key drivers.</description></item></channel></rss>