<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accountability on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accountability/</link><description>Recent content in Accountability on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accountability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dalli Saga: A Story of Accountability and Defenestration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City University
The forced resignation of the Santer Commission in 1999 due to accusations of fraud, maladministration, and mismanagement remains a relevant topic even after nearly two decades. The European Commission has faced ongoing criticism for its administrative shortcomings and the structural flaws within the Union&amp;rsquo;s accountability system. Numerous reports have portrayed the Commission as an institution grappling with systemic and political irregularities.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>Is there another accountability gap with the European Peace Facility?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</guid><description>Ellen Cantraine, PhD researcher, Ghent European Law Institute
Photo credit: Dietmar Rabich / Wikimedia Commons / “Münster, Stadtweinhaus, Beflaggung Ukraine und EU &amp;ndash; 2022 &amp;ndash; 0219” / CC BY-SA 4.0 / see also
Introduction
Following the 2021 coup attempt in Mali, the EU&amp;rsquo;s mission in Mali (EUTM) continued operating despite concerning reports of serious misconduct by EU-trained soldiers. Funded by the European Peace Facility (EPF), EUTM&amp;rsquo;s case exposed significant flaws in the EU&amp;rsquo;s external funding mechanisms.</description></item></channel></rss>