<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Arab on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arab/</link><description>Recent content in Arab on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The perspectives of Gen Z differ from those of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</guid><description>A panel discussion at the Global Islamic Economy Summit focused on the characteristics of Generation Z, the generation following Millennials. Growing up with the internet and mobile phones, Gen Z is not only tech-savvy but also possesses a distinct perspective.
Sunil John, CEO of ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller, pointed out that governments are increasingly paying attention to this generation, questioning if current education and employment systems meet their needs. Citing the ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey 2016, John highlighted that 58% of young Arabs desire higher education, and 36% aim to start businesses, a departure from the traditional reliance on government jobs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Within the next five years, one-third of young Arabs intend to launch their own businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</guid><description>According to the 2016 ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey, over one-third of young Arabs plan to launch their own businesses within the next five years. The survey indicates that young Arabs believe governments could do more to support them, such as promoting affordable lending, enhancing training and education opportunities, and reducing bureaucratic hurdles.
When asked if their generation is more likely to start businesses than previous ones, 54% agreed. GCC youth were the most optimistic at 62%, compared to 54% in North Africa and 44% in the Levant...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>