<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Automation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-automation/</link><description>Recent content in Business Automation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EarthLink Offers Healthcare IT Resources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</guid><description>The potential for healthcare automation to significantly reduce costs in healthcare settings like doctor&amp;rsquo;s offices, clinics, and hospitals is substantial. However, not all healthcare providers have the necessary IT capabilities to modernize and leverage these new technologies. They might also struggle to meet privacy regulations like HIPAA. This is where large network service providers such as EarthLink Business can bridge the gap. An example of this can be seen in how EarthLink supports Monadnock Community Hospital in Peterborough, New Hampshire, as shown in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>