<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coffee on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coffee/</link><description>Recent content in Coffee on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 05:35:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience the superior, well-balanced flavor profile of Cafédirect Tarrazu Terroir Roast &amp; Ground Coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-superior-well-balanced-flavor-profile-of-caf-direct-tarrazu-terroir-roast-ground-coffee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 05:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-superior-well-balanced-flavor-profile-of-caf-direct-tarrazu-terroir-roast-ground-coffee/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect. Cafédirect Tarrazu Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee pairs well with fruit.
Cafédirect, a leading UK company specializing in Fairtrade hot drinks, has introduced its award-winning Cafédirect Tarrazu Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee. This coffee originates from the Llano Bonito cooperative in Costa Rica&amp;rsquo;s Tarrazu region, known for its mountainous terrain and fertile volcanic soil.
Cafédirect Tarrazu Terroir Coffee is made from Caturra and Catuai Arabica beans, known for their low-growing trees that produce a high yield of flavorful beans.</description></item><item><title>Limited edition spring drinks are being introduced at Starbucks stores in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-spring-drinks-are-being-introduced-at-starbucks-stores-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 22:36:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-spring-drinks-are-being-introduced-at-starbucks-stores-in-asia/</guid><description>Starbucks is celebrating spring in Asia with a variety of limited-edition drinks, ranging from refreshing iced options to comforting hot beverages.
Source: Starbucks. Coconut Water Espresso Shakerato.
The Coconut Water Espresso Shakerato blends Starbucks&amp;rsquo; espresso with ice, poured over chilled coconut water sweetened with coconut syrup. It&amp;rsquo;s finished with espresso foam and a lime slice. This beverage is available iced only.
Source: Starbucks. New Valencia Orange Cocoa Cappuccino.
The New Valencia Orange Cocoa Cappuccino starts with a Valencia orange mocha sauce, layered with steamed milk and espresso shots.</description></item><item><title>Caffè Vergnano 1882 has chosen the top three baristas in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Caffè Vergnano 1882. From left: third place winner Rudel Rivera, first place winner Joseph Bringcula, and second placer Stephen Wong.
Caffè Vergnano 1882 held its first-ever Barista Challenge at South Beach. Out of 16 participants, three distinguished themselves as top contenders.
Source: Caffè Vergnano 1882. The winning latte art from Bringcula.
The competition assessed fundamental barista techniques, including the ability to brew espresso properly and steam milk to enhance its flavor.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces Cauca Terroir Roast &amp; Ground Coffee in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 07:21:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</guid><description>According to Cafédirect, their Cauca Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee pairs well with sweet and fruity flavors. Ideal pairings in Colombia include pan de queso (cheese bread) and alfajores (caramel cookie sandwiches). &amp;ldquo;Terroir&amp;rdquo; encapsulates the unique environmental and geographic factors of a region that influence a beverage&amp;rsquo;s taste.
Cafédirect recently introduced their Cauca Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee to Singapore. Colombians describe this high-altitude coffee as &amp;ldquo;black as night, hot as hell and sweet as love&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Indulge in these food-themed gifts and enjoy!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 03:45:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</guid><description>As the holiday season approaches, businesses are looking for unique and thoughtful gifts for clients and employees. Here are a few distinctive gift ideas:
Source: Cafédirect.
For coffee lovers, Cafédirect, a British beverage company, introduced a premium freeze-dried instant coffee in Singaporean supermarkets this year. This meticulously crafted blend combines the sweetness and chocolate notes of South American Arabica beans with the well-rounded flavor of Central American beans and the boldness of East African Robusta beans.</description></item><item><title>Beijing is the first place outside of the Americas to experience Starbucks Nitro Cold Brew</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</guid><description>The China World Trade Centre Starbucks in Beijing is the first location outside of the US and Canada to offer Nitro Cold Brew on tap in addition to their regular Cold Brew. Starbucks plans to introduce this in more locations over the coming months. This follows a very successful launch of Starbucks Cold Brew across China.
&amp;ldquo;We are dedicated to achieving perfection in our coffee expertise, and Nitro Cold Brew shows our significant investment in coffee innovation.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new packaging for its premium-quality coffee blends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-packaging-for-its-premium-quality-coffee-blends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-packaging-for-its-premium-quality-coffee-blends/</guid><description>Cafédirect, a UK beverage company, has launched its Smooth, Lively, and Intense Roast Coffees in redesigned packaging.
These coffees are expertly crafted by Cafédirect’s own Q-graders (coffee experts) to showcase the rich flavor of the beans and highlight specific notes. Q grading guarantees consistency in coffee evaluation, much like sommeliers do for wines.
“The exciting aspect of crafting these blends is our ability to select coffees that complement one another. Blending different varieties and regional beans not only allows Cafédirect to tailor the coffee to a particular taste profile but also provides you with a consistent cup of coffee,” explained Georgios Kokkalis, Q Grader and Production Manager at Cafédirect UK.</description></item><item><title>Singapore to host a coffee consumer festival driven by heritage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</guid><description>Source: La Kopi.
The first-ever La Kopi festival, launched in 2019, is a joyous weekend event celebrating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s coffee and bakery culture. Supported by the Singapore Coffee Association, the festival aims to raise awareness and appreciation for these local staples.
This unique coffee festival will take place at the Singapore Expo Hall from January 25th to 27th, 2019. Spanning 4,000 square meters, the event features nearly 70 vendors from various countries, including Japan, Taiwan, Malaysia, and Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Strangers' Reunion cafe introduces new menu items</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strangers-reunion-cafe-introduces-new-menu-items/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:32:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strangers-reunion-cafe-introduces-new-menu-items/</guid><description>Source: Strangers&amp;rsquo; Reunion. Ocean Trout on Hash.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a new lunch spot, you might want to try Strangers’ Reunion, a cafe in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Kampong Bahru district that recently updated its menu. World Gourmet Summit-recognized chef Daniel Chin has crafted dishes with a minimum of five components to entice your taste buds.
The cafe is well-known for its coffee, which is chosen and curated by Ryan Tan, a three-time Singapore Barista Champion and Co-founder of Strangers’ Reunion.</description></item><item><title>De’Longhi introduces the La Specialista Prestigio, a high-end pump espresso coffee machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/de-longhi-introduces-the-la-specialista-prestigio-a-high-end-pump-espresso-coffee-machine/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/de-longhi-introduces-the-la-specialista-prestigio-a-high-end-pump-espresso-coffee-machine/</guid><description>De&amp;rsquo;Longhi recently unveiled its new La Specialista Prestigio espresso machine with a global campaign titled &amp;ldquo;Perfetto.&amp;rdquo; This campaign, directed by Damien Chazelle and starring Brad Pitt, offers a glimpse into Pitt&amp;rsquo;s daily routine, emphasizing how De&amp;rsquo;Longhi&amp;rsquo;s products seamlessly integrate into a refined lifestyle. The advertisement showcases a world where achieving the perfect cup of coffee is as simple as pressing a button, providing a luxurious bean-to-cup experience. The campaign can be viewed on YouTube.</description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new Medium Roast Freeze-Dried instant coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect.
Cafédirect, a British beverage company, has introduced a new premium instant coffee in Singapore. This medium roast, freeze-dried coffee offers a convenient solution for those seeking a flavorful cup on the go, featuring a smooth, vibrant taste with hints of caramel.
Interestingly, a growing number of Singaporean coffee drinkers who typically prefer milk in their coffee are developing a taste for black coffee. This shift is attributed to Cafédirect&amp;rsquo;s master blender, who has crafted a unique blend using sweet and chocolatey Arabica beans from South America, well-rounded beans from Central America, and robust Robusta beans from East Africa (60%).</description></item><item><title>Allspice Institute develops recipes inspired by Cafédirect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allspice-institute-develops-recipes-inspired-by-caf-direct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:57:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allspice-institute-develops-recipes-inspired-by-caf-direct/</guid><description>Culinary experts from the Allspice Institute collaborated with Cafédirect to develop innovative recipes featuring their coffee blends.
Cafédirect, a UK beverage company, unveiled new packaging for its Smooth, Lively, and Intense Roast Coffees. The launch event showcased coffee-infused recipes created in partnership with the Allspice Institute, a renowned culinary school.
Chef Sakthivel Karuppiah, COO of Allspice, prepared coffee-smoked tandoori chicken using coffee in two unique ways. He marinated the chicken in coffee for tenderness and then smoked it using spent coffee grounds.</description></item><item><title>During the month of September, BODUM is offering a promotion on coffee makers and toasters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-month-of-september-bodum-is-offering-a-promotion-on-coffee-makers-and-toasters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-month-of-september-bodum-is-offering-a-promotion-on-coffee-makers-and-toasters/</guid><description>BODUM is offering a special deal for customers in Singapore throughout September. When you buy a BODUM ePEBO Vacuum Coffee Maker, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive a complimentary BODUM Toaster. Alternatively, shoppers can choose a 15% discount on BODUM Toasters.
Source: BODUM. The ePEBO coffee maker.
Here are the specifics:
Purchase a BODUM ePEBO Vacuum Coffee Maker for S$369 and receive a free BODUM toaster valued at S$99. Enjoy a 15% price reduction on BODUM toasters, bringing the cost down to S$84.</description></item><item><title>Lateefa AlWaalan has been awarded the title of Saudi Arabia's EY Entrepreneur Of The Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</guid><description>Lateefa AlWaalan, the driving force behind the Arabic coffee startup Yatooq, has been crowned Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s EY Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) for 2015.
A panel of independent judges selected AlWaalan from a pool of eleven finalists representing ten different companies. Her entrepreneurial spirit, robust financial performance, strategic thinking, and positive social impact distinguished her as a leader. Fahad Altoaimi, EY&amp;rsquo;s Office Managing Partner in Riyadh and the Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader, emphasized that this award recognizes AlWaalan&amp;rsquo;s significant business accomplishments, innovative spirit, and contributions to her community.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces Nespresso-compatible coffee capsules in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-nespresso-compatible-coffee-capsules-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 16:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-nespresso-compatible-coffee-capsules-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect. Cafédirect launches premium coffee capsules that are compatible with Nespresso Machines.
Cafédirect, a UK-based company known for its award-winning Fairtrade hot drinks, has introduced its premium coffee capsules to supermarkets in Singapore. These capsules, compatible with Nespresso machines, offer a convenient way to enjoy Cafédirect&amp;rsquo;s signature coffee.
Crafted from 100% Arabica beans, each capsule boasts an intensity level of 8 out of 12. The 5.3g blend combines Tanzanian and Mexican coffee beans, resulting in a rich flavor profile.</description></item><item><title>Wilfa Precision: Just like it was crafted by a professional barista</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wilfa-precision-just-like-it-was-crafted-by-a-professional-barista/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wilfa-precision-just-like-it-was-crafted-by-a-professional-barista/</guid><description>You can now enjoy coffee that&amp;rsquo;s just as good as your local coffee shop at work every morning. The Wilfa Precision, an automatic coffee brewer, has been launched in Singapore and Malaysia by Papa Palheta, a specialty coffee roaster and retailer.
Source: Papa Palheta. The aluminium
version of the Wilfa Precision.
Developed in Norway, the Wilfa Precision is the result of a collaboration between Wilfa and world-renowned barista Tim Wendelboe. It promises a simplified drip coffee experience without compromising on quality.</description></item></channel></rss>