<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unified Inbox on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified-inbox/</link><description>Recent content in Unified Inbox on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified-inbox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The first product on Unified Inbox's roadmap, Outbox Pro, has been launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-product-on-unified-inbox-s-roadmap-outbox-pro-has-been-launched/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-product-on-unified-inbox-s-roadmap-outbox-pro-has-been-launched/</guid><description>Source: Unified Inbox website.
Unified Inbox, a company specializing in unified communications as a service, recently launched its first product: Outbox Pro, a cloud-based platform. Outbox Pro simplifies and accelerates the process of creating and distributing posts across various social media platforms. This web browser extension, currently compatible with Chrome, empowers users to generate, share, review, modify, approve, schedule, publish, and monitor both original and curated online content. Multiple authors can collaborate on this content, which can be shared across Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn.</description></item><item><title>The introduction of InboxRank is brought to you by Unified Inbox</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-introduction-of-inboxrank-is-brought-to-you-by-unified-inbox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 16:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-introduction-of-inboxrank-is-brought-to-you-by-unified-inbox/</guid><description>Unified Inbox has introduced InboxRank, a smart sorting tool designed to simplify communication management across various platforms such as email, social media, SMS, and instant messaging.
Source: Unified Inbox.
InboxRank prioritizes information by analyzing various factors related to individual user&amp;rsquo;s inbox activity. It continuously learns and adapts to user preferences over time. Key factors considered include:
Communication frequency between the sender and receiver. The duration of their acquaintance (determined by the date of initial contact).</description></item></channel></rss>