<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Replacement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/replacement/</link><description>Recent content in Replacement on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/replacement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the RAM Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 utilizes a 3V battery to power its 16-word memory chip, an MCM144102, which is described as a peripheral memory unit in the Motorola 6804 manual but lacks readily available detailed specifications. This chip is responsible for storing calibration data and potentially the system time, although further investigation is required. A visual representation of the circuit is included below.
A positive aspect of the design is the inclusion of diode D27, which safeguards the battery against reverse polarity connection.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Lubrication of Platter Motor Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the DC motor was lubricated. This particular motor uses brushes and has simple sleeve bearings.
To access the bearings for lubrication, the pulley and outer housing were removed. The pulley is attached to the shaft with glue, allowing for easy removal. After taking out two small screws, the housing can be opened and the motor taken out.
Next, the black rubber vibration insulation boot was removed, revealing the circuit board connected to the brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Main PCB and Installation of a Biasing Trimmer for TR3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</guid><description>After getting the Beogram 4002 (5513) operational again, I focused on fully restoring the main PCB. This involved installing a trimmer to correctly calibrate TR3, the transistor responsible for amplifying the signal from the record detection sensor. The board&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown below:
The RPM relay and trimmers had already been replaced by the owner. I finished the restoration by replacing all electrolytic capacitors
and adding a trimmer to enable bias adjustment at the base of TR3.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of Bearings, and Repair of a Broken Off Brush and a Disconnected Sensing Coil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-repair-of-a-broken-off-brush-and-a-disconnected-sensing-coil/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-repair-of-a-broken-off-brush-and-a-disconnected-sensing-coil/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor from the Netherlands. The motor was dead on arrival, so I opened it up and discovered a broken commutator spring that had been taped on with electrical tape.
Unsurprisingly, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t turn. I also found a broken lead on one of the sensing coils, which should have a resistance of 22 Ohms between the contact terminals.
This break disabled the motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable and have reached the stage of addressing cosmetic details. A common issue with this model, as with approximately 90% of them, is a worn keypad. The original coating deteriorates over time due to exposure to skin oils and acids. This results in unsightly smudges, especially on units that have seen regular use. I recently acquired some refurbished keypads from a contact in Denmark to have on hand for my restoration projects.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523) began, as always, with the arm lowering mechanism. The lubricants in these mechanisms often harden with age, preventing the tonearm from lowering correctly. The mechanism is shown here in its original condition:
Each moving part was removed
for cleaning and re-lubrication before reassembly. Next, I lubricated the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point. This required removing the sensor arm, as pictured below from the back:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoring the DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the motor. The motor was noticeably loud, a common issue in DC 4002 models often caused by dried lubricant in the sleeve bearings. Addressing this requires disassembling the motor, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubricant.
The first image highlights the upper sleeve bearing after the rotor was removed.
The next image provides a view of the lower bearing, feedback coils, and brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Infusing Oilite Brass Bearings of DC Motor with Oil Under Vacuum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-infusing-oilite-brass-bearings-of-dc-motor-with-oil-under-vacuum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-infusing-oilite-brass-bearings-of-dc-motor-with-oil-under-vacuum/</guid><description>Restoring the DC motors found in Beogram 4002/4 turntables (models 551x and 552x) presents a significant challenge. Many of these motors exhibit loud operation and inconsistent rotational speed due to their age. While lubricating the motor&amp;rsquo;s brass sleeve bearings with grease might seem like a solution, this often only yields temporary improvement.
The root of the issue lies in the use of &amp;lsquo;oilite&amp;rsquo; bearings, which are designed to operate without external lubrication.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated DIN Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</guid><description>During the ongoing refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a corroded DIN5 plug was replaced after a new output relay had been installed. The original plug showed significant signs of wear.
A high-quality Rean DIN5 plug with gold-plated terminals was chosen as a replacement. Photos document the preparation of the cable and the installation process. The author notes the limited space inside the DIN5 plug, making it difficult to separate the signal and ground connections.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor: Spark Snubber Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</guid><description>I recently had a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor on my workbench that I had previously worked on in November 2016 due to a broken brush and a severed pickup coil lead.
The motor recently began experiencing RPM fluctuations again.
This pointed to a problem with the spark snubbers. To access the rotor, I opened the motor:
The spark snubbers, marked with red dots, are located around the commutator. The replacements are on the black pad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and RPM Stability Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor from France was received for restoration.
As is typical, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite brass bearings needed fresh oil. This requires disassembling the motor and extracting the bearings for a vacuum oiling process.
The bearings were submerged in motor oil under vacuum, forcing air out of the porous material and drawing oil in. This process generally takes about 24 hours.
This shows the bearings after the oil infusion.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration and Test Drive with Cal Tjader and Claus Ogerman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable for an Australian customer who purchased it on eBay. The turntable arrived in poor condition.
My initial evaluation is documented here.
This post details the unit&amp;rsquo;s restoration, excluding the dust cover, which will be covered separately.
I began with the DC platter motor, as is customary, since the bearing lubrication process requires a few days. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of DC Motor and a Dead TR2 Transistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</guid><description>After refreshing the PCBs and the RPM trimmer scale backlighting on a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, I turned my attention to its DC motor. Most DC motors in these models need their Oilite brass bearings replenished with oil, as the oil tends to seep out over time, leading to RPM instability. To do this, the motor needs to be disassembled.
The bearings sit on a black pad within the motor. I noticed the motor had been previously repaired, evident in the bent brushes, which would have hindered its performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable. Initial assessment of the unit can be found on a separate blog post.
The restoration began with the platter motor, as its bearings require a lengthy oil treatment. The motor was extracted, disassembled, and its bearings were submerged in oil under a vacuum to allow for optimal oil diffusion.
Concurrently, the carriage assembly was cleaned. All &amp;ldquo;motion critical&amp;rdquo; parts, including the arm and its associated mechanisms, were removed, ultrasonically cleaned, and reassembled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Original DIN5 Plug with a Modern All-Metal Gold Plated Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</guid><description>To fully restore a 4002, replacing the often corroded DIN5 connector is essential. The delicate low-voltage signals need optimal contact. Gold is an ideal material due to its resistance to oxidation, ensuring a strong and long-lasting connection. The pictures illustrate this process, showing the old connector&amp;rsquo;s condition, preparing the cable for the new connector, the soldering process, and finally, the pristine new gold-plated connector installed. This upgrade is a significant step towards bringing the Beogram back to its former glory.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Non-Working End Groove Detection - Repair of a Detached Carriage Position Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. One peculiar problem was a detached carriage position sensor, which is housed within a black light shield. This shield was hanging at an angle, but it needs to be positioned vertically. The sensor works by using black sections on a plexiglass strip attached to the carriage to interrupt light from an IR diode. If the sensor is misaligned, stray light can disrupt the carriage&amp;rsquo;s movement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Oil Infusion of DC Platter Motor Bearings and RPM Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</guid><description>To fully rebuild the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 DC motor, you must relubricate the motor bearings. Many DC motor Beograms have fluctuating RPMs because the oil in their porous brass bearings (called &amp;ldquo;Oilite&amp;rdquo;) depletes over time. These bearings can be &amp;lsquo;refilled&amp;rsquo; by using a vacuum to remove air and allow oil to replenish the pores. The challenge lies in extracting the bearings without causing damage. I documented this process in a recent video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration Including a Refurbished Keypad and Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This unit is currently for sale. Please, see here.
This post details the complete restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) from Arizona, which I first inspected as shown here. The unit&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is pictured below:
My first step, as always, was to initiate oil infusion for the platter motor bearings. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:
I took it apart to extract the bearings (two small rings on the black pad):</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Exciting DC Motor Failure Mode Due to a Shorted Spark Snubber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-exciting-dc-motor-failure-mode-due-to-a-shorted-spark-snubber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 05:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-exciting-dc-motor-failure-mode-due-to-a-shorted-spark-snubber/</guid><description>Another Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor in need of repair recently came to my workbench. During my standard pre-restoration test using a Beogram 4002, this motor was unusually sluggish, only operating with assistance. This contrasted with the typical DC motors I encounter, which generally run powerfully but exhibit RPM fluctuations and often produce high-pitched sounds due to dried-out bearings. This particular motor was noticeably underpowered.
I disassembled the motor and performed my usual bearing oil infusion to ensure the mechanical components were within specifications before addressing the sluggishness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Installation of a New DIN5 Plug With Gold Coated Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration is coming along nicely. I believe a key part of revitalizing these turntables is installing a new, all-metal DIN 5 plug with gold-plated contacts. The old plugs often suffer from corrosion, which hinders the delicate signal transfer from the MMC cartridge. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the old plug with tarnished terminals:
This image showcases the soldering work within the updated plug:
And finally, the finished product:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This blog post details the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a client in Florida. A previous post documented the initial assessment of the unit.
Upon beginning the restoration, the turntable was in relatively original condition. However, the platter motor showed signs of prior work, evidenced by an incorrectly installed pulley.
To address this, the motor was removed and disassembled to extract and lubricate the bearings. This involved immersing them in motor oil under vacuum until air bubbles ceased to appear, indicating the bearings were properly saturated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 11:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism/</guid><description>My work began on the recently acquired Beogram 4002 (5513). The arm lowering mechanism, as is common, was the first issue to address. The usual hardened lubricant was present, resulting in sluggish movement. The setup can be seen here:
To address this, I removed the linkages and the damper to clean and lubricate them:
Here, the disassembled damper and linkages are visible:
A detailed video demonstration of this process is available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and one of the challenges is finding modern replacements for the large capacitors used in the 1970s. I received a 3D-printed adapter that allows me to neatly install smaller, current-generation capacitors.
These photos show the adapter with the new capacitors in place:
For reliability, I used two 300uF capacitors wired together to replace the original 150uF motor capacitor. The remaining capacitors are high-quality Rubycon, Panasonic, and Multicomp components chosen for their longevity.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Deteriorated Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002, deteriorated transport lock bushings, evidenced by small orange plastic pieces within the unit, were discovered. To address this, 3D-printed replacement bushings were designed for convenient installation without major disassembly. These bushings are comprised of two halves, insertable from above and below the sub-chassis.
The replacement bushings are available for purchase, with each bushing requiring two of the 3D-printed parts. A video detailing the installation process is accessible online.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Strange Solenoid and an Alien 7812 Impostor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</guid><description>As I was testing the restored tonearm carriage on my Beogram 8000 with some recently purchased Genesis reissues (Trespass, Foxtrot, Nursery Crime, etc.), I decided to turn my attention to the Beogram 4000 I had recently acquired from Italy. The most critical issue was its malfunctioning solenoid, which appeared unusual and unlike standard B&amp;amp;O components.
Upon disassembling the damper/solenoid assembly, I discovered a makeshift repair job. The original solenoid had been replaced with a different one, and a nail was used as a plunger to activate the solenoid linkage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Adjusting Platter and Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 23:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</guid><description>The visual appeal of a Beogram 400x relies heavily on the platter&amp;rsquo;s alignment with its surrounding aluminum panels. A correctly aligned platter sits flush with these panels, allowing the black &amp;lsquo;ribs&amp;rsquo; to stand out against a flat aluminum surface. Achieving this alignment is intricate, requiring several parameters to be perfectly adjusted. I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that a sensor arm that isn&amp;rsquo;t entirely parallel to the floating chassis often complicates this process. Both the service manual and my videos detail an adjustment procedure assuming the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s parallelism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Replacement of Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) DC platter motor, previously restored in 2016, displayed RPM fluctuations and required attention. Although the motor&amp;rsquo;s bearings had been treated with oil at that time, the spark snubbers were not replaced. The motor had functioned correctly following the initial restoration.
Initial testing involved installing the motor in a 4002 turntable and monitoring its RPM stability over 24 hours. The results are represented by the blue line in the provided graph.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Mechanisms, and Installation of a New Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, often problematic due to hardened lubricants, required attention. While the lowering damper section was functional, the damper-to-arm linkage was stuck and only moved because its pin had loosened.
The restoration process involved carefully disassembling the arm lowering mechanism, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubrication. The seized damper-to-arm linkage was removed, requiring a workbench procedure to press out its stuck pin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/4002/4004 Relays: Professionally Manufactured PCBs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</guid><description>I recently updated the design of the Beogram 4000/4002/4004 relay adapter boards to allow for professional manufacturing. I&amp;rsquo;ve begun taking and fulfilling orders with these new boards, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled with how they turned out.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the boards:
These boards are compatible with both the older Siemens relays and the newer National relays commonly found as RPM and signal path grounding relays in the 400x series. They are designed as direct replacements for the original relays.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</guid><description>I am currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) and focused on refurbishing its dust cover. As you can see in the first image, the cover had multiple scratches and abrasions common for its age.
My first step was to sand the cover using 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the imperfections.
Following this, I used a Micro-Mesh polishing cloth to restore the cover&amp;rsquo;s clarity. The final result is a clear and revitalized dust cover.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My work began on the Beogram 4000 turntable that arrived from Germany. As is my practice, the tracking and arm lowering mechanisms were the first to be refurbished. The arm lowering mechanism, controlled by a solenoid and damper arrangement, is pictured here:
After removing components requiring cleaning and lubrication, the area looked like this:
Here are the disassembled parts:
With cleaning and lubrication complete, reassembly followed. Next, I addressed the seized damper-to-arm linkage, accessible only after detaching the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and Dependence of RPM Performance on the Value of C10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</guid><description>I recently obtained two DC motors from Beogram 4002 turntables that are being refurbished. One of the motors is pictured here.
The first step in restoring these motors is addressing the brass sleeve bearings, which are often dry after more than 35 years of use. I do this through an oil infusion process, which requires complete disassembly, as shown.
The bearings, visible on the black pad in the front, are submerged in oil and placed under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Upgrade of the Tracking System with a LED Based Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</guid><description>With the DC motor operating correctly, the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) continued with the arm lowering mechanism and tracking feedback system.
The arm lowering mechanism, consisting of a solenoid and damper, was disassembled, cleaned, and lubricated. This process involved removing the damper, linkages, retaining washer, and spring. Detailed videos illustrating the rebuilding process are available. After reassembly, the arms were meticulously aligned parallel to each other and the keypad edge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Intermittent "17" Position Switch Causing Immediate Touchdown After Launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</guid><description>I thought I was finished with this Beogram 4000 turntable after refurbishing its dust cover. However, a new problem emerged. After playing a few records, the tonearm would drop next to the platter as soon as I pressed &amp;ldquo;ON.&amp;rdquo; Luckily, the stylus wasn&amp;rsquo;t damaged (thanks to proper arm height adjustment), but I clearly needed to examine the carriage mechanism&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;17&amp;rdquo; position switch. This particular switch is the most troublesome of the position switches because it&amp;rsquo;s the only &amp;ldquo;break switch.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Installing Rebuilt Rubber Pinch Rollers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-installing-rebuilt-rubber-pinch-rollers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 03:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-installing-rebuilt-rubber-pinch-rollers/</guid><description>Thorough testing of the Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape deck revealed an occasional issue where the leading capstan would cease to move the tape forward. This occurred under specific conditions, particularly when humidity hovered around 60% and room temperature dipped below 65°F. As a result, the supply capstan would continue to push the tape forward, causing it to slip out of place between the erase head and the supply pinch roller. Fortunately, the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s auto-stop function activated quickly enough to prevent damage to the tape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: A New Day, a New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</guid><description>I recently got a new dust cover for a Beogram turntable from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, so they have a seamless look, unlike older reproduction covers that were made by fusing together laser-cut pieces. The result is a cover that&amp;rsquo;s indistinguishable from the original.
This photo shows the new cover:
The hinge for the cover was missing the small plastic pieces that prevent the spring mechanism from rubbing against the hinge&amp;rsquo;s metal parts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My first step when restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable is to focus on the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. The arm lowering mechanism often requires attention because hardened lubricants can hinder the solenoid and damper assemblies. To address this, I disassemble the mechanism.
Once the solenoid and linkages are removed, I take the parts to my workbench for cleaning and re-lubrication.
Next, I address the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm, as it can cause delays in arm lowering, particularly after storage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Plexiglass Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>The restoration of my Beogram 4000 is nearly complete. The final cosmetic touch was adding a new, reproduction dust cover from Classic Audio in Denmark. They also supplied a matching aluminum trim piece for the back edge. Installing the dust cover was simple.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the process:
This image showcases the original hinge being installed with new stainless steel screws:
The pre-drilled holes in the new cover aligned perfectly, and the screws went in just like the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 AC Platter Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-ac-platter-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-ac-platter-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 AC platter motor from Massachusetts that had a knocking sound. Adjusting the voltage and tilt did not fix the problem. To address this, I typically disassemble the motor and submerge the housing parts in motor oil. Using a vacuum, I ensure the oil fills the material pores. Below is a picture of the motor upon arrival:
I drilled out the rivets and disassembled the motor:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Sub-Chassis and the Platter, and RPM Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 04:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</guid><description>Today was dedicated to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis on a Beogram 4002 (5513) that I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I aimed to align the platter&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface with the surrounding panels, center the sub-chassis within the transport locks&amp;rsquo; limits, and ensure the arms were parallel to the aluminum surfaces. It&amp;rsquo;s intricate work involving aligning numerous components. After gaining experience with this process, I achieved a satisfactory result, aligning the Beogram to specifications.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): DC Motor Restoration and Yet Another Exciting Aspect of Achieving RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 22:43:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</guid><description>To restore the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor, several upgrades are necessary. These include installing modern multi-turn RPM trimmers, a new RPM relay, replacing the RPM trimmer backlights with LEDs, and refreshing the motor bearings with oil. Testing the RPM stability after each step reveals their individual impact on performance.
This particular Beogram 4002 had already undergone most of these improvements, with the exception of the motor restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: A New Tool on the Bench and the Importance of the Orientation of the Top Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was acquired for restoration. Evidence suggested prior repair attempts on the motor, including scratches on the bearing assembly and damaged brushes.
Upon disassembly, it was clear the bearings hadn&amp;rsquo;t been properly oiled. A vacuum oil infusion process was conducted on both the top and bottom bearings. After cleaning and reassembly, a short circuit was detected, pointing to faulty spark snubbers.
The old spark snubbers were replaced with modern TVS devices.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (I)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m waiting for a part for a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, I&amp;rsquo;ve started restoring another one with faulty displays. It seems cassettes are making a comeback! I&amp;rsquo;m even hoping for new tapes and maybe even a revival of the Sony Walkman II.
This particular Beocord 9000 has a very dim display:
[Image of dim display]
The &amp;ldquo;Time Cal&amp;rdquo; bulb is also weak, a common issue. I began with the VU meter (or Peak Program Meter), as I haven&amp;rsquo;t refurbished this type before.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 02:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>I finally decided to refurbish the dust cover of the Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway, a task that takes me around 3 hours. I had been putting it off because I was enjoying working on a custom transformer for a Beomaster 4000 receiver.
As is common with vintage turntables, the dust cover on this Beogram 4000 was showing its age. It had numerous scratches and blemishes, as you can see here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Broken Sensor Arm Photocell with Three SMD Photodiodes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-sensor-arm-photocell-with-three-smd-photodiodes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-sensor-arm-photocell-with-three-smd-photodiodes/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a broken photocell presented a challenge. This component, crucial for record detection, was no longer available. While a previous solution involved using a modern phototransistor with circuit modifications, a simpler approach was considered.
Recognizing the functional similarity between photovoltaic cells and the original photocell, a test was conducted using readily available photodiodes. Initial results with a single photodiode proved insufficient, but connecting three in parallel yielded a promising voltage output.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion, New Spark Snubbers and an Ultrasonic Cleaning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was recently sent in for repair. Initial testing showed the motor was barely functional. To address this, the motor was disassembled, and the bearings were removed for lubrication.
The bearings, designed to be porous and oil-filled, were treated with a vacuum oil infusion process. This process, evidenced by vigorous bubbling, helps to replenish the oil within the bearings over time. After a few days, the bubbling subsided, indicating the bearings were adequately filled with oil, and they were removed from the oil bath.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Missing Leaf Spring on a Plate Lock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</guid><description>During the rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5513), I encountered an issue while adjusting the sub-chassis, platter, and tonearm. The large aluminum plate wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly against the plinth when it was pushed back, making it impossible to align the platter flush with the plate.
The problem originated from one of the locking mechanisms in the back left corner. These locks, equipped with leaf springs, are designed to secure the plate to the frame when the plinth is moved back.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (III)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</guid><description>This article, the third in a series about restoring a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s peak program meters (PPM), focuses on installing and calibrating the rebuilt PPM.
The initial step involved switching the original current limiting resistors with values suitable for modern SMD LEDs. These LEDs are more efficient and brighter, requiring significantly larger resistors to match the original brightness. Testing showed that 470 Ohm and 330 Ohm resistors for red and green LEDs, respectively, produced slightly brighter output compared to the original 180 Ohm and 120 Ohm resistors.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Repair of a Broken Out Leaf Spring in the Tape Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-leaf-spring-in-the-tape-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-leaf-spring-in-the-tape-mechanism/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, a loose part was discovered within the device&amp;rsquo;s casing. This component turned out to be the left leaf spring responsible for securing the head carrier. A comparison with the corresponding right spring revealed that a small ball bearing, crucial for smooth head movement, was missing.
Further investigation determined the ball bearing&amp;rsquo;s diameter to be 2.5 mm, and a readily available supply was procured. The broken plastic piece attached to the loose spring indicated that the original assembly, constantly under tension, had given way.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</guid><description>The final stage of my recent Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project involved reviving the dust cover. Like many Beograms of its era, the cover required attention, particularly the rubber bumpers which needed replacing. The extent of the damage is evident in this photo:
Fortunately, the scratches weren&amp;rsquo;t severe. A 320-grit sanding step effectively leveled the plexiglass, preparing it for polishing to regain its transparency:
After approximately ten stages of polishing, using progressively finer sandpaper and polishing cloths, the cover regained its shine:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of a Wobbly Carriage Pulley with a New Aluminum Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</guid><description>As I was finishing the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5523), I noticed a concerning noise coming from the carriage when it moved quickly, especially when returning to its starting position. This led me to believe there was an issue with the carriage pulley. Upon inspection, I discovered that the pulley was cracked, which is a common problem with this model. It seems the original plastic can&amp;rsquo;t handle the stress from the setscrew over time and eventually cracks.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the Incandescent Indicator Light Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, two indicator lights presented problems. One had a typical issue with a broken lead, while the other had become dim due to a deteriorating filament.
To address this, I opted to use SMD LEDs as replacements, similar to a method I&amp;rsquo;ve used for Beomaster 8000 units, documented on my blog. This provides lasting stability and safeguards against potential shipping damage. However, the Beocord 9000 has more compact reflector housings compared to the Beomaster 8000, necessitating a redesign of the PCBs for the LEDs.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Total Recap - Replacement of all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 10:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>This article revisits a complete restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, focusing on the replacement of electrolytic capacitors for improved long-term reliability. While not as crucial as with amplifiers due to lower operating temperatures, capacitor replacement is recommended for optimal performance.
The Beocord 9000, designed for serviceability, allows access to its numerous electrolytic capacitors. Unlike its predecessors, it offers easier access by removing the front and back panels instead of extracting the main circuit boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Floating Chassis Height</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</guid><description>After adjusting the main platter bearing in a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to set the height of the floating chassis. The goal is to make sure the aluminum surface of the platter is level with the surrounding aluminum panels. You can adjust the height by turning the nuts on the leaf springs that hold the chassis and provide vibration isolation. Using an 8 mm hex wrench is recommended.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion of Bearings and New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A DC motor, removed from a Beogram 4002 in Arlington, VA, was sent in for repair.
The initial step involved taking the motor apart and extracting its bearings for lubrication.
The bearings, resembling small rings, were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied. This process causes air bubbles to emerge from the bearing material, indicating oil infusion.
After a day, the bubbling stopped, signifying that the bearings were saturated with oil.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival on Beolover's Bench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</guid><description>During the holiday season, I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable for repair. My initial assessment showed that it was packaged very well, with some innovative methods used to protect it during shipping.
The dust cover was secured using soft foam blocks to hold the sub-platter and the RPM panel in place.
The MMC20E cartridge was also protected by foam and arrived in good condition.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the cartridge after unpacking:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Lubricating and Adjusting the Solenoid to Tonearm Linkages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</guid><description>Following the solenoid replacement and removal of the faulty voltage regulator on my Beogram 4000 restoration project, the arm mechanism remained sluggish. This indicated a need to lubricate the connection between the damper and tonearm lift. Additionally, the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s horizontal alignment was significantly off. While attempting to adjust this with the set screw on the tonearm counterweight&amp;rsquo;s connecting arm, I discovered it was glued in place with epoxy, preventing screwdriver access - likely another consequence of a previous repair attempt.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Polishing and Exchange of the Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 19:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration project required a hood restoration. I had two hoods: one had a cracked corner, and the other had a good plexiglass body but a corroded hinge.
Corrosion is common on Beogram 4000 hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s fixable with sanding and repainting, but finding a good hinge is preferable. Luckily, the cracked hood had a usable hinge, so I decided to swap them.
Removing the hinge requires care to avoid damaging the aluminum strip on the back of the hood.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of a New All-Metal DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Contacts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</guid><description>I believe that any restoration of a Beogram 4002 isn&amp;rsquo;t truly finished until the old output plugs, which are often corroded, are replaced with modern, all-metal ones featuring gold-plated terminals. High-quality analog signals deserve the best possible connections. Here are some photos documenting the DIN5 plug replacement I completed on a Beogram 4002 (5503) restoration:
The original DIN5 plug is shown here:
This photo shows the &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; soldering work:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002/4004: Replacement of a Broken Cable Clamp/PCB Holder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a broken cable clamp/PCB holder presented an opportunity to test a replacement part file. A fellow Beogram enthusiast from New Zealand shared the file, and in return, received access to parts in my Shapeways store. Photos document the broken clamp, the 3D-printed replacement, and the final installation. The new clamp fits securely with the PCB, keeping the audio cable properly positioned. With the successful trial complete, the part was made available for purchase in my store for other B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the DC Motor and a Significant Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-dc-motor-and-a-significant-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 02:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-dc-motor-and-a-significant-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>A recently acquired Beogram 4002 turntable exhibited significant speed variations during an initial performance test. The frequent and irregular drops in rotations per minute (RPM) pointed to a need for cleaning and lubrication of the DC motor.
The motor was removed from its housing for servicing.
The motor was then disassembled to allow for cleaning and lubrication of its bearings.
Following reassembly and reinstallation of the motor, a 24-hour RPM test was conducted.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Exchange of Trim, Fixing Cracked Hinges, Spray Painting Corroded Metal Parts and Polishing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a damaged dust cover. It was scratched, the metal hinges were corroded, the plexiglass around the hinges was cracked, and it had the typical early-model plastic trim that imitated aluminum.
To start, I removed the plastic trim. It was attached with contact cement, so I warmed the dust cover in the oven at approximately 80 degrees Celsius (wrapped in aluminum foil to prevent hot spots) to soften the adhesive.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Infusing the DC Motor Oilite Bearings with Fresh Oil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-infusing-the-dc-motor-oilite-bearings-with-fresh-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 16:42:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-infusing-the-dc-motor-oilite-bearings-with-fresh-oil/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5524), the DC motor required attention. The Oilite brass bearings, designed with a &amp;rsquo;lifetime&amp;rsquo; lubricant within their pores, typically need replenishing after approximately four decades. This involves submerging the bearings in motor oil and using a vacuum to extract air from the pores, allowing oil to penetrate. A detailed video demonstrating this process is available here.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse at this specific motor, both extracted from the turntable:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 06:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</guid><description>My work began with the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, as is customary for me. My client had already addressed the cleaning and lubrication of the damper and solenoid linkages, so my task was to detach the linkage connecting the damper and tonearm. This required removing the sensor arm assembly, as shown here:
Extracting the sensor arm involved removing two screws at its base:
The linkage could then be detached:</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoring the Peak Program Meters with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s Peak Program Meter (PPM), even though it was fully functional. This decision stemmed from my success in restoring a different Beocord&amp;rsquo;s PPM that had several broken segments.
Since the technology behind these PPMs is similar to that of a 7-segment display, I realized that the segments in this unit were also susceptible to future breakage. Therefore, I chose to preemptively address the issue while I had the opportunity.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Exchanging the Rubber Parts in the Tape Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</guid><description>My Beocord 9000 restoration project saw some good progress. I recently installed new rubber tires on the idler wheels of the tape drive mechanism to address a rewinding issue. The deck wasn&amp;rsquo;t rewinding smoothly, becoming very slow and sometimes even stopping at the end of the process. This seemed like a common problem attributed to hardened idler wheel rubber, as suggested by Beoworld.org.
However, upon disassembling the mechanism, I discovered that a previous repair attempt had damaged a crucial friction pad, which was the root cause of the problem.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Tracking Sensor Incandescent Bulb with a Drop-In SMD LED Assembly and a Peek at the Opto-Resistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</guid><description>The tracking sensor bulb in my Beogram 4000 recently burned out. This was the fourth bulb to fail. I decided to use this opportunity to install my new SMD LED replacement assembly. This assembly uses efficient white LEDs at low power for longevity, likely exceeding 50 years. It also reduces the unit&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption by a few watts, lessening the load on the aging transformer. Details about the assembly and adjustments can be found in this video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Aluminum Pulley for the Carriage Servo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</guid><description>Recently, I completed the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable. The final piece I needed was a new aluminum pulley for the carriage servo. The original pulley was cracked and causing unwanted noise and vibration, particularly during rapid carriage movements like starting and stopping. This was not acceptable for a quality turntable.
A standard replacement pulley wasn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with this early 5501 model. These early models use a unique end groove detection system requiring a pulley with four holes that function as an optical chopper to monitor the carriage speed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Too Early Arm Lowering and RPM Change During START</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5524) turntables I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing had a recurring issue: during the start-up sequence, the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consistently lower at the 30 cm mark. Occasionally, the RPM would unexpectedly switch to 45 right after pressing start.
Troubleshooting was challenging because the problem was intermittent. I replaced all the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay, and trimmers, as detailed on my blog. To test, I installed the boards in my own Beogram 4002 (5513).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-switches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-switches/</guid><description>A significant issue with the Beogram 4000 design lies in its numerous exposed mechanical switches. Many usability problems stem from oxidized or bent contact tabs on these switches. Attempts to fix these issues often involve bending the contact tabs, which can worsen the problem. This was true for the Beogram I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring. After replacing the solenoid, the right slide transfer button malfunctioned.
While replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with SMD LEDs, I also cleaned the switch contacts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Upgrade of Signal Path with New DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The DIN5 plug on the Beogram 4000 being restored was heavily oxidized and needed replacement. A new, fully metal plug with gold-plated terminals was installed.
To improve the signal output, a switch was added to connect the signal and system grounds. This feature is beneficial when using a DIN5 to RCA adapter, as RCA cables lack a system ground. Connecting the system ground to the signal ground on the Beogram can reduce humming.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>Some time ago, a customer in Texas purchased a Beogram 4000 turntable on eBay from a seller in New York. The turntable was in fair condition, as detailed on the blog (see hyperlink). To address a cracked corner on the dust cover, the decision was made to acquire a second Beogram 4000, allowing the creation of one flawless unit from the two. With the arrival of the second turntable, the restoration began.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Very Oily DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:44:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from Berlin, Germany, for restoration. The motor&amp;rsquo;s exterior was noticeably oily, likely due to an attempt to improve its RPM stability through lubrication.
Disassembly was necessary to access and treat the bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was also oil-coated. However, this is ineffective for the bearings, as they require vacuum oil infusion. This process removes air trapped within the porous Oilite brass material, enabling new oil to penetrate the bearing effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a Plug-In Ready SMD LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I installed the latest iteration of my SMD LED light source for the tracking sensor.
Previously, I designed a drop-in SMD LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb fixture, which worked well. However, it still relied on the original, cumbersome tracking sensor sensitivity adjustment process. This process involves carefully positioning the light sensors relative to the light source, a task made difficult by the mechanism&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and the adjustment mechanism&amp;rsquo;s coarseness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a Brand New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</guid><description>Before returning the recently restored Beogram 4002 (5513) to its owner, one final detail needed attention: the original dust cover showed early signs of cracking around the hinges.
The owner opted for a brand new replacement dust cover from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These reproduction dust covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, resulting in a seamless look, unlike previous versions made by fusing laser-cut panels. The result is indistinguishable from the original.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Repair of a Broken Out DIN-7 Jack With 3D Printed Inserts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-din-7-jack-with-3d-printed-inserts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-din-7-jack-with-3d-printed-inserts/</guid><description>Repairing the broken DIN 7 jack on the Beocord 9000 was simpler than anticipated. The part is identical to the one used for the Beomaster 8000&amp;rsquo;s Phono input. A 3D printed part, designed previously, was used to replace the fragile tabs on these sockets, which often break and cause the jack to fall into the panel cutout. Images of the broken jack and the 3D printed replacements are included.
A short video demonstrating the installation process and the repaired plug is provided.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Smoking Solenoid Resistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</guid><description>This continues my series &amp;ldquo;A Fun Evening with&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A Beogram 4000 turntable, which I had previously restored, was returned with a malfunctioning arm lowering mechanism and a burning smell.
I removed the turntable from its case and took off the aluminum plates to examine it. When I powered it on, it initially started up as usual, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower at the record&amp;rsquo;s starting point. Instead, there was a strong burning smell and a plume of smoke coming from the circuit board with the carriage switches.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Rebuilding the Main and Output PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</guid><description>I recently got the main circuit board, output circuit board, and DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5524) turntable. A customer in the UK sent them to me to fix because the platter&amp;rsquo;s RPM wasn&amp;rsquo;t consistent and the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower to the correct position when starting.
My usual process for these is to replace the electrolytic capacitors, install a new relay, and swap the single-turn RPM adjustment knobs with 25-turn ones for more precise control.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Return of an Old Friend from Australia - Dead Solenoid Transistor and a Carriage Motor with a Corroded Lead</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-return-of-an-old-friend-from-australia-dead-solenoid-transistor-and-a-carriage-motor-with-a-corroded-lead/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-return-of-an-old-friend-from-australia-dead-solenoid-transistor-and-a-carriage-motor-with-a-corroded-lead/</guid><description>Unfortunately, I recently received a well-used Beolover Beogram shipping container from Australia. Inside was a Beogram 4002 (5501) that I had previously restored in 2016. The 5501 model is unique because it represents a short-lived transitional version produced during B&amp;amp;O&amp;rsquo;s shift from the Beogram 4000 to the 4002. Although the 5501 features the analog control system of the 4002 series (unlike the 4000&amp;rsquo;s more sophisticated hard-wired digital logic system, which was sadly simplified in the 4002), it retains the mechanical carriage position switches found in the 4000.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Changing out the tonearm phono cartridge connector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 restoration project was paused until a new batch of Beolover replacement parts for the Beogram 400x tonearm cartridge mounts became available. With the parts in hand, the installation process could begin.
One of the cartridge connector contacts on this particular Beogram 4002 was defective. Whether this was a factory issue or a result of wear and tear is unclear, but the owner&amp;rsquo;s prior problems with cartridge mounting made replacing the connector a necessary step.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Increasing Tonearm Lowering Delay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</guid><description>After installing a new hood on a Beogram 4000 turntable, the author noticed the tonearm descended too quickly. Adjusting the damper&amp;rsquo;s screw didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem, as the tonearm still dropped rapidly despite the damper slowing down.
Further inspection revealed the damper&amp;rsquo;s linkage was positioned very close to the damper plunger. This proximity meant the linkage moved immediately when the damper activated, even before the damper could build up enough vacuum to slow the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s descent effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Preamplifier and the Radio Amplifier Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s review the Beocord 5000! This model contains many tantalum capacitors that, due to their age (around 35 years), should be replaced. Tantalum capacitors pose a fire risk if they short circuit because of the intense heat released when tantalum reacts with oxygen. While tantalum capacitors were favored in the 1970s due to their smaller size compared to aluminum electrolytic capacitors, advancements in manufacturing have closed the size gap. Today, modern aluminum capacitors can be just as small as the older tantalum ones.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the AC Motor Voltage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 turntable restoration, I observed a noisy motor, especially at 45 RPM. Replacing the electrolytic capacitors helped but didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem completely. To investigate further, I examined the motor voltage and the signal waveform from the Wien bridge oscillator, a clever design that uses an incandescent light bulb as a variable resistor for amplitude control. I measured the AC waveform amplitude at one of the motor leads relative to ground.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Display Restoration with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:28:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-display-restoration-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 being restored has a common issue: a faulty 7-segment display. While only one segment was out, these large, early LED displays are a key design element, making repair essential.
This display resembles the Beomaster 8000&amp;rsquo;s frequency display, but they are not interchangeable. The repair process, however, is the same as documented in previous posts.
To begin, PCB #11 and the bezel are removed to access the display for desoldering.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of New Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 and it was time to replace the large capacitors. This is a process I enjoy, made easier with a 3D printed adapter I designed. This adapter allows for the use of smaller, modern capacitors while maintaining a neat and organized appearance. I have a previous post detailing the connections for anyone who might find it helpful, as there are several jumpers that require re-soldering.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration involved replacing the motor phase capacitor and reservoir. I used a 3D-printed adapter I designed, which allows for secure mounting of modern, smaller capacitors in the original location using the factory bracket. This post provides a closer look at the replacement process and includes a comprehensive wiring diagram for the capacitors. This can be particularly helpful for those tackling this task for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: First Prototype Installed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</guid><description>I was tasked with creating an internal RIAA preamplifier for a restored Beogram 4002 (5521). This addition makes sense since many modern receivers lack a dedicated phono input. Additionally, the pre-opamp RIAA preamps found in many vintage B&amp;amp;O receivers introduce more noise compared to modern low-noise audio op-amps.
Researching contemporary RIAA preamp designs led me to the LM833 operational amplifier, a specialized low-noise op-amp for audio applications. I adapted a high-precision RIAA preamp circuit from a Texas Instruments application note AN-346, as established RIAA preamplifier designs exist.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Power Supply, Motor Control, Electronic Switch and Operational Control Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</guid><description>The restoration continues! Today, I replaced the remaining electrolytic capacitors on my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716). New electrolytics bring peace of mind!
The power supply board, including its reservoir and AC motor capacitors, along with the motor control, electronic switch, and operational control boards, were all addressed:
The Motor Control board, responsible for the take-up motor, had only one Tantalum capacitor that needed replacement:
Here it is after the replacement:
Next is the Electronic Switch board.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism, and Tracking Sensor Bulb Replacement and Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</guid><description>The initial step for restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable typically involves reconditioning the arm lowering mechanism and calibrating the tracking system. In this instance, hardened lubricants had affected the mechanical operation, and excessive sensitivity in the tracking sensor led to uncontrolled carriage movement after the arm lowered. The solenoid and damper assembly is depicted below:
The restoration began by disassembling the mechanism, cleaning all parts, and applying fresh lubrication:
A video illustrating the tracking sensor adjustment process is available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A Second Beogram 4002 (5523) Arrived for some TLC - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) in need of restoration arrived with its MMC4000 cartridge still attached and transport locks disengaged, causing initial concern about potential damage. The foam meant to support the tonearm had deteriorated, leaving it to swing freely.
Fortunately, the cartridge appeared undamaged, likely due to the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s light weight and protective tape. Testing on a restored Beogram 4000 confirmed its functionality.
The hood was in good condition, showing only minor scratches and signs of polishing.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating Recording Current and Bias</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</guid><description>Pleased with the seemingly functional Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape mechanism, an initial test recording was conducted using a waveform generator. Playback revealed a 3 dB channel imbalance on the Peak Program Meter (PPM), indicating a calibration issue. This was unsurprising given the deck&amp;rsquo;s age and highlighted the fortunate performance of a previously rebuilt Beocord 5000 in a Beolab 6000 setup, which operated well without calibration. To establish a solid calibration baseline, a reliable frequency response measurement was deemed essential.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Redesigned Drop-In Tracking Sensor Light Bulb Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I decided to upgrade the tracking sensor light bulb with a new SMD LED design I had created. My previous design lacked stability with the intensity adjustment trimmer, so I redesigned it to be more secure and visually appealing.
The new design incorporates the trimmer directly onto the circuit board and houses it within the light shield. This required modifications to the 3D printed housing to accommodate the trimmer.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Full Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 22:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable originating from California. The restoration process commenced with the reconstruction of the carriage and arm lowering mechanisms, encompassing meticulous cleaning and lubrication of components like the solenoid and damper.
Following the mechanism restoration, focus shifted to the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm. This involved addressing a common issue: a detached copper pad on the sensor arm assembly. The pad was reattached using epoxy to ensure smooth operation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and the Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I was working on had a completely frozen arm lowering mechanism. The old lubricant had become so hardened that I had to use a screwdriver to pry the linkages off their pivot pins. This is a common issue, easily resolved by cleaning and re-lubricating the mechanism. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the solenoid, damper, and linkages before disassembly:
This image shows the disassembled parts laid out on my workbench:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor, sent from Pennsylvania for repair, showed typical signs of needing lubrication, emitting a high-pitched noise when first turned on.
The motor was taken apart to access the bearings for oil treatment.
The bearings were placed in oil and a vacuum was applied. The appearance of bubbles showed air being pulled from the bearings, making room for oil to enter. After two days, the bubbles ceased, signaling the completion of the oil infusion process.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) began with the arm lowering and tracking systems, as these are essential for any further testing or repair work.
To start, I took out the damper and linkages to clean and lubricate them. Thankfully, all the components were in good condition, so lubrication and reassembly were straightforward. Next, I lubricated the pivot point connecting the damper to the arm linkage. This required removing the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Slow Slide Transport Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem was encountered where the tonearm carriage would continue moving after attempting to move it in reverse. This issue stemmed from a damaged keypad switch, specifically a bent contact terminal that prevented a clean shut-off connection. This damage was likely caused by a previous repair attempt.
To address this, the control panel and circuit board were removed to access and extract the switch terminals.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): First Contact and Two Dead Transistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 that was already being repaired but needed further troubleshooting. The unit is in good cosmetic condition with minor wear. Upon inspection, the platter motor ran when turned on, but the carriage remained static.
Further investigation revealed that transistor TR20, responsible for the carriage motor control, was faulty. Replacing this component restored carriage movement.
However, the carriage would move only slightly before returning to its starting position.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Adjustment of Platter and Sub-Chassis Alignment, Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and Adjustment of the Tonearm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 02:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</guid><description>After restoring the mechanics and electronics of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, it was time to ensure proper alignment of the platter, sub-chassis, and tonearm. The first step was centering the sub-chassis within the transport locks. However, a previous repair attempt had misaligned the transport locks, preventing adjustment. Taking the opportunity, new bushings were installed to replace the deteriorated originals, evidenced by orange plastic fragments within the enclosure.
[Images of deteriorated bushings and new bushings installed]</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</guid><description>During a recent Beogram 4000 restoration, my customer opted for a brand new reproduction hood from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These hoods mark a significant advancement in Beogram 400x restoration. Crafted through injection molding, they perfectly mirror the original hoods, eliminating the seams found in laser-cut and fused alternatives.
Simply put, these hoods are identical in appearance to the originals. Developed by Beoworld&amp;rsquo;s Dillen, their availability has greatly benefited Beogram 400x restorations.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>Following the repair of the MMC cartridge mount on the Beogram 4000, attention shifted to the malfunctioning arm lowering and tracking mechanisms.
The arm lowering system, comprising a solenoid and damper, was examined. The damper and its associated linkages were removed for cleaning and lubrication.
Inspection revealed the absence of a vital rubber washer in the damper unit, substituted with a makeshift transparency foil piece. This modification hindered proper damper function.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the carriage transport and arm lowering mechanisms, the electrolytic capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration project required attention. Replacing the original reservoir and motor capacitors in AC motor Beograms is always satisfying, and the 4000 boasts an impressive collection of large capacitors.
The initial step involved removing the outdated capacitors. A quick assessment using a BK LCR tester identified two faulty capacitors. One of the 2200uF capacitors registered a meager 7.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This article details the refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5504) turntable. An initial assessment of the unit is documented in a previous post here.
The turntable, stripped of its panels and platter, appeared relatively untouched. However, evidence of previous work emerged later.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly, which was quite dirty. After disassembling and cleaning the parts, the platter motor and capacitors were removed for thorough cleaning. The motor housing, including the bearings, underwent an oil infusion process under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Plexiglass Hood With Laser Cut Patches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</guid><description>The hinge area is the most delicate part of plexiglass hoods found on Beogram turntables. It&amp;rsquo;s subject to significant stress when opened and closed, while the presence of screw holes for the metal hinge makes it structurally vulnerable. I recently worked on a Beogram 4000 with a cracked hood and a broken-off piece.
Inspired by a previous restoration of a Beogram 3000 hinge, I aimed to create a similar solution for the 4000/4002 models.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor and Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently obtained a main PCB and DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002. I began with the motor refurbishment, a process that often requires several days for the bearings to become saturated with oil.
The motor is depicted here:
Disassembly was necessary to access the bearings, visible as two small rings on the black component in the front:
The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was noticeably oily, suggesting prior tampering. This was supported by a damaged commutator brush that was bent out of its intended form:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Aluminum Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all spring terminals in the switches, this Beogram 4000 received another upgrade: a replacement for the old, unstable plastic carriage pulley, now made from aluminum. The original pulley is shown below:
And here it is equipped with one of Nick&amp;rsquo;s well-crafted aluminum pulleys:
Contact me if you need a pulley for your Beogram; I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to connect you with Nick. These pulleys are compatible with the 4002 and 4004 models as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Some Final Touches - Replacing Plinth and Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</guid><description>Following the installation of the BeoloverRIAA internal preamplifier and the Commander remote control, this Beogram 4002 (5523) needed a few finishing touches.
The original plinth of the Beogram was damaged. A replacement plinth was sourced, but it also had minor damage, particularly to the corners. Inspired by a previous veneer repair on a Beomaster 8000, a similar approach was taken to address the plinth&amp;rsquo;s corners. Veneer was added and color-matched to the existing finish, significantly improving the appearance, although not completely perfect.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all switch terminals on a Beogram 4000 restoration project, the next step involved addressing the electronics. The restoration typically begins by replacing outdated reservoir and motor capacitors, as they are frequently out of specification and nearing failure. The image provided showcases these original components.
To ensure proper fitment of the (smaller) modern replacement capacitors, a custom 3D-printed fixture was designed and utilized. This fixture secures the capacitors in the correct position.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Unusual Keypad PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-unusual-keypad-pcb/</guid><description>This article highlights a unique Beogram 4000 keyboard PCB. Typically, the two bulbs illuminating the position scale are wired in series, using two 12V bulbs connected between the 24V power source and ground. This setup is illustrated in the first image and diagram. Notably, this series configuration results in the bulbs having opposite polarity.
This polarity difference is ideal for the author&amp;rsquo;s polarized LED replacement boards. The second image showcases these boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and Rebuilding of the Platter RPM Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</guid><description>During the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable, the electrolytic capacitors were replaced and new relays were installed to enhance RPM stability. The aging tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail catastrophically, were replaced as a precautionary measure. The main board was refurbished, replacing the electrolytic capacitors and installing new relays, including a custom-designed replacement for the Siemens relay that ensures precise RPM control.
The original reservoir capacitor, a dual-capacitor unit no longer in production, was replaced with a 3D-printed fixture housing two modern capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A Stuck Tonearm and Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously repaired, returned with a tonearm tracking issue. The problem was a misaligned tracking sensor aperture obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. To fix this, I slightly repositioned the aperture after loosening its screw. I replaced the original screw with a more secure flat socket head screw to prevent future misalignment. I then recalibrated the tracking sensor feedback.
While the Beogram was with me, the customer decided to have the dust cover polished.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5501 from Sweden: Full Technical Restoration and Some Interesting Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 turntable (Type 5501 with optical carriage position detection) for a complete technical restoration. The unit arrived without a dust cover. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the Beogram right after unpacking:
Besides a number of loose parts that fell out when I opened the box, I was surprised to see that the cartridge was still mounted on the tonearm:
Fortunately, the MMC4000 cartridge had a small plexiglass guard in place, preventing any damage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED and Improvement of the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>Replacing the sensor arm LED is typically the final step in converting a Beogram 4002 to use all LEDs. After restoring the DC motor, the next task was to install a recently designed flex-PCB-based LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb. The image below shows the sensor arm with the detector assembly removed:
Upon zooming in on the full-resolution image, a small black spot is visible on the glass bulb. This spot indicates significant tungsten evaporation from the filament, suggesting the bulb is nearing the end of its life and could soon fail, rendering the Beogram inoperable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Motor: A New Tool and a New Spark Suppressor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-motor-a-new-tool-and-a-new-spark-suppressor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 21:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-motor-a-new-tool-and-a-new-spark-suppressor/</guid><description>I worked on restoring a Beogram 4002 DC motor, a process that unveiled a new and interesting failure point for these motors. This experience further refines the restoration process for these motors.
The motor needed its usual oil infusion for the porous brass bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s rough operation when powered confirmed this need.
Upon disassembly, I found this motor had the older brush carrier design, notorious for being glued to the alignment posts and feedback coils.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from the Netherlands, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t use it. The top bearing suspension was damaged beyond repair.
As a result, I refurbished a different motor I had on hand.
To lubricate the bearings, I took the motor apart and submerged them in oil.
A vacuum was applied to the oil-submerged bearings. This caused significant bubbling, signifying air escaping from the bearing material and creating space for oil to enter.</description></item><item><title>Bang&amp;Olufsen MMC20EN Vintage Cartridge Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</guid><description>The MMC20EN cartridge that came with my recently restored Beogram 4004 parts was tested using my evolving cartridge testing methodology.
My approach involves evaluating the frequency range and trackability of a cartridge. For this, I utilize three test records: the Analogue Audio Ultimate Test LP for checking frequency response up to 20kHz, the Fisher Test &amp;amp; Performance Standard Quadradisc to observe 30kHz carrier frequency reproduction, and the Clearaudio Trackability Test Record to assess the cantilever suspension&amp;rsquo;s condition at different groove amplitudes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the AC Motor and Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s printed circuit boards, attention shifted to the capacitors associated with the reservoir and motor, as well as the AC motor itself. The capacitor and motor section appeared as shown before any servicing.
Visual inspection revealed leakage from the larger capacitors, indicating a critical need for replacement. The extent of the capacitor bay&amp;rsquo;s condition was evident upon their removal.
The AC motor was extracted for servicing, taking advantage of its disconnected state from the capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the DIN 5 Cable with a Cable Featuring RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-din-5-cable-with-a-cable-featuring-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 05:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-din-5-cable-with-a-cable-featuring-rca-plugs/</guid><description>I am rebuilding a Beogram 4002(5513) turntable to use with a McIntosh Preamplifier. The standard DIN5 connector on Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen equipment is incompatible, so I am replacing it with RCA connectors for the best shielding and lowest EMI. Direct installation inside the turntable offers superior performance compared to adapters.
For optimal sound, I chose high-quality, open-ended RCA cables from Sounds Heavenly in the UK. These cables feature individually shielded, twisted-pair left and right channels, embodying an &amp;ldquo;audiophile&amp;rdquo; design.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of Upgrades - Internal RIAA Preamp, Commander Remote Control and a New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</guid><description>Following the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) from Oklahoma, the next step was to add the customer&amp;rsquo;s desired upgrades. These included an internal Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier (designed for AC motor Beogram 4002s), a Beolover Commander remote control system, and a new hood for a pristine appearance.
The first upgrade was preparing the keypad for the Commander remote system. AC motor Beograms primarily use directly soldered wiring harnesses, so Commander installation isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;plug and play&amp;rdquo; like the DC motor version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>This article details the comprehensive restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The initial evaluation of this unit is detailed in a separate post.
The turntable was first disassembled, revealing the need for bearing lubrication in the platter motor, a common issue in these models. This process typically takes a few days.
While the bearings were being re-lubricated, the intricate carriage mechanism, responsible for raising and lowering the tonearm, was addressed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Recapping the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 restoration, I replaced all electrolytic capacitors as a preventative measure, opting for durable 105C types from reputable Japanese brands. Tantalum capacitors, particularly in older equipment, can fail dramatically, even catching fire.
On the power supply board, I discovered a missing screw and a loose one, potentially creating a dangerous short circuit scenario. Thankfully, no damage was evident. I replaced the tantalum capacitors and secured the board with a new stainless steel M3 screw.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with Stanley Turrentine and Milt Jackson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Kentucky. The unit, pictured below, was in excellent condition, making it ideal for a complete refurbishment.
As is typical with DC motor Beograms, the platter motor was the starting point. These motors commonly suffer from dried-out bearings, leading to speed instability. The extracted motor is shown here:
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings:
The bearings, visible as two small rings on the black pad, were then submerged in motor oil under a vacuum:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Complete Functional Restoration and a Spin with the Cal Tjader Quartet!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The restoration began with addressing the motor, a common procedure for these models. After removing and disassembling the motor, the Oilite bearings were submerged in oil and placed under a vacuum for several days to replenish lubrication.
Next, the carriage and arm mechanisms were disassembled, cleaned, and re-lubricated. This included taking apart and servicing the damper. The main PCB was removed, and both power transistors were replaced.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding DC Motor with Oil Infused Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the RPM relay and trimmers in the Beogram 4002 (5513) with updated parts, the DC motor required attention. The DC motor often proves to be the most challenging aspect of restoring a 4002 and nearly always demands attention. The primary hurdle lies in restoring the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite oil-infused brass sleeve bearings. These bearings are &amp;ldquo;pre-lubricated&amp;rdquo; in a new motor. From a typical consumer perspective, with a lifespan of 10-15 years, these bearings might be considered &amp;ldquo;maintenance-free.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating the Peak Program Meters (VU Meters)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</guid><description>After reassembling and successfully testing a Beocord 5000 tape deck, I decided to calibrate its Peak Program Meters (PPMs) according to the service manual.
Instead of directly inputting a 300 Hz signal into the Dolby B ICs as the manual suggested, I opted to feed a 25 mV, 300 Hz signal into the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inputs while in record mode (paused). Using a multimeter, I adjusted the recording levels to achieve the specified 740 mV RMS output at the Dolby B ICs (pin 7), allowing for the calibration of the PPMs&amp;rsquo; 0 dB level.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: RPM Performance Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</guid><description>I recently measured the RPM performance of my restored Beogram 4000 turntable. I was curious to see how the AC motor compared to the DC motors found in other models, like the Beogram 8000/8002 with their computer-controlled linear motors. After running the 4000 for 12 hours using my BeoloverRPM device, the results were interesting.
The AC motor demonstrated excellent stability, as evidenced by the graph. However, there was an initial period of drift as both the oscillator and motor warmed up.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Comparison of the RPM Stability Between Four Motors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-comparison-of-the-rpm-stability-between-four-motors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-comparison-of-the-rpm-stability-between-four-motors/</guid><description>Sonavor is currently restoring four Beogram 4002 turntables and recently asked for assistance in refurbishing the DC motors.
The restoration process involves removing the motor bearings, cleaning them, and applying fresh oil. To ensure effectiveness, a vacuum is used to draw the oil into the porous bearing material. The bearings are then cleaned of excess oil and reinstalled.
After reassembly, each motor undergoes a 24-hour RPM stability test using a specialized device.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Grounding Switch That Allows to Connect System and Signal Grounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</guid><description>During my latest restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I encountered a loud hum when playing records through my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s 4-channel phono input. The issue was resolved by connecting the signal and system grounds. Although the root cause of the hum remains unclear, I decided to install a switch to allow for easy toggling between the original separate grounding configuration and a direct connection between signal and system grounds at the turntable&amp;rsquo;s output.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</guid><description>I noticed a knocking sound coming from my Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s AC motor, which meant the Oilite brass bearing needed lubrication. These bearings are designed to release oil onto the motor shaft over time. Eventually, they need to be replaced or re-lubricated. Using a food vacuum sealer and a mason jar, you can replenish the oil. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I did it:
First, I removed the motor.
Next, I removed the two rivets holding the motor together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and Reservoir Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the tonearm and drive carriage mechanisms on this Beogram 4002 (5513), attention turned to the electronics. The initial phase involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, RPM trimmers, and the relay to guarantee smooth operation for years to come.
The main PCB in its original state is shown here.
The same PCB is pictured here after component replacement.
This image provides a detailed view of the RPM control section.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding a Noisy DC Motor with Oil Infused Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-a-noisy-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 11:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-a-noisy-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-bearings/</guid><description>The majority of Beogram 4002 turntables equipped with a DC motor require motor refurbishment. Indicators of this need include abrupt drops in revolutions per minute (RPM) or audible motor noise during operation. This specific Beogram 4002 (5514) exhibited significant noise during unloaded operation. As part of my restoration process for all 4002 turntables, I comprehensively rebuild the DC motors to preemptively address these common issues.
The primary contributor to these performance issues lies in the brass sleeve bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Restoring the Plexiglass Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I recently restored had a very scratched dust cover.
[Image of scratched dust cover]
If I can feel the scratches with my fingernail, the first restoration step is sanding with 220 grit sandpaper. This creates a smooth surface for polishing. This is what the surface looks like after sanding:
[Image of dust cover after sanding]
It looks a bit like wood at this stage. After approximately 10 polishing steps using progressively finer sandpaper and then micro-mesh polishing cloths, the surface is restored:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 551x: Exciting!! Replica DC Motor Bearing Prototypes from Beoparts Successfully Tested</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</guid><description>I received another set of Beogram 4002 platter motor components and an RPM panel from a customer in the Netherlands to restore. My work started with the motor, as it usually does.
I disassembled the motor to get to the bearings.
Typically, I would show a picture of the bearings being oiled in a vacuum chamber, but I received new Oilite bearings from www.beoparts-shop.com specifically for these DC motors, which I am testing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Bearings and Installation of New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 06:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor arrived from New Zealand for restoration. The upside-down pulley suggested prior repairs. Disassembly revealed a bent brush, a possible cause for the motor&amp;rsquo;s poor performance.
[Image of motor with bent brush]
The motor was fully disassembled, and the bearings underwent an oil infusion process to address potential RPM instability, a common issue.
[Image of disassembled motor] [Image of bearings in oil]
After the infusion, the bent brush was straightened.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the DC motor required attention. The bearings were making noise, indicating a need for lubrication. This is a common issue in Beogram DC motors of this age, often requiring oil replenishment for stable performance.
The motor was removed from the turntable for servicing.
The bearings, identified as two ring-shaped components, were taken out of the motor.
To lubricate them, the bearings were submerged in motor oil, and a vacuum was applied to remove trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): DC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently restored a DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The turntable exhibited the common issue of inconsistent RPM, indicating the need to lubricate the motor bearings. I documented this process in detail in a video posted earlier. Here are some observations from the motor restoration.
The first image shows the motor in its initial condition upon arrival:
This image shows the motor after disassembly:
The two small &amp;ldquo;donut&amp;rdquo; shapes in the front right of the photo are the bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Oil Infusion of Bearings, Replacement of Spark Snubbers, and Repair of a Disconnected Pickup Coil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-replacement-of-spark-snubbers-and-repair-of-a-disconnected-pickup-coil/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-replacement-of-spark-snubbers-and-repair-of-a-disconnected-pickup-coil/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor arrived from Michigan. Initial inspection showed no obvious external issues.
However, a bench test revealed the rotor was blocked, preventing the motor from spinning.
Upon disassembly, it was evident that someone had previously attempted a repair: the brushes were deformed and a pickup coil pin was broken. Further disassembly revealed a loose and disconnected coil near the missing pin.
To address potential bearing issues, the bearings were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</guid><description>During the ongoing restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the incandescent bulbs illuminating the RPM trimmer scales were replaced with LEDs for enhanced longevity. Custom-designed circuit boards housing SMD LEDs were crafted to seamlessly replace the original bulbs, ensuring a direct fit.
These LED assemblies are offered to fellow enthusiasts, with an instructional video demonstrating their installation available online.
The following images detail the RPM trimmer panel, initially showcasing the rear view with original bulbs in place.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (II)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s rebuilt Peak Program Meters (PPM) display passed a 24-hour test, confirming its functionality.
To reattach the red-green covers, I secured the display to ensure a tight seal, preventing light leakage. Using a soldering iron, I melted the plastic posts of the covers, replicating the original attachment method.
During cleaning, the glue holding the light guide dissolved, indicating it was likely polyvinyl ester-based. I used &amp;lsquo;Aleene&amp;rsquo;s Original Tacky Glue&amp;rsquo; as a substitute, providing a clear and durable bond.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Linear Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</guid><description>My restoration project of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable started with the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. These mechanisms often require attention because of hardened lubricants and misadjusted tracking sensors.
After taking the mechanism apart for cleaning and lubrication, I addressed the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm, which commonly experiences stiffness due to hardened lubricants.
The sensor arm was then removed for disassembly to further work on the linkage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A Broken Off Solenoid Plunger and New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, recently serviced and returned to a customer, unexpectedly came back with a faulty tonearm. The culprit was a broken solenoid plunger, a part responsible for lowering the tonearm. This unusual breakage was likely due to material fatigue.
To fix the issue, the solenoid was replaced with one from a donor Beogram 4002. During the repair, it was discovered that the transport lock bushings had also deteriorated and needed replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Worn Keypad Restoration - My Process Finally Appears Reproducible...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a common issue: a worn-out keypad. The start button, in particular, was in rough shape due to frequent use.
After a multi-month endeavor, I successfully restored the keypad to an almost-new appearance. My refined restoration method finally produces consistent results, marking a significant step forward in the 4002&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation.
During the process, I discovered another problem: a broken RPM panel clamp. This prevented the RPM panel from staying securely in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Broken SO ('Shut Off') Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 05:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about a malfunctioning &amp;ldquo;Shut Off&amp;rdquo; (SO) switch, which was missing a crucial plastic part, causing issues with the deck&amp;rsquo;s shutdown process. To address this, a 3D printed replacement part was designed and created. The &amp;ldquo;End Switch&amp;rdquo; (ES), still equipped with its plastic component, is pictured alongside the SO switch, highlighting the missing element.
Creating a functional replacement part was challenging due to its small size and the limitations of the 3D printer.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: First Contact and Installing New Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-first-contact-and-installing-new-belts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 10:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-first-contact-and-installing-new-belts/</guid><description>I recently received a Beocord 9000 cassette deck that needed some care. It was shipped in its original Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen box, which was then placed inside a second box for protection. However, the B&amp;amp;O box was incorrectly oriented inside the outer box, likely resulting in an upside-down journey. The original box had some water damage:
Thankfully, the Beocord 9000 itself appeared unharmed:
As a rule, I never connect devices to power immediately after unpacking.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of Beolover RIAA Preamp and 4002 Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (5523), culminating in the installation of gold-plated RCA plugs. My customer opted to have my recently developed internal BeoloverRIAA preamplifier added, along with the 4002 Commander remote control system, which enables control of all functions via a paired Apple remote.
This marks the first 4002 to feature both the Commander and the RIAA preamp – a true fusion of past and present!
Pictures showcasing the installation process of the BeoloverRIAA board and the 4002 Commander are included.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Some Microsurgery on Disconnected Pickup Coils</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-some-microsurgery-on-disconnected-pickup-coils/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 10:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-some-microsurgery-on-disconnected-pickup-coils/</guid><description>I recently obtained a DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002 located in Norway. The motor required repair. The owner had already performed the &amp;lsquo;oil infusion&amp;rsquo; procedure for the Oilite bearings. However, after reassembling and reinstalling the motor into the Beogram, the platter&amp;rsquo;s speed was excessively high and could not be adjusted.
This image displays the motor, without the pulley, in the condition I received it:
Uncontrollably high speed in a DC platter motor usually indicates a problem with one or both of the RPM feedback pickup coils within the motor, assuming the motor control circuit is functioning correctly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:19:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The last step in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5523) was replacing the old and slightly corroded RCA plugs. The picture highlights the original plugs:
This image showcases the new gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs during installation:
The straightforward design of these plugs, which simplifies installation and ensures solid solder connections, is something I appreciate. And here is the finished product:
I need to wait for the PCBs for my new RIAA phono preamp design, so there will be a slight delay.</description></item></channel></rss>