<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Card on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/card/</link><description>Recent content in Card on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/card/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Consumer Card achieves outstanding success, according to DIB's report</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</guid><description>Source: DIB website. Banner for the Consumer Card page.
The Consumer Card, a collaboration between the Department of Economic Development (DED) in Dubai and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the largest Islamic bank in the UAE, has surpassed expectations in a very competitive market by the close of 2016. This success highlights how much customers value the card&amp;rsquo;s transparency and customer-centric approach.
Customers appreciate the card&amp;rsquo;s straightforward rewards system, which focuses on everyday transactions rather than requiring increased spending.</description></item><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer.</description></item><item><title>Customize SPD paper and electronic greeting cards with your own branding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</guid><description>Source: SPD website.
The SPD, a Singaporean organization supporting individuals with disabilities, operates a supported employment facility that creates physical and digital greeting cards. These cards are suitable for various events like birthdays and holidays such as Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, and Chinese New Year.
Customization options are available for these cards, including adding company branding, personalized notes, or designs for other special events.
Interested parties can explore the complete selection of cards on the SPD e-shop.</description></item><item><title>Discover financial products in Malaysia with GoBear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</guid><description>GoBear, a metasearch engine that simplifies financial product comparison, has officially launched in Malaysia. The platform offers unbiased, side-by-side comparisons of products like travel insurance and credit cards, with over 1,000 options currently listed and more to come.
Iskandar Ezzahuddin, GoBear&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, emphasized the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: &amp;ldquo;GoBear stems from the understanding that modern consumers demand convenient access to service information and straightforward product comparisons before making financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces Visa Infinite debit card for exclusive VIP clients</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new debit card, Visa Infinite, exclusively for its ‘Priority’ private banking customers.
Each customer is assigned a personal relationship manager who oversees the issuance of the new card and serves as their primary point of contact for all KFH services. According to Private Banking General Manager, Matthew Welch, the card offers customers unique benefits and support services.
These benefits include access to over 500 airport lounges globally, special offers and priority reservations at a wide range of upscale restaurants, and a 24/7 international concierge service for reservations, ticket bookings, car rentals, and taxi arrangements.</description></item><item><title>The goal of the BTSE Debit Card is to provide worldwide access to funds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</guid><description>Source: BTSE. The BTSE Debit Card.
There&amp;rsquo;s a new player in the crypto debit card arena. Accepted at over 53 million MasterCard merchants and compatible with over a million ATMs globally, the BTSE Debit Card sets itself apart by allowing users to fund it with various fiat and cryptocurrencies without needing a traditional bank account.
BTSE, a fintech company focused on financial freedom, designed this card to give users more control over their money.</description></item><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here.</description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa.</description></item><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015).</description></item><item><title>Al Rajhi's initiative to promote card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</guid><description>Al Rajhi Bank has introduced its &amp;ldquo;House, Car and Salary&amp;rdquo; campaign, offering over SR4 million in prizes to encourage the use of its Mada and credit cards within Saudi Arabia and internationally.
The grand prize, exclusively for Saudi citizens, includes a house, a BMW 7 Series car, and a year of monthly SR20,000 payments. Four additional winners will receive a BMW 7 Series car each, while seven others will get a year of monthly SR20,000 payments.</description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay is expanding its presence in Turkey through partnerships with ZIRAAT BANK and Garanti Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</guid><description>Ziraat Bank in Turkey has partnered with UnionPay International to enable UnionPay card acceptance across all its ATMs and POS terminals within the year. This initiative aims to broaden the reach of UnionPay cards within Turkey and enhance the experience for visiting UnionPay cardholders.
UnionPay anticipates that this collaboration will increase the acceptance rate of UnionPay cards at Turkish ATMs from 50% to nearly 70% by year-end. Similarly, POS terminal acceptance is projected to rise from 80% to almost 90%.</description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year.</description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay International introduces a new cross-border marketing campaign with global promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</guid><description>Source: UnionPay International. Ge Huayong, Chairman of China UnionPay (sixth from the right), Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International (fifth from the right), and representatives from initial partners were present at the ceremony.
UnionPay International, in collaboration with Bank of China, China Merchants Bank, CYTS, Ctrip, Spring Airlines, SaSa Hong Kong, Prince Jewellery &amp;amp; Watch, LUKFOOK JEWELLERY, and ISA, has introduced 优计划 (Youjihua), translating to &amp;lsquo;a beneficial strategy&amp;rsquo; and playing on the &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; in UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s Chinese name.</description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave.</description></item><item><title>UOB creates profiles of the contemporary Singaporean woman and customizes card privileges to suit her needs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 08:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first profiles of the modern Singaporean woman, categorized by their behaviors and spending habits. The UOB Leading Ladies report identifies these women as digital natives, young professionals, and cosmopolitan leaders.
Jacquelyn Tan, UOB&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director and Regional Head of Cards and Payments, highlighted the report&amp;rsquo;s focus on the entrepreneurial spirit and spending trends of contemporary Singaporean women. She emphasized the significant contribution of women to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s GDP, exceeding 40%, and their dedication to both work and family.</description></item><item><title>Experience an abundance of travel rewards with the NBK Miles World Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</guid><description>Source: NBK. The NBK Miles World Mastercard.
People who travel frequently from Kuwait can accumulate points and enjoy airport lounge access with the NBK Miles World Mastercard.
These NBK Miles Points can be used to reserve flights from over 800 airlines, book accommodations at more than 150,000 hotels, and rent vehicles from well-known agencies worldwide. Cardholders can redeem their miles for any destination, airline, origin point, and time of year, without blackout dates or seat restrictions.</description></item><item><title>UOB introduces its inaugural credit card tailored for millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</guid><description>A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB), the UOB Young Professionals Survey, has revealed that the spending habits of millennials are influenced by their desire for travel and sharing food experiences with loved ones. UOB aims to secure half of all millennials as customers within the next three years, recognizing their imminent rise as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s dominant consumer group.
UOB categorizes millennials as individuals between the ages of 26 and 35.</description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE.</description></item><item><title>ADIB introduces the Spice credit card specifically for Non-Resident Indians and Non-Resident Pakistanis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</guid><description>Source: ADIB. The new Spice Card offers a range of cashbacks if the owner hits a minimum spend.
Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) has introduced the Spice Card, a new product designed specifically for non-resident Indians (NRIs) and non-resident Pakistanis (NRPs) living in the UAE.
The ADIB Spice Card provides NRIs and NRPs with opportunities to save money through a variety of competitive offers and discounts. These include cashback rewards of 9% on dining, 7% on supermarket purchases, 4% on fuel, and 1% on utility bills.</description></item></channel></rss>