<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Financial on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financial/</link><description>Recent content in Financial on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discover financial products in Malaysia with GoBear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</guid><description>GoBear, a metasearch engine that simplifies financial product comparison, has officially launched in Malaysia. The platform offers unbiased, side-by-side comparisons of products like travel insurance and credit cards, with over 1,000 options currently listed and more to come.
Iskandar Ezzahuddin, GoBear&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, emphasized the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: &amp;ldquo;GoBear stems from the understanding that modern consumers demand convenient access to service information and straightforward product comparisons before making financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit card applications can now be approved instantly by DBS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-card-applications-can-now-be-approved-instantly-by-dbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 11:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-card-applications-can-now-be-approved-instantly-by-dbs/</guid><description>DBS Bank in Singapore has introduced a new online application service using the national platform, MyInfo. This service allows new and existing customers to apply for credit cards and open DBS Cashline accounts with instant approval and access to funds, making it a first in Singapore.
Available to 3.3 million SingPass holders, this service, accessible through DBS/POSB Internet banking and websites, simplifies the application process. Typically, new customers wait up to a week for credit card or DBS Cashline access, but using MyInfo eliminates the need for traditional applications and physical documents, providing real-time approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-card-applications-can-now-be-approved-instantly-by-dbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-card-applications-can-now-be-approved-instantly-by-dbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Financial services companies are placing a greater emphasis on developing a strong risk culture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</guid><description>A recent study by Mercer focusing on executive compensation in the global financial services industry found that a majority of firms are prioritizing the development of robust risk cultures within their organizations. Sixty-two percent of surveyed firms reported significant efforts to penalize misconduct and non-compliance, while 60% demonstrated clear leadership commitment to ethical behavior. Furthermore, 58% have established and communicated unambiguous objectives related to risk culture.
Vicki Elliott, Senior Partner and Financial Services Talent Leader at Mercer, highlighted the importance of senior leaders setting a positive example when it comes to risk management and compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In July, Walton will be hosting a gaming session for Cashflow 101</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-july-walton-will-be-hosting-a-gaming-session-for-cashflow-101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-july-walton-will-be-hosting-a-gaming-session-for-cashflow-101/</guid><description>Source: Walton eDM.
The Walton Group (Walton), a multinational real estate investment and development company specializing in pre-development land investments in North America, is hosting another session of the Cashflow 101 board game in Singapore.
Cashflow 101, also known as the Cash Flow game, was created by Robert Kiyosaki, author of Rich Dad Poor Dad. The game aims to help players connect their life goals with their finances by shifting their perspective on cash flow and investment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-july-walton-will-be-hosting-a-gaming-session-for-cashflow-101/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-july-walton-will-be-hosting-a-gaming-session-for-cashflow-101/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC experienced a 12.3% increase in new company registrations in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:21:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</guid><description>Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC), a prominent international business and financial hub in the Asia Pacific region, demonstrated strong performance across all financial sectors in 2014. These sectors include banking, insurance, leasing, wealth management, and Islamic finance, with a 12.3% rise in new company registrations compared to the previous year.
The organization highlights that 70% of companies registered in Labuan IBFC come from Asia, with 57% from Southeast Asia, particularly Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Walton encourages financial literacy through moderated Cashflow games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walton-encourages-financial-literacy-through-moderated-cashflow-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 04:34:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walton-encourages-financial-literacy-through-moderated-cashflow-games/</guid><description>Playing the Cashflow game was a thrilling experience. I managed to buy and sell a startup within an hour, earning a quick $100,000 profit. With my pilot&amp;rsquo;s salary, cash flow was excellent. However, other players faced financial struggles, barely making ends meet or lacking funds for investments.
I focused on smaller investments initially, cleared some liabilities with guidance from the banker, and increased my spending and income. Although my passive income was slightly less than my expenses, someone else came closer to achieving financial freedom...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walton-encourages-financial-literacy-through-moderated-cashflow-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walton-encourages-financial-literacy-through-moderated-cashflow-games/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>