<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Convergence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-convergence/</link><description>Recent content in Network Convergence on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-convergence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Are VoIP and SIP Trunking So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</guid><description>When your outdated PBX system needs an upgrade, consider transitioning to an IP PBX and replacing traditional phone lines with a SIP Trunk. This shift to modern technologies is driven by their ability to deliver new features and cost savings without compromising call quality.
Upgrading doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require replacing existing phones. While VoIP SIP phones offer advantages like network connectivity and simplified management, older phones can connect to the IP PBX via interface cards with FSX ports...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Convergence for Small Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 23:27:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>The convergence of voice and data networks is a cost-saving strategy employed by businesses of all sizes. Combining these networks into one is more cost-effective than running separate networks for internet and phone services.
While larger companies have readily adopted converged networks, smaller businesses can also benefit, especially with new installations. Integrated T1 service is a practical solution for smaller companies with 6 to 12 phone lines and broadband internet. This technology is relevant for various businesses, from dealerships and real estate offices to manufacturing facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>