<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Clothing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/clothing/</link><description>Recent content in Clothing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/clothing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benetton will concentrate on empowering women through their new collection, A Collection of Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</guid><description>The idea that women sharing their experiences and learning from each other is crucial for creating a brighter future is the driving force behind A Collection Of Us. This new United Colors of Benetton collection, launching in four parts throughout October 2015, December 2015, February 2016, and April 2016, embodies this philosophy.
Each capsule within the collection reimagines a core aspect of Benetton&amp;rsquo;s brand identity—heritage, technique, color, and performance—giving it a fresh and modern significance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The potential marketing opportunities presented by a customizable wearable device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</guid><description>Source: Broadcast Wear website. Control the shirt&amp;rsquo;s display with an app.
Broadcast Wear, an innovative company from Hyderabad, has introduced a programmable t-shirt with touch-sensitive technology, opening up exciting possibilities for marketing.
Their invention incorporates a flexible, washable LED screen directly into the fabric. Users can pair the shirt with the Broadcast Wear smartphone app to instantly show any text or image. A simple tap turns the screen on and another tap switches it off...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AIN has added English and Chinese websites for those interested in fashion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</guid><description>Source: AIN English website.
A Korean women&amp;rsquo;s fashion brand is aiming to become a global name, focusing particularly on mainland China, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
AIN has seen positive results selling on international e-commerce platforms. To further expand its reach, the company has launched English and Chinese websites through cafe24, a leading Korean e-commerce platform. AIN&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Park A-In, shared that customers appreciate the brand&amp;rsquo;s distinct, contemporary designs and overall aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean fashion designers are displaying their collections that have been digitally printed by Epson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. Display, Wai Yang.
Epson, a printing technology company, partnered with designers based in Singapore for FashionisTech, a showcase at the recent FUZE Fashion Technology 2017 event in Singapore. The designers used Epson&amp;rsquo;s digital printing technology to create their collections.
Organized by Textile and Fashion Federation (TAFF), the summit was the first of its kind in Singapore. It promoted advancements in materials and highlighted creative uses of technology by Singaporean fashion brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: Customizable, reusable clothing in an instant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 13:33:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</guid><description>SiDi Huang, the creator behind ZipSeam, has developed an innovative solution for achieving a tailored look without the need for traditional sewing. ZipSeam offers a quick and easy way to create secure, temporary seams in loose clothing, providing a better fit for the wearer.
This invention has a wide range of applications, from the modeling industry and hand-me-downs to simply adjusting the fit of clothes you love. It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that this project has garnered significant attention and support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Belstaff has opened its flagship store in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Belstaff.
The renowned British heritage brand, Belstaff, recently celebrated the grand opening of its flagship store in Tokyo, Japan. Situated within the expansive Ginza Six retail complex, the new store occupies a prime location within this 47,000 square meter shopping destination. This strategic move underscores Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s growing presence in the Japanese market and its commitment to global retail expansion.
Upon its debut, the Tokyo flagship presents a curated selection of Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s offerings, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s complete menswear collection and, for the first time in Tokyo, its womenswear line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>