<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contract Expiration Means Opportunity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</guid><description>Business telecom services often come with fixed-price contracts lasting 1 to 3 years, providing price stability but limited cost-saving opportunities. However, the fear of potential price increases upon contract renewal is often overstated. In many cases, businesses can find better deals by exploring alternative providers.
The misconception about limited options arises from a perceived lack of competition. While you may have negotiated what seemed like the best price at the time, there are often numerous competitive service providers not listed in traditional directories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS1 Telephone Service Lowers Business Phone Bills</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</guid><description>DS1, more commonly known as T1, is a digital telecommunications standard that can potentially save businesses substantial amounts of money on their phone bills. Despite its benefits, many people are unfamiliar with it.
Although the terms are often used interchangeably, there&amp;rsquo;s a slight distinction between DS1 and T1. DS1 (Digital Signal 1) refers to the format of the digital signal transmitted over the line, while T1 describes the physical four-wire copper connection itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Services Proliferate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</guid><description>The increasing need for bandwidth in the business world has driven the rapid expansion of high-speed voice and data services. While T1 lines were once considered high-end, businesses now have a variety of options, including various DSx copper and fiber optic connections, wireless broadband, and even point-to-point laser technology.
DS3 is gaining popularity as companies find their T1 connections inadequate. Upgrading from a DS1&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 Mbps to DS3&amp;rsquo;s 45 Mbps accommodates more users and allows for dedicated internet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 PRI is More Than Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</guid><description>T1 lines are the most common way to link PBX phone systems to the telephone network. T1 PRI service is often the preferred choice because it can transmit Caller ID information to business phones or call centers. However, there are additional ways that T1 PRI can offer the most budget-friendly phone line trunking.
T1 PRI is a highly specialized telecom service. T1 lines have been in use for over half a century to carry phone calls, and more recently, for point-to-point data, dedicated internet service, and connections to private networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Business Needs Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There was a time when the only way to communicate electronically was with that clunky black phone on your desk. While that phone might still be there, modern technology has made it lighter and brought a wealth of new communication methods. Email, text messages, mobile phone calls, and video chats are now commonplace across various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, smartphones, and even watches.
A significant challenge, particularly in business, is that these platforms and applications don&amp;rsquo;t always work well together...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tell Me You're Not PAYING For Equipment Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</guid><description>Stop wasting money on expensive equipment leads that often lead nowhere.
There&amp;rsquo;s a smarter way to generate sales and marketing leads for your telephone systems and IT networking equipment: commission-based leads. This means you receive qualified leads from serious businesses in your area as they emerge, completely free of charge. You then select the leads you want to pursue and focus your efforts on closing the deal. Only after a successful sale and payment from the customer do you share a small percentage with the agency that provided the lead...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom and Network Domain Names For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong domain name is crucial for any online business. The best names reflect your business, are easy to remember for offline use, and are pronounceable. Owning your own domain provides a much stronger online identity compared to generic alternatives. This ownership gives you full control over your website, email, and branding.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in business telecom for almost 15 years and acquired many domain names related to that industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Attention: Telephone System Dealers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</guid><description>For businesses selling, installing, or servicing business telephone systems, a new business model called the VAR Network is gaining popularity nationwide. This model helps generate more business without requiring upfront expenses.
The VAR Network is an online database system showcasing business profiles of numerous telephone and computer networking dealers. This fully automated platform connects potential customers seeking telecom assistance with qualified dealers in their area. Dealers are notified of potential matches and can choose to pursue these opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Quality Call Termination With SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Prioritizing voice packets on a network ensures high-quality VoIP calls within an organization. However, connecting to the outside world poses a challenge due to the incompatibility between modern packet-switched networks and the traditional circuit-switched phone system. To bridge this gap, organizations can either manage the conversion internally or outsource it to a third-party provider through SIP trunking.
SIP trunking offers a potentially cost-effective solution by consolidating multiple phone lines into a single &amp;ldquo;trunk&amp;rdquo; line and utilizing the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for call switching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Neutral Connectivity at Colocation Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses struggling to find enough bandwidth might be overlooking a simpler solution. Instead of waiting for carriers to come to them, companies can benefit by going where the carriers already are.
Colocation Centers: A Hub for Connectivity
Carriers are drawn to locations called colocation centers, or colos, and carrier hotels. These large data centers are designed to accommodate multiple tenants, unlike typical data centers that serve a single company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Twice the T1 Line Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your internet connection feeling a little slow? That T1 line that used to be more than enough might be struggling to keep up with your current needs. You&amp;rsquo;re not the only one experiencing this. While T1 bandwidth was sufficient for even large companies a decade ago, today, even small and medium-sized businesses are finding themselves needing more. The shift towards online applications and connectivity, while beneficial for productivity, has led to a significant increase in bandwidth demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Phone Lines For PBX Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 16:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</guid><description>Many modern business phone systems utilize T-1 lines to link their buildings to the local telephone company. This is because merging multiple individual lines into one or two T-1 lines is more cost-efficient. This holds true whether your internal phone system is analog or digital, as even most VoIP systems rely on T-1 lines for external calls.
Smaller setups like basic one or two-line phones or key systems with 4-6 lines typically use analog lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Filling Coverage Gaps With High Quality Business Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses in big cities have it easy when it comes to internet and phone service. There are so many options! But what if your business isn&amp;rsquo;t in a big city? What if you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with slow internet and outdated phone lines? You&amp;rsquo;re not out of luck!
Look Up for Better Options
Stop looking for internet and phone service on the ground. Look up! Satellite service is a great option for businesses that need fast, reliable service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</guid><description>Businesses can now benefit from a new, cost-effective broadband connection service: Ethernet Internet. To learn more about this exciting development, watch my concise YouTube presentation here: Ethernet Internet business presentation.
As the presentation highlights, Ethernet Internet offers a rare combination of affordability and superior performance. This cutting-edge technology is rapidly evolving and expanding beyond metropolitan areas. Soon, it will be accessible across the country, delivered wirelessly in rural regions and through copper or fiber optic connections in urban centers, with speeds reaching up to 10 Mbps or higher...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadview Networks OfficeSuite Brings The Cloud To SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</guid><description>Smaller companies often want to adopt money-saving technologies like VoIP, private networks, and cloud services, but the initial investment can be daunting. While internet-based options seem appealing, their quality and reliability are often a concern. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for businesses of all sizes to access these advanced tools without breaking the bank.
Broadview Networks&amp;rsquo; OfficeSuite offers a comprehensive solution, effectively serving as a company&amp;rsquo;s central office across multiple locations. This enterprise-grade PBX system provides the functionality of a traditional system with the convenience of easy administration through a web browser...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services For The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</guid><description>Initially only utilized by telecom companies, wavelength services are now accessible to large organizations. These high-bandwidth fiber optic services are necessary for entities like hospitals, financial institutions, government service providers, video production companies, content delivery networks, and research facilities. The demand for faster data transfer solutions is constantly increasing. But are wavelength services the answer?
A wavelength, or lambda, is light at a specific frequency, similar to a distinct color. It is usually measured in nanometers (wavelength) rather than terabits per second (frequency)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Are T1 Lines Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of unreliable DSL and cable internet for your business, consider a T1 line. While DSL and cable are suitable for home use, T1 offers a different level of service. As a regulated telecommunications service, T1 ensures consistent bandwidth and reliable uptime, unlike the consumer-grade alternatives.
T1 lines are widely accessible for businesses and function similarly to utilities. If your business has electricity, water, and phone service, you can likely get a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Better Than a T3 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 voice and data lines, once a reliable option for businesses, now offer insufficient speed (45 Mbps) for modern demands, which often exceed 100 Mbps. Businesses today require significantly faster connections, with some even seeking speeds beyond 10 Gbps. If you&amp;rsquo;re still using a T3 line, you might find better bandwidth options at a similar or lower cost.
What is a T3 Line?
Developed by Bell Labs, the T3 line was designed to carry numerous simultaneous phone conversations, a function it still serves in certain settings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Concatenation for Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Many businesses are choosing Carrier Ethernet services for their wide area and metropolitan area networks. Ethernet is directly compatible with local area networks and offers greater bandwidth than traditional telecom services like T1 (1.5 Mbps) and DS3 (45 Mbps). The demand for bandwidth is rising as more content shifts from emails and simple websites to videos and high-resolution images. Ethernet (10 Mbps), Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), and Gigabit Ethernet (1,000 Mbps) often provide the most cost-effective solutions for bandwidth expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LMDS Fills the Fiber Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</guid><description>Although fiber optic bandwidth is widely available across the country, connecting businesses to this network over the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; is a different story. It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to realize that less than 20% of commercial buildings are equipped for fiber optic telecommunications services.
This is primarily due to the high cost of installing fiber optic cables, a process that&amp;rsquo;s difficult to justify when businesses already have access to telephone and data services through existing copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Lifesaver</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</guid><description>Imagine your company facing a critical situation. It&amp;rsquo;s growing, and you need more bandwidth than your reliable T1 line can offer. Upgrading to DS3 seems logical, but your provider can only offer a limited increase, nowhere near the 25 or 50 Mbps you require. They suggest fiber optic service, but your location lacks it, meaning months of waiting and a hefty construction bill.
This presents a difficult choice: secure funding and wait for fiber installation, or relocate to a fiber-ready area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Branching Out With MPLS and VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</guid><description>Is secure communication between multiple locations critical for your business? As businesses increasingly rely on electronic forms and transactions, traditional methods like fax machines, overnight mail, and dial-up connections are no longer sufficient. To stay competitive, businesses need real-time access to sales and inventory data, rapid transfer of large files like medical images and CAD drawings, and instant delivery of important documents. A broadband connection linking all your key locations is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How AI is Helping to Improve Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Customer service calls are increasingly frustrating due to rising costs and labor shortages, negatively impacting both customers and companies. Tech expert David Pogue, in a CBS News report, suggests a blend of human agents and AI as a solution.
One such AI, called Grace, can handle customer interactions independently. However, AI like Grace can falter in complex situations, necessitating a transfer to human agents. While some of the best agents are located internationally and may have accents, this can be a hurdle for some US customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Cuts Costs, Expands Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/</guid><description>In the business world, we often face tough decisions where we must choose between two desirable options. But what if we didn&amp;rsquo;t have to choose? What if we could have it all? That&amp;rsquo;s precisely the advantage that Ethernet service offers.
Ethernet provides a win-win situation: increased bandwidth at a lower cost. You might wonder how that&amp;rsquo;s possible. The answer lies in technological progress and the emergence of ambitious new providers determined to revolutionize telecommunications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying Out of the Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 19:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</guid><description>While the use of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is widespread in information technology, understanding its complexities is crucial. The cloud often represents large, intricate networks that users may not fully comprehend.
Although many users are content with the cloud&amp;rsquo;s seemingly magical abilities, David G. Rusin, CEO of American Fiber Systems, argues against perceiving internet clouds as uniform entities. He emphasizes the differences in integrity, reliability, and delivery among cloud providers, highlighting the importance of scrutinizing these aspects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Steal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</guid><description>Everyone appreciates a bargain, especially for telecommunications services. The current prices for Ethernet might even make you wonder if they&amp;rsquo;re legitimate. To see just how competitive these prices are, take a moment to compare Ethernet costs for your business locations.
The reason Ethernet services are so affordable now is due to rapid technological advancements. Until recently, traditional telephone company services were the only option. Today, competition has introduced alternatives that have completely changed the landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips To Reduce Your Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 07:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses are facing a challenging time as they grapple with the fluctuating economic landscape brought on by the Covid-19 crisis. While growth was once the primary focus, survival has now taken center stage, making cost control paramount. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some immediate steps you can take to reduce expenses without jeopardizing operations.
Are You Paying For Unused Services?
It might seem improbable, but both individuals and businesses frequently pay for services they don&amp;rsquo;t utilize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ignore That PBX Behind the Curtain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:31:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</guid><description>Operating a small business doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to sound like it, especially with tools like virtual PBX systems. These systems can give your two-person office the professional edge of a Fortune 500 corporation.
Traditional PBX systems, standard in large companies, offer features such as individual extensions, direct dialing, call transferring, and outside line access. However, they come with a hefty price tag. iTeleCenter, a virtual PBX solution, offers an affordable alternative that transforms your existing phones into a robust communication system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ethernet Next Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</guid><description>Feeling constrained by your internet speed? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While your business might be struggling with a slow T1 line, your competitors may have a secret weapon: a new, affordable broadband service called Carrier Ethernet.
This service, rapidly being deployed across the nation, is an extension of the familiar Ethernet standard used in local area networks (LANs). Instead of converting data to different protocols for external connections, businesses can now use Ethernet for seamless, high-speed access to the internet and connections with other facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Port At Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</guid><description>You might be surprised to learn that a connection to the outside world could be as simple as an Ethernet port in your telecom closet. This is due to a relatively new technology called Ethernet WAN (Wide Area Network).
Traditionally, organizations have relied on the public switched telephone network (PSTN) for external connections. Technologies designed for phone calls, like T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services, were adapted to carry data traffic and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your 50 Mbps WAN Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The need for 50 Mbps bandwidth has increased due to businesses needing to use cloud services, access remote data centers, transfer large data files, run e-commerce platforms, send high-resolution images, and distribute video content. There are various ways to get 50 Mbps bandwidth connectivity, each with its own benefits and drawbacks.
DS3 &amp;amp; T3
DS3, or T3, is a traditional telecom service designed for transmitting many calls simultaneously between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>