<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Awareness on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/awareness/</link><description>Recent content in Awareness on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/awareness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is prepared to take action in response to Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Health (MOH) has implemented the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s (WHO) recommendations for Ebola virus disease (EVD) preparedness and is going even further. The ministry is prepared to adjust its measures as the situation changes.
One of the recommendations is to educate travelers about the potential dangers of EVD. The MOH is using various channels, such as its website and media releases, to inform the public and potential travelers about the disease.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone Offers Awareness In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The traditional office phone, once a large and stationary fixture on every desk, is becoming a relic of the past. Modern business communication has evolved into a dynamic and multifaceted process, incorporating instant messaging, online collaboration tools, file sharing, and web-based applications alongside traditional voice calls and conferencing. This evolution begs the question: are conventional PBX systems still equipped to handle the demands of today&amp;rsquo;s business environment?
As outdated phone systems increasingly hinder productivity, many companies are turning to cloud-based solutions for a more modern approach.</description></item></channel></rss>