<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kuwait on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kuwait/</link><description>Recent content in Kuwait on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:45:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kuwait/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kuwait is anticipated to experience slight growth in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-is-anticipated-to-experience-slight-growth-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-is-anticipated-to-experience-slight-growth-in-2015/</guid><description>Source: KFH Research website.
According to KFH Research, Kuwait&amp;rsquo;s economy is projected to experience stable growth in 2015. In their late December 2014 publication, &amp;ldquo;Kuwait Focus 2015: Positive Adjustments,&amp;rdquo; the firm predicts a 3.8% growth in real GDP for 2015, slightly lower than the estimated 4.1% for 2014.
This prediction aligns with the anticipated moderate GDP growth of 4.5% in the overall Gulf Cooperative Council region from 2014 to 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-is-anticipated-to-experience-slight-growth-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-is-anticipated-to-experience-slight-growth-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the Al Rabeh salary account by Kuwait Finance House</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced the Al-Rabeh account, a salary account that offers customers chances to win valuable prizes like Range Rovers and gold each quarter. Al-Rabeh is also designed as an investment savings account, providing customers with annual dividends.
This account caters to individuals who want to transfer their salaries and manage their personal finances while benefiting from savings and investment opportunities. The Al-Rabeh account is available in Kuwaiti Dinars (KD) and requires regular salary transfers to be eligible for prize draws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an abundance of travel rewards with the NBK Miles World Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</guid><description>Source: NBK. The NBK Miles World Mastercard.
People who travel frequently from Kuwait can accumulate points and enjoy airport lounge access with the NBK Miles World Mastercard.
These NBK Miles Points can be used to reserve flights from over 800 airlines, book accommodations at more than 150,000 hotels, and rent vehicles from well-known agencies worldwide. Cardholders can redeem their miles for any destination, airline, origin point, and time of year, without blackout dates or seat restrictions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>