<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Texting on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-texting/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Texting on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-texting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LG Xenon Exotic Messaging Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-xenon-exotic-messaging-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:11:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-xenon-exotic-messaging-phone/</guid><description>The LG Xenon gets its name from the element Xenon, which gives off a blue glow when electrically charged, just like the blue version of this phone. But the red one is named for being &amp;ldquo;red hot&amp;rdquo; - a nod to its impressive messaging features.
Messaging is the heart of the LG Xenon. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for those who love to text, featuring a full-length slide-out QWERTY keyboard for effortless typing. And when you&amp;rsquo;re not messaging, the Xenon easily transitions back to a sleek and pocket-friendly candybar-style phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-xenon-exotic-messaging-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-xenon-exotic-messaging-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ghost Routers In The Sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wireless internet access on airplanes is becoming a reality. Although it had a slow start, major airlines like American, Delta, Northwest, and Virgin are now embracing in-flight Wi-Fi.
This shift is inevitable in a society increasingly reliant on technology. We might be giving up old habits, but staying connected online is non-negotiable. Just like hotels and restaurants adapted to this need, airlines are following suit. Passengers are willing to endure cramped conditions and forgo traditional amenities, but internet access is a must-have...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>