<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Environmental on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environmental/</link><description>Recent content in Environmental on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environmental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses becomes a part of the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</guid><description>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is among the first to sign the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative. This initiative, spearheaded by the UN Environment Programme and UN World Tourism Organization with the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, aims to tackle plastic waste in the tourism sector.
By signing the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative, Six Senses reinforces its commitment to eliminate, innovate, and circulate its plastic use by 2025, aiming to be plastic-free as early as 2022.</description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>