<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hilton on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hilton/</link><description>Recent content in Hilton on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hilton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub.</description></item><item><title>Hilton guests will enjoy Live Nation experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and Live Nation, a live entertainment company, have launched a new five-year marketing partnership. This collaboration will provide unique experiences, including artist connections and concerts, to Hilton HHonors members, guests, and employees across Hilton&amp;rsquo;s global network of over 4,250 hotels.
Source: Hilton Worldwide. Hilton
aims to motivate a new,
healthier way of thinking - urging
individuals to embrace the unfamiliar,
gain perspective, and learn from daily
life and travel.</description></item><item><title>Would you like to try a mooncake with osmanthus and white lotus?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</guid><description>For the Mid-Autumn Festival, Hilton Hotel offers a variety of classic baked and contemporary mini snowskin mooncakes.
Baked mooncake choices include white lotus paste, traditional mixed nuts, green tea walnut, and a new osmanthus white lotus flavor. Caramel cheese, lychee chocolate truffle, D24 durian, and black sesame with hazelnut praline are among the snowskin varieties.
Interested?
For a closer look at the selection, view the Hilton mooncake collection brochure (PDF). Mooncakes are available from September 4th to October 4th, 2017.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request.</description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc.</description></item></channel></rss>