<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Philippines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/philippines/</link><description>Recent content in Philippines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/philippines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The MyNumber service from Hashtag assists businesses in reducing their hotline expenses in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>PLDT, through its corporate business group PLDT ALPHA Enterprise, has launched the PLDT #MyNumber service. This service streamlines a business&amp;rsquo;s hotline system into a memorable four to eight-digit contact number that starts with the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; symbol (for example, #8888). This single number can be reached by consumers nationwide using PLDT landlines, Smart, Talk N’ Text, and Sun mobile phones.
This service is designed for businesses that currently advertise different hotline numbers for different regions.</description></item><item><title>LBC 360 provides comprehensive business services in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 20:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: LBC YouTube channel.
In November 2014, LBC Express, the top cargo and logistics company in the Philippines, introduced a unique, fully integrated payment and logistics solution for the country. This platform, called LBC 360, aims to assist Filipino businesses of all types and sizes in overcoming supply chain obstacles.
“LBC 360 is intentionally crafted to be advantageous for all business models, from physical stores to online marketplaces,” explained Miguel Camahort, LBC President and Chief Operating Officer.</description></item><item><title>The IMF is analyzing the economy of the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) mission, headed by Chikahisa Sumi, has assessed the Philippine economy&amp;rsquo;s performance as positive but believes there&amp;rsquo;s room for improvement.
During their visit to Davao and Manila from June 28 to July 12, the mission engaged with various stakeholders, including the Governor of the Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP), economic ministers, high-ranking government representatives, private sector leaders, and financial experts. Sumi&amp;rsquo;s post-mission statement highlighted the following:</description></item><item><title>The Philippines' economic outlook has improved according to the World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</guid><description>The World Bank has improved its economic forecast for the Philippines from 2016 to 2018.
They now predict the Philippine economy will grow by 6.8% in 2016, up from their previous prediction of 6.4% made in October (World Bank Philippines Economic Update October 2016). This adjustment is based on stronger than expected growth in the third quarter of 2016, fueled by increased investment and private consumption. This follows robust economic performance in the first half of 2016, driven by the government’s pre-election spending.</description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms.</description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process.</description></item><item><title>FMCG brands are well-regarded in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. Brandindex 2016 rankings for the Philippines are heavy on toiletry brands.
The YouGov BrandIndex rankings from 2016 show that personal care products are very popular in the Philippines. The top 10 includes Colgate dental care, Cream Silk hair products, Dove soaps and hair care, Safeguard soaps and washes, and Olay skin care. Bench, primarily a clothing retailer, also has a presence with their bath and body products.</description></item><item><title>Three new routes have been announced by Air Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</guid><description>AirAsia is expanding its network in Indonesia and the Philippines with three new routes starting on March 27th. The airline will now offer flights from Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia to Pontianak, Indonesia, from Johor Bahru, Malaysia to Medan, Indonesia, and from Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia to Cebu, Philippines.
The Indonesian routes will operate twice a week, while the Kota Kinabalu to Cebu route, operated by AirAsia Zest, will operate four times a week.</description></item><item><title>Travel to Banwa Private Island with Ascent Flights Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</guid><description>Banwa Private Island, a secluded island in Northeast Palawan known for its pristine beaches, has joined forces with Ascent Flights Global to provide exclusive and secure travel options for its guests. This collaboration aims to create a protected travel environment through personalized on-demand flights using seaplanes, helicopters, or private jets based on individual preferences.
Source: Banwa Private Island. Banwa Private Island has partnered Ascent Flights Global to offer guests safe, private transport to their accommodation.</description></item><item><title>Discover Clark by participating in the CLARK BIKE TOUR this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</guid><description>Source: PDOT.
The Philippines Department of Tourism (PDOT), alongside the Clark Development Corporation, announced the upcoming CLARK BIKE TOUR happening in July. This bike tour aims to raise awareness about the significance of health and wellness as a way of life while promoting travel and tourism. It also seeks to highlight Clark as a bike-friendly area.
The event, scheduled for July 30 at the parade ground, anticipates around 400 road bikers, forming 100 teams of four members each, to engage in a non-competitive day-long tour of different attractions within the freeport zone.</description></item><item><title>AsiaKredit has introduced a consumer lending platform in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>AsiaKredit&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make financial services more accessible in the Philippines. They aim to achieve this by making credit easier to obtain and improving the approval rates for individuals with limited or no credit history.
Source: pera247 website. Screenshot of the pera247 app.
Pera247 is a completely digital platform offering short-term loans, up to 90 days, through a mobile wallet. These loans are typically small, unsecured, and target consumers with limited financial history.</description></item><item><title>The increasing involvement of women in commerce and industry in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) in the Philippines has reported a rise in the number of women participating in skills training programs for traditionally male-dominated fields.
Amelito Cardenas, a supervising specialist at TESDA Pangasinan, mentioned that more women are enrolling in technical-vocational (tech-voc) and private institutions to learn trades such as welding and automotive repair, as reported by the Philippines Information Agency.
Cardenas also shared that TESDA offers a free training program specifically for women who run sari-sari stores and carinderia.</description></item><item><title>This year in the Philippines, the focus is on mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</guid><description>In the Philippines, technology is synonymous with mobile technology.
According to Jubert Alberto, Research Manager at IDC Philippines, &amp;ldquo;The younger generation is entering the workforce, and they have a strong desire to be connected, informed, and entertained. They also tend to have fewer dependents. These factors indicate a growing demand for all things mobile, including devices, services, and applications.&amp;rdquo; IDC predicts that the Philippines will experience a 22% rise in smartphone spending and a 40% increase in tablet expenditure in 2014, fueled by a positive economic outlook.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring social media shows the sentiments towards Formula One in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>In July, Microsoft launched Microsoft Social Listening in eight Asia Pacific markets. This service is designed to help professionals in sales, marketing, and customer care understand and engage with customers on social media more effectively. Microsoft Social Listening provides tools for analyzing market intelligence from social conversations, including sentiment analysis across multiple platforms. It also allows users to monitor products, brands, competitors, and campaigns globally in real time to gain a comprehensive understanding of their customers and their business in the social media landscape.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is increasing the number of weekly flights between Abu Dhabi and Manila</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2016, Etihad Airways will increase its Abu Dhabi to Manila route from 14 to 17 roundtrip flights per week. This provides convenient connections from Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s hub to popular destinations for Philippine travelers, including Bahrain, Kuwait, Dammam, Doha, Jeddah, and Riyadh.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, highlighted the Abu Dhabi-Manila route&amp;rsquo;s high demand and limited capacity in recent years. The added flights will increase capacity by nearly 2,500 seats weekly, improving travel options between the UAE and the Philippines.</description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www.</description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right).</description></item><item><title>Global Payout expands MoneyTrac assistance to the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 12:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</guid><description>Global Payout, a company that offers business-to-business electronic payment solutions, has expanded its proprietary MoneyTrac consolidated payment gateway (CPG) platform to the Philippines.
MoneyTrac allows users to make secure payments to employees and business partners. Users can configure virtual accounts to meet specific payment needs, sending funds to bank accounts in supported countries, debit cards, credit cards, or even other users on the system.
Bill Rochfort, President and VP of Sales, highlighted the significant opportunity in providing financial services to the Philippines&amp;rsquo; large population, including millions of Filipinos working abroad (OFWs).</description></item><item><title>HOOQ is launching new original content produced by Globe Studios</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 10:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</guid><description>Globe Studios and HOOQ are launching the first episode of their original series, &amp;ldquo;OTJ: The Missing 8,&amp;rdquo; in early 2017. This series promises a cinematic experience that&amp;rsquo;s different from typical television, mirroring the gritty and fast-paced style of the original movie, which premiered at the 2013 Cannes Film Festival. This six-part series, based on Erik Matti&amp;rsquo;s award-winning film &amp;ldquo;OTJ&amp;rdquo; (or &amp;ldquo;On The Job&amp;rdquo;), is the first major production made specifically for an online video service in the region.</description></item></channel></rss>