<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shopping on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shopping/</link><description>Recent content in Shopping on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shopping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ICSC's Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards honor D-Cube City, Jem, and Siam Center with gold awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</guid><description>The International Council of Shopping Centers (ICSC) Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards recently celebrated excellence in the region&amp;rsquo;s shopping center industry. Awards recognized outstanding achievements in marketing, retail property design and development, and retail store design.
The Design &amp;amp; Development category acknowledges retail properties for their overall design quality and development creativity, whether through renovation or expansion of an existing property or the innovative design of a new retail project. This category includes both new developments and renovations &amp;amp; expansions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Checkpoint Systems in Hong Kong is dedicated to preventing shoplifting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</guid><description>Checkpoint Systems, a leading provider of retail merchandise availability solutions, has introduced innovative loss prevention and RFID solutions tailored for Hong Kong retailers. These solutions aim to safeguard valuable merchandise from loss and theft across the entire supply chain, from the manufacturer to the store shelf.
Checkpoint&amp;rsquo;s enhanced Merchandise Visibility Solution utilizes cutting-edge labeling and RFID technology, allowing manufacturers to apply RFID tags cost-effectively at the point of manufacture. These tags enable real-time tracking and location identification of individual products throughout the supply chain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is launching the 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day in September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</guid><description>Source: Shopee website. The countdown begins 1 September.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace owned by Garena Interactive Holding, is launching its first-ever 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day. This one-day event will take place on September 9th and offer shoppers a mobile shopping experience.
The event is anticipated to be the largest mobile shopping sale in the region. Shoppers in Singapore can expect 24 hours of continuous deals and promotions. These include discounts of up to 90%, a selection of items under S$0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online retailing is becoming increasingly popular for smartphones in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</guid><description>Want to expand your customer base? Consider partnering with an e-mall, especially in China. A recent IDC Mobile Phone Tracker report indicates a rise in the share of e-tailers, like JD, Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Tmall, and Suning Yigou, in China&amp;rsquo;s smartphone market, from 14% in Q2 2014 to 21% in Q2 2015. This translates to a 58% year-on-year surge in the number of smartphones sold via these online platforms.
Tay Xiaohan, a Senior Market Analyst at IDC Asia/Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Client Devices team, highlights that as operators scale back smartphone subsidies, vendors find more opportunities in the open market, with e-tailers emerging as a crucial channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Free Phones Online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-free-phones-online/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 01:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-free-phones-online/</guid><description>After a couple of years, your old phone probably looks outdated. Its functionality likely pales compared to the latest models, even if you&amp;rsquo;ve kept it in pristine condition. While you might be dreaming of upgrading, don&amp;rsquo;t assume those high-tech phones are out of your price range. You can get amazing deals, even free phones, from resources like Cell Phone Plan Finder.
A quick glance at the deals available through Cell Phone Plan Finder reveals a surprising number of top-tier phones are available for free with a new service plan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-free-phones-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-free-phones-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are seeking additional retail technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 09:25:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</guid><description>Source: Zebra infographic. Almost two-thirds of shoppers surveyed in Europe and the Middle East stated that customer service directly impacts their purchasing decisions. Meanwhile, nearly a third of Asia Pacific respondents prefer collecting online purchases from a physical store.
Consumers are setting higher expectations for their shopping experience, while retailers lag in matching these expectations with their in-store technology investments. Retail customers desire a wide array of options for receiving their purchases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe: Consumer sentiment in the Asia-Pacific region remains positive in the middle of 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</guid><description>Even though many COVID-19 lockdown restrictions have been lifted globally, research from Adobe, presented at their Adobe Experience Makers Live event, reveals that the extended home confinement has significantly altered consumer shopping habits and brand interactions.
The research highlights how COVID-19 has impacted daily life, with nearly seven in ten consumers (67%) concerned about the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s overall impact, particularly regarding personal health (73%), job security (40%), and the economy (36%). Millennials (72%) expressed higher concern levels compared to Gen Z (58%), Boomers (62%), and Traditionalists (48%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bricks and Mortar Apocolypse, Now?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</guid><description>The physical world is struggling while the virtual world thrives. We may be approaching a point where the internet becomes dominant, and traditional businesses may suffer for unexpected reasons.
Retail has been declining, but recently, there&amp;rsquo;s been a sharp downturn due to rising gas prices. This discourages driving, which leads to less shopping. Shopping is crucial for the economy; a decline in shopping could lead to an economic depression.
Our society relies heavily on driving...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Research Your Cell Phone Online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/research-your-cell-phone-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/research-your-cell-phone-online/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about your cell phone options when your contract expires. Instead of just visiting electronics stores or carrier outlets, try exploring your choices online.
Online research offers convenience and a pressure-free environment. You can browse at your own pace without feeling pressured by salespeople.
More importantly, you&amp;rsquo;ll find significant price savings online due to lower overhead costs. You can get the same service plans online as you would in a store, often at reduced prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/research-your-cell-phone-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/research-your-cell-phone-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Shizuoka guide provides exclusive tips for exploring the city</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 09:27:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</guid><description>Source: Shizuoka City Tourism &amp;amp; City Relations Division.
The Shizuoka City Tourism &amp;amp; City Relations Division in Japan has created the &amp;ldquo;SHIZUOKA GUIDE,&amp;rdquo; a 52-page guidebook containing coupons. The guide helps inbound tourists enjoy local food and shopping at affordable prices.
Information was collected from locals who typically share recommendations through word-of-mouth. The guide features:
Lists of popular restaurants ranked by popularity. Locations offering local products like green tea and Mount Fuji souvenirs at reasonable prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australian consumers are pleased to use contactless cards for payment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard survey highlights the increasing popularity of digital payment methods among Australians. Over 80% of Australians use contactless payments, also known as &amp;ldquo;tap and go,&amp;rdquo; weekly. This preference is so strong that a significant number of consumers get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer this option, with some even choosing to shop elsewhere.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and petrol stations are the most common places where Australians use contactless cards. Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, Garry Duursma, emphasizes that Australians view tap and go as a faster and more convenient payment method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For Free Phone Aficionados Only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</guid><description>Looking for a free cell phone? Look no further than Cell Phone Plan Finder&amp;rsquo;s free phones section. This site is completely dedicated to showcasing free phones available when you sign up for a service contract.
This screenshot only displays a limited selection. As of today, there are 23 free phone models from leading carriers such as Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, AT&amp;amp;T, and Sprint.
The selection includes various BlackBerry models like the Bold, Curve, Storm, and Tour...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shoppers are interested in clothes, cosmetics, and baby products on 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 22:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</guid><description>Source: Alizila blog. The 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival logo is illuminated in neon.
Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival is surpassing the sales of the previous year. Alizila reports show that it took a mere 1 minute and 25 seconds for the festival to reach over US$1 billion in total gross merchandise volume (GMV).
By 1:15 p.m., Tmall Global had already exceeded its total GMV from the entire 2017 11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>