<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MOOC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mooc/</link><description>Recent content in MOOC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mooc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hasso Plattner Institute is offering a free six-week MOOC on the Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</guid><description>The Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) is offering a free, six-week online course in English about the fundamentals of the Internet. Starting on March 31st, HPI&amp;rsquo;s director, Professor Christoph Meinel, will teach participants about the technical basis of the Internet through a massive open online course (MOOC) titled &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Internetworking with TCP/IP.&amp;rdquo; The course is available to anyone and can be accessed through free registration.
Professor Meinel believes that anyone who uses the Internet for daily tasks like online shopping, reading news articles, or sending emails should understand the technologies that make these actions possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACCA is sponsoring a MOOC on FutureLearn that grants learners an exemption from the F1 paper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) is breaking new ground as the first professional accountancy body to use massive open online courses (MOOCs) for professional recognition. They are partnering with FutureLearn, a UK-based social learning platform, to offer free online courses in accounting, finance, and business.
This partnership aims to reach a global audience, providing valuable supplementary knowledge for professionals and introducing career paths to those new to the field...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>