<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Delivery on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/delivery/</link><description>Recent content in Delivery on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/delivery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tips from Akamai for optimizing app engagement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</guid><description>A report from Akamai highlights that 95% of gamers quit playing a game within the first month. The company states that slow loading times are a major factor, causing 40% of players to abandon games. Additionally, 20% of gamers expect instant page loads.
To enhance user retention, Akamai suggests strategies applicable to any app:
Anticipate Large-Scale Success: Be prepared for a global player base. Utilize a robust content delivery network to handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout.</description></item><item><title>Zap Delivery in Singapore guarantees fast and reliable couriered deliveries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</guid><description>Source: Zap Delivery.
Zap Delivery, an on-demand courier service, promises quick, safe, and dependable deliveries of packages and documents within Singapore in two hours or less using their new mobile app. This app utilizes advanced authentication and real-time tracking to provide peace of mind for those awaiting deliveries.
“We’ve experienced our fair share of delivery issues, so we created a user-friendly app that fosters trust,&amp;quot; explained Michael Tan, Zap Delivery Co-founder and CEO.</description></item><item><title>Foodpanda has introduced a high-end delivery service in the Central Business District of Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</guid><description>Source: foodpanda website.
In celebration of its third anniversary in Singapore, foodpanda Singapore has introduced a premium delivery service. This service includes approximately 50 restaurants and covers the central business district. It aims to serve busy professionals who want diverse food choices delivered directly to their workplaces.
Launched a month after securing US$110 million in funding, this new service reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing user experience and customer service.</description></item><item><title>Singpost will collaborate with Shippit on final delivery services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</guid><description>Shippit has partnered with Singapore Post (SingPost) to offer their delivery services and special negotiated rates on its platform. This collaboration allows small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to deliver parcels throughout Singapore.
This partnership provides SMEs on Shippit&amp;rsquo;s platform with more e-commerce fulfillment options. They can now offer customers island-wide parcel collection through SingPost&amp;rsquo;s POPStation network. Additionally, Shippit will provide access to SingPost&amp;rsquo;s Speedpost Express Service and discounted, pre-negotiated rates for next-day and economy deliveries—services previously exclusive to larger companies.</description></item><item><title>SingEx has introduced Last Mile Fulfilment Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 06:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</guid><description>Last Mile Fulfilment Asia (LMFAsia), a debut trade show and conference centered around last-mile fulfillment in logistics and e-commerce, will premiere in Singapore next year.
This is the first event of its kind to hone in on last-mile fulfillment challenges and prospects in Asia. SingEx anticipates the event will attract around 1,500 attendees, representatives, and exhibitors from the Asian region in its first year. LMFAsia aims to unite four crucial sectors – e-commerce, retail, logistics, and parcel delivery – under one roof to maximize business opportunities for e-commerce in Asia.</description></item></channel></rss>