<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Connections on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:35:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Reviving The Local Loop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</guid><description>Local loop usage has decreased as people switch from traditional phone lines to wireless or internet-based phone services. This has prompted some to suggest that these copper lines be completely removed. However, just as this idea emerges, new technology is giving these old lines a new purpose.
Fiber optic connections may be the future, but they’re not widely available yet. Only a small percentage of businesses currently have fiber, due to lack of demand, high installation costs, or limited infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits Of An MPLS Mesh Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</guid><description>When your company grows to have multiple locations like branches, data centers, or factories, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a way to connect them all on the same network. The best way to do this is with an MPLS Mesh Network.
Smaller companies with only two locations usually start by connecting the locations with a point-to-point T1 or Ethernet line. While this works, using an MPLS network might be more cost-effective depending on the distance between locations and the availability of T1 or Ethernet services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>