<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>APJ on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apj/</link><description>Recent content in APJ on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apj/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technology usage in 2015 could be vastly different</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</guid><description>Source: Intel infographic. Learn more here.
Our current world relies on multiple connected devices, and this trend will only intensify. Intel believes that while we currently utilize various devices like wearables, smartphones, tablets, and PCs, the future holds even more significant changes.
Hermann Eul, VP and GM, Mobile and Communications Group at Intel, points out that users constantly demand better device performance. He highlights that in 2015, devices will need to meet the need for improved imaging, extended battery life without sacrificing performance, integrated experiences, and enhanced responsiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>