<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Voice on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voice/</link><description>Recent content in Voice on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Router Included With Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</guid><description>Considering upgrading your voice or data bandwidth? DS3 service offers 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads, suitable for demanding tasks like video transfer, medical imaging, or call centers. But finding the right DS3 router for your network can feel like an added burden.
Rest assured, DS3 is a well-established technology with readily available equipment and decreasing prices. As more companies switch from T1 lines to DS3 bandwidth, implementation is becoming increasingly straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE now offers conference call support for groups of up to 200 people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</guid><description>Source: LINE. Screenshots of the new voice call feature.
LINE has introduced a new feature for group calls in its latest update (iPhone and Android v.5.11, Windows Desktop v.4.5). This update allows up to 200 users to participate in a single voice call. The group voice call function will soon be available for LINE&amp;rsquo;s Mac desktop client, too.
When someone starts a group call, members in the group chat are notified and can choose to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The speech recognition app can transcribe discussions involving several individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 11:46:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</guid><description>Source: NVIDIA blog post. The Otter team at AISense.
AISense, a company based in the US, has introduced Otter, an application that uses GPU technology to record and transcribe speech from multiple speakers. Unlike most currently available software that needs to be trained on a single voice, Otter can accurately recognize and differentiate between various speakers.
Sam Liang, AISense co-founder and CEO, highlights in a blog post that capturing human-to-human interactions is significantly more challenging than interactions like those with virtual assistants like Alexa, Siri, or Google Assistant...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces two phablets in the Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 05:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new mobile devices to their collection: the 6-inch HP Slate6 VoiceTab and the 7-inch HP Slate7 VoiceTab. These &amp;ldquo;voice tablets&amp;rdquo; will be released in India this February*.
These devices combine the functions of a phone and a tablet into one portable design. “The voice tablet market is growing because consumers want to combine their phones and tablets into one device,” said Ron Coughlin, Senior VP of HP&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Personal Systems Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you ask LG ThinQ AI TVs, Google Assistant will respond</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</guid><description>LG Electronics has integrated the recently launched Google Assistant into their OLED and SUPER UHD TVs.
This feature, available on all LG ThinQ AI TV models, enables users to search for information, check weather forecasts, and more using voice commands, all without interrupting their TV viewing.
Previously, voice commands were limited to basic functions like changing channels or adjusting volume. Now, users can search for specific content using the TV remote, for example, &amp;ldquo;show me romantic comedy movies on Netflix&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;show me yoga videos&amp;rdquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides triple the mobile data for a low price, along with Wi-Fi calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</guid><description>Singtel launched a new mobile data add-on called DataX3 at their iPhone 7 event held at Marina Bay Sands Convention Centre. For S$9.90 per month, DataX3 allows customers to triple their mobile data limit. This add-on is available to Singtel Combo Plan customers (Combo 2 and above). It follows the successful launch of the DataX2 add-on earlier this year.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, highlighted the importance of affordable mobile data for communication, shopping, banking, and entertainment in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>