<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Avaya on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/avaya/</link><description>Recent content in Avaya on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/avaya/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>