<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Justice and Home Affairs on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/justice-and-home-affairs/</link><description>Recent content in Justice and Home Affairs on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/justice-and-home-affairs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Details of the upcoming referendum on Denmark's participation in EU Justice and Home Affairs Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Denmark&amp;rsquo;s involvement in international criminal law, exemplified by the TV show &amp;ldquo;The Bridge,&amp;rdquo; is facing uncertainty due to changing EU regulations. This situation will soon lead Denmark to vote on modifying its current near-total opt-out of EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) laws. While the general implications have been discussed, the specifics of this vote are now clearer.
To recap, Denmark negotiated opt-outs from the euro, defense, and parts of JHA law in 1992...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Inquiries for potential Commissioners of Home Affairs and Justice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 01:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Emilio de Capitani, and Henri Labayle present a series of questions for Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to pose to the candidates for Commissioners of Immigration and Home Affairs and Justice. These questions aim to understand the candidates&amp;rsquo; plans and secure commitments on crucial matters.
Immigration and Asylum
Given the Commission&amp;rsquo;s stance on framing migration policy with the non-binding Global Approach to Migration and Mobility Partnerships, would the candidate propose a legally binding basis for agreements with relevant nations, based on Articles 77, 78, and 79 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>