<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Carriers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-carriers/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Carriers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-carriers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services For The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</guid><description>Initially only utilized by telecom companies, wavelength services are now accessible to large organizations. These high-bandwidth fiber optic services are necessary for entities like hospitals, financial institutions, government service providers, video production companies, content delivery networks, and research facilities. The demand for faster data transfer solutions is constantly increasing. But are wavelength services the answer?
A wavelength, or lambda, is light at a specific frequency, similar to a distinct color. It is usually measured in nanometers (wavelength) rather than terabits per second (frequency)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>