<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asia Plantation Capital on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asia-plantation-capital/</link><description>Recent content in Asia Plantation Capital on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asia-plantation-capital/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fragrance Du Bois opens a temporary store at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Fragrance Du Bois.
Fragrance Du Bois has opened a temporary boutique at TANGS, a major department store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road shopping area, until September 4, 2015. This marks their second appearance at TANGS this year. The pop-up offers customers a direct encounter with niche perfumery and showcases Fragrance Du Bois&amp;rsquo; fragrances, all made with 100% pure, natural oud.
Nicola Parker, Brand Director of Fragrance Du Bois, noted a rising interest in niche perfumery.</description></item><item><title>Asia Plantation Capital is researching the advantages of agarwood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-plantation-capital-is-researching-the-advantages-of-agarwood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:27:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-plantation-capital-is-researching-the-advantages-of-agarwood/</guid><description>Source:
Asia Plantation Capital
website.
Asia Plantation Capital (APC) has initiated a new investment program to collaborate with Southeast Asian academics in studying the science of agarwood, a valuable substance derived from infected Aquilaria trees and known by various names like gaharu, jinkoh, aloeswood, and oud. The program aims to pinpoint areas for in-depth research and potential clinical trials to gain approval from European and American medical authorities.
In Thailand, APC&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Prince Songkhla University, led by Prof.</description></item></channel></rss>