<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wdm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wdm/</link><description>Recent content in Wdm on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wdm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers.</description></item><item><title>Many Wavelengths to Serve You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</guid><description>When your network reaches its maximum capacity, you typically need to upgrade to a faster network with faster components. Upgrading your entire network infrastructure can be extremely expensive. However, with fiber optic networks, you can significantly increase bandwidth within the same cables using a technique called Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM).
WDM allows multiple light beams to transmit data simultaneously over a single fiber optic cable. Each beam operates on a different wavelength, increasing capacity proportionally to the number of beams.</description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services For The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</guid><description>Initially only utilized by telecom companies, wavelength services are now accessible to large organizations. These high-bandwidth fiber optic services are necessary for entities like hospitals, financial institutions, government service providers, video production companies, content delivery networks, and research facilities. The demand for faster data transfer solutions is constantly increasing. But are wavelength services the answer?
A wavelength, or lambda, is light at a specific frequency, similar to a distinct color. It is usually measured in nanometers (wavelength) rather than terabits per second (frequency).</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward.</description></item></channel></rss>