<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bg4002/</link><description>Recent content in BG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacement of Rusty RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 14:56:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration, I swapped out the old, worn-out RCA plugs. The originals were showing their age.
I chose robust, gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs as replacements. These are excellent for transmitting the low-voltage MMC signal to the amplifier. The metal housing provides superior shielding against electromagnetic interference, ensuring signal integrity. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look after soldering:
And here they are secured:</description></item></channel></rss>