<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lenovo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lenovo/</link><description>Recent content in Lenovo on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lenovo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lenovo issues global recall for Thinkpad batteries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</guid><description>Lenovo has expanded a battery recall that was first announced on March 27, 2014. This recall now includes all affected lithium-ion batteries globally. The batteries, as announced in late April 2015, were manufactured for ThinkPad notebook computers shipped between February 2010 and June 2012.
Lenovo stated that they are offering free-of-charge replacement batteries for all recalled batteries in the interest of public safety.
The batteries were sold with new notebook computers or as optional or replacement batteries for the following models:</description></item><item><title>Understand your social media presence with Socialbakers' Social Health Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</guid><description>Socialbakers, a company specializing in social media analytics and optimization, has launched its Social Health Index, a tool created in collaboration with Lenovo. This industry benchmark offers brands a single metric to assess their social marketing performance across multiple platforms. It allows them to effortlessly measure their overall social media presence and compare it to their competitors over a period of time.
Jan Rezab, CEO and Co-Founder of Socialbakers, stated that the Social Health Index is the first benchmark of its kind, providing context to brands&amp;rsquo; social marketing efforts.</description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing.</description></item><item><title>Lenovo introduces new Tiny all-in-one workstations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 18:49:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</guid><description>Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s new TiO features a compact desktop computer (shown on the left) that connects to the back of a 23-inch monitor (on the right). These components can function independently or as a combined unit.
Lenovo introduced workstations and a &amp;lsquo;Tiny-in-one&amp;rsquo; (TiO) as part of its final significant product launch in 2014.
Pictured on the left are Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s latest workstation models.
&amp;ldquo;We carefully considered extensive customer feedback after the recent debut of our P300 workstation,&amp;rdquo; stated Jessie Quek, Lenovo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Country General Manager.</description></item><item><title>Lenovo introduces the ThinkStation P series of desktop workstations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 15:41:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</guid><description>Lenovo has introduced the ThinkStation P Series, a new line of desktop workstations. The P900, P700, and P500 models join the entry-level P300, which was launched in May 2014, to form Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s most potent professional-grade desktop workstations.
Rob Herman, Director of Worldwide Workstation Product and Vertical Marketing at Lenovo, stated that the company listened to customer feedback regarding the need for faster, more dependable, and user-friendly workstations, and the ThinkStation P Series is their response.</description></item></channel></rss>