<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sweets on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sweets/</link><description>Recent content in Sweets on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 02:28:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sweets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In India, Swarn Amrit produces sweets made with edible gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 02:28:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</guid><description>Swarn Amrit, a high-end confectionery brand, has introduced a first-of-its-kind product line in India: sweets made with real 24-karat gold. The company believes that gold symbolizes purity, prosperity, and good fortune, and even suggests it may promote longevity.
Swarn Kalash
The new collection features a variety of sweets with names like kalash, mukhi, madhu, yukti, and katak, representing both Indian and international flavors. For example, Swarn Mukhi layers cashews, almonds, pistachios, and gold, while Swarn Madhu combines Belgian chocolate with gold, and Swarn Katak adds a touch of gold to Turkish delight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Haldiram's is promoting mithai in India that is free from adulteration at SwaadMarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 04:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</guid><description>Source: SwaadMarket.com website.
Haldiram&amp;rsquo;s, a leading brand in the Indian sweets market, is now available on SwaadMarket.com. SwaadMarket is an Indian online marketplace that guarantees authentic, hygienic, and pure sweets and other food products. Giving Indian sweets (mithai) as gifts is a long-standing tradition, but recently the mithai market has declined due to a lack of new ideas and concerns about hygiene and purity. This trend inspired both companies to start promoting unadulterated sweets within India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>