<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Italy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/italy/</link><description>Recent content in Italy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/italy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>As the lawyers entered the bar, the Court of Justice made it easier for legal professionals to practice across borders.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Julian Lonbay, Senior Lecturer,
Postgraduate Research Admissions Tutor, Birmingham Law School, University
of Birmingham
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice judgment in the Joined Cases C-58/13 and C-59/13 Angelo Alberto Torresi and Pierfrancesco Torresi v Consiglio dell&amp;rsquo;Ordine degli Avvocati di Macerata considered whether EU law permits citizens to pursue the fastest route to professional qualification, even if it bypasses significant portions of training mandated by national law for entry into the corresponding national profession.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Court of Justice reconsidering the European equivalent of the 'fifth amendment'? The CJEU makes a decision on the right to remain silent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</guid><description>Inês Pereira de Sousa, Lecturer and PhD candidate at Porto Faculty of Law, Universidade Católica Portuguesa; Researcher at CEID – Católica Research Centre for the Future of Law; Member of ANESC – Academic Network on the European Social Charter and Social Rights; Member of EUCRIM –European Criminal Law Associations’ Forum - isousa@porto.ucp.pt
On February 2, 2021, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) had the chance to reexamine the right to remain silent and the right against self-incrimination in a case originating from the Italian Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero.</description></item><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015.</description></item><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit.</description></item><item><title>Contrasting torture and other forms of ill-treatment: Cestaro v. Italy and the necessity of a "prohibited purpose" condition.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contrasting-torture-and-other-forms-of-ill-treatment-cestaro-v-italy-and-the-necessity-of-a-prohibited-purpose-condition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 06:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contrasting-torture-and-other-forms-of-ill-treatment-cestaro-v-italy-and-the-necessity-of-a-prohibited-purpose-condition/</guid><description>Christina Kosin (LL.M. Edinburgh), Ph.D. candidate and academic assistant at the German Police University, argues that the &amp;ldquo;prohibited purpose&amp;rdquo; requirement, while crucial, is not the only factor differentiating torture from inhuman or degrading treatment. The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo;s (ECtHR) judgment in Cestaro v. Italy illustrates this point.
The Judgment
Mr. Cestaro, a peaceful protester at the 2001 G-8 summit in Genoa, Italy, was subjected to severe beatings by Italian police while staying at a school being searched for radical protesters.</description></item><item><title>Italian Court of Cassation: Vos Thalassa ruling clears migrants who opposed being sent back to Libya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/italian-court-of-cassation-vos-thalassa-ruling-clears-migrants-who-opposed-being-sent-back-to-libya/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/italian-court-of-cassation-vos-thalassa-ruling-clears-migrants-who-opposed-being-sent-back-to-libya/</guid><description>Yasha Maccanico, Statewatch
Photo credit: Sergio D&amp;rsquo;Afflitto, via Wikimedia commons In December 2021, Italy&amp;rsquo;s highest court overturned the convictions and prison sentences of two men who were found guilty of leading a protest on a rescue ship. The men, from Ghana and Sudan, were part of a group of 67 migrants rescued from a distressed boat in the Libyan Search and Rescue zone in July 2018. Initially, the rescue ship was instructed to take the migrants to Italy, but later received orders to return them to Libya.</description></item><item><title>A duo from Singapore and Italy have introduced Oro D’ Italia at the Singapore Jewellery and Gem Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-duo-from-singapore-and-italy-have-introduced-oro-d-italia-at-the-singapore-jewellery-and-gem-fair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 10:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-duo-from-singapore-and-italy-have-introduced-oro-d-italia-at-the-singapore-jewellery-and-gem-fair/</guid><description>Source: UBM Asia, the organizers of SJGF 2016. From left: Cascapera and Lim.
Oro D’ Italia (Oro Di Italia), a purveyor of 100% Italian handmade fine jewelry, has premiered at the fourth Singapore Jewellery and Gem Fair (SJGF 2016) at Marina Bay Sands.
The platform is the creation of Rosalind Lim, a Singaporean, and Fabio Cascapera, an Italian. Lim possesses over three decades of experience in fine jewelry and has collaborated closely with affluent individuals and buyers.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts.</description></item><item><title>A group of business representatives travels to Singapore to showcase the "Made In Italy" brand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-group-of-business-representatives-travels-to-singapore-to-showcase-the-made-in-italy-brand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 16:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-group-of-business-representatives-travels-to-singapore-to-showcase-the-made-in-italy-brand/</guid><description>Leading Italian industry groups have revealed their collaborative strategy with local organizations for an upcoming visit to Singapore to champion the &amp;ldquo;Made in Italy&amp;rdquo; brand. They emphasized Italy&amp;rsquo;s top-tier capabilities, aligning perfectly with the needs of a rapidly developing ASEAN region, and highlighted how ASEAN can utilize this success to accelerate its own progress.
The year 2018 marks two decades of formal economic collaboration and trade between Singapore and Italy. Recognizing innovation as a key driver of economic and societal transformation, both nations agreed to strengthen their long-term cooperation across diverse sectors, ranging from fashion and healthcare to furniture and technology.</description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU Grand Chamber "Ilva" judgment: Balancing environmental law and human rights from a Kirchberg perspective.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</guid><description>Jacques Bellezit, University of Strasbourg (France)
Photo credit: mafe de baggis, via Wikimedia Commons
To understand the historical development of European construction, one must acknowledge the European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC). Established following the Schumann Declaration on May 9th, 1950, the ECSC marked the first attempt to create a common market for coal and steel, deemed strategic materials. This initiative aimed to not only bolster post-war reconstruction in Europe but also to curb rearmament efforts on both sides of the Rhine during the nascent Cold War.</description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU judgment in NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford has erased the blurry line between employment discrimination and the right to freedom of expression.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Ph.D. Researcher in International Studies at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case C‑507/18, NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford, centers around the balance between freedom of expression and the harmful impact of discriminatory language. Advocate General Eleanor Sharpston aptly used bird metaphors in her opinion, likening discriminatory statements to volatile birds that can quickly spread their harmful effects.</description></item></channel></rss>