<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>104EMBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/104embg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 104EMBG4002 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/104embg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</guid><description>I am currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) and focused on refurbishing its dust cover. As you can see in the first image, the cover had multiple scratches and abrasions common for its age.
My first step was to sand the cover using 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the imperfections.
Following this, I used a Micro-Mesh polishing cloth to restore the cover&amp;rsquo;s clarity. The final result is a clear and revitalized dust cover...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of a New All-Metal DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Contacts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</guid><description>I believe that any restoration of a Beogram 4002 isn&amp;rsquo;t truly finished until the old output plugs, which are often corroded, are replaced with modern, all-metal ones featuring gold-plated terminals. High-quality analog signals deserve the best possible connections. Here are some photos documenting the DIN5 plug replacement I completed on a Beogram 4002 (5503) restoration:
The original DIN5 plug is shown here:
This photo shows the &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; soldering work:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Keyboard Repair - Detached Backstops</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 11:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</guid><description>Following the AC motor hood restoration on a Beogram 4002 (5503), the next cosmetic issue addressed was the loose keypad backstops. Some keys were protruding and functioned erratically, requiring multiple presses.
Upon removing the keypad and its PCB, it was discovered that several plastic backstops had detached. A previous attempt to reattach them using double-sided tape proved unsuccessful, causing an uneven keypad surface.
The remaining backstops were easily removed, but precisely reattaching them posed a challenge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter and Tonearm Weight and Limits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</guid><description>The final stage of restoring the Beogram 4002 (5503) involved balancing the sub-chassis, setting the correct platter height, and adjusting the tonearm. To ensure the best range of motion, the sub-chassis must be carefully positioned between the transport lock clamps. The platter height and vertical alignment need to be set so that the platter sits level with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s aluminum covers. This allows for the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit to be established and the tracking weight to be calibrated against the adjustment dial located on the arm weight housing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Exchanging all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>After finishing most of the mechanical work, it was time to start repairing the electronics on a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable. Replacing all electrolytic capacitors is recommended, as their internal fluid often leaks or dries up. I use high-quality Japanese capacitors to ensure my repairs last as long as possible. Tantalum capacitors, in particular, must be replaced because they can fail dramatically if a short circuit occurs, potentially damaging the circuit board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (5503) for restoration. The 5503 is the North American version of the 5501/5502 models, evident in the non-functional voltage switch included to maintain a consistent appearance.
This Beogram is in excellent overall condition, featuring high-quality veneer on the plinth and a dust cover with typical scratches that can be polished to near-original clarity. Internally, it appears largely untouched, though there are indications of prior work, such as loose bolts in the tracking and tonearm mechanisms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>