<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtualized Servers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtualized-servers/</link><description>Recent content in Virtualized Servers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtualized-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market.</description></item><item><title>From CAPEX to OPEX In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The cost model for Information Technology is shifting from capital expenditure (CAPEX) to operational expenditure (OPEX) due to economic uncertainty and the rise of cloud computing.
Traditionally, businesses invested heavily in on-site data centers with servers, storage, and network equipment. This approach, while effective, requires substantial upfront capital and incurs ongoing operational costs like electricity, bandwidth, staffing, and software maintenance.
While this capital-intensive model was the norm, the economic downturn made businesses more cost-conscious.</description></item></channel></rss>