<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gender Violence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gender-violence/</link><description>Recent content in Gender Violence on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gender-violence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analyzing Complex Legal Issues from a Legal Standpoint with Partiality and Passion, or The European Union's Approval of the Istanbul Convention: Jurisdiction, Foundations, and Consensus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - @CateBriddick*
On March 11, 2021, Advocate General Hogan of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) presented his legal opinion on the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s inquiry regarding the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) potential membership in the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Istanbul Convention).</description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries.</description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013.</description></item><item><title>The EU's groundbreaking Directive 2024/1385 on Violence Against Women is a significant step forward in promoting gender equality.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</guid><description>Dr. Ceren Kasım, Postdoctoral Research and Teaching Fellow, University of Hildesheim, Germany
Photo credit: MesserWoland, via Wikimedia Commons
INTRODUCTION
May 14, 2024, marked a pivotal moment for the European Union (EU) as it unveiled its first legally binding instrument to combat violence against women and domestic violence. This Directive, officially known as Directive 2024/1385, signifies the EU&amp;rsquo;s strong commitment to achieving genuine equality for women.
Gender-based violence is a pervasive issue across the EU.</description></item><item><title>Disappointing ruling by the CJEU on reverse discrimination against rape victims</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 20:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</guid><description>Steve Peers
National criminal justice systems are frequently criticized for overlooking the needs of crime victims. In contrast, the EU has been attentive to this matter since the initial stages of EU criminal law development. Early on, one of the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Framework Decisions&amp;rsquo; addressed victims&amp;rsquo; rights. This measure has since been superseded by a comprehensive Directive on this subject, which Member States are required to implement by October 2015.</description></item></channel></rss>