<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Caution: Superman is poisonous</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</guid><description>According to a McAfee blog post, Superman poses a significant online threat. The company argues that the widespread presence of superheroes beyond comic books allows hackers and scammers to exploit them for cybercrime.
McAfee&amp;rsquo;s survey, which used their SiteAdvisor site ratings, revealed that Superman is the &amp;ldquo;Most Toxic Superhero.&amp;rdquo; The study found that searches combining &amp;ldquo;Superman&amp;rdquo; with terms like &amp;ldquo;free torrent download,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;watch,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;free app,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; have a 16.5% chance of leading to websites containing threats like spyware, adware, spam, phishing, viruses, and other malware.</description></item><item><title>Numerous White Papers Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through a phase where white papers feel incredibly relevant to challenges we face internally and with clients. I wanted to share some of my top picks:
Microsoft Dynamics GP and SQL Server 2008
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false This paper offers valuable insights into leveraging SQL Server 2008 compression, including performance benchmarks.
Choosing a Development Tool for Microsoft Dynamics GP 10
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false A must-read for developers and consultants, this paper provides a comprehensive overview of development tools, licensing costs, required skillsets, and tool capabilities.</description></item><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints.</description></item><item><title>Acronis has launched Blockchain-supported data protection through Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-launched-blockchain-supported-data-protection-through-acronis-true-image-2017-new-generation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-launched-blockchain-supported-data-protection-through-acronis-true-image-2017-new-generation/</guid><description>Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation offers four key advantages: comprehensive backup, Blockchain-based authentication to ensure data integrity, protection against ransomware, and secure e-signatures.
Acronis, a global provider of hybrid-cloud data protection and storage solutions, has introduced Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation. This release builds upon the existing backup features of Acronis True Image with three significant additions:
Acronis Active Protection safeguards user data against ransomware attacks in real time.</description></item><item><title>Should Brazil be considered a cyber security threat?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 04:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</guid><description>Cybercriminals frequently target major events like the Olympics to spread malware, and the 2016 Rio Games were no exception. While it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to stay vigilant against phishing attempts that exploit current events, a report from Fortinet, &amp;ldquo;FortiGuard Eye of the Storm,&amp;rdquo; highlights why the 2016 Olympics warranted particular concern.
Although cyberattacks at the Olympics are not a recent phenomenon, with incidents dating back to the 2004 Athens Games, Fortinet raised concerns about the Rio Games for two key reasons that could impact attendees and have a ripple effect on those back home:</description></item><item><title>Be cautious of insiders when it comes to protecting data privacy: Infowatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</guid><description>The most significant danger to data privacy in Southeast Asia comes from internal actors. Cybersecurity firm InfoWatch Group&amp;rsquo;s recent study reveals that careless top executives and employees with access to sensitive data are the primary cause of data leaks in ASEAN nations.
The company states that executives, employees, IT administrators, and other authorized personnel caused slightly more than 56% of compromised data incidents in Southeast Asia. External attacks and former employees were responsible for the remaining 44%.</description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2018 features AI technology that can detect ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</guid><description>Acronis Integrates AI into True Image 2018 for Enhanced Data Protection Image: Beloussov introducing Acronis ahead of the launch of Acronis True Image 2018.
Beloussov speaking at the Acronis True Image 2018 launch event.
Acronis, a global leader in hybrid cloud data protection, is incorporating artificial intelligence (AI) into its entire product line. Serguei Beloussov, co-founder and CEO of Acronis, emphasized their commitment to AI integration across all products. This announcement was made during the launch of their flagship product, Acronis True Image 2018.</description></item><item><title>ESET introduces the latest version of its security suite for consumers, version 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-security-suite-for-consumers-version-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:08:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-security-suite-for-consumers-version-10/</guid><description>ESET has introduced version 10 of its home security software lineup. Their top product, ESET Smart Security Premium, uses ESET&amp;rsquo;s NOD32 technology, designed for a balance of effective threat detection, speed, and user-friendliness.
This latest version includes a new password manager for simplified secure logins and ESET Secure Data for robust and convenient file encryption. In addition to ESET Smart Security Premium, users can also choose ESET Internet Security. &amp;ldquo;As online threats become more varied, users need comprehensive internet security suites with customizable features,&amp;rdquo; explains Lukas Raska, ESET&amp;rsquo;s COO for Asia Pacific.</description></item><item><title>Make sure to keep your passwords secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/make-sure-to-keep-your-passwords-secure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:32:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/make-sure-to-keep-your-passwords-secure/</guid><description>The first Thursday of May, which falls on the 7th this year, is World Password Day, a day dedicated to highlighting the importance of regularly updating passwords. Despite this annual reminder, the number of passwords we need to remember doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be decreasing.
David Higgins, CyberArk&amp;rsquo;s Technical Director, noted that this year&amp;rsquo;s World Password Day occurs as many people are adjusting to a &amp;ldquo;new normal&amp;rdquo; of increased remote work. This shift has blurred the lines between personal and work devices, with more people using personal devices for work purposes.</description></item><item><title>LG Electronics has introduced a new website dedicated to product security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</guid><description>LG Electronics has launched a dedicated website to address security concerns related to their mobile products. The website, managed by LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security Response Team (PSRT), will serve as a central hub for security announcements, updates, and a platform for reporting vulnerabilities.
LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security website will feature regular updates and bulletins on security matters concerning their mobile products, aiming to provide a secure and safe user experience. The website will prioritize vulnerabilities based on their severity, starting with the most critical ones, followed by high, moderate, and low-risk threats, including those identified by Google for the Android operating system.</description></item><item><title>Today is World Backup Day. Have you ensured the safety of your data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</guid><description>A recent worldwide study funded by Acronis, a prominent name in hybrid cloud data protection, highlights a rising awareness of the importance of safeguarding personal data on computers, mobile phones, and tablets.
Almost half of the surveyed individuals possess more than four devices per household requiring protection, and 45% are most afraid of misplacing photos and videos. Security and privacy were identified as crucial factors in data backup.
Evolving Concerns in Personal Data Security The traditional worries of hardware malfunctions and accidental deletions are no longer the sole reasons for data loss apprehension.</description></item><item><title>ESET introduces security solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a company that provides proactive digital protection, has launched two new security products: ESET Multi-Device Security Home Office and ESET Small Office Security. These products are designed for small office/home office (SOHO) users.
&amp;ldquo;Cybercriminals often target small and home offices because they assume these businesses lack strong security measures,&amp;rdquo; said Andrew Lee, CEO of ESET North America. &amp;ldquo;There are 28 million businesses in this sector, and they need security solutions tailored to their unique needs.</description></item><item><title>Check Point has discovered a vulnerability in a preinstalled app on Xiaomi devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</guid><description>Slava Makkaveev, a researcher from cybersecurity firm Check Point Software, recently discovered a concerning security flaw in Xiaomi phones.
This vulnerability was found within the pre-installed &amp;ldquo;Guard Provider&amp;rdquo; app (com.miui.guardprovider), designed to identify malware. Ironically, this app could allow attackers on the same Wi-Fi network to perform a man-in-the-middle (MiTM) attack. This type of attack enables the interception and copying of data transmitted between the phone and online services.
Furthermore, by exploiting a third-party software development kit (SDK) update mechanism, attackers could potentially disable malware protection and inject malicious code.</description></item><item><title>There has been an increase in crypto giveaway scams</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</guid><description>Source: Group-IB. A screen capture from a fake YouTube video that appears to show Elon Musk.
Group-IB, a cybersecurity firm based in Singapore, has detected a significant surge in websites promoting cryptocurrency giveaway scams using fake YouTube live streams during the first half of 2022. These scams have become increasingly organized, evolving into a distinct market segment with various services supporting fraudulent activities.
The firm&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that while 63% of these new scam domains are registered with Russian registrars, they primarily target English and Spanish-speaking individuals interested in cryptocurrency.</description></item><item><title>Phones become unresponsive due to Android vulnerability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</guid><description>Trend Micro has identified a weakness in the Android operating system that can cause a phone to seem non-functional. Affected phones exhibit symptoms like no ringing or notification sounds, an inability to make calls, and an unresponsive screen. Additionally, locked phones cannot be unlocked.
This vulnerability affects Android versions from 4.3 (Jelly Bean) to 5.1.1 (Lollipop), encompassing over half of all Android devices currently in use. Despite being reported to the Android Engineering Team in late May, no official fix has been released through the Android Open Source Project (AOSP).</description></item><item><title>Trend Micro advises Windows users to update their operating system to safeguard against the Winshock bug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-advises-windows-users-to-update-their-operating-system-to-safeguard-against-the-winshock-bug/</guid><description>A recently discovered flaw in Microsoft Windows has Trend Micro urging all Windows users to immediately update their systems. The issue exists in Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s data transfer platform, which is designed for secure communication. Trend Micro warns that users who don&amp;rsquo;t update are highly vulnerable to attacks, potentially allowing hackers to take control of their systems without any user interaction.
This bug, nicknamed &amp;ldquo;Winshock,&amp;rdquo; received a severity score of 9.3 out of 10 from the Common Vulnerability Scoring System.</description></item><item><title>Are there any consequences to the WhatsApp hacking?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-there-any-consequences-to-the-whatsapp-hacking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-there-any-consequences-to-the-whatsapp-hacking/</guid><description>Even though WhatsApp claims to use encryption for secure communications, the platform has experienced a security breach. Such attacks on widely used software have the potential to impact vast numbers of users, and while this specific vulnerability has been addressed, it highlights the possibility that everyday software might not be as secure as users believe.
Nabil Hannan, a Managing Principal specializing in Financial Services at Synopsys&amp;rsquo; Software Integrity Group, explained that this incident poses a risk because, theoretically, any WhatsApp user could be targeted using their phone number.</description></item><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA.</description></item><item><title>Intel Security has released a list of the holiday gifts that are most vulnerable to hacking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</guid><description>· A survey indicates that 80% of shoppers are anticipated to make purchases online this year.
· While 85% of consumers begin utilizing connected devices within a day of obtaining them, a mere 45% report taking the appropriate security precautions.
· Despite acknowledging the significance of device security, nearly half of consumers (46%) are unsure if they are implementing adequate protective measures.
Intel Security has released its second yearly McAfee Most Hackable Holiday Gifts list, aiming to spotlight potential security vulnerabilities linked to popular gift items this holiday season.</description></item><item><title>Acronis highlights the divide between cybersecurity awareness and personal protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-highlights-the-divide-between-cybersecurity-awareness-and-personal-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-highlights-the-divide-between-cybersecurity-awareness-and-personal-protection/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyber protection company based in Singapore, has discovered a discrepancy between the understanding of the need for data protection and the actions taken to achieve it.
A global survey conducted for World Backup Day on March 31st опросила 4,400 IT users and professionals across 22 countries and 6 continents, including Singapore. The results challenge the assumption that simply using more solutions will address cybersecurity and data protection concerns.</description></item><item><title>Intel Security is turning to the cloud to enhance consumer security protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-is-turning-to-the-cloud-to-enhance-consumer-security-protection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-is-turning-to-the-cloud-to-enhance-consumer-security-protection/</guid><description>Intel Security has released its 2017 consumer security product line, aiming to provide better protection for everyday devices. The main feature is a new anti-malware engine that increases efficiency and effectiveness by performing analysis in the cloud. Enhancements for multiple devices are also included in McAfee AntiVirus Plus, McAfee Internet Security, McAfee Total Protection, and McAfee LiveSafe.
The McAfee Labs Threats Report: June 2016 revealed a 120% rise in new ransomware since Q1 2015 and over 4.</description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points.</description></item><item><title>Singapore residents are being targeted by a phone-based phishing campaign, according to DBS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</guid><description>DBS Bank has issued a warning to residents of Singapore about a phishing scam making use of automated phone calls. Given their customer base of over 4 million in Singapore alone, it is highly likely that scammers will connect with a DBS account holder.
The scam, as reported on the DBS website, begins with an automated voice message in either English or Mandarin. The recipient is told they have an urgent message from DBS Bank and instructed to press either &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces the latest version of its software, Acronis True Image 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 19:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</guid><description>Acronis introduces the Acronis Survival Kit, a comprehensive system recovery solution.
New active disk cloning functionality for Mac enables data migration to other devices.
Acronis Active Protection, powered by AI, effectively combats ransomware threats.
Acronis Notary and ASign leverage blockchain technology to guarantee data integrity through notarization and e-signatures.
Enhanced backup solutions now extend protection to social media profiles.
Acronis, a leading provider of cyber protection and hybrid cloud solutions, has unveiled the 15th-anniversary edition of its renowned personal backup software, Acronis True Image 2019.</description></item><item><title>Singapore businesses can access cybersecurity and financing services from Acronis and Minterest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyberprotection company, has partnered with Minterest, a Singaporean online financial services provider, to offer financing to Singaporean businesses. This collaboration, called Acronis #CyberFit Financing, Powered by Minterest, aims to help businesses in Singapore stay resilient and #CyberFit during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Acronis and Minterest want to empower businesses by providing easily accessible, customized financing solutions. This will help businesses navigate challenging times while also strengthening their cybersecurity defenses.</description></item><item><title>Stay away from Pokemon Go scams and malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</guid><description>Source: Niantic blog.
The augmented reality game Pokémon Go, highly popular since its July launch, has attracted scammers and cybercriminals. While the game hasn&amp;rsquo;t officially launched in all of Asia, Symantec warns of potential risks for players.
Symantec&amp;rsquo;s blog post details several Pokémon Go scams, from fake PokeCoins to privacy concerns.
Free PokeCoin scams
Pokémon Go offers in-app purchases using real money to buy PokeCoins, a virtual currency. Players use these coins to purchase items like incense to attract Pokémon.</description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances.</description></item><item><title>Trend Micro demonstrates ways to enhance the security of Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</guid><description>In 2014, Android controlled the global smartphone market, shipping one billion units and representing 81% of all smartphones shipped, as reported by Strategy Analytics.
Trend Micro researcher, Paul Oliveria, points out that Android&amp;rsquo;s popularity stems from its affordability, efficient data storage, and availability across various brands and price points.
This widespread use makes Android a prime target for hackers. To combat this, Trend Micro proposes seven security measures for mobile users:</description></item><item><title>Group-IB reports that phishing attacks are still ongoing without any signs of slowing down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-ib-reports-that-phishing-attacks-are-still-ongoing-without-any-signs-of-slowing-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:08:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-ib-reports-that-phishing-attacks-are-still-ongoing-without-any-signs-of-slowing-down/</guid><description>Source: Group-IB. List of Classiscam APAC targets ranked by the number of brands impersonated.
Group-IB, a Singapore-based cybersecurity firm, has discovered that the scam-as-a-service operation, Classiscam, is continuing its global activities into 2023.
A recent report from Group-IB analysts explains how this automated scheme utilizes Telegram bots to generate phishing websites that mimic legitimate companies across various sectors, including online retailers, classified ad platforms, and logistics providers. These fraudulent sites are engineered to steal funds, payment details, and increasingly, online banking credentials from unsuspecting internet users.</description></item><item><title>The Siren Song of Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</guid><description>The pervasiveness of cloud computing, services, and networks in technological discussions today is undeniable. This buzz might even remind you of the catchy tune, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Computing,&amp;rdquo; by Loose Bruce Kerr (a playful nod to Joni Mitchell).
Similar to the shift from mainframes to networked PCs and back to a centralized system in the cloud, cloud services represent a significant technological advancement. While security and connectivity concerns exist, the widespread adoption of cloud services could make purchasing and updating software seem as outdated as physical switches on computers.</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Troublesome Window and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mystery-of-the-troublesome-window-and-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mystery-of-the-troublesome-window-and-security/</guid><description>It can be frustrating when setting up security in GP 10.0 (or GP 2010). Take limiting access to payroll data, for instance. You disable the Payroll Clerk role, thinking that&amp;rsquo;s enough, but then you test it and find various Payroll windows still accessible.
While the Payroll Clerk role manages transactions and cards, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t cover setup, utilities, routines, reports, Smartlists, or inquiries. Even after removing relevant tasks and roles, like those within the Accounting Manager role, some windows remain stubbornly visible.</description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security.</description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1.</description></item><item><title>New OCBC Securities app and Android OCBC app now offer fingerprint security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 08:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</guid><description>Source: OCBC. The iOCBC TradeMobile app allows users to perform in-depth technical analyses of stocks using standard indicators.
OCBC Securities has introduced a new mobile app called iOCBC TradeMobile for iPhone users. Existing OCBC Securities customers can now conveniently monitor their stock portfolios and access real-time market data for their stocks using Apple&amp;rsquo;s Touch ID technology. This fingerprint authentication feature, known as OneTouch, offers both OCBC Bank and OCBC Securities customers a secure and convenient way to access their banking and brokerage accounts.</description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2020 streamlines the 3-2-1 backup approach</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2020-streamlines-the-3-2-1-backup-approach/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 15:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2020-streamlines-the-3-2-1-backup-approach/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyber protection company, has launched Acronis True Image 2020, a new personal cyber protection solution. This version allows users to automatically copy local backups to the cloud, making it the first personal solution to automate the 3-2-1 backup rule recommended by data protection experts.
This release supports Acronis&amp;rsquo;s vision of cyber protection, which combines traditional data protection and cybersecurity into one solution. As a result, Acronis True Image 2020 is the only personal solution to address all five vectors of cyber protection—safety, accessibility, privacy, authenticity, and security of data (SAPAS).</description></item><item><title>Consumers in the Asia Pacific region are more concerned about the security of their computer data than their mobile payment data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 11:58:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</guid><description>New benchmark data from ACI Worldwide and the Aite Group reveals that consumers in the Asia Pacific region are more worried about the security of their financial and payment information on computers compared to mobile wallets. This conclusion comes from their Global Consumer Survey: Consumer Trust and Security Perceptions report.
The study, which surveyed over 6,000 consumers across 20 countries, found that only 46% of Asia Pacific consumers trust businesses, such as restaurants and retailers, to safeguard their financial data.</description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal.</description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC places a strong emphasis on ensuring compliance and transparency in all business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 11:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</guid><description>Following the release of the Panama Papers, the Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC) has reaffirmed its commitment to facilitating cross-border trade and investment, especially within the ASEAN region. The organization emphasizes its dedication to maintaining strict transparency and regulatory standards for all business activities conducted within the centre.
In a statement, the organization highlighted its continuous efforts to strengthen its regulatory framework and supervisory system. These efforts aim to meet international standards and practices related to transparency and regulatory compliance.</description></item><item><title>Companies that experience data breaches in the Asia Pacific region are unlikely to be forgiven</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 02:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</guid><description>New research from SafeNet reveals that data breaches significantly influence customer trust. The global study, including participants from Japan and Australia, found that 65% wouldn&amp;rsquo;t patronize a business that experienced a financial data breach, compromising credit card details, bank accounts, or login credentials.
SafeNet&amp;rsquo;s Q2 Breach Level Index reported 237 data breaches from April to June 2014, exposing over 175 million records globally. These findings highlight the impact of data breaches on customer loyalty and revenue.</description></item><item><title>Identifying a GP 10 security task that is providing unauthorized access to a window.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-a-gp-10-security-task-that-is-providing-unauthorized-access-to-a-window/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-a-gp-10-security-task-that-is-providing-unauthorized-access-to-a-window/</guid><description>While I appreciate the design of GP 10&amp;rsquo;s security model, I find the process of setting up security roles and tasks to be rather cumbersome. Thankfully, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to do it very often.
GP 2010 has some improvements that make configuring security easier. However, for those still using GP 10, researching specific security settings can be challenging.
I recently addressed a question about GP 10 security where a user wanted to restrict access to particular SmartLists.</description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals are using the popularity of Netflix and WhatsApp to distribute malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</guid><description>Source: Check Point Research. The Google Play page for the FlixOnline app.
Hackers are spreading Android malware disguised as an app to unlock Netflix content. Check Point Research (CPR) discovered that this malware automatically responds to incoming WhatsApp messages with malicious links.
The malware was initially concealed within an app called FlixOnline on Google Play. While promising users access to global Netflix content on their phones, it actually tracked victims’ WhatsApp notifications and automatically replied to messages using externally provided content.</description></item><item><title>INTERPOL warns against Simda, urges PC owners to conduct scans on their devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interpol-warns-against-simda-urges-pc-owners-to-conduct-scans-on-their-devices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:41:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interpol-warns-against-simda-urges-pc-owners-to-conduct-scans-on-their-devices/</guid><description>A global operation based out of INTERPOL&amp;rsquo;s Global Complex for Innovation in Singapore recently disrupted the Simda botnet, which is estimated to have compromised over 770,000 computers globally. Cybercriminals used Simda to gain unauthorized access to computers, enabling them to steal sensitive data like banking credentials and spread additional malicious software.
Simda, active over several years, had become increasingly sophisticated. New, harder-to-detect versions were being created and disseminated every few hours.</description></item><item><title>Are your passwords secure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-passwords-secure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-passwords-secure/</guid><description>Intel Security commemorated World Password Day by providing helpful advice on enhancing online security through diverse authentication methods.
Steer Clear of Predictable Logins
Short and seemingly clever passwords are easily guessed. Cybercriminals often begin their attacks by testing common password combinations. Simple keyboard patterns like &amp;ldquo;qwerty&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;12345678&amp;rdquo; are just as insecure as passwords like &amp;ldquo;welcome&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;login.&amp;rdquo;
Craft Strong, Complex Passwords
Longer passwords are always more secure. Incorporate a mix of numbers, lowercase and uppercase letters, and symbols.</description></item><item><title>Singtel will provide ZoneAlarm Mobile Security protection from Check Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:16:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</guid><description>Singtel has partnered with Check Point Software Technologies to launch ZoneAlarm Mobile Security. This mobile security app offers extensive protection against digital threats like malware, hacking attempts, and Wi-Fi attacks.
ZoneAlarm, available for both iOS and Android devices, conducts thorough risk evaluations. It scans installed applications, identifies unsafe Wi-Fi networks, and suggests the safest Wi-Fi hotspot choices. Additionally, it alerts users of any questionable processes running on their phones and safeguards their operating systems from attacks.</description></item><item><title>CyberArk warns that allowing third parties access to your network can provide hackers with an entry point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyberark-warns-that-allowing-third-parties-access-to-your-network-can-provide-hackers-with-an-entry-point/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:31:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyberark-warns-that-allowing-third-parties-access-to-your-network-can-provide-hackers-with-an-entry-point/</guid><description>CyberArk, a cybersecurity firm, released a report highlighting the risks of granting external vendors access to company networks.
Source: CyberArk. View the complete infographic here.
&amp;ldquo;Cybercriminals often exploit vulnerabilities within IT security, particularly accounts shared with external vendors for network access,&amp;rdquo; warned John Worrall, Chief Marketing Officer at CyberArk. He added that these vendors often have weaker security measures compared to their larger counterparts, creating a point of entry for attackers.</description></item><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Network Monitoring Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</guid><description>The increasing reliance on electronic transactions, online services, and cloud technologies has made networks essential for businesses. This dependence requires IT departments to prioritize network monitoring, either through in-house solutions or external providers.
While companies have traditionally monitored their internal networks, extending this practice to telecom connections is crucial. This includes dedicated lines, public internet connections, and VPNs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to enhance network monitoring processes.
Smaller businesses often face challenges with network monitoring outside of business hours.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel Cyber Security Institute aims to enhance the skills of individuals and businesses in the field of cyber security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</guid><description>Singapore Telecommunications established the Singtel Cyber Security Institute (CSI) to bolster the cyber security skills of businesses and governments in the Asia Pacific region. The CSI is the first organization of its kind in the region, merging an advanced cyber range with an educational institute to provide companies with realistic training to handle complex cyber threats.
Bill Chang, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Group Enterprise CEO, highlighted the lack of preparedness among companies, with over 85% lacking robust cyber response plans or realistic training opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Home networks must be made more secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 06:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</guid><description>The increasing availability of faster and cheaper internet in Southeast Asia is driving a surge in home users adopting internet-connected devices. This trend is happening alongside more employees working remotely, often from home. While these connected devices offer convenience and improve communication, Fortinet, a global cybersecurity leader, warns that &amp;ldquo;home networks&amp;rdquo; are becoming attractive targets for cybercriminals.
Peerapong Jongvibool, Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s VP for Southeast Asia and Hong Kong, points out the vulnerability of internet-connected devices.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?</description></item><item><title>Be cautious of malware with a Christmas theme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</guid><description>Christmas tree, Marina Bay Sands.
_&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;On the twelfth day of Christmas
my true love gave me:
Twelve pieces of malware
Eleven malfunctioning firewalls
Ten ransomware dangers
Nine account breaches
Eight adware websites
Seven deceitful emails
Six compromised PDFs
Five warning signs
Four spyware-infected games
Three junk text messages
Two Trojan horses
And a phishing email!&amp;quot;_
Holiday greetings can carry hidden cyber threats, even if sent from loved ones. Yeo Siang Tiong, Southeast Asia General Manager at Kaspersky Lab, emphasizes the importance of robust computer and mobile device protection before engaging in holiday activities like downloading festive content, sending emails, or online shopping.</description></item><item><title>ESET advocates for the use of two-factor authentication to enhance security for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, cautions that small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) are frequently targeted by cybercriminals due to the vulnerability of their data. Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research&amp;rsquo;s study reveals that stolen personal data fuels a multi-billion dollar industry.
Lukas Raska, COO of ESET Asia, emphasizes the evolution of cybercrime from viruses to the current threat of identity theft, highlighting its potential to cripple businesses and compromise customer trust.
Parvinder Walia, Director at ESET APAC, explains that SMBs are attractive targets because they often lack the robust cybersecurity budgets and dedicated personnel of larger companies.</description></item><item><title>The launch of ESET Smart Security 9 and ESET NOD32 Antivirus 9 has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</guid><description>ESET, a global cybersecurity company, has launched ESET Smart Security 9 and ESET NOD32 Antivirus 9. These releases feature a redesigned user interface and enhanced security features.
Parvinder Walia, ESET&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific Sales and Marketing Director, highlighted the Asia-Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s rapid growth in internet and mobile usage, leading to increased adoption of online and mobile banking. He emphasized that the new banking and payment protection in ESET Smart Security 9 will allow customers to conduct secure financial transactions online.</description></item><item><title>The second season of The Wolf, produced by HP Studios, demonstrates the capabilities of hackers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 22:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</guid><description>Source: HP eDM. Christian Slater stars in The Wolf: The Hunt Continues.
The second season of The Wolf, starring Christian Slater, is out now from HP Studios. This film follows a hacker&amp;rsquo;s exploitation of the healthcare system, revealing how vulnerable endpoints like printers can be compromised, leading to critical data loss.
HP claims that their printers and PCs offer the highest level of security globally.
Want to learn more?</description></item><item><title>Smaller companies can benefit from Cisco's advanced firewall security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</guid><description>Source: Cisco website. Some members of the Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services family.
Cisco has introduced new Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services models designed for small to mid-sized businesses and branch offices. These models offer the same advanced malware protection and threat detection used by larger organizations.
A recent study by PwC revealed a 64% increase in security breaches among mid-sized organizations in 2014. These organizations face similar security challenges as larger enterprises when safeguarding their network and data.</description></item><item><title>Top-paying technology jobs for 2014 - for those in the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</guid><description>The 2014 Salary Guides published by Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group identify six technology and digital jobs experiencing high demand in the US. This demand may also be reflected in the Asia Pacific region.
Companies are specifically seeking professionals skilled in information and network security, data analysis for business intelligence, and mobile development.
&amp;ldquo;Building a strong online presence and engaging customers through mobile platforms is crucial for businesses today,&amp;rdquo; says John Reed, Senior Executive Director of Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own World Wide Web</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet has its downsides despite the benefits of global and instant information access. Sharing large files between offices, conducting high-quality teleconferences, and experiencing seamless application interactions can be challenging. Network crashes, congestion from high-bandwidth activities, and constant security threats further diminish the internet&amp;rsquo;s appeal. So, is there a better alternative?
The Connectivity Conundrum
Imagine having an exclusive internet solely for your business, customers, and suppliers. Bandwidth wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue, and the network would operate seamlessly.</description></item><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions.</description></item><item><title>Sophos has simplified the process of securing corporate information on mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Source: Sophos website.
Sophos recently launched Sophos Mobile Control 5 (SMC 5), a software solution designed to differentiate personal and company data on devices to enhance corporate data security.
Managing devices like laptops, tablets, and smartphones often involves individual configuration, updates, and management. SMC 5 simplifies this process for IT administrators by allowing them to establish user-specific rules once to protect company data stored on the device or in personal cloud storage.</description></item><item><title>Trend Micro cautions that hackers are focusing on small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Trend Micro website.
Trend Micro warns that hackers are shifting tactics, moving away from mass spamming and towards sending personalized emails containing harmful attachments to compromise businesses. This method, the company cautions, could become the standard attack strategy in the Asia Pacific region.
A Trend Micro report titled &amp;ldquo;Piercing the HawkEye: Nigerian Cybercriminals Use a Simple Keylogger to Prey on SMBs Worldwide&amp;rdquo; reveals that two Nigerian hackers, known as &amp;ldquo;Uche&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Okiki,&amp;rdquo; are using inexpensive keylogging software called Hawkeye to target small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) globally.</description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers.</description></item><item><title>Two Routes to Virtual Private Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</guid><description>VPNs have become the go-to solution for connecting multiple business locations due to their cost-effectiveness and ease of maintenance. Managed service providers allow businesses to enjoy secure multipoint communication without the burden of extensive staffing or high monthly line lease fees.
Virtual private networking is now cloud-based, but the choice of cloud type remains. You can opt for a VPN solution using the public internet or choose a completely private network for enhanced performance.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling on the Legality of the Revised European Firearms Directive: Gun Control in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 22:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, PhD candidate, Dublin City University
Introduction
On December 3rd, 2019, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) delivered its final ruling on a case concerning Czech firearm regulations. This judgment, providing guidance on EU lawmaking, addressed key EU law principles and refined their interpretations. Following terrorist attacks in Paris and Copenhagen, the EU legislature utilized its single market powers (Article 114 TFEU) to pass Directive (EU) 2017/853, amending existing firearms Directives 91/477 and 2008/51/EC.</description></item><item><title>Check Point warns that free USB devices may be carriers of malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</guid><description>Source: Victoria Police. The unmarked USB drives used are similar to these.
On September 21st, law enforcement in Victoria, Australia, issued a warning to residents of Pakenham, a Melbourne suburb, about unlabeled USB drives found in mailboxes.
According to the Victoria police statement, people have been discovering unmarked USB drives in their mailboxes. When connected to computers, these drives have exposed victims to fraudulent streaming service offers and other serious problems.</description></item><item><title>Dell updates tablets, unveils new 5K monitor and smart desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 20:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</guid><description>Dell has improved its PC selection to boost productivity with new tablet functionalities, a 5K Ultra HD monitor, and a futuristic &amp;ldquo;smart desk&amp;rdquo; workspace.
Jeff Clarke, Dell&amp;rsquo;s Vice Chairman of Operations and President of Client Solutions, highlighted Dell&amp;rsquo;s focus on improving productivity and business outcomes at the recent Dell World Executive Summit.
The Dell UltraSharp 27 Monitor, available in December for US$2,499, offers Ultra HD 5K resolution (5,120 x 2,880), seven times sharper than Full HD.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry introduces WatchDox by BlackBerry Email Protector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-introduces-watchdox-by-blackberry-email-protector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 22:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-introduces-watchdox-by-blackberry-email-protector/</guid><description>BlackBerry has launched WatchDox by BlackBerry Email Protector, a new product designed to give businesses greater control over file security. This is achieved by incorporating digital rights management (DRM) at the file level for emails, ensuring protection beyond the company&amp;rsquo;s firewall.
WatchDox by BlackBerry is a comprehensive file management platform that facilitates file syncing and sharing across multiple operating systems. By integrating DRM security into individual files, the solution reduces the risks of data breaches.</description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity.</description></item><item><title>Before you decide to check out Ronaldo, reconsider your decision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</guid><description>A study by McAfee, a part of Intel Security, reveals that cybercriminals often use popular figures like Cristiano Ronaldo to lure unsuspecting users to malicious websites. These websites, designed to look like legitimate fan pages, can infect devices with malware capable of stealing personal information. McAfee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Red Card Club&amp;rdquo; list highlights the top eleven footballers whose names are most frequently used in these scams, with Ronaldo topping the list, followed by Lionel Messi and Iker Cassillas.</description></item><item><title>The attitudes towards cybercrime and security in Singapore vary across different generations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</guid><description>This past week, I encountered WhatsApp spam shortly after a friend forwarded a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s discount coupon from Sniflr. Upon researching, I discovered Sniflr is a phishing scam that tricks people into sharing the coupon with 10 friends on WhatsApp, adding those numbers to a spam list.
Yesterday, a promoted tweet on my Twitter feed advertised a S$100 discount on a S$120 purchase at NTUC, a popular Singaporean supermarket chain. However, a Google search revealed a months-old news article warning about fake NTUC coupons on Facebook, a claim supported by NTUC&amp;rsquo;s official Twitter account.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible that your computer is generating wealth for someone else?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</guid><description>Fortinet, a leading cybersecurity company, is warning users to be alert if their computers drastically slow down, as it could be a sign of &amp;ldquo;browser cryptojacking.&amp;rdquo; This new cybercrime involves hackers secretly using victims&amp;rsquo; computers to mine Monero, a type of cryptocurrency.
This is how it works: a malicious script is secretly embedded into a website. When a user visits the site, the script uses their computer&amp;rsquo;s processing power to mine Monero for the cybercriminal.</description></item><item><title>A new version of McAfee Mobile Security has been launched by Intel Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</guid><description>Intel Security has released the newest version of McAfee Mobile Security (MMS) for Android devices. This updated software offers enhanced security and improved device performance.
As people increasingly rely on their mobile devices for personal and sensitive tasks, MMS provides protection and addresses the need for faster speeds, longer battery life, and secure browsing on Android phones and tablets.
This new version of MMS allows users to maximize their Android device performance with features that optimize speed and battery life.</description></item><item><title>Kaspersky Lab is providing security tips in preparation for the Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown is prominently featuring dog decorations in celebration of the new year.
As shoppers navigate the excitement and rush of Chinese New Year shopping, Kaspersky Lab cautions that they are more susceptible to making simple errors that could jeopardize their personal information.
Sylvia Ng, General Manager of Kaspersky Lab Southeast Asia, acknowledges that holiday shopping is a top priority for consumers. However, she emphasizes that it&amp;rsquo;s also an opportune time for cybercriminals.</description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM.</description></item><item><title>CloudGuard SaaS from Check Point is now accessible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudguard-saas-from-check-point-is-now-accessible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 21:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudguard-saas-from-check-point-is-now-accessible/</guid><description>Check Point Software Technologies, a leading global cybersecurity provider, has launched CloudGuard SaaS, a new cloud-based security suite.
As part of Check Point&amp;rsquo;s CloudGuard product line, CloudGuard SaaS is designed to safeguard businesses against advanced threats targeting software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications.
This solution protects companies using SaaS applications and cloud-based email, such as Office 365, GSuite, and OneDrive, from targeted attacks aimed at stealing sensitive information. It detects unauthorized SaaS application use, prevents data breaches, and provides immediate threat visibility.</description></item><item><title>Here are five tips for creating stronger passwords, according to ESET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-are-five-tips-for-creating-stronger-passwords-according-to-eset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 02:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-are-five-tips-for-creating-stronger-passwords-according-to-eset/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, used World Password Day on May 3rd as an opportunity to share advice on creating stronger passwords.
World Password Day is a global event designed to promote the importance of strong passwords and safe online practices. ESET&amp;rsquo;s Senior Research Fellow, Nick FitzGerald, pointed out that even with secure password storage, weak or predictable passwords still leave users vulnerable to hacking.
FitzGerald highlighted a recent case involving Singapore Airlines, where hackers may have exploited weak passwords to steal KrisFlyer frequent flyer miles.</description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2021 provides a combination of cybersecurity and backup solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2021-provides-a-combination-of-cybersecurity-and-backup-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 02:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2021-provides-a-combination-of-cybersecurity-and-backup-solutions/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyber protection company, has introduced Acronis True Image 2021. This new product combines robust cybersecurity features with personal backup, creating a comprehensive personal cyber protection solution for individuals, demanding home users, and small businesses with up to five users.
With the increase in remote work, securing home computers has become crucial. However, an Acronis survey revealed that nearly half (47%) of remote workers haven&amp;rsquo;t received clear guidance on cybersecurity while working from home.</description></item><item><title>Generating passwords can be likened to navigating a minefield</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generating-passwords-can-be-likened-to-navigating-a-minefield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generating-passwords-can-be-likened-to-navigating-a-minefield/</guid><description>A popular joke on Twitter highlights the struggle of creating secure passwords, mocking the complex requirements that often feel excessive. However, the humor underscores a serious issue: the necessity of strong passwords in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Simple passwords are widely considered inadequate in preventing unauthorized access, leading organizations to ban easily guessable combinations.
Despite this understanding, the recent Adobe security breach revealed that many users still rely on weak passwords. The most common passwords found in the leaked data were alarmingly basic, with &amp;ldquo;123456&amp;rdquo; topping the list.</description></item><item><title>Asia is included in global ransomware attacks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 20:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</guid><description>WannaCrypt, also referred to as WannaCry or WCry, holds data files hostage and demands a $300 USD ransom in Bitcoin. The ransom message warns that the payment will double after three days. If payment isn&amp;rsquo;t received within seven days, the encrypted files are permanently deleted.
A key feature of WannaCrypt is its ability to self-propagate within company networks without any user intervention. This is achieved by exploiting a known weakness in the Microsoft Windows operating system.</description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers.</description></item><item><title>The increasing financial consequences of cybercrime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</guid><description>Source: HP infographic.
HP recently released the findings of their sixth annual study, conducted in partnership with the Ponemon Institute, exploring the financial effects of cyberattacks on both public and private sectors.
The study shows a substantial rise in the total cost of cybercrime, indicating that smaller companies bear a proportionally larger cost than larger ones.
The 2015 Cost of Cyber Crime Study, carried out by the Ponemon Institute and supported by HP Enterprise Security, calculates the yearly cost of cybercrime for businesses across seven countries: the US, UK, Japan, Germany, Australia, Brazil, and Russia.</description></item><item><title>Are you still using Windows XP? Norton and Qihoo 360 are here to assist you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</guid><description>The AV-Test Institute, located in Germany, tested ten antivirus programs for Windows XP. Out of these, Qihoo 360 Internet Security 9 and Norton Internet Security 2014 proved most effective.
Source: Qihoo 360. AV-TEST Report: Exploit Protection on Windows XP
The institute designed 54 attack simulations using various methods and vulnerabilities to thoroughly test each program. The tested antivirus solutions included products from Qihoo 360, Avast, AVG, Avira, Bitdefender, Eset, Kaspersky, and Norton.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is showcasing career opportunities in the field of cyber security to the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 23:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</guid><description>Singtel launched the Singtel Cyber Security Experience (CSX), an interactive online platform, to bolster Singapore&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity workforce. This portal aims to attract students and career changers to the field.
CSX showcases cybersecurity career paths through profiles of professionals from Singtel, Trustwave (its US-based subsidiary), and the Cyber Security Agency of Singapore (CSA). The platform features interactive simulations that mimic real-world scenarios, illustrating the skills needed for various roles.
Visitors can test their knowledge through challenges focused on fundamental cybersecurity concepts.</description></item><item><title>What’s to Become of Data Centers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</guid><description>The increasing costs and rapid technological advancements are putting pressure on both large colocation facilities and traditional in-house data centers. This infographic from David Vellante on Wikibon provides a concise overview of the current situation:
Exploring Data Center Alternatives
If you&amp;rsquo;re reconsidering the viability of investing in a new data center or maintaining your existing one, you have numerous options. These range from colocation services at large commercial data centers to cloud-based solutions.</description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware.</description></item><item><title>Businesses operating in the South China Sea region should be cautious of the Spring Dragon APT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</guid><description>Kaspersky Lab is issuing a warning about a threat actor targeting nations surrounding the South China Sea. The cybersecurity company has observed a rise in attacks since 2017 from an advanced persistent threat (APT) known as Spring Dragon (or LotusBlossom) using new and enhanced tactics.
Noushin Shabab, Senior Security Researcher at Kaspersky Lab&amp;rsquo;s Global Research &amp;amp; Analysis Team (GReAT), emphasizes the importance of vigilance, stating, &amp;ldquo;We believe Spring Dragon will continue to reappear in the Asian region, making it crucial to be familiar with its methods.</description></item><item><title>Don't fall for the scam of cheap Ray-Ban sunglasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</guid><description>Source: ESET.
ESET&amp;rsquo;s spam filters have identified a growing trend of fraudulent emails enticing recipients with deeply discounted luxury items, particularly Ray-Ban sunglasses. These counterfeit websites lack encryption and might be designed to capture victims&amp;rsquo; payment information. While ESET had issued prior warnings about this scam targeting Facebook users, the shift to email attacks broadens the potential victim pool significantly.
“Providing payment card information on these fake websites poses a substantial financial risk,&amp;quot; cautions Lukáš Štefanko, an ESET Malware Researcher.</description></item><item><title>Card-not-present fraud is on the rise, leaving two-thirds of credit card issuers in the Asia-Pacific region vulnerable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 11:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</guid><description>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing a surge in e-commerce, but this growth is accompanied by an increase in online fraud. A survey of fraud professionals in the region, conducted by predictive analytics firm FICO, revealed that card-not-present (CNP) fraud is the fastest-growing type of fraud. Nearly all (94%) of the survey respondents reported an increase in CNP fraud.
eMarketer, a research firm, projects that B2C e-commerce sales in the Asia Pacific region will reach US$525.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is urging the public to take an active role in digital defense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 02:35:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</guid><description>Source: Tableau. Minister Maliki addresses the audience.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for Defence &amp;amp; Foreign Affairs, Dr. Mohamad Maliki Bin Osman, was the guest of honor and keynote speaker at Tableau Software&amp;rsquo;s 5th annual Public Sector Day. During his speech, he emphasized the importance of digital defense in the digital age.
Dr. Maliki highlighted how digital technology&amp;rsquo;s interconnected nature has increased vulnerability to cyberattacks, disinformation campaigns, and the spread of fake news.</description></item><item><title>Veritas presents a concise overview of ransomware in just five minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veritas-presents-a-concise-overview-of-ransomware-in-just-five-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 08:41:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veritas-presents-a-concise-overview-of-ransomware-in-just-five-minutes/</guid><description>Justin Loh, Singapore Country Director at Veritas, points out that the shift to remote work, using various often unsecured personal devices and networks, has made businesses more vulnerable to attacks. This creates opportunities for malicious actors to steal sensitive information and hold it for ransom.
Here’s a concise overview of ransomware:
What is ransomware?
Ransomware is a type of malicious software that blocks access to computer systems or data until a ransom is paid.</description></item><item><title>Kaspersky provides solutions to combat ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</guid><description>Ransomware is increasingly targeting businesses, encrypting files and demanding payment for decryption keys.
A Kaspersky Lab report reveals a six-fold increase in ransomware attacks against businesses from 2015 to 2016, affecting one in ten business users.
Cybercriminals are focusing on businesses, particularly small and medium-sized companies. A Kaspersky Lab and B2B International study found that 42% of respondents from these businesses considered ransomware a major threat.
Even brief data unavailability can severely impact small businesses, potentially halting operations entirely.</description></item><item><title>Companies in the Asia Pacific region are allocating funds for security, infrastructure, and business intelligence applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</guid><description>When planning technology budgets for the year, remember to allocate resources for infrastructure software, business intelligence applications, and, most importantly, security. Research firm Forrester states that security software is now the fastest-growing software category in the Asia Pacific region, leading in projected software spending growth for 2014.
In a survey of 3,382 IT executives and technology decision-makers across Asia Pacific organizations, 55% indicated they would increase their security software budget by &amp;lsquo;5% to 10%, or more&amp;rsquo; in 2014 compared to 2013.</description></item><item><title>Imperva cautions about potential scams on Singles Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imperva-cautions-about-potential-scams-on-singles-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imperva-cautions-about-potential-scams-on-singles-day/</guid><description>Imperva, a leading cybersecurity firm dedicated to safeguarding data, has released a new report on e-commerce security and provided recommendations for secure online shopping in light of the upcoming global shopping event on November 11th.
The company highlighted that Chinese e-commerce giants Alibaba and JD.com achieved a record-breaking US$115 billion in sales during Singles Day 2020, emphasizing that the rise in online shoppers is accompanied by a parallel increase in scams.</description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:</description></item></channel></rss>