<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Novotel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/novotel/</link><description>Recent content in Novotel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:50:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/novotel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor will assume management of the Star Convention Centre in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</guid><description>In 2020, Accor will assume management of the 571-room Star Convention Centre in Thailand, rebranding it as the Novotel Rayong Star Convention Centre. The hotel, situated in Rayong province&amp;rsquo;s city center, will undergo a significant two-year renovation. The initial phase will focus on revamping public spaces, dining establishments, and 235 guest rooms. Subsequently, the remaining 336 guest rooms will be renovated in the second phase.
Patrick Basset, COO of Accor for Upper Southeast &amp;amp; Northeast Asia and the Maldives, expressed enthusiasm about the hotel joining Accor&amp;rsquo;s network and expanding their presence in Rayong.</description></item><item><title>Accor has launched the Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp; Residences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</guid><description>Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences, the largest five-star hotel in Kolkata, is now open in the city’s New Town precinct.
Source: Accor Hotels. The Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences. The hotel has 347 guest rooms and suites. It is located near the airport and offers the city&amp;rsquo;s first serviced apartments. Guests can enjoy amenities such as a flat-screen LED TV, coffee and tea maker, in-room safe, refreshment center, and complimentary internet access.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food.</description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan.</description></item></channel></rss>