<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pop on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pop/</link><description>Recent content in Pop on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers.</description></item><item><title>KKBOX has initiated a Cpop campaign on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</guid><description>Source: Twitter. Screenshot of Tia Ray&amp;rsquo;s tweet.
Twitter and KKBOX, a popular music streaming service in Asia, are collaborating to increase global recognition and appreciation of Chinese pop music, known as Cpop (#Cpop).
To achieve this, KKBOX is developing exclusive Cpop content (#OnlyOnTwitter) for their main Twitter account (@KKBOX). This includes weekly live question and answer sessions with Cpop artists, personalized video messages from Cpop musicians and producers using Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Challenger app, frequent #KKvote contests to encourage international fan participation, and live streams of Cpop concerts and the yearly KKBOX music awards through Periscope (@KKBOXTW).</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Point of Presence Locator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting more bandwidth for your money, and finding an Ethernet Point of Presence (POP) Locator can help. But what is a POP and how can it save you money?
Essentially, a POP is a carrier&amp;rsquo;s service location, such as a central office with termination equipment for their fiber optic network. Think of it as a station for accessing high-speed data and voice services. POPs aren&amp;rsquo;t always in carrier offices; they can be in colocation centers, shared facilities housing servers and offering resources like bandwidth, security, and backup power.</description></item></channel></rss>