<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cash on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cash/</link><description>Recent content in Cash on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Purchase online and make your payment at a nearby convenience store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</guid><description>MOLPay, a Southeast Asian online payment provider, is partnering with 7-Eleven Malaysia to introduce a new e-commerce payment method.
This service, called MOLPay CASH, will launch first in select Klang Valley 7-Eleven stores, with 735 stores currently offering this option and plans for further expansion. By July 2014, all 1,569 Malaysian stores will provide this service.
MOLPay CASH allows merchants to accept cash payments from customers at their nearest 7-Eleven. After an online purchase, a barcode is generated for the customer to use for payment at a 7-Eleven location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cash For Clunker Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</guid><description>While the government&amp;rsquo;s Cash for Clunkers program for cars might be ending, there&amp;rsquo;s a similar concept for old electronics. You can get cash for your unwanted devices, including cell phones, laptops, and more!
You might not have heard about this, but it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to earn money from your unused gadgets. From cell phones and laptops to gaming consoles and cameras, many devices have value. Don&amp;rsquo;t let them sit around collecting dust – see how much they&amp;rsquo;re worth!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Cash For Your Used or Broken iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</guid><description>Your old iPhone may be worse for wear, but don&amp;rsquo;t throw it away! It&amp;rsquo;s still valuable. Discarding it wastes money and harms the environment when you can easily sell it for cash.
Surprisingly, companies will buy your used iPhone regardless of its condition. Naturally, better condition means more money, but even damaged phones have value, ranging from a few dollars to over $100! A functional iPhone 4S can fetch over $100, far more than you&amp;rsquo;d get tossing it in the garbage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exchange your remaining loose change for digital currency at airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</guid><description>Source: TravelersBox. A kiosk at Singapore Changi Airport (airside).
Travelers passing through Singapore Changi Airport can now utilize their leftover foreign currency or remaining Singapore dollars more effectively. This is made possible by the new TravelersBox kiosks situated within the airport.
TravelersBox, a financial technology company, assists travelers in converting their remaining foreign currency, both bills and coins, into digital money. This digital money can be redeemed online with well-known brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drowning in a Sea of Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 10:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</guid><description>Current estimations show approximately three billion mobile phone users globally, with a billion new devices sold annually. Given that phones are typically replaced every two to three years, this equates to roughly one billion phones becoming obsolete yearly. The question then arises: where do these discarded devices end up?
Contrary to assumptions that they are forgotten in drawers, a recent study revealed that only 44% of old phones remain unused at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>