<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Commander on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commander/</link><description>Recent content in Commander on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commander/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This article details the installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control Module into a Beogram 4002 (Type 5504) turntable. This particular unit was restored for a customer in Australia and also features an internal Beolover RIAA phono pre-amplifier.
The Commander Module, seen here before installation, allows for remote control of the turntable:
The module includes an IR receiver (black wire at the bottom), an adapter board (narrow board on the right), a wiring harness (white wires), and an auto-repeat indicator (red wire at the top).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of Upgrades - Internal RIAA Preamp, Commander Remote Control and a New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</guid><description>Following the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) from Oklahoma, the next step was to add the customer&amp;rsquo;s desired upgrades. These included an internal Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier (designed for AC motor Beogram 4002s), a Beolover Commander remote control system, and a new hood for a pristine appearance.
The first upgrade was preparing the keypad for the Commander remote system. AC motor Beograms primarily use directly soldered wiring harnesses, so Commander installation isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;plug and play&amp;rdquo; like the DC motor version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of Beolover RIAA Preamp and 4002 Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (5523), culminating in the installation of gold-plated RCA plugs. My customer opted to have my recently developed internal BeoloverRIAA preamplifier added, along with the 4002 Commander remote control system, which enables control of all functions via a paired Apple remote.
This marks the first 4002 to feature both the Commander and the RIAA preamp – a true fusion of past and present!
Pictures showcasing the installation process of the BeoloverRIAA board and the 4002 Commander are included.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander MkII: Remote Control for Beogram 4002 Now With Integrated Auto-Repeat Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable and planned to install my 4002 Commander Remote control system. This system is great because it keeps the keypad pristine and allows for operation without touching it. You can find demonstration and installation videos on my blog if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in upgrading your own 4002. The Commander board is compatible with all models equipped with a DC motor.
This restoration project inspired me to create an updated MkII version of the 4002 Commander, featuring an auto-repeat function similar to the Beogram 8000 and 8002 turntables.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Upgrade with SyncDrive Platter Motor, Commander Remote Control and Internal RIAA Pre-Amplifier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</guid><description>A customer from Kentucky requested a full upgrade for their Beogram 4002 turntable, including three modifications: a SyncDrive motor for enhanced speed stability, a Commander remote control system for convenient operation and keypad protection, and a Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier for direct connection to modern audio equipment.
All upgrades were installed without soldering. The SyncDrive replaced the original DC motor, connecting to existing mounting points and the main circuit board. The Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier replaced the output board, using compatible connectors for easy installation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of Beolover Commander MkII Remote and Internal RIAA Pre-Amp Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 09:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</guid><description>The owner of the Beogram 4002 (5513) requested the installation of a 4002 Commander remote control and an internal RIAA pre-amplifier module. The Commander enables complete control of the 4002 using an Apple remote, while the RIAA provides a strong output signal, allowing direct connection to modern amplifiers via CD/DVD/AUX inputs.
The first image displays the RIAA board and its mounting adapter, which elevates it above the output PCB headers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of 4002 Commander MkII Remote Control and Internal RIAA Preamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</guid><description>I recently completed a Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration, and the customer requested two upgrades I developed: the Beolover 4002 Commander MkII remote control receiver and the internal RIAA pre-amplifier. These upgrades are detailed further on my blog, along with installation instructions. Both are available for purchase; feel free to contact me for more information.
This image showcases both boards:
The lower board is the Commander MkII. This version includes a repeat function, indicated by the CD4 light on the keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Mass Production!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 02:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</guid><description>More orders for the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control have been placed. The Commander is now compatible with a designated Apple TV remote, eliminating interference with other Apple devices in the same room. Designed specifically for later models of the 4002 turntable (types 551x and 552x) that feature the keypad connector on the main circuit board, the Commander offers a simple plug-and-play installation process. Today, five new units were assembled.</description></item></channel></rss>