<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Press on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/press/</link><description>Recent content in Press on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/press/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Today is the day for the landrush of .global, .website, and .press domain names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</guid><description>Starting August 27th, Singapore time, several top-level domain names will be up for grabs in a &amp;ldquo;landrush&amp;rdquo; phase, according to online brand specialist IP Mirror.
The &amp;ldquo;sunrise&amp;rdquo; phase, reserved for trademark holders to register their brands, precedes this period. During the landrush phase, anyone can secure remaining domain names at a premium price.
IP Mirror highlights &amp;ldquo;.global&amp;rdquo; as a particularly appealing option, signifying a broad international reach. This domain&amp;rsquo;s landrush phase lasts from August 27th to September 4th.</description></item><item><title>HP believes that the digital printing revolution has the potential to make businesses even more agile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</guid><description>Source: HP. High-impact retail graphics, floor covering and corrugated display applications printed using HP Latex and Scitex Digital printing technologies at the new HP Graphics Solutions Centre of Excellence in Singapore.
The way businesses approach printing is being transformed by commercial digital printing presses. Unlike traditional offset printing, which requires large quantities for cost-effectiveness, digital printers can economically personalize any volume of items, from a single piece to thousands, across diverse materials.</description></item></channel></rss>