<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2017 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2017/</link><description>Recent content in 2017 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The World Bank has released its 2017 forecast for the Thai economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</guid><description>The 2016 Thailand Economic Monitor, published today by the World Bank, projects Thailand&amp;rsquo;s economic growth to reach 3.1% in 2016 and 3.2% in 2017, surpassing the previous year&amp;rsquo;s 2.8%.
The report identifies private consumption and public investments, such as rail infrastructure projects, as primary growth drivers. Tourism has also performed well in 2016, with tourist arrivals, particularly from China, rising by 13.1% in the third quarter. A temporary slowdown and economic inactivity following the passing of HM King Bhumibol Adulyadej in October are anticipated to be partially counterbalanced by year-end holiday tax incentives for shopping and domestic tourism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber has announced the launch of the Dubai Smartpreneur Competition for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, working with the Smart Dubai Office, launched the second annual Dubai Smartpreneur Competition. This aligns with the vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, to make Dubai a leading smart city.
Source: Dubai Chamber. The event featured a panel discussion about the UAE government&amp;rsquo;s progress on smart city and innovation initiatives, and what will drive future sustainable growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, a settlement network powered by blockchain announced that it would waive fees for transfers to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</guid><description>OKLink, a global settlement platform, has introduced the first entirely free remittance corridor. The company stated that transfers up to US$100,000 each month to Singapore will be free throughout 2017.
Previously, OKLink applied a 0.1% fee on cross-border payments to Singapore, while other companies might charge up to US$5 per transaction.
&amp;ldquo;As the world&amp;rsquo;s largest blockchain-powered global settlement network, we can process cross-border payments faster and more affordably as more partners join,&amp;rdquo; explained Jack Liu, Chief Strategy Officer at OKLink...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Al Ain Cultural Programme for 2017/2018 is currently in full swing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</guid><description>The Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi recently held three events showcasing Emirati culture and heritage as part of the annual Al Ain Cultural Programme.
On October 19th, Qasr Al Muwaiji (Al Muwaiji Palace) hosted the Bisht Workshop, which delved into the history of the traditional garment worn by UAE rulers and the unique patterns associated with each ruler. Attendees also participated in a hands-on workshop, learning to create their own bisht...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Delicious Medallions from Swensen's</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</guid><description>Swensen&amp;rsquo;s is offering early bird discounts on their chocolate-covered Sweet Medallions mooncakes until September 20th, 2017.
The mooncakes are available in a variety of flavors like cookies &amp;rsquo;n cream surprise, durian royale, Rocher crunch, and sticky chewy chocolate.
Source: Swensen&amp;rsquo;s website. Four chocolate-covered flavours are on offer in Swensen&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017. Place your order to take advantage of the 20% early bird discount available to Swensen&amp;rsquo;s Cool Rewards and Kids&amp;rsquo; Club members...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Hong Kong offers a plethora of high-end gift options. Make a lasting impression with these distinctive incentive or corporate gift suggestions:
For the Fashionable
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjTOBGQGtqMhlt_i0m3XHwBn1QjO906znU9xMy97VBPqWBHVy80nBxjOKm1Lgg1I_v5sIp6sxy7HGCTZRC2xSpXTAGFdVOIKDSwZQes3MFguk5NpzGOVFh1lp4vHGEYKbE_CzRPC6l2PblW/s1600/chandelier+earrings.JPG)
Source: The 5th C. My 5-Ways chandelier earrings.
The 5th C, a Hong Kong-based diamond consultancy and jewelry brand, presents My 5-Ways, a completely customizable pair of diamond earrings. At their core, My 5-Ways are elegant stud earrings. However, with a few simple adjustments, they transform into studs with drops, elegant dangle earrings, or eye-catching chandelier earrings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emojis are sweeping the world by storm 🌩</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/</guid><description>On July 17, in honor of World Emoji Day, App Annie wanted to learn more about the world&amp;rsquo;s love for emojis. They teamed up with Leanplum to publish a report called &amp;ldquo;Winning App ❤ (&amp;amp; 💸 ) With Emojis&amp;rdquo; which explores mobile marketing trends.
The report highlights some interesting findings, including the fact that the word &amp;ldquo;emoji&amp;rdquo; is now officially in the Oxford Dictionary. Additionally:
The use of emojis grew significantly in 2016, increasing by 163%, and the range of emojis used by marketers also expanded by 10%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zhaopin reveals changes in the entry-level job market in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</guid><description>Zhaopin, a Chinese career platform that connects users with job opportunities, conducted a 2017 career survey of college graduates in China, revealing notable trends. The survey indicated that graduates faced a more challenging job market and lower average salaries, presenting a difficult situation for the 7.95 million graduates entering the workforce.
2017 Labor Market for College Graduates Difficult and very challenging: 40.8% Difficult, but acceptable: 47.0% The market was OK: 9...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017 award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</guid><description>Employee engagement at companies recognized as Aon Best Employers rose by two percentage points this year, reaching 82%.
Aon Best Employers are setting the standard for positive employer branding, achieving scores from 83% to 92% in employee perception across all levels of tenure.
Five special recognitions were given this year, including the introduction of a new award category: Best Employer for Startups.
Source: Aon. Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The amount of money given as gifts for Chinese New Year in 2017 was calculated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</guid><description>Source: Gift Something blog post. Survey results for monetary gifts during Chinese New Year in Hong Kong. Values are in Hong Kong dollars.
Gift Something, a Hong Kong-based online retailer specializing in premium gifts, conducted a survey to understand the practice of giving red envelopes (known as angpow or red packets in Singapore, and lai see or red pockets in Hong Kong) during Chinese New Year. Traditionally, married couples give these envelopes to unmarried individuals during the first 15 days of the Lunar New Year to bring luck...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anticipate more sustainable and environmentally-friendly buildings in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Building and Construction Authority (BCA) announced new initiatives during the opening ceremony of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW). These initiatives, stemming from a review of the third Green Building Masterplan, focus on improving occupant indoor environmental quality, promoting energy-efficient buildings, and incorporating green practices into existing structures.
Desmond Lee, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Social and Family Development and Second Minister for National Development, was the guest of honor at the ceremony...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with the One Lagi Best Deal!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</guid><description>Source: One Faber Group. Cable car visual.
In honor of Singapore’s 52nd birthday, One Faber Group is offering the One Lagi Best Deal, featuring local promotions on its leisure activities and services from Faber Peak Singapore to Sentosa Island.
Until September 17th, Singaporeans* can take advantage of a special offer: a S$52 bundle for adults and a S$42 bundle for children. The adult bundle includes a round-trip Singapore cable car ride, a standard ticket to the Wings Of Time show, a standard ticket to Sentosa Merlion, a three-course meal at the Good Old Days restaurant, and a batik orchid magnet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Philippines' economic outlook has improved according to the World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</guid><description>The World Bank has improved its economic forecast for the Philippines from 2016 to 2018.
They now predict the Philippine economy will grow by 6.8% in 2016, up from their previous prediction of 6.4% made in October (World Bank Philippines Economic Update October 2016). This adjustment is based on stronger than expected growth in the third quarter of 2016, fueled by increased investment and private consumption. This follows robust economic performance in the first half of 2016, driven by the government’s pre-election spending...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Founders' Friday session in Singapore by Huawei will showcase Scott Bales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</guid><description>Source: Scott Bales website.
Huawei is launching a new networking series called Founders&amp;rsquo; Friday. The series aims to connect business leaders with professionals to exchange ideas, address difficulties, and develop innovative solutions for advancing the digital world.
The inaugural event, presented alongside the HUAWEI Mate 9, features prominent digital and innovation expert Scott Bales. He will discuss essential principles for fostering a culture of innovation within organizations. Bales, the Managing Director of Singapore-based Innovation Labs Asia, brings over a decade of global experience in innovation, thought leadership, implementation planning, and strategy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IPO activity in Singapore is expected to exceed that of 2016 in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</guid><description>During the first half of 2017, Singapore saw a surge in initial public offerings (IPOs), attracting US$329 million in investments, as reported by PwC Singapore. This momentum is projected to continue, potentially exceeding the total funds raised in 2016. Professional services are emerging as a leading sector, with HRnetGroup and Shopper360&amp;rsquo;s IPOs securing a combined US$134 million, a significant leap from the previous year.
While Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) and business trusts, a traditional strength for the Singapore Exchange (SGX), constituted 33% of IPO proceeds, the anticipated listing of NetLink Trust, estimated at US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival showcases performances by exceptionally talented artists with disabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</guid><description>The True Colours Festival, showcasing talented performing artists with disabilities from the Asia Pacific region, will run from March 22nd to 25th, 2018 in Singapore.
The festival will feature up to 20 artist/troupe performances representing Japan, China, India, Korea, Malaysia, Cambodia, Kazakhstan, New Zealand, Australia, and Singapore. Guest artists from the UK and Canada will also be featured. Performances will take place at a multimedia concert experience inside the Singapore Indoor Stadium and at the nearby True Colours Festival Village...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business sentiment in Singapore for 2017 is characterized by caution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</guid><description>The Singapore government has released business sentiment data for 2017, covering both the manufacturing and retail sectors.
In the manufacturing sector, a survey conducted by the Singapore Economic Development Board revealed that a weighted 76% of firms expect business conditions in the first half of 2017 to remain similar to the previous quarter. While 13% anticipate improvement, 11% foresee a decline. Overall, the net weighted balance sits at 2%, indicating a slightly positive outlook for the manufacturing sector in early 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jane's Walk is back in Singapore for its fifth year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 22:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore Peatix website. Aerial view of Queenstown.
Now in its fifth year, Jane’s Walk Singapore is hosting a weekend of free walking tours throughout the city.
Inspired by urbanist, author, and activist Jane Jacobs, Jane’s Walk is a series of free, volunteer-led walking tours. Jacobs advocated for walkable, lively neighborhoods and encouraged community involvement in urban development. Her most renowned work, The Death and Life of Great American Cities, emphasizes the importance of observation, inquiry, and exploration in understanding cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF has finished its 2017 Article IV consultation with Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its regular economic review of Vietnam, finding that the country&amp;rsquo;s economy remains in good shape, supported by strong underlying economic conditions. Despite a slowdown in 2016 to 6.2% growth due to agricultural challenges from drought and saltwater intrusion, as well as reduced oil production, Vietnam’s economy has shown resilience.
While the oil sector continued to struggle in early 2017, strong manufacturing and foreign direct investment, healthy domestic demand, and a resurgence in agriculture are driving overall economic momentum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap reveals video predictions for each Chinese zodiac animal for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Joey Yap, founder and CEO of the Mastery Academy of Chinese Metaphysics and Chief Consultant of the Joey Yap Consulting Group, created 12 videos outlining the year ahead for the 12 Chinese zodiac animal signs in areas such as career, relationships, business, and health.
The videos are in English and include traditional Chinese subtitles.
The year of the fire rooster starts on January 28, 2017. Yap considers the rooster one of the luckiest animals in 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Winners of the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Awards are influential figures in promoting knowledge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 01:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. A representative from the MiSK Foundation receives the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award.
The Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award recipients, celebrated on November 21st, share a common goal: shaping the future. This award acknowledges those who significantly contribute to the creation and dissemination of knowledge globally.
Among the winners, Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s MiSK Foundation focuses on developing educational institutions and bolstering scientific research...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways is the designated airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</guid><description>The image showcases young people at work, sourced from the WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017 website.
Etihad Airways is the official airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017, a major international event focusing on vocational education and skills excellence. Taking place at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) from October 14th to 17th, 2017, the event will host over 3,000 participants and experts representing approximately 75 countries.
WorldSkills encompasses a variety of industries, from construction and creative fields like arts and fashion to technology, manufacturing, engineering, social services, and transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you have digital or tech skills, chances are your salary is above average</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</guid><description>Source: Willis Towers Watson. Report cover.
The financial sector, particularly in digital roles, is experiencing salary stability due to a high demand for tech professionals. This trend persists despite overall economic weakness in other industries, including banking, according to the global advisory firm Willis Towers Watson.
Businesses across all sectors are becoming progressively reliant on data and technology, and the banking industry is no exception. This shift has resulted in a talent competition where technological expertise is more valuable than financial background...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience cutting-edge VR gaming at Bugis Junction and Bugis+, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</guid><description>This Halloween, shoppers at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bugis Junction and Bugis+ malls can participate in an immersive virtual reality (VR) gaming experience. This event marks the first time malls in Singapore have hosted a VR experience of this magnitude.
The &amp;ldquo;Time Zombies&amp;rdquo; competition invites shoppers to assume the roles of time-traveling detectives. Their mission: to stop the nefarious Dr. Virago, a mad scientist attempting to unleash a zombie apocalypse. This competition utilizes cutting-edge Arctic Fox wireless technology, allowing players to move freely within the virtual world using a wireless headset, eliminating the need for cumbersome cables or backpack computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Promotions for Dell at CEE 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</guid><description>Dell is promoting several products at the Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) 2017. These products, equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors, are designed for an excellent visual experience and enhanced gameplay.
Here are some of the featured products:
Inspiron 13 5000 2-in-1
Original Price: Starting from S$1,699 Show Price: Starting from S$1,299 Features:
Latest 7th Gen Intel Core processor 13.3&amp;quot; FHD (1,920 x 1,080) IPS Truelife LED-backlit touchscreen with wide viewing angles and an infrared (IR) camera Four versatile modes: tent, stand, laptop, and tablet XPS 13 2-in-1..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bakerzin introduces seven new mooncake collections for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:24:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</guid><description>Bakerzin has introduced its Creme de la Creme mooncake assortment, featuring handcrafted mooncakes made with low-sugar white lotus paste. The collection includes seven distinct lines, available in both traditional baked and snow skin varieties.
[Image of Bakerzin&amp;rsquo;s 2017 mooncake collection]
Source: Bakerzin Facebook page. Bakerzin&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017.
The Bold Collection showcases baked mooncakes with unique flavors such as American ginseng, ginger, tom yam, and sakura ebi.
The Signature Collection features the return of their popular premium egg yolk blend baked mooncake...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in celebrating at Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong and Macau are celebrating this December with special holiday menus.
An American feast at Grand Central
Source: Eclipse Hospitality Group. Cardamom spiced snapper fillet combined with winter squash, asparagus and lemongrass broth.
Grand Central, situated on the roof of the Elements shopping mall, is offering three-course dinners for HK$368 and four-course dinners for HK$398. Start with roasted sweet potato soup or roasted beets with blue cheese mousse, poached pears, and pistachios...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new LVL UP plan tailored for young people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The LVL UP plan is targeted at youths.
Singtel introduced a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;LVL UP&amp;rdquo; for young adults, coinciding with the start of The PC Show 2017. The name, inspired by the gaming term &amp;ldquo;level up,&amp;rdquo; signifies advancement to higher levels of difficulty in games. This plan provides free upgrades for Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Youth Combo plans and additional data.
This plan, available to students and full-time National Servicemen aged 26 and under, offers close to S$600 in savings over two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Would you like to try a mooncake with osmanthus and white lotus?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</guid><description>For the Mid-Autumn Festival, Hilton Hotel offers a variety of classic baked and contemporary mini snowskin mooncakes.
Baked mooncake choices include white lotus paste, traditional mixed nuts, green tea walnut, and a new osmanthus white lotus flavor. Caramel cheese, lychee chocolate truffle, D24 durian, and black sesame with hazelnut praline are among the snowskin varieties.
Interested?
For a closer look at the selection, view the Hilton mooncake collection brochure (PDF). Mooncakes are available from September 4th to October 4th, 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park introduces new fruit-infused mooncake flavors to its 2017 lineup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 21:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</guid><description>This mid-autumn, Goodwood Park Hotel is excited to present a selection of new and unique snowskin mooncake flavors. Among the new offerings is the blush pink prickly pear with bergamot snowskin mooncake. This confection features the sweet and succulent fruit of a cactus, complemented by a citrusy bergamot flavor and the crunch of diced pears.
Goodwood Park Hotel will also be bringing back popular snowskin favorites. These include premium durian and tropical fruit varieties alongside traditional baked mooncakes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment commitments in Singapore remain in a positive trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</guid><description>Global companies continued to view Singapore as a crucial base in Asia for expansion and innovation in 2016, with investment commitments meeting or exceeding the Economic Development Board (EDB)&amp;rsquo;s projections. The EDB remains committed to pursuing opportunities in thriving sectors to foster sustained economic growth and create quality employment prospects for Singaporeans.
Attracting S$9.4 billion in fixed asset investments, Singapore exceeded its forecast of S$8 billion to S$10 billion. Total business expenditure reached S$8...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels will be introducing a Gourmet Food &amp; Wine Festival in Singapore in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Jaan was awarded a Michelin Star in the Singapore Michelin Guide 2016 and secured the 29th spot in Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2016.
AccorHotels, the leading hotel operator in the country, is launching its first-ever Gourmet Food &amp;amp; Wine Festival, anticipated to be one of the most extensive events of its kind in Singapore.
The festival will feature several Michelin-starred chefs. Graham Wilson, Chief Marketing &amp;amp; Distribution Officer for AccorHotels Asia Pacific, stated, “In a city celebrated for its culinary scene, AccorHotels will bring together some of our finest chefs from around the world and showcase the immense talent of Singaporean chefs to create a food festival as lively and diverse as Singapore itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dream Collective is empowering potential female leaders in Singapore with their first-ever bootcamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</guid><description>Source: The Dream Collective.
The Dream Collective, a global platform for training women in corporate leadership, has introduced the Emerging Leaders Bootcamp - Singapore Edition. This program offers a new approach to female empowerment and initiates a crucial conversation about developing female leadership talent in the corporate world. Modeled after MBA programs from top business schools, the program collaborates with major corporations to find, develop, and empower high-potential young women with leadership skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New sites have been added to the World Heritage List for 2017 by the World Heritage Committee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sites-have-been-added-to-the-world-heritage-list-for-2017-by-the-world-heritage-committee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sites-have-been-added-to-the-world-heritage-list-for-2017-by-the-world-heritage-committee/</guid><description>Source: UNESCO. Kulangsu: a Historic International Settlement, China. © Cultural Heritage Conservation Center of THAD / Qian Yi | Image Source: Nomination File (Update).
The World Heritage Committee designated 21 new locations to UNESCO’s World Heritage List in 2017. Additionally, the boundaries of five existing sites were expanded or adjusted. These additions bring the total number of sites on the World Heritage List to 1,073.
The Asia Pacific region saw the addition of these new natural sites:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sites-have-been-added-to-the-world-heritage-list-for-2017-by-the-world-heritage-committee/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sites-have-been-added-to-the-world-heritage-list-for-2017-by-the-world-heritage-committee/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF predicts a positive outcome for Pakistan's economic growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</guid><description>The IMF Executive Board finalized its regular economic assessment of Pakistan on June 14, 2017.
The IMF determined that Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic outlook is positive, with real GDP expected to reach 5.3% in FY2016/17 and rise to 6% in the medium term. This growth is attributed to increased investments from the China Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), greater energy availability, and structural reforms that support economic expansion. While inflation has gradually risen, the IMF team stated it remains manageable, and the financial sector is stable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Airport introduces a new reward for the Be a Changi Millionaire campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 03:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. This year&amp;rsquo;s Be a Changi Millionaire competition offers a chance to win a Volvo sedan as well.
Changi Airport has enhanced its well-known *Be a Changi Millionaire*_ retail promotion this year by adding a new prize: a Volvo S90 T5 luxury sedan. This is in addition to the existing S$1 million cash prize. According to Changi Airport, this is the largest retail promotion at any airport globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating new ideas in environmentally friendly buildings and construction areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</guid><description>Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier trade show for green building solutions, has commenced at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre. The event is anticipated to draw visitors from over 50 nations, all eager to witness the latest advancements in Asian green building, HVAC-R (heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, and refrigeration), water, energy, and heating technologies.
BEX Asia, which runs until September 14, 2017, is held in conjunction with Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional trade show specializing in energy-efficient solutions for industrial, commercial, and residential structures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has modified its regulations for the protection of designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Law (MinLaw) has introduced the Registered Designs (Amendment) Bill to Parliament for its first reading. The bill aims to modernize Singapore&amp;rsquo;s design protection laws by reflecting current design and technology developments. It seeks to foster growth in the design sector by streamlining the process for designers to safeguard their creations.
This bill stems from a joint review of Singapore’s registered designs system by MinLaw and the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore (IPOS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers from Singapore have a strong affinity for Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</guid><description>Source: KAYAK. Tokyo skyline.
The travel search platform, KAYAK, has identified the top five destinations Singaporeans are traveling to for the Chinese New Year (CNY) holiday. The Year of the Rooster begins with a long weekend that starts on Saturday, January 28th, and ends on Monday, January 30th, 2017.
The most popular travel destination for Singaporeans between January 28th and February 5th is Bangkok, Thailand. Tokyo, Japan, and Manila in the Philippines are the second and third most popular destinations, respectively:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Festive takeaways and buffets at Hotel Jen Tanglin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 06:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</guid><description>Hotel Jen Tanglin&amp;rsquo;s popular &amp;ldquo;Fully-Loaded&amp;rdquo; holiday takeaway meal is back. This offering features a whole roasted turkey, accompanied by all the fixings, conveniently packaged in a thermal bag. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to easily serve 10 to 12 guests.
According to Vathsala Subramaniam, General Manager of Hotel Jen Tanglin Singapore, they&amp;rsquo;ve crafted a special Asian roasted turkey using the &amp;ldquo;percik&amp;rdquo; style. This approach aims to blend tradition with a distinct Asian flavor. For those with bigger parties, ordering both the Western and Asian style turkeys ensures a diverse culinary experience for everyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get your hands on StarHub's flyers for CEE 2017 by downloading them now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</guid><description>Source: StarHub.
StarHub, recognized as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s most environmentally friendly telecommunications company, will participate in the 2017 Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE).
Details about StarHub&amp;rsquo;s mobile, television, broadband, and bundled services are available in online promotional flyers. These flyers, which include information about the Business Fibre Broadband Bundle, are specifically designed for business customers.
The 2017 CEE will take place at Suntec from June 1st to June 4th. The event will be open from 11 am to 9 pm on levels 1 and 3, and from 12 pm to 9 pm in Halls 403 to 406 on level 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AkzoNobel has chosen Denim Drift as the Color of the Year for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 02:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</guid><description>Source: AkzoNobel. From left: Farhan Akhtar, Dulux Brand Ambassador; Rajiv Rajgopal, Director of Decorative Paints, AkzoNobel South Asia Cluster; Jeremy Rowe, Managing Director of AkzoNobel Decorative Paints, South East &amp;amp; South Asia, Middle East; and Shraddha Kapoor, Dulux Brand Ambassador, revealed Denim Drift as the Colour of the Year for 2017.
AkzoNobel, a global paints and coatings company, specialty chemicals producer, and the manufacturer of Dulux paints in India, has announced Denim Drift as the Colour of the Year for 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Concorde Hotel Singapore is introducing mooncake gift sets in elegant mirror chests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 06:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website. Mooncakes from the Concorde Hotel will come in LED mirror chests.
The Concorde Hotel in Singapore is known for its unique mooncake packaging, and this year is no exception. This year, the mooncakes will be presented in a special LED mirror chest that lights up when opened.
Customers can choose from a variety of mooncake flavors, including bamboo charcoal with red dragon fruit and black sesame, golden jade lotus with a single yolk, pure lotus, white lotus, pure lotus with a single yolk, and white lotus with a single yolk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify celebrates the year of the rooster with a fresh playlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Welcoming the lunar new year.
To celebrate the Lunar New Year on January 28th, Spotify has launched a special playlist. This playlist features popular songs by artists born in the Year of the Rooster.
Interested?
Check out Spotify&amp;rsquo;s 恭賀新年 (welcoming the new year) playlist..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2017 Budget is on handling uncertainty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Budget website. View of Singapore.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2017 aimed to prepare the nation for the future amidst significant global economic shifts, presenting both obstacles and prospects. Finance Minister Heng Swee Keat stressed the need for companies and workers to develop robust adaptability to navigate these changing economic structures and technologies. He highlighted that digitalization, innovation, and a highly skilled workforce are key for cities and regions to thrive while maintaining global openness and connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Foh San provides mooncake corporate orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</guid><description>Foh San, a restaurant originally known for its dim sum, has become a popular provider of both dim sum and mooncakes. They offer a diverse selection of halal mooncakes, with both baked and non-baked options available. Customers can purchase these mooncakes in elegant presentation boxes designed to hold either two or four mooncakes. Additionally, there is a premium box option which includes four mooncakes and a special gaharu (agarwood or oud) tea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In August, an innovation event will be held in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</guid><description>The second one-north Festival, a celebration of research, innovation, creativity, and enterprise, will take place on August 18th and 19th, 2017, at Biopolis in Singapore.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOAcpbDhuBLMHwpNFri5j6kbRVLkScIKw4TiGhwymXBdx3y6jgeTVWIOLN9OP71ghrtTERYqlpvKkMaup28rURdUpbA6fK2EH9AWxwQi-iB9M-tHLvfmrD43zz1zcSGOThoKLcuV0Yd6k/s1600/20170720_125101.jpg)
This advertisement for the one-north Festival was seen at Raffles station.
Organized by A*STAR and JTC, the festival&amp;rsquo;s theme, Pioneering an Innovation Future, centers around future health, living, and work. This year&amp;rsquo;s festival will incorporate Science Centre Singapore&amp;rsquo;s X-periment!, showcasing cutting-edge health innovations.
Highlighting the collaborative spirit of the one-north community, the festival showcases how partnerships between research performers and industry partners drive advancements in research, innovation, and enterprise, benefiting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy and enhancing lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Gadget Gift Guide for Christmas 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</guid><description>As 2017 comes to a close, treat yourself to a range of exciting new gadgets! WorkSmart Asia presents its top picks for this year, featuring:
Limited Edition Star Wars Shavers Source: Philips Singapore. Philips limited edition shavers, inspired by Star Wars. From left: the Poe Dameron-inspired Philips _Star Wars _Shaver SW6700/14; the BB-8-inspired SW5700/07 and the Stormtrooper-inspired SW170/04.
Philips introduces a new line of limited-edition shavers inspired by iconic Star Wars characters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bayara excels in creating engaging digital activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</guid><description>Bayara, a Middle Eastern brand famous for dried fruits, nuts, and spices, hosted a unique iftar (Ramadan fast-breaking meal) at The Oberoi in Dubai. The buffet featured recipes submitted by their social media followers.
Source: Bayara. Jean-Marc Lourau, CEO of Bayara, congratulated the winners whose dishes were featured at the buffet and also shared the progress that Bayara has made over the last 25 years that they have been in the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The MICE industry in KSA is expanding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</guid><description>In 2017, Saudi Arabia held more than 10,129 business events that were approved by the Saudi Exhibition and Convention Bureau (SECB), reflecting a 16% rise from the previous year.
The healthcare, education, technical, and communications industries made up the largest portion of business events within the 22 targeted economic sectors in 2017. The Riyadh region hosted 47% of these events, claiming the most business activity for the year. Following Riyadh, the Makkah region held 32% of events and the Eastern Province hosted 17%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore Computer Society reveals the top 10 tech companies to work for in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</guid><description>The Singapore Computer Society (SCS), the largest professional organization for infocomm and digital media professionals in the country, has revealed the winners of its &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Company to Work For Award&amp;rdquo;. The announcement took place at the SCS&amp;rsquo;s annual Tech3 Forum conference.
This award recognizes four organizations out of the ten &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Companies to Work For&amp;rdquo; as overall winners. These companies have developed innovative practices and demonstrated workplace excellence within the infocomm and digital media (ICM) industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks' festive beverages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/</guid><description>An advertisement for Starbucks&amp;rsquo; holiday beverages at a train station in Singapore.
Starbucks has launched its holiday drink menu in participating stores globally. Some of the drinks available in the Asia Pacific region include:
Teavana Apple Joyful Medley Tea
This new Christmas beverage features a blend of black, oolong, and jasmine green teas, combined with apple juice and topped with cinnamon foam. It&amp;rsquo;s available hot or iced.
Christmas Panettone Latte..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Employees in Singapore are seeking opportunities for career advancement and a positive work environment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employees-in-singapore-are-seeking-opportunities-for-career-advancement-and-a-positive-work-environment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 23:09:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employees-in-singapore-are-seeking-opportunities-for-career-advancement-and-a-positive-work-environment/</guid><description>Source: CareerBuilder Singapore. The attributes of an Employer of Choice.
A 2017 survey by CareerBuilder Singapore reveals that simply offering a competitive salary isn&amp;rsquo;t enough to attract and keep talented employees. The study, titled Employer of Choice Survey* 2017, showed that Singaporean workers prioritize strong career growth prospects and an inclusive work environment over financial compensation when selecting an ideal employer.
Source: CareerBuilder Singapore. What an ideal job looks like...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employees-in-singapore-are-seeking-opportunities-for-career-advancement-and-a-positive-work-environment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employees-in-singapore-are-seeking-opportunities-for-career-advancement-and-a-positive-work-environment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Robert Half suggests diversifying incentives in order to retain talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 08:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/</guid><description>A significant portion of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s workforce prioritizes work-life balance over higher salaries, according to a recent study.
The Robert Half 2017 Salary Guide highlights that 69% of Singaporean employees are driven by more than just monetary compensation. The study reveals that nearly half (43%) would accept lower pay for flexible work hours, while over a third (37%) would choose the ability to work remotely over a pay raise.
Non-financial benefits are highly valued by Singaporean workers, with 28% willing to trade a portion of their salary for increased medical benefits and 20% favoring more vacation time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp; Spa is offering meeting packages for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa. Executive team members at Hyatt Regegncy Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa will help event planners make any meeting a success.
Located on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Hoi An coastline and close to Danang, the Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa has announced new meeting packages for 2017.
The resort offers a wide range of event and meeting spaces, both indoors and outdoors on the beachfront. These venues can accommodate up to 250 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An open house event was held at Changi Airport's fourth terminal before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: CAG. CAG organises open house for Changi T4.
The Changi Airport Group (CAG) has invited Singapore residents to preview Terminal 4 (T4) before its official opening. From August 7th to 20th, 2017, the public can attend an Open House for a sneak peek of the new terminal.
Construction on the 195,000 square meter, two-story T4 began in early 2013 and finished in December 2016. Though only half the size of Terminal 3 (T3), it can accommodate 16 million passengers annually, roughly 70% of T3&amp;rsquo;s capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IIA addresses the challenges of internal auditing in the digital era</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fifth yearly Public Sector Internal Audit (PSIA) Conference, themed Rising to the Challenges of the Future, centered on economic shifts and transformations.
The Institute of Internal Auditors (IIA), organizer of the PSIA, emphasized that organizations face mounting hurdles in our increasingly digital world, including cybercrime and technological disruptions. Consequently, internal audits are even more critical for strong governance in both public and private sectors.
To maintain effective and independent assurance, internal auditors must embrace innovation and acquire new skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Everything is going well at PARKROYAL on Beach Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</guid><description>Beginning January 16, 2017, PARKROYAL on Beach Road will be offering a new take on Lunar New Year celebrations as Executive Chef Ken Ang introduces his culinary perspective to the dishes at Plaza Brasserie, their all-day dining restaurant.
Known for his mastery of traditional Cantonese roasting methods, Executive Chef Ang will be presenting his version of the lucky facai yusheng (发财鱼生, also called lohei), enhanced with additions like crispy salmon and chicken skin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Purchase the "liusha" flavored mooncakes from VLV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-the-liusha-flavored-mooncakes-from-vlv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-the-liusha-flavored-mooncakes-from-vlv/</guid><description>VLV, a multifaceted venue featuring a modern Chinese restaurant, lounge, entertainment courtyard, and riverfront dining, has introduced its mooncake selection for 2017.
The collection showcases two flavors: the lotus paste with salted egg custard liusha mooncake and the white lotus paste black sesame liusha mooncake.
Drawing inspiration from VLV&amp;rsquo;s popular salted egg charcoal bun, Executive Chef Martin Foo has crafted a mooncake version. The lotus paste with salted egg custard liusha mooncake boasts a savory pastry and a smooth lotus paste filling surrounding a creamy, flowing salted egg custard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-the-liusha-flavored-mooncakes-from-vlv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-the-liusha-flavored-mooncakes-from-vlv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangkok is the top tourist destination in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Mastercard. Report cover.
Although Bangkok, Thailand remains the top spot for visitors in the Asia Pacific, the latest Mastercard Asia Pacific Destinations Index 2017* shows that Singapore outpaces the Thai capital in total tourist spending.
Singapore experienced an 18% increase in visitor spending between 2015 and 2016. As one of just five destinations in the top 20 for overall expenditure to hit a minimum daily spend of US$200, Singapore drew in the biggest spenders at US$254 per day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vacationing at Black Sheep Restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Elevate your holiday celebrations with the Black Sheep Restaurants group in Hong Kong:
Carbone
This New York-Italian establishment will be serving up generous portions of classics, like their 40oz Prime Porterhouse with a rosemary infusion. For a luxurious New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, enjoy an early dinner (6pm-8:45pm) or partake in The Fiasco, a mobster-themed dinner theater experience from 9pm-1am (HK$1,500).
Details:
Carbone is located at 9/F, LKF Tower, 33 Wyndham St, Central, Hong Kong..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Double 12 Global Shopping Festival aims to attract Alipay users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 09:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</guid><description>Source: Alipay Facebook page. Flag advertising the Double 12 Global Shopping Festival.
Alipay, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading online and mobile payment and lifestyle platform operated by Ant Financial Services Group, launched its 2017 Double 12 Global Shopping Festival in Southeast Asia. The festival includes Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, and the Philippines.
Double 12 is a global event spanning 15 countries and territories across four continents. Over 500 brands and 100,000 merchants worldwide participate, offering Alipay users exclusive promotions throughout December...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big discounts on Honda vehicles in the UAE during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Honda cars are on Ramadan offer in the UAE.
This Ramadan, Al-Futtaim Honda, the exclusive distributor of Honda vehicles, motorcycles, marine engines, and power products in the UAE, is offering reduced starting prices and complimentary service and warranty coverage across their car lineup. Ramadan is typically a popular time for purchasing new vehicles in the GCC region, and various brands offer promotions during this period.
Honda Civic..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian cities have been rearranged in Mercer's Cost of Living Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</guid><description>Five Asian cities—Hong Kong (ranked 2nd), Tokyo (3rd), Singapore (5th), Seoul (6th), and Shanghai (8th)—were named among the top 10 most expensive cities for expatriates in this year&amp;rsquo;s ranking.
Currency fluctuations played a significant role in shaping the rankings of most Asian cities.
While all mainland Chinese cities surveyed experienced a drop in ranking, Tianjin (12th) stood out as an exception, climbing 18 positions.
Mumbai, India made a remarkable jump of 25 places this year, attributed to robust economic growth, inflation, and a stable currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The carnival at People's Park Complex will feature opera performances, games, and information on cashless services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</guid><description>Zhongguo Remittance and the management of People&amp;rsquo;s Park Complex in Singapore are collaborating on a free event at the mall from August 25th to 27th, 2017.
Attendees can enjoy daily Chinese opera performances at noon, participate in stage games and a shop hunt, and try their luck in lucky draws for prizes. Food sampling will be available, alongside retail booths and demonstrations of CCPay&amp;rsquo;s cashless services, including remittance options through Zhongguo Remittance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Haenyeo Singapore visually captures the story of Jeju's female divers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. HAENYO SINGAPORE will be exhibited in Singapore until November 23rd.
Jose Jeuland, a French photographer based in Singapore, is presenting his debut photography exhibition. This exhibition, hosted at The Fullerton Hotel in Singapore, focuses on haenyo (해녀) - female divers from Jeju Island in South Korea. Epson Singapore, the official print sponsor for the exhibition, provided prints produced on one of their commercial and industrial photographic production printers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore companies are considering hiring senior technology professionals to address the shortage of talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</guid><description>Despite job market growth, a 2017 survey by the Singapore Infocomm Technology Federation (SiTF) reveals that the infocommunications (ICM) industry struggles to find talent with the right IT and business skills.
The survey of 181 companies found that 75% consider recruiting suitable talent their biggest challenge. This problem particularly affects startups (91%), followed by small and medium enterprises (SMEs) at 76% and multinational corporations (MNCs) at 75%.
Source: SITF. The talent situation in Singapore for ICM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia has announced the release of its 2017 budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s King Salman bin Abdulaziz recently announced the nation&amp;rsquo;s budget for 2017. The budget is set at SAR890 billion, representing an 8% rise from the previous year. It is anticipated to significantly reduce the kingdom&amp;rsquo;s deficit by a historic 33%.
King Salman emphasized the strength and resilience of the Saudi economy, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our economy is firm and it has sufficient strength to cope with the current economic and financial challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/</guid><description>As the holiday season approaches, it&amp;rsquo;s time to search for unique gifts for employees or clients. Here are a few ideas:
Facials
Kew Organics&amp;rsquo; Red Carpet Organic Facial presents a natural, non-surgical method for achieving a more youthful appearance. This facial utilizes non-invasive skin-firming methods to deliver a lifted, firmer, and more radiant look.
Kew Organics states that this facial, which incorporates organic botanicals from their serum line, rejuvenates the skin and firms all 57 facial muscles, resulting in revitalized, youthful skin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Businesses operating in the South China Sea region should be cautious of the Spring Dragon APT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</guid><description>Kaspersky Lab is issuing a warning about a threat actor targeting nations surrounding the South China Sea. The cybersecurity company has observed a rise in attacks since 2017 from an advanced persistent threat (APT) known as Spring Dragon (or LotusBlossom) using new and enhanced tactics.
Noushin Shabab, Senior Security Researcher at Kaspersky Lab&amp;rsquo;s Global Research &amp;amp; Analysis Team (GReAT), emphasizes the importance of vigilance, stating, &amp;ldquo;We believe Spring Dragon will continue to reappear in the Asian region, making it crucial to be familiar with its methods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an unexpected Christmas at Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel in Singapore has designed a Christmas menu featuring new versions of classic dishes, playful food presentations, and delightful surprises. These festive meals and unique takeaway options aim to make holiday celebrations even more memorable.
This year&amp;rsquo;s new gourmet takeaway options center around turkey with unique Asian flavors for savory dishes and chocolate-focused sweet treats.
Source: Goodwood Park Hotel. The 12 Treasures turkey is available for takeaways.
12 Treasures Turkey | S$268, serves eight to 10 people - New for 2017..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Glory mooncakes are available in both traditional and novelty shapes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glory-mooncakes-are-available-in-both-traditional-and-novelty-shapes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glory-mooncakes-are-available-in-both-traditional-and-novelty-shapes/</guid><description>Glory Food Products has unveiled its mid-autumn festival collection, featuring a variety of mooncakes in different sizes and shapes. The halal-certified collection includes individually packaged mini mooncakes in unique designs like bears, mice, cats, fish, the Ding Dang cartoon character, and the classic round form, ranging from S$0.50 to S$0.65. For those who prefer a traditional treat, full-sized mooncakes are also available starting at S$4.20, with fillings like lotus paste, single yolk lotus paste, and double yolk lotus paste...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glory-mooncakes-are-available-in-both-traditional-and-novelty-shapes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glory-mooncakes-are-available-in-both-traditional-and-novelty-shapes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of the 2017 Sony World Photography Awards in Singapore have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-2017-sony-world-photography-awards-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 08:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-2017-sony-world-photography-awards-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</guid><description>Lester Koh Meng Hua has been named the winner of the Singapore National Award, as part of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest photography competition.
Source: Sony. Singapore at dawn won the Singapore National Award for the Sony World Photography Awards 2017.
The photograph titled Singapore at dawn by Lester Koh Meng Hua has been chosen by the judges of the 2017 Sony World Photography Awards as the winner of the Singapore National Award...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-2017-sony-world-photography-awards-in-singapore-have-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-2017-sony-world-photography-awards-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>