<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hong Kong on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hong-kong/</link><description>Recent content in Hong Kong on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hong-kong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amber is the sole Hong Kong restaurant featured in the World's 50 Best Restaurants 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</guid><description>Source: World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants website. Dishes from Amber. Amber, located in The Landmark Mandarin Oriental hotel in Hong Kong, has secured a place on the esteemed World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list for the sixth consecutive year, achieving the ranking of 20th. Notably, Amber is the sole representative from Hong Kong to be featured on this prestigious list. The World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list, likened to the Oscars of fine dining, serves as an annual global celebration of gastronomy, acknowledging restaurants worldwide for their culinary excellence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong government confirms the schedule for releasing statistics from March to May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</guid><description>Companies interested in monitoring the Hong Kong economy can stay informed through press release schedules published by the Hong Kong government. These releases provide insights into various economic indicators.
A schedule of upcoming releases for March to May 2014 is provided below, starting with March 3rd.
March 2014
3rd: January 2014 Retail Sales Statistics
7th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Statistics on Vessels, Port Cargo, and Containers
10th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Quarterly Business Receipts Indices for Service Industries..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Now in Hong Kong, exclusive to employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</guid><description>Source: Employees Only. View of the interior.
Employees Only (EO), the speakeasy and restaurant established in downtown Manhattan in 2004, has now opened a branch in Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s vibrant nightlife area, at 19 Lan Kwai Fong, Central.
This marks the group&amp;rsquo;s fourth global location and their second in Asia, following the successful launch of EO Singapore in June 2016.
Co-founder Igor Hadzismajlovic leads this project alongside Singapore-based partners Joshua and Sarissa Rodriguez Schwartz, GM Rachel Tow, and Beverage Director Owen Gibler...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The future was examined at the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>The second day of the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong brought together over 50 prominent figures from various industries to discuss the future of living. The event, which ran until March 24th, featured experts, business leaders, and creatives sharing their insights with attendees from around the world.
With a focus on the prediction that 70% of the global population will reside in urban areas by 2050, the festival examined the implications for how we live, eat, travel, and interact with the natural world through panels and demonstrations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with TVB programming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</guid><description>Singtel TV is adding Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s TVB Jade and TVB Xing He channels to its lineup. From September 9th to October 8th, 2019, viewers can enjoy a free preview.
Singtel customers will have access to the same TVB Jade as Hong Kong viewers, featuring Cantonese dramas, variety shows, and infotainment programs.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CEO of Consumer Singapore, shared that the company is fulfilling customer requests by introducing these channels, broadening their comprehensive TV offerings and solidifying their position as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading pay-TV provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the 'Butterfly' smartphone in specific Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 to the Japanese market through KDDI. This phone, also known as the HTC Butterfly 2, will be available from various carriers, including Chunghwa Telecom in Taiwan, CSL in Hong Kong, and others in South Asia.
Source: HTC.
The new HTC Butterfly 2 simplifies daily tasks with features like HTC Sense 6, an HTC Duo Camera, and the Motion Launch sensor.
Using au carrier aggregation*, the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 offers download speeds up to 150Mbps and supports WiMAX2+...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Hong Kong offers a plethora of high-end gift options. Make a lasting impression with these distinctive incentive or corporate gift suggestions:
For the Fashionable
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjTOBGQGtqMhlt_i0m3XHwBn1QjO906znU9xMy97VBPqWBHVy80nBxjOKm1Lgg1I_v5sIp6sxy7HGCTZRC2xSpXTAGFdVOIKDSwZQes3MFguk5NpzGOVFh1lp4vHGEYKbE_CzRPC6l2PblW/s1600/chandelier+earrings.JPG)
Source: The 5th C. My 5-Ways chandelier earrings.
The 5th C, a Hong Kong-based diamond consultancy and jewelry brand, presents My 5-Ways, a completely customizable pair of diamond earrings. At their core, My 5-Ways are elegant stud earrings. However, with a few simple adjustments, they transform into studs with drops, elegant dangle earrings, or eye-catching chandelier earrings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the end of the year with eco-friendly festivities at East, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</guid><description>The environmentally conscious EAST, Hong Kong hotel is ready to celebrate the holiday season this year with special decorations and exciting events.
Continuing a tradition that began in 2014, EAST&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Village highlights creative recycling. This year, the EAST team gathered fallen logs left behind by Typhoon Mangkhut from the city streets to create unique Christmas decorations. Students from Jockey Club Sarah Roe School (JCSRS), the only school in Hong Kong offering an English curriculum for students with additional learning needs, collaborated with the EAST team on this project...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Food tours are available in Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo through Eating Adventures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</guid><description>Source: Eating Adventures website.
Eating Adventures has expanded its food tour services to Hong Kong. The company, already established as the leading provider of food tours in Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo, China, aims to provide travelers with an authentic cultural and culinary experience by guiding them through local neighborhoods.
Wai Zhou, owner of Eating Adventures Food Tours, highlights that while Hong Kong has existing food tour operators, most are not run by locals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests are now welcomed at The Murray, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Wharf Hotels. The Murray,
Hong Kong.
Wharf Hotels is pleased to announce the launch of The Murray, Hong Kong, a new Niccolo Hotel. This addition represents the group’s newest flagship Niccolo property and joins their luxury contemporary chic collection.
The Murray boasts a rich history, standing as one of eight historic landmarks protected by the Conserving Central initiative, launched by the Hong Kong government in 2013. Situated in the city’s vibrant Central district, the building has been recognized for its pioneering approach to sustainability throughout its nearly 50 years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Art Basel at the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong offers menus that are inspired by art</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong, the official hotel partner of Art Basel Hong Kong for the third consecutive year, will offer guests a range of special services this March. These include art-themed menus at the Michelin-starred restaurants Mandarin Grill + Bar and Pierre, as well as an exclusive accommodation package.
From March 11th to 17th, 2015, Chef Pierre Gagnaire of the two-Michelin-starred restaurant Pierre will present unique menus entitled &amp;ldquo;The Art of Pierre Gagnaire...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sparkle under the moonlight during an afternoon tea in Hong Kong this September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</guid><description>Source: The Langham, Hong Kong. The Twinkle in the Moonlight Afternoon Tea set.
The Langham Hotel in Hong Kong is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with a special afternoon tea inspired by Eastern flavors.
Offered throughout September at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Palm Court restaurant, the menu, created by Executive Pastry Chef David Puig, features treats like &amp;ldquo;The Moon,&amp;rdquo; a lychee and raspberry mousse cake decorated with a galaxy glaze. This dessert also includes rose essence, Sacher sponge cake, and a golden crescent moon topping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>NOBU presents Harvest in Aomori at InterContinental Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hong Kong. Steamed abalone, sea urchin shijimi dashi jelly, and cured mackerel sashimi with chrysanthemum dressing.
NOBU InterContinental Hong Kong presents the fifth installment of its GOURMET TOUR OF JAPAN series – Harvest in Aomori – which runs from September 12th to October 22nd.
Executive Chef Sean Mell and Executive Sushi Chef Arakai Kaazunari have crafted special lunch and dinner menus that showcase the fall bounty of Aomori Prefecture, a region in northern Japan&amp;rsquo;s Tōhoku region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens promotion is now available at the Grand Hyatt Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Hong Kong. Poster for the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens 2023.
To celebrate the return of the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens from March 31st to April 2nd, 2023, Grand Hyatt Hong Kong, an official supplier and package provider, is offering special deals for a complete Sevens experience.
Exclusive packages combining accommodation and Sevens tickets are available starting from HK$3,900. Options include one- or three-night stays, paired with a choice of Friday, weekend, or three-day event tickets to suit every fan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LEOCoin launches LEOxCHANGE in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: LEOxCHANGE. Andersson speaks at the launch of LEOxCHANGE in Hong Kong, emphasizing the high security of LEOCoin and its ability to protect consumer privacy.
A new digital currency has entered the market. Launched in London on March 25, 2015, LEOCoin is reportedly recognized by other digital currency exchanges and boasts the support of approximately 100,000 entrepreneurs.
The company behind LEOCoin, UK-based LEO (Learning Enterprises Organisation), provides entrepreneurship and leadership training via online tutoring, e-learning platforms, and in-person seminars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exciting pre-game activities at Shangri-La hotels before the Hong Kong Sevens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 03:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</guid><description>Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Shangri-La Group is offering rugby enthusiasts special hotel and experience packages for the Hong Kong Sevens. Fans can choose to stay at the Island Shangri-La, Kowloon Shangri-La, or Kerry Hotel, with each offering exclusive day passes to the event. Packages include pre-game accommodations and breakfast. Additional breakfast and day passes are available for a bundled price.
Source: Shangri-La Group Hong Kong. The Hong Kong Rugby Sevens.
Island Shangri-La, Hong Kong..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pottinger Hong Kong is now open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</guid><description>Sino Group, a hospitality branch of Sino Land Company, manages various properties including hotels, a yacht club, serviced apartments, and residential dining establishments. They have recently introduced The Pottinger Hong Kong, a luxurious 68-room boutique hotel. Situated on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s oldest paved street, the hotel holds a notable position on a site recognized as a Grade I historic place by the Antiquities Advisory Board of Hong Kong.
As per the Sino Group of Hotels, The Pottinger Hong Kong features 68 upscale guestrooms and suites, with sizes varying from 23 to 68 square meters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen collaborate for a flash sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 01:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</guid><description>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen have teamed up to offer the Grand Spring Voyage flash sale, featuring accommodation packages ranging from two to five nights in both cities. This convenient travel opportunity is made possible by the newly extended MTR East Rail line, which directly connects the two hotels. The journey between the nearest stations, Exhibition Centre Station in Hong Kong and Lo Wu Station in Shenzhen, is a quick 40 minutes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Foodie Tour introduces a new tour to Tai Po Market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</guid><description>Source: Hong Kong Foodie.
Hong Kong Foodie has created a food tour in Tai Po Market. This is their third food tour, and it will take people to six family-owned restaurants in Tai Po Market that serve authentic Hong Kong cuisine.
Cecilia Leung, the Founder and Director of Hong Kong Foodie, believes that Tai Po Market is the perfect location for their newest tour because it has many beloved local restaurants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in celebrating at Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong and Macau are celebrating this December with special holiday menus.
An American feast at Grand Central
Source: Eclipse Hospitality Group. Cardamom spiced snapper fillet combined with winter squash, asparagus and lemongrass broth.
Grand Central, situated on the roof of the Elements shopping mall, is offering three-course dinners for HK$368 and four-course dinners for HK$398. Start with roasted sweet potato soup or roasted beets with blue cheese mousse, poached pears, and pistachios...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-disciplinary conversations are reshaping the service economy at KODW 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Pictured at the KODW 2021 opening ceremony are (from left) Lofai Lo (Director and GM, ViuTV); Dr Lay Lian Ong (Principal, Hong Kong Design Institute &amp;amp; Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education); Victor Tsang (Head of Create Hong Kong); Professor Eric Yim (Chairman of Hong Kong Design Centre); guest of honor The Honourable Edward Yau (Secretary for Commerce and Economic Development); Victor Lo (Chairman, KODW Steering Committee of Hong Kong Design Centre); Professor Kun-Pyo Lee (Dean of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Design), and Dr Edmund Lee (Executive Director of Hong Kong Design Centre)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget provides a significant boost to the commercial sector in various ways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</guid><description>In yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Budget, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized exploring new ideas and diversity to help Hong Kong citizens achieve their goals.
He stated his commitment to utilizing resources generated by the community, supporting those in need, and promoting sustainable development to ensure that people from all sectors of society and future generations can benefit from economic growth.
The Budget outlines measures for the cultural and creative sector:
An extra HK$400 million will be allocated to the CreateSmart Initiative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Chinnery was rejuvenated at the Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong. The Chinnery.
The renowned Chinnery, located within Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Mandarin Oriental, has reopened its doors following a stylish interior update.
Originally a private gentlemen&amp;rsquo;s club, The Chinnery has been a beloved destination since 1963. Its classic British colonial design, featuring rich mahogany, plush carpets, and luxurious leather, continues to offer a peaceful escape amidst the bustling city. The overall ambiance is a perfect blend of history and enduring elegance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia, Singapore, and the UAE are among the top 10 destinations on people's relocation wishlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</guid><description>A recent report by Hydrogen Group, a global recruitment firm, reveals a growing trend of professionals seeking international work opportunities. The study found that the number of individuals open to working abroad doubled over a five-year period, rising from 16% in 2010 to 35% in 2014. Furthermore, 40% of respondents believe there are no obstacles to relocating for work.
While the US and UK were the most popular destinations, followed by Australia, Singapore ranked as the most preferred Asian country at seventh place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Business of Design Week 2021 is open to participants from all over the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Officiating guests join Business of Design Week 2021’s opening ceremony.
The 19th edition of Business of Design Week (BODW) 2021 has begun. This major Asian design, innovation, and brand event, organized annually by the Hong Kong Design Centre (HKDC) since 2002, will run for a week. The summit showcases a diverse range of speakers and television programs centered around the theme of Global Design Reset.
The event adopts a hybrid format this year, broadcast simultaneously online, on ViuTV, and at various partner venues such as the PMQ in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Angloinfo and Nexus have joined forces to launch additional expat sites in Asia through a joint venture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angloinfo-and-nexus-have-joined-forces-to-launch-additional-expat-sites-in-asia-through-a-joint-venture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angloinfo-and-nexus-have-joined-forces-to-launch-additional-expat-sites-in-asia-through-a-joint-venture/</guid><description>Source: Angloinfo&amp;rsquo;s Hong Kong portal.
Angloinfo, a global network for expats, has partnered with Nexus to establish Angloinfo Asia, a joint venture. Their first project is the Angloinfo.com/hongkong website, which has been launched gradually and is expected to be fully operational by August 2016.
The joint venture aims to introduce more localized versions of Angloinfo throughout Asia and China in the coming months, catering to the growing number of expats in these regions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angloinfo-and-nexus-have-joined-forces-to-launch-additional-expat-sites-in-asia-through-a-joint-venture/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angloinfo-and-nexus-have-joined-forces-to-launch-additional-expat-sites-in-asia-through-a-joint-venture/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong offers a winter wonderland experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:08:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</guid><description>Source: HKTB website.
With temperatures dipping below 15°C, December is an ideal time for a winter escape to Hong Kong. The ongoing 2015 Hong Kong WinterFest offers a variety of attractions and experiences for visitors.
A short walk from the Observation Wheel, where visitors can enjoy a 15-minute ride with panoramic views of Victoria Harbour and the Hong Kong skyline from luxurious gondolas, stands a dazzling, jewellery-inspired Serpenti light art installation in Statue Square, Central...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The restaurants at InterContinental Hong Kong have been awarded a combined total of three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>The 2018 Michelin Guide recognized two restaurants at the InterContinental Hong Kong, awarding a total of three Michelin stars. Yan Toh Heen, their Cantonese restaurant, earned two stars, while Rech by Alain Ducasse, a recent addition opened in March 2017, received one. Rech by Alain Ducasse is not only the hotel&amp;rsquo;s newest culinary venture but also marks the first international location of the acclaimed Parisian seafood restaurant.
Claus Pedersen, General Manager of the InterContinental Hong Kong, expressed his pride, stating that achieving these stars is a testament to the dedication and effort of their entire team...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CHKLC has announced the winners of the 2014 HK Corporate Governance Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</guid><description>The Chamber of Hong Kong Listed Companies (CHKLC) recently revealed the winners of the Hong Kong Corporate Governance Excellence Awards 2014. The CHKLC defines corporate governance as respecting shareholder rights and values, maintaining board and management integrity, and demonstrating transparency and accountability.
Dr. Eddy Fong, Judging Panel Chairman, highlighted that the awardees went beyond standard practices, tailoring their governance strategies to address industry-specific risks and challenges.
&amp;ldquo;Furthermore,&amp;rdquo; he stated, &amp;ldquo;winning companies view sustainability as inseparable from good corporate governance, crucial for long-term growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Strong job market in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>A new report by recruitment firm REED indicates that 78% of employees in Hong Kong received a pay raise in the last year. The report, titled REED 2015 Salary Survey and Market Insight, covers 14 countries across Asia, Australia, Europe, and the Middle East.
REED predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s thriving job market will continue to grow in 2015, driven by substantial foreign investments. The financial, digital marketing, e-commerce, and sales &amp;amp; marketing industries are expected to be particularly strong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fynd, the startup that offers on-demand phone repair services, is planning to expand in the Southeast Asia region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fynd-the-startup-that-offers-on-demand-phone-repair-services-is-planning-to-expand-in-the-southeast-asia-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 19:31:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fynd-the-startup-that-offers-on-demand-phone-repair-services-is-planning-to-expand-in-the-southeast-asia-region/</guid><description>Source: Fynd. The Fynd team: from left, Ian De La Cruz, CTO; Jack Leow, Chief Strategy Officer; Albert Tirtohadi, CEO; and Alex Devendran, COO.
Fynd, a Singapore-based on-demand platform for mobile device repair, has secured S$520,000 (US$385,000) in pre-Series A funding. This investment will allow the company to expedite its expansion across Southeast Asia.
Referred to as the &amp;ldquo;Uber for mobile phone repair,&amp;rdquo; Fynd has commenced operations in Hong Kong and aims to establish a presence in Jakarta by year-end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fynd-the-startup-that-offers-on-demand-phone-repair-services-is-planning-to-expand-in-the-southeast-asia-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fynd-the-startup-that-offers-on-demand-phone-repair-services-is-planning-to-expand-in-the-southeast-asia-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Residents of Hong Kong can enjoy an additional complimentary night at New World Millennium Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</guid><description>The New World Millennium Hong Kong Hotel, a prominent five-star establishment situated on the Victoria Harbour waterfront in Tsim Sha Tsui East, is offering a special &amp;ldquo;1+1 Bonus Night&amp;rdquo; room package to Hong Kong residents. Until September 30th, residents booking a one-night stay can enjoy an additional night free of charge.
This promotion is exclusively available to Hong Kong residents and requires HKID verification upon check-in. By reserving a City View room or a higher category for a single night, guests will automatically receive a second night&amp;rsquo;s stay complimentary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has launched a new mobile broadband service called DataPass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</guid><description>HP has introduced new technology designed for business travelers in the Asia Pacific region called HP DataPass.
&amp;ldquo;In today&amp;rsquo;s constantly connected, fast-moving, and virtual business world, new opportunities are emerging for businesses and individuals,&amp;rdquo; said Nick Lazaridis, Senior VP, Printing and Personal Systems, and Managing Director of HP Asia Pacific and Japan. &amp;ldquo;At HP, our focus is on developing innovations that provide the best possible customer experience while creating opportunities for our customers to transition to the New Style of IT...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines increases frequency on Hong Kong-Haikou route with two additional flights per week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</guid><description>Starting December 25th, Hong Kong Airlines will offer two more weekly flights on its route between Hong Kong and Haikou, increasing the total frequency to nine flights per week. The new flights to Haikou will operate on Fridays and Sundays.
Flight no.*
Route
Departure/Arrival time*
Frequency
HX157
Hong Kong to Haikou
19:25/20:50
Every Friday
18:15/19:45
Every Sunday
HX158
Haikou to Hong Kong
21:55/23:15
Every Friday
21:15/22:35
Every Sunday
*Flight number and schedule may change without prior notice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>YouGov's ranking of the top brands in Hong Kong for the first half of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</guid><description>In the first half of 2016, Mannings was the most talked-about brand among Hong Kong respondents, according to YouGov&amp;rsquo;s 2016 Mid-Year Best Brand Ranking for Hong Kong. Nike and Adidas secured the second and third positions, respectively. This ranking, drawn from YouGov BrandIndex data, reflects the brands generating the most positive buzz.
The leading brands across various industries in Hong Kong are:
Source: YouGov. The top 10 brands by buzz...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vacationing at Black Sheep Restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Elevate your holiday celebrations with the Black Sheep Restaurants group in Hong Kong:
Carbone
This New York-Italian establishment will be serving up generous portions of classics, like their 40oz Prime Porterhouse with a rosemary infusion. For a luxurious New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, enjoy an early dinner (6pm-8:45pm) or partake in The Fiasco, a mobster-themed dinner theater experience from 9pm-1am (HK$1,500).
Details:
Carbone is located at 9/F, LKF Tower, 33 Wyndham St, Central, Hong Kong..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia will be able to watch a Hong Kong food series on Discovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</guid><description>Discovery Channel has released a new show, Kung Food! Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Grandmasters of Cuisine. This show delves into the intricate and special world of Hong Kong cuisine from the viewpoint of Michelin-starred chefs.
Source: Discovery Channel. Chef Chaneton of Mono at a market in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong dominates Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2021 list with 11 restaurants featured. Chefs David Lai, Guillaume Galliot, Hideaki Sato, Ricardo Chaneton, Richard Ekkebus and Vicky Cheng, all recognized by Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, were chosen to discuss their passion for Hong Kong and illustrate how they craft their culinary masterpieces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong and Vistajet provide a rare and unique experience called Once in a Blue Moon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</guid><description>VistaJet, a prominent business aviation company, has partnered with the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong to create the &amp;ldquo;Once in a Blue Moon&amp;rdquo; experience. This exclusive offer celebrates the Mid-Autumn Festival with a luxurious private jet journey featuring an in-flight menu designed by Chef Wong, the Executive Chinese Chef of the Michelin-starred Man Wah restaurant at the Mandarin Oriental.
Available from September 15 to October 15, 2020, this unique offering features a customized private jet experience departing from Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia Miles has launched a new Facebook travel game specifically designed for travelers in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Asia Miles members in Hong Kong have the opportunity to win 100,000 miles this month. To participate, visit the Asia Miles Facebook page and find the post featuring travel tips for Taipei from social media influencer Ming Jai (Ming 仔).
Participants are asked to identify two Asia Miles categories that apply to Ming Jai&amp;rsquo;s itinerary. Then, they need to design an additional day of travel in Taipei with a budget of HK$5,000 or less, incorporating at least three categories for earning miles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most popular videos on YouTube in Hong Kong for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</guid><description>Content related to local news, tutorials, and parodies were the most popular on YouTube in Hong Kong this year.
A wider variety of music genres are gaining traction.
YouTube Hong Kong Rewind 2019 highlights this year&amp;rsquo;s trending videos, showcasing categories like the Top 10 Trending Videos, Top 10 Trending Local Music Videos, Top 10 Trending International Music Videos, and Top 10 Emerging Channels.
Music, in various forms like music videos, live shows, remixes, and covers, remains a favorite among Hong Kong viewers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget prioritizes innovation to capitalize on opportunities in a changing economic landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</guid><description>In his 2016-17 Budget address, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized the need for the city to adapt to a changing global economy driven by technology and the rise of emerging markets. He highlighted robotics, healthy aging, and smart city initiatives as potential areas for Hong Kong to leverage its strengths.
Tsang announced plans to promote smart production and research in the Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate, utilizing robotics and IT to advance the entire value chain, from research and development to marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental Hong Kong has become more environmentally friendly than ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</guid><description>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong is implementing environmentally friendly practices to offer guests sustainable luxury, including producing its own eco-friendly water and starting a rooftop garden.
The hotel is the first in Hong Kong to work with Nordaq FRESH, a Swedish company, to provide filtered and purified water in reusable glass bottles. This system reduces plastic waste and carbon emissions associated with traditional bottled water. Guests can also refill BPA-free bottles at the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Details of the farewell accommodation package at The Excelsior, Hong Kong are provided below</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 13:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</guid><description>To commemorate its rich history, The Excelsior, Hong Kong is offering a special &amp;ldquo;Fond Farewell Room Package&amp;rdquo; for guests to experience the hotel one last time before its closure on March 31, 2019. Guests who book this package will also be invited to a special farewell reception in the hotel lobby.
Three package options are available, each highlighting the four-star hotel&amp;rsquo;s renowned Michelin-star cuisine and its prime location on the Victoria Harbour waterfront for the past 45 years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take a look at the lineup for YouTube FanFest Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: YouTube. Poster for YouTube FanFest Hong
Kong 2018.
The Manulife-sponsored YouTube FanFest returns to Hong Kong on August 3 at the Kowloonbay International Trade &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre (KITEC).
This live event bridges the gap between prominent YouTube creators from Hong Kong and around the globe, offering a platform for fan engagement. YouTube FanFest Hong Kong will feature:
- Matt Steffanina, a US-based dancer, YouTuber, and social media figure known for his dance-centric content..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>