<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hybrid Clouds on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hybrid-clouds/</link><description>Recent content in Hybrid Clouds on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hybrid-clouds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers.</description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>