<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellphone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellphone/</link><description>Recent content in Cellphone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Craving the Motorola ZN4 Krave</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</guid><description>The Motorola Krave ZN4&amp;rsquo;s unique design, reminiscent of futuristic helmets, features a protective visor. This &amp;ldquo;touch cover&amp;rdquo; can be lifted to interact with the full touchscreen or closed to shield the display while still allowing access to essential functions like the camera, media, and messages. This design combines the appeal of both flip phones and touchscreen devices, offering a large screen ideal for media consumption and showcasing the capabilities of the phone&amp;rsquo;s 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inexpensive cellphone you recently purchased may be counterfeit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 02:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</guid><description>The global black market for counterfeit and substandard cell phones is a significant issue, costing the industry an estimated US$6 billion each year, as reported in a recent study by the Mobile Manufacturers Forum (MMF). This comprehensive analysis, &amp;ldquo;Counterfeit/Substandard Mobile Phones - A Resource Guide for Governments&amp;rdquo;, examines the prevalence of these phones across all major brands.
According to MMF Secretary General Michael Milligan, research suggests approximately 148 million counterfeit or substandard cell phones were sold in 2013 alone, primarily through established retail channels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Motorola ROKR Rocks On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</guid><description>The first iTunes phone, the Motorola ROKR, was a huge success. But instead of fading away, it has evolved into the modern ROKR E8 for T-Mobile. Is it still a great phone? You be the judge.
The sleek black design with red accents makes the Motorola ROKR E8 a striking multimedia phone. It&amp;rsquo;s actually three devices in one: a cell phone, music player, and digital camera. The touch-sensitive keypad adapts to the function you&amp;rsquo;re using...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get 300 Free Minutes With a Net10 Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-300-free-minutes-with-a-net10-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-300-free-minutes-with-a-net10-phone/</guid><description>Net10 provides straightforward and affordable cell phone service at a rate of 10 cents per minute. With no contracts, credit checks, or complicated requirements, users can purchase a Net10 phone and add minutes as needed. As a bonus, Net10 is offering 300 free minutes and 60 days of service with any phone purchase, along with free shipping.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Net10 focuses on providing basic cell phone service at an affordable price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-300-free-minutes-with-a-net10-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-300-free-minutes-with-a-net10-phone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>