<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DDoS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ddos/</link><description>Recent content in DDoS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ddos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions.</description></item><item><title>Earth to Cloud Network Security Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 18:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</guid><description>Information technology specialists understand the need for secure corporate networks, including enterprise-level security for cloud computing services in remote data centers. However, maintaining security across the entire network, especially when extending the LAN remotely, poses a significant challenge.
Level 3 Communications offers a solution with its “Earth to Cloud” comprehensive global security suite. This multi-layered protection strategy aims to secure every aspect of the network from potential threats.
A key factor in this approach is having a single provider for both connectivity and network security, a role Level 3 is well-equipped to fill.</description></item></channel></rss>