<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Millennial on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/millennial/</link><description>Recent content in Millennial on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/millennial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The perspectives of Gen Z differ from those of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</guid><description>A panel discussion at the Global Islamic Economy Summit focused on the characteristics of Generation Z, the generation following Millennials. Growing up with the internet and mobile phones, Gen Z is not only tech-savvy but also possesses a distinct perspective.
Sunil John, CEO of ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller, pointed out that governments are increasingly paying attention to this generation, questioning if current education and employment systems meet their needs. Citing the ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey 2016, John highlighted that 58% of young Arabs desire higher education, and 36% aim to start businesses, a departure from the traditional reliance on government jobs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ascott's latest brand, Lyf, is aimed at Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</guid><description>Source: Capitaland. CapitaLand’s President &amp;amp; Group CEO, Lim Ming Yan (left) and Ascott’s CEO, Lee Chee Koon (right) try their hand at baking at Lyf’s ‘Bond’ social kitchen.
CapitaLand&amp;rsquo;s serviced residence branch, The Ascott Limited (Ascott), is launching Lyf, a new brand designed for Millennials who want to experience travel like locals.
Lyf goes beyond typical hospitality models by creating a community where guests can connect with fellow travelers and innovators to live and collaborate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>"Credit Suisse identifies three major trends for 2018"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Cavalli.
The sixth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference 2018, held in Singapore, focused on three significant trends: technology designed to benefit humanity, including AI and robotics; a future shaped by Millennials; and the expanding silver economy.
Benjamin Cavalli, Head of Private Banking Southeast Asia and Singapore CEO of Credit Suisse, explained in his opening remarks that these megatrends represent investment themes based on Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s expert insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Millennial 20/20 APAC Summit will span two days and focus on the future of commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 11:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Millennial 20/20.
From September 7th to 8th, 2016, Singapore will be the site of the Millennial 20/20 APAC Summit. This two-day event will feature discussions centered around understanding the millennial consumer, with over 130 speakers, interactive exhibits, 50 panel discussions, and 24 keynote presentations and interviews.
Rupa Ganatra, Founding Partner of Millennial 20/20, emphasizes the rapid changes in the marketplace driven by millennials, stating that the summit will be crucial for brands to adapt and remain relevant in this influential movement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Honor Magic is redefining the limits of smartphone capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Honor. Honor Magic utilizes AI technology to anticipate user needs.
Honor, a Huawei Group brand targeting young, tech-savvy consumers, celebrated its third anniversary by introducing the innovative Honor Magic smartphone. This device incorporates artificial intelligence (AI) for a more interactive user experience.
The Honor Magic boasts a sleek and ergonomic design featuring a 3D curved glass body. Powered by a Kirin 950 processor, it offers a 5.09&amp;quot; 2K AMOLED curved screen, intelligent sensors, and advanced recognition technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UOB introduces its inaugural credit card tailored for millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</guid><description>A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB), the UOB Young Professionals Survey, has revealed that the spending habits of millennials are influenced by their desire for travel and sharing food experiences with loved ones. UOB aims to secure half of all millennials as customers within the next three years, recognizing their imminent rise as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s dominant consumer group.
UOB categorizes millennials as individuals between the ages of 26 and 35...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New e-book series examines generational disparities in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>The INSEAD Emerging Markets Institute collaborated with employer branding specialist Universum, Singapore-based think tank The HEAD Foundation, and MIT Leadership Centre to release Brave New Workplace, the first in a series of e-books called Generations Series.
As companies aim to create optimal work environments and policies for multigenerational workforces, they may find generational differences to be a significant factor, though this is not always the case. Brave New Workplace examines how Gen X, Gen Y, and Gen Z are transforming the nature of work and workplace culture by looking at their behaviors and attitudes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>