<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Institute on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/institute/</link><description>Recent content in Institute on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:12:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/institute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 6th Directors' Conference of the Singapore Institute of Directors will prioritize innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-6th-directors-conference-of-the-singapore-institute-of-directors-will-prioritize-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-6th-directors-conference-of-the-singapore-institute-of-directors-will-prioritize-innovation/</guid><description>Source: SID brochure.
The critical importance of boards in driving innovation will be the central theme at the Singapore Institute of Directors (SID) sixth annual Directors&amp;rsquo; Conference. Taking place on September 16, 2015, at the Marina Bay Sands, Singapore, this yearly event is designed to cultivate leadership skills for Singaporean businesses and is anticipated to draw over 800 attendees.
Organized by SID, the conference will be inaugurated by guest-of-honor S Iswaran, Minister in the Prime Minister’s Office; Second Minister for Home Affairs; and Second Minister for Trade and Industry.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place.</description></item><item><title>A white paper providing solutions for talent management in the Chinese hospitality industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</guid><description>Florida International University&amp;rsquo;s Chaplin School of Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Management (CSHTM) and its Institute for Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Education &amp;amp; Research (IHTER) have published a new resource for HR professionals and hospitality businesses, particularly those working with Chinese markets. The white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Managing Growing Pains of China’s Relentless Hotel Development Pipeline,&amp;rdquo; examines the significant lack of qualified talent within China&amp;rsquo;s rapidly expanding hotel industry. The paper offers practical solutions such as professional development programs, conflict resolution strategies, and clearly defined career paths to attract and retain skilled employees.</description></item><item><title>The top 10 workplaces in Singapore have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 08:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>A recent study by the research and consulting firm Great Place to Work Institute Singapore reveals a strong connection between high levels of trust and engagement among employees and a high-performing work environment.
In addition to the new report, Singapore Insights 2015, Great Place to Work Institute Singapore has unveiled its first-ever 10 Best Companies to Work For in Singapore List. Salesforce, the cloud computing giant, claims the top spot.</description></item></channel></rss>