<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digitalisation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digitalisation/</link><description>Recent content in Digitalisation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:03:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digitalisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kampong Glam introduces new digital initiatives with the participation of 150 merchants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:03:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</guid><description>Haji Lane in Kampong Glam.
Kampong Glam, the first neighborhood in Singapore to embrace digital technology, has introduced five initial projects to help its traditional businesses thrive in the digital world.
This neighborhood revitalization project, spearheaded by the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), involves collaboration with Enterprise Singapore, One Kampong Gelam (OKG) association, and the Singapore Malay Chambers of Commerce and Industry (SMCCI). Its objective is to make the neighborhood more attractive to tech-savvy shoppers and tourists seeking immersive retail experiences, while enabling businesses to increase their productivity through technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Establishing companies online in Lithuania within a comparative framework: Enforcing the Digitalisation Directive and more</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establishing-companies-online-in-lithuania-within-a-comparative-framework-enforcing-the-digitalisation-directive-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 14:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establishing-companies-online-in-lithuania-within-a-comparative-framework-enforcing-the-digitalisation-directive-and-more/</guid><description>Virginijus Bitė, Law Professor at Mykolas Romeris University Law School
Ivan Romashchenko, Senior Researcher at the Legal Technology Centre, Mykolas Romeris University Law School
Photo credit: Elian, via Wikimedia Commons
For years, company registration heavily relied on paper documentation. The 2019 Digitalisation Directive pushed EU members to offer digital company formation for private businesses. While Lithuania already had online legal entity formation pre-2019, this directive still prompted necessary legal updates, mostly enacted by July 1, 2022...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establishing-companies-online-in-lithuania-within-a-comparative-framework-enforcing-the-digitalisation-directive-and-more/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establishing-companies-online-in-lithuania-within-a-comparative-framework-enforcing-the-digitalisation-directive-and-more/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The idea of a virtual registered office in accordance with EU law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-idea-of-a-virtual-registered-office-in-accordance-with-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 23:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-idea-of-a-virtual-registered-office-in-accordance-with-eu-law/</guid><description>Virginijus Bitė, Law Professor at Mykolas Romeris University Law School
Ivan Romashchenko, Senior Researcher at the Legal Technology Centre, Mykolas Romeris University Law School
Photo credit: EmDee, via Wikimedia Commons
On March 29th, 2023, the European Commission unveiled a proposed Directive as part of an initiative to modernize digital company law. This proposal primarily emphasizes increased transparency, information accessibility, and the cross-border exchange of company data. These objectives were previously outlined in an inception impact assessment report released on July 20th, 2021...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-idea-of-a-virtual-registered-office-in-accordance-with-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-idea-of-a-virtual-registered-office-in-accordance-with-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>