<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Anti-Terrorism on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/anti-terrorism/</link><description>Recent content in Anti-Terrorism on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:53:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/anti-terrorism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is there Friendly Fire in the European Union? AG Sharpston's view on the revised firearms Directive's validity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</guid><description>Niels Kirst (University Paris II – Panthéon-Assas)
Advocate General Sharpston (AG) issued an opinion on April 11, 2019, regarding the legitimacy of Directive 2017/853, known as the Firearms Directive. The Czech Republic challenged this directive, arguing that the European Parliament and the Council should not have used the internal market harmonization clause (Article 114 TFEU) as the legal basis for its adoption.
This case is noteworthy for several reasons. First, it centers around the crucial aspect of legal basis, drawing considerable attention from EU legal experts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a need for additional anti-terrorist legislation in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 01:42:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Following the horrific attacks in Paris two days ago, the EU Commission wasted no time in announcing its intention to propose new anti-terrorism measures within a month. While the specifics of this legislation remain unclear, the very notion of enacting new laws is fundamentally flawed.
The EU institutions were right to express sympathy for the victims and emphasize their commitment to defending freedom of speech. Utilizing existing EU anti-terrorism laws, such as the European Arrest Warrant (EAW), to apprehend suspects who may have fled to another Member State, would also be appropriate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on data retention: Mass surveillance is prohibited.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</guid><description>Steve Peers
On July 7, 2005, a relative of mine was on her way to work on a London tube train when terrorists detonated bombs on her train and three others across the city. While my relative was unharmed, dozens of people tragically lost their lives.
This event, along with the prior attacks on 9/11 and in Madrid, understandably fueled public anxiety around terrorism and spurred the EU to introduce additional anti-terrorism measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice has clarified that foreign fighters' accomplices are not eligible for refugee status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 15:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</guid><description>When can someone be refused asylum for terrorism? Professor Steve Peers
What happens when a person seeking refuge is suspected of terrorism or aiding terrorists? Can they still be considered a refugee? If not, how do we legally define &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; to justify denying their claim? The recent EU Court of Justice judgment in the Lounani case clarifies some aspects of this complex issue but leaves some challenging questions unanswered.
Legal Framework The UN Refugee Convention (Geneva Convention) outlines an &amp;rsquo;exclusion&amp;rsquo; clause in Article 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cracking down on online terrorism - a threat to freedom of speech? The EU Regulation on online terrorist content under scrutiny.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
On September 12th, 2018, the European Commission presented a proposal for a regulation aimed at combating terrorist content online. This regulation would mandate that EU Member States require internet platforms to proactively remove such content and ensure that authorities possess the capabilities to address this illegal material. This proposal builds upon existing voluntary partnerships like the EU Internet Forum and previous non-binding recommendations from the Commission on tackling illegal content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What's all the fuss about the draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</guid><description>Cian C. Murphy, The Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London
The transnational public sphere continues to be gradually suppressed. The European Union&amp;rsquo;s initial legislative response to recent killings by Islamic State militants in Europe and elsewhere is a draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism, which was published last month. The Directive, which seeks to expand the scope of EU law in national criminal law regarding terrorism, will replace the Framework Decision on Combating Terrorism, which was initially approved in 2002 and revised in 2008...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>