<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Movement of Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-services/</link><description>Recent content in Free Movement of Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Does the new Council of Europe treaty on match-fixing comply with EU internal market regulations?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</guid><description>Tom Serby, a Senior Law Lecturer at Anglia Law School, Anglia Ruskin University, discusses the escalating problem of betting-related match-fixing in sports. He highlights the Council of Europe&amp;rsquo;s recent Convention aimed at tackling this issue, while also pointing out Malta&amp;rsquo;s legal challenge against it at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). Malta argues that the treaty clashes with internal market rules, particularly the freedom to provide services, underscoring the difficulties in achieving a unified international response to match-fixing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice is deciding whether monks can be prohibited from practicing law, posing the question, "Can a man serve two masters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:08:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</guid><description>Rebecca Zahn, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Strathclyde
Lawyers in the European Union hold a distinctive position. They ensure access to justice, manage its administration, and uphold the rule of law within their Member States. Similar to other professions like medicine or architecture, national bodies strictly regulate entry. However, legal practice is inherently location-specific, unlike other professions. A lawyer&amp;rsquo;s knowledge base is tied to the jurisdiction where they were trained and qualified...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling in McFadden: Public Wi-Fi and Responsibility for Unauthorized Downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case, McFadden, examined whether businesses offering free wi-fi are responsible for customers&amp;rsquo; illegal downloads. This case centered around Article 12 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s eCommerce Directive, which protects &amp;ldquo;mere conduits&amp;rdquo; of information from liability. While generally aligning with existing laws, the ruling raised potentially significant points regarding injunction costs and internet access provision requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU’s Patients’ Rights Directive in practice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</guid><description>Tamara Hervey, Professor of Law and Head of Law School, University of Sheffield
As Europe focuses on the immense refugee crisis, discussing other migration matters can seem trivial. However, this week also saw the release of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s report on the &amp;ldquo;Patients&amp;rsquo; Rights Directive.&amp;rdquo; This report reveals that the directive&amp;rsquo;s name is misleading, as its primary goal appears to be safeguarding national health systems instead of patients&amp;rsquo; rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gathering of EU citizens residing in their home country: Understanding the Surinder Singh and Carpenter rulings for family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
This article examines when an EU citizen residing in their home country can assert rights under EU law for family members to join them. This analysis stems from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressing judgments in the Surinder Singh and Carpenter cases. These cases involve family reunification for EU citizens who return to their home country after residing in another Member State and for EU citizens who provide services in another Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regulation of Audiovisual Media Services and the "Exception for Newspapers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 01:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Case C-347/14 New Media Online GmbH v. Bundeskommunikationssenat, 21 October 2015
Traditionally, broadcasting and newspapers have been regulated differently. Newspapers have enjoyed more lenient, often self-regulatory, oversight. EU law harmonized television broadcasting through the Television without Frontiers Directive. Newspapers, if subject to EU law, fell under general free movement and competition rules. As technology evolved and online information services emerged, the Television without Frontiers Directive underwent revisions, becoming the Audiovisual Media Services Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ERGA and the Audiovisual and Media Services Directive 2.0: A European Regulators Group without Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
In 2014, the European Commission created ERGA to help implement the Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) and support a unified European market. This built upon the existing High Level Group of Regulatory Authorities, established in 2003, which brought national enforcement bodies together twice a year. The goal was to improve collaboration between these authorities to ensure the AVMSD was applied consistently across Europe. This reflects a broader EU trend of forming networks, sometimes including member states, to promote harmonization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recognition of Professional Qualifications after Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 23:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</guid><description>Dáire McCormack-George*
*The author, a Ph.D. Candidate in Law and Scholar of Trinity College Dublin, the University of Dublin, based this blog post on his presentation at the third Radboud University Economic Law Conference, ‘Upgrading Trade and Services in EU and International Economic Law’, on June 15, 2018. He thanks the conference participants and attendees for their engaging questions. All errors are his own.
Introduction
The current draft withdrawal agreement between the UK and the EU proposes the temporary application of Directive 2005/36/EC (the Recognition Directive) until the transition period ends, ensuring continued recognition of qualifications recognized beforehand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice resolves the issue of posting third-country workers within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Amedeo Arena, Assistant Professor of European Law - University of Naples &amp;ldquo;Federico II&amp;rdquo; School of Law
Judgment of the court (Second Chamber) of 11 September 2014, Essent Energie Productie BV v. Minister van SocialeZaken en Werkgelegenheid, Case C-91/13.
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) has consistently maintained that, in contrast to workers from EU Member States, Turkish nationals do not possess the right to freedom of movement within the European Union...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How do the Court's rulings on December 21, 2023 impact UEFA's position as a 'gatekeeper' in the Football Revolution?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</guid><description>Steve Weatherill, Somerville College and Faculty of Law, University of Oxford
Photo credit: Werner100359, via Wikimedia Commons
Summary
Recent Court of Justice rulings on December 21, 2023, determined that practices requiring prior approval for new sporting competitions created by external entities clash with EU law. This decision primarily stemmed from the lack of clear, unbiased, and transparent criteria and procedures. While governing bodies, particularly in football, are obligated to adjust their practices, the extent of their authority as gatekeepers remains unclear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union provides clarification on the Singh and Carpenter rulings for EU citizens' family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Typically, EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant residency rights to non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in their own home country. However, recent court rulings have clarified two key exceptions to this rule, albeit with unexpected outcomes. These rulings stem from Advocate-General Sharpston&amp;rsquo;s December 2013 opinion, as discussed in a prior blog entry.
The O and B case: Revisiting Singh
In 2007, O, a non-EU citizen, and their Dutch partner, sponsor O, moved to Spain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>