<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Risk on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/risk/</link><description>Recent content in Risk on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:32:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/risk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Financial services companies are placing a greater emphasis on developing a strong risk culture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</guid><description>A recent study by Mercer focusing on executive compensation in the global financial services industry found that a majority of firms are prioritizing the development of robust risk cultures within their organizations. Sixty-two percent of surveyed firms reported significant efforts to penalize misconduct and non-compliance, while 60% demonstrated clear leadership commitment to ethical behavior. Furthermore, 58% have established and communicated unambiguous objectives related to risk culture.
Vicki Elliott, Senior Partner and Financial Services Talent Leader at Mercer, highlighted the importance of senior leaders setting a positive example when it comes to risk management and compliance.</description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware.</description></item><item><title>International SOS recommends implementing improved risk management strategies for business travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-recommends-implementing-improved-risk-management-strategies-for-business-travel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 15:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-recommends-implementing-improved-risk-management-strategies-for-business-travel/</guid><description>International SOS, a company specializing in health and security risk services, emphasizes the growing need for improved risk management for both individual travelers and organizations.
Their data reveals a significant rise in travel between the start of 2023 and October 2023, with international travel surging by 59% and domestic travel increasing by 48.4%. These figures align with a recent report from the International Air Transport Association (IATA), which highlights a global travel resurgence.</description></item></channel></rss>