<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cybersecurity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cybersecurity/</link><description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints.</description></item><item><title>The Cyber Resilience Act as it relates to the Internet of Things.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cyber-resilience-act-as-it-relates-to-the-internet-of-things/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cyber-resilience-act-as-it-relates-to-the-internet-of-things/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip, PhD candidate, Radboud University
Image credit: Grafiker61, via Wikicommons Media
The Internet of Things (IoT), encompassing devices with integrated hardware and software like smartwatches and WiFi security cameras, is becoming increasingly prevalent in homes and industries. However, the cybersecurity of these connected devices is a growing concern. Hackers have exploited vulnerabilities in these devices, as demonstrated by the Mirai botnet attack, where thousands of devices were compromised to disrupt websites and businesses.</description></item><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions.</description></item><item><title>Before you decide to check out Ronaldo, reconsider your decision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</guid><description>A study by McAfee, a part of Intel Security, reveals that cybercriminals often use popular figures like Cristiano Ronaldo to lure unsuspecting users to malicious websites. These websites, designed to look like legitimate fan pages, can infect devices with malware capable of stealing personal information. McAfee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Red Card Club&amp;rdquo; list highlights the top eleven footballers whose names are most frequently used in these scams, with Ronaldo topping the list, followed by Lionel Messi and Iker Cassillas.</description></item><item><title>The attitudes towards cybercrime and security in Singapore vary across different generations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</guid><description>This past week, I encountered WhatsApp spam shortly after a friend forwarded a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s discount coupon from Sniflr. Upon researching, I discovered Sniflr is a phishing scam that tricks people into sharing the coupon with 10 friends on WhatsApp, adding those numbers to a spam list.
Yesterday, a promoted tweet on my Twitter feed advertised a S$100 discount on a S$120 purchase at NTUC, a popular Singaporean supermarket chain. However, a Google search revealed a months-old news article warning about fake NTUC coupons on Facebook, a claim supported by NTUC&amp;rsquo;s official Twitter account.</description></item><item><title>40% of Singaporeans have experienced a data breach within the last year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</guid><description>Parvinder Walia, during his presentation, revealed that 72% of consumers react negatively to news of a company suffering a cyberattack or data breach.
ESET, a cybersecurity software company, conducted a survey to examine consumer online behavior and perspectives on cybersecurity in light of recent data breaches.
The ESET 2018 APAC Consumer Behaviour Survey found that 42% of Singaporeans had experienced some form of data breach in the preceding year. These breaches included theft and misuse of personal information, bank account fraud, social media account compromise, and attacks from malware and viruses.</description></item></channel></rss>