<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/os/</link><description>Recent content in OS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/os/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Huawei smartphones in Singapore are now receiving the EMUI 9.1 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 06:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</guid><description>Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group started releasing its newest software update, EMUI 9.1, in Singapore on June 27th. This version is based on Android 9.0 Pie.
The update will be available in stages, beginning with the Mate 20 Series in late June. Following that, the P20 Series and Nova 3 Series will get the update in July, and finally, models like the Mate RS, P10, and P10 Plus will receive it in August.</description></item><item><title>Huawei has released the schedule for the EMUI10 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</guid><description>Huawei has released the global update schedule for EMUI 10. This latest version features an updated interface, a &amp;ldquo;Dark Mode&amp;rdquo; setting, performance and security improvements, and &amp;ldquo;Multi-screen Collaboration&amp;rdquo; which allows Huawei PCs and Android devices to seamlessly connect.
Starting this month, users with the HUAWEI P30 Pro, HUAWEI P30, HUAWEI Mate 20 Pro, HUAWEI Mate 20, HUAWEI Mate 20 X (4G) and HUAWEI nova 5T will get push notifications to install the EMUI 10 update.</description></item><item><title>Starting on July 29, upgrades to Windows 10 will be available for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</guid><description>Source: Windows blog.
Microsoft has revealed that Windows 10 will launch on July 29th in 190 countries. The company states that Windows 10 will enhance productivity and offer a more personalized and intuitive user experience across devices. Windows 7 and 8.1 users can upgrade to Windows 10 for free, making it accessible to a majority of current Windows users.
&amp;ldquo;Windows 10 empowers users to achieve remarkable things,&amp;rdquo; says Terry Myerson, Executive VP at Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>The initial significant update is now accessible for Windows 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Microsoft has released its first significant update for Windows 10, available for both PCs and tablets. This update brings enhancements across the platform, improving user experience according to the company&amp;rsquo;s official announcement. The rollout of Windows 10 has also begun for Xbox One and is expected to reach selected mobile phones shortly.
Terry Myerson, Executive VP of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows and Devices Group, expressed confidence in the update, stating that it marks a level of platform maturity suitable for organization-wide deployment.</description></item></channel></rss>