<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Purchase on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/purchase/</link><description>Recent content in Purchase on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/purchase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Purchase online and make your payment at a nearby convenience store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</guid><description>MOLPay, a Southeast Asian online payment provider, is partnering with 7-Eleven Malaysia to introduce a new e-commerce payment method.
This service, called MOLPay CASH, will launch first in select Klang Valley 7-Eleven stores, with 735 stores currently offering this option and plans for further expansion. By July 2014, all 1,569 Malaysian stores will provide this service.
MOLPay CASH allows merchants to accept cash payments from customers at their nearest 7-Eleven. After an online purchase, a barcode is generated for the customer to use for payment at a 7-Eleven location.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor has discovered that India and China have lower-than-average per capita calorie purchases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</guid><description>A new study by Euromonitor International reveals how many nutrients people consume daily from packaged foods and beverages. This data, found in their Passport: Nutrition database, tracks the consumption of calories, fats, saturated fats, carbohydrates, sugars, salt, protein, and fiber across 54 countries.
Globally, we buy enough packaged food and soft drinks to consume 1.5 trillion calories per day, averaging 765 calories per person. While a healthy daily intake is around 2,000 calories, North America and Western Europe exceed 1,500 calories, contrasting with India&amp;rsquo;s 150 and China&amp;rsquo;s 510.</description></item><item><title>IDC reveals the preferences of APAC consumers when it comes to mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 05:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</guid><description>The International Data Corporation (IDC) has released an infographic that reveals how consumers in the Asia Pacific region make decisions about mobile devices. Key findings from the Essential Guide to Device Decisions of a Connected Consumer in Asia Pacific report include:
Source: IDC infographic. What consumers like about bigger phone screens.
77% of surveyed consumers reported having a larger smartphone now than their previous device, while only 8% opted for a smaller one.</description></item></channel></rss>