<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Patents on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/patents/</link><description>Recent content in Patents on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:33:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/patents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it cheerleading or judging? The CJEU supports the EU's unified patent system.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:33:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Two recent rulings by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirm the EU regulations for a unitary patent system are legal. This analysis examines the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning and evaluates its coherence.
Background
Establishing EU-wide patent regulations has been a long-standing challenge. The Lisbon Treaty introduced Article 118 TFEU, aiming to streamline intellectual property rules. While most rules fall under ordinary legislative procedures (requiring qualified majority voting), language regulations necessitate unanimous agreement.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice (CJEU) provides clarification on the patentability of stem cells in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther; all views are the author&amp;rsquo;s own
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently clarified its stance on biotechnology patents in the International Stem Cell Corporation case, modifying its earlier decision in Brüstle. The court now emphasizes the &amp;ldquo;inherent capacity&amp;rdquo; of a non-fertilized human egg stimulated by parthenogenesis to become a human being as the defining factor for it to be considered a &amp;ldquo;human embryo&amp;rdquo; and thus ineligible for patenting under the Biotechnology Directive.</description></item></channel></rss>