<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Arabic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arabic/</link><description>Recent content in Arabic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:59:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arabic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Check out Rahlat.com for the best travel prices in Arabic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</guid><description>Source: Rahlat.com website. Screen capture of the home page.
Rahlat.com is an Arabic travel search website designed by Arabs, for Arabs. Its goal is to help travelers in the Middle East and Gulf region find the best prices on flights and hotels. This free, independent metasearch engine is available in both Arabic and English, making it easy for users to compare prices from numerous travel and airline websites with just one click.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai government is collaborating with Microsoft to develop a new font named "Dubai."</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-government-is-collaborating-with-microsoft-to-develop-a-new-font-named-dubai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-government-is-collaborating-with-microsoft-to-develop-a-new-font-named-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Government Media Office.
The Dubai Crown Prince and Chairman of the Dubai Executive Council, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid, has instructed the General Secretariat of the Dubai Executive Council to create a new font called &amp;ldquo;Dubai.&amp;rdquo; The initial phase will concentrate on developing unique Arabic and English fonts with advanced typographic capabilities.
Sheikh Hamdan emphasized that this initiative will reinforce Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing in information technology, aligning with the government&amp;rsquo;s strategy for leadership and innovation.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces a mobile site in Arabic language</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced an Arabic version of its mobile website. This platform allows customers to book flights, check in online, upgrade their travel class, and access and download Apple Passbook boarding passes directly to their smartphones, regardless of the language they use on the Emirates mobile site.
The Arabic mobile platform has been launched concurrently in 15 countries across the Middle East and North Africa, including the UAE, Bahrain, Iraq, Jordan, Kuwait, Lebanon, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Morocco, and Sudan.</description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base.</description></item><item><title>Lateefa AlWaalan has been awarded the title of Saudi Arabia's EY Entrepreneur Of The Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</guid><description>Lateefa AlWaalan, the driving force behind the Arabic coffee startup Yatooq, has been crowned Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s EY Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) for 2015.
A panel of independent judges selected AlWaalan from a pool of eleven finalists representing ten different companies. Her entrepreneurial spirit, robust financial performance, strategic thinking, and positive social impact distinguished her as a leader. Fahad Altoaimi, EY&amp;rsquo;s Office Managing Partner in Riyadh and the Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader, emphasized that this award recognizes AlWaalan&amp;rsquo;s significant business accomplishments, innovative spirit, and contributions to her community.</description></item></channel></rss>