<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Skills on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skills/</link><description>Recent content in Skills on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:57:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singaporean IT leaders are concerned that a shortage of skills could impede the progress of the Smart Nation initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</guid><description>93% of Singaporean Chief Information Officers (CIOs) are worried that Singapore lacks the IT talent pool needed to successfully implement Smart Nation initiatives.
Six out of 10 CIOs believe Smart Nation initiatives will lead to more IT jobs, and 53% believe these initiatives will boost average IT salaries.
New independent research* commissioned by specialized recruiter Robert Half reveals that over 9 in 10 (93%) Singaporean IT leaders are concerned about the lack of readily available IT talent in Singapore to build a Smart Nation-ready workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans will receive increased support for SkillsFuture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</guid><description>Source: SkillsFuture Singapore. Minister Puthucheary watches on as Ng (left) and Kevin Wo, Country GM, Microsoft Singapore (right) sign the MoU.
To better equip Singapore&amp;rsquo;s workforce and businesses for a digital-centric economy, SkillsFuture Singapore (SSG) has launched new initiatives. These include a partnership with Microsoft and enhancements to the national SkillsFuture for Digital Workplace program.
Dr. Janil Puthucheary, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Transport and Ministry of Communications and Information, announced these developments at the first SkillsFuture Festival X Smart Nation (SFFXSmart Nation) event...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways is the designated airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</guid><description>The image showcases young people at work, sourced from the WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017 website.
Etihad Airways is the official airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017, a major international event focusing on vocational education and skills excellence. Taking place at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) from October 14th to 17th, 2017, the event will host over 3,000 participants and experts representing approximately 75 countries.
WorldSkills encompasses a variety of industries, from construction and creative fields like arts and fashion to technology, manufacturing, engineering, social services, and transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing involvement of women in commerce and industry in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) in the Philippines has reported a rise in the number of women participating in skills training programs for traditionally male-dominated fields.
Amelito Cardenas, a supervising specialist at TESDA Pangasinan, mentioned that more women are enrolling in technical-vocational (tech-voc) and private institutions to learn trades such as welding and automotive repair, as reported by the Philippines Information Agency.
Cardenas also shared that TESDA offers a free training program specifically for women who run sari-sari stores and carinderia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Jobs Come Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</guid><description>Although the Great Recession continues, the impact varies across industries. In fact, the technology sector is performing quite well in terms of employment. From November to December of last year, while 85,000 jobs were lost overall, the tech industry actually added 5,200 new positions. This suggests that technology might be a promising field.
However, having technological skills doesn&amp;rsquo;t guarantee employment. Many factory workers, for instance, would likely agree. The manufacturing sector was already moving overseas even before the recession...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>