<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Aggregation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-aggregation/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Aggregation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-aggregation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High Bandwidth Dissimilar Line Bonding From Mushroom Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</guid><description>Want to create your own high-bandwidth internet connection without the exorbitant cost of dedicated services like SONET OC3? Combining consumer-grade options like DSL, cable, or wireless might seem appealing, but achieving a reliable, high-speed connection this way is practically impossible with standard routers.
Instead of another router, consider the Truffles appliance from Mushroom Networks. This innovative device combines multiple internet connections, regardless of type, into a single, high-bandwidth connection.
While traditional &amp;ldquo;T1 bonding&amp;rdquo; offered by carriers has limitations in terms of speed and requiring identical lines from a single provider, Truffles takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Combine T1 Lines For Higher Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a popular choice for small and medium-sized businesses for many years due to their reliability, security, dedicated bandwidth, and accessibility. While their affordability has increased in recent years, their speed has remained a limitation. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution to overcome this without sacrificing the benefits of T1 technology: bonding.
Bonding is a standard industry technique that allows you to combine the bandwidth of multiple T1 lines. This effectively merges them into a single, faster connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>