<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workforce on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/workforce/</link><description>Recent content in Workforce on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/workforce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Epson has launched three business inkjet printers that offer a range of connectivity options and high capacity features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WorkForce WF-2661.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has launched three new inkjet printers for businesses in Singapore. These models are designed for small offices and home offices.
The ultra-compact Epson WorkForce series is designed for small spaces and cost-effective printing. These printers include automatic document feeders (ADFs) and Epson Connect, enabling users to print directly from their mobile devices.
The new WorkForce series offers easy and flexible printing over Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>Helping individuals with disabilities transition from training programs to meaningful employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Individuals with disabilities should be placed in jobs where they can acquire skills on the job, rather than receiving training without a clear path to employment. Christy Lynch, CEO of KARE Ireland, an organization supporting individuals with intellectual disabilities and their families, emphasized the importance of collaborating with both individuals with disabilities and employers to create truly empowering opportunities. He spoke at the &amp;ldquo;Towards an Inclusive Workforce 2015&amp;rdquo; event, co-organized by SPD and supported by SG Enable and the Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA).</description></item><item><title>SCALA, the Singapore Workforce Development Agency, is offering a logistics reskilling program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 14:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</guid><description>The Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA) and Supply Chain and Logistics Academy (SCALA) joined forces to launch the Logistics Professional Conversion Programme (PCP). The initiative aims to help professionals, managers, executives, and technicians (PMETs) gain the necessary skills to enter the logistics industry.
This program seeks to create opportunities for newcomers and seasoned professionals in logistics, allowing them to expand their skillsets and advance their careers. Over the next two years, the PCP will offer 150 positions for PMETs, specifically as Logistics Officers and Logistics Executives.</description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future.</description></item><item><title>New e-book series examines generational disparities in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>The INSEAD Emerging Markets Institute collaborated with employer branding specialist Universum, Singapore-based think tank The HEAD Foundation, and MIT Leadership Centre to release Brave New Workplace, the first in a series of e-books called Generations Series.
As companies aim to create optimal work environments and policies for multigenerational workforces, they may find generational differences to be a significant factor, though this is not always the case. Brave New Workplace examines how Gen X, Gen Y, and Gen Z are transforming the nature of work and workplace culture by looking at their behaviors and attitudes.</description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:</description></item></channel></rss>