<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chinese New Year on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chinese-new-year/</link><description>Recent content in Chinese New Year on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:10:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chinese-new-year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing the Xbox CosPups inspired by the Chinese zodiac</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-xbox-cospups-inspired-by-the-chinese-zodiac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-xbox-cospups-inspired-by-the-chinese-zodiac/</guid><description>Source: Xbox. The Xbox Cospups.
To celebrate the Year of the Dog, Xbox has created the Xbox CosPups. This group of canine characters embodies traits of the Chinese zodiac through their portrayal of famous gaming characters and worlds.
&amp;ldquo;Cospups&amp;rdquo; refers to dogs participating in &amp;ldquo;cosplay,&amp;rdquo; which involves dressing up as characters from different forms of media like books, games, and movies.
The Xbox CosPups have names such as Master Chihuahua, Sea of Fleas, Mutt-cus Fenix, Fur-za, and the small but mighty PUG-G.</description></item><item><title>Year of the Tiger Poken</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/year-of-the-tiger-poken/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 07:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/year-of-the-tiger-poken/</guid><description>February 14th was a significant date, marking not only Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day but also the beginning of the Chinese New Year. In the Chinese Zodiac, a 12-animal cycle is used to name the years, including the tiger. The year 2010 is designated as the &amp;ldquo;Year of the Tiger&amp;rdquo;.
Beyond its association with the tiger, 2010 is poised to be recognized as the &amp;ldquo;Year of the Poken&amp;rdquo;. Introduced late last year, the Poken, a social networking device originating in Switzerland, has gained popularity in America.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese New Year promotion by Digi highlights the importance of family and tradition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</guid><description>Source: Digi website.
For many Chinese individuals, the Chinese New Year signifies the only opportunity to reconnect with distant family members. Malaysian telecommunications company Digi is capitalizing on this tradition with a new promotional campaign designed for a global audience.
Recognizing that in today&amp;rsquo;s world, many individuals simply use titles like &amp;lsquo;aunt,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;uncle,&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cousin&amp;rsquo; for relatives beyond their immediate family, Digi&amp;rsquo;s campaign encourages the use of more precise family titles within Chinese families.</description></item><item><title>Book with ONYX in February to receive exclusive discounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</guid><description>Source: Onyx web page. Several ONYX Hospitality Group properties are offering special deals for the Chinese New Year.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, guests can enjoy up to a 20% discount at the Oriental Residence Bangkok or at one of the 25 participating Amari, OZO, Shama, and Mosaic Collection hotels. These offers are available at locations in Thailand, Sri Lanka, mainland China, Hong Kong, Qatar, and Bangladesh.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th.</description></item><item><title>Add some festive flowers to the office to celebrate Chinese New Year and bring some brightness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</guid><description>Starting January 19, 2015, Viva La Fleur will debut a new collection of long-lasting bouquets and table arrangements. The color palette for this collection features predominantly red, orange, and yellow tones, symbolizing love, luck, and fortune, perfectly aligning with the festive season.
This arrangement, part of Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s new collection, showcases deep red roses, hydrangeas, and caspia accented with brown twigs. You can find this arrangement in Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s online shop here.</description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist.</description></item><item><title>Businesses have the opportunity to take part in the For a Golden Home charity campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</guid><description>Cromly.com, a design portal and social media platform, has launched &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home.&amp;rdquo; This online charity campaign aims to improve the lives of needy elderly individuals in Singapore this Chinese New Year. The platform allows organizations to create their own fundraising projects in support of this shared goal.
Source: Cromly.com. Participating companies can create a pledge project to raise funds. Eunice Olsen and Paul Foster are ambassadors for the &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home&amp;rdquo; campaign.</description></item><item><title>Greetings for Chinese New Year in the office and business with a traditional lohei celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/greetings-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-office-and-business-with-a-traditional-lohei-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/greetings-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-office-and-business-with-a-traditional-lohei-celebration/</guid><description>This scroll says 生意興隆/生意兴隆 (sheng yi xing long), which translates to &amp;ldquo;may the business thrive greatly.&amp;rdquo;
The celebratory atmosphere in mainland China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Singapore is palpable this time of year. Everywhere you look, lucky red and gold decorations are for sale, along with symbols of the upcoming year&amp;rsquo;s zodiac animal. Chinese New Year falls on February 8th in 2016, and well-wishes in the form of traditional greetings will be exchanged from the very first day.</description></item><item><title>Travellers from Singapore have a strong affinity for Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</guid><description>Source: KAYAK. Tokyo skyline.
The travel search platform, KAYAK, has identified the top five destinations Singaporeans are traveling to for the Chinese New Year (CNY) holiday. The Year of the Rooster begins with a long weekend that starts on Saturday, January 28th, and ends on Monday, January 30th, 2017.
The most popular travel destination for Singaporeans between January 28th and February 5th is Bangkok, Thailand. Tokyo, Japan, and Manila in the Philippines are the second and third most popular destinations, respectively:</description></item><item><title>Prepare for Chinese New Year with Amazon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</guid><description>Preparing your office for Chinese New Year might be easier with a little help from Amazon.sg&amp;rsquo;s dedicated Chinese New Year store.
Finding the right gifts for clients is made simpler with choices like an abalone gift set, priced at S$310.80 for two 454g cans, or bird&amp;rsquo;s nest, available for S$39.90 for six jars. To help everyone in the office get into the spirit, festive treats are a must-have:
Source: Amazon. Snacks for the office for Chinese New Year.</description></item><item><title>Everything is going well at PARKROYAL on Beach Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</guid><description>Beginning January 16, 2017, PARKROYAL on Beach Road will be offering a new take on Lunar New Year celebrations as Executive Chef Ken Ang introduces his culinary perspective to the dishes at Plaza Brasserie, their all-day dining restaurant.
Known for his mastery of traditional Cantonese roasting methods, Executive Chef Ang will be presenting his version of the lucky facai yusheng (发财鱼生, also called lohei), enhanced with additions like crispy salmon and chicken skin.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singtel's Chinese New Year short film is on building connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Stills from the festive video emphasizing the importance of positive connections.
Singtel released its yearly short film for the Lunar New Year season. This year&amp;rsquo;s film uses humor to highlight the importance of connecting with others and nurturing relationships. The lighthearted short, His Grandfather’s Road, portrays a heated encounter between two families during the holiday rush. However, their road rage takes an unexpected turn when they discover shared ground and end their confrontation amicably.</description></item><item><title>Business Chinese New Year Greetings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-chinese-new-year-greetings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 22:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-chinese-new-year-greetings/</guid><description>The Chinese New Year, which lands on January 31st in 2014, is a time to offer New Year greetings to your Chinese colleagues and business contacts. These greetings are customary upon the first meeting or conversation during the 15 days of the New Year celebrations.
The most popular greetings are &amp;ldquo;Happy New Year&amp;rdquo; (新年快乐, xin nian kuai le) and &amp;ldquo;Congratulations on receiving riches and prosperity&amp;rdquo; (恭喜发财, gong xi fa cai).</description></item></channel></rss>