<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cyber on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cyber/</link><description>Recent content in Cyber on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cyber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Singtel Cyber Security Institute aims to enhance the skills of individuals and businesses in the field of cyber security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</guid><description>Singapore Telecommunications established the Singtel Cyber Security Institute (CSI) to bolster the cyber security skills of businesses and governments in the Asia Pacific region. The CSI is the first organization of its kind in the region, merging an advanced cyber range with an educational institute to provide companies with realistic training to handle complex cyber threats.
Bill Chang, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Group Enterprise CEO, highlighted the lack of preparedness among companies, with over 85% lacking robust cyber response plans or realistic training opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing financial consequences of cybercrime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</guid><description>Source: HP infographic.
HP recently released the findings of their sixth annual study, conducted in partnership with the Ponemon Institute, exploring the financial effects of cyberattacks on both public and private sectors.
The study shows a substantial rise in the total cost of cybercrime, indicating that smaller companies bear a proportionally larger cost than larger ones.
The 2015 Cost of Cyber Crime Study, carried out by the Ponemon Institute and supported by HP Enterprise Security, calculates the yearly cost of cybercrime for businesses across seven countries: the US, UK, Japan, Germany, Australia, Brazil, and Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>