<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aircards on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aircards/</link><description>Recent content in Aircards on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aircards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Maestro Smart Antenna Improves Fixed Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</guid><description>Accel Technologies, a branch of Accel Networks, is launching a groundbreaking product for fixed wireless connections: the Maestro smart antenna system. Maestro aims to make 3G and 4G fixed wireless broadband a more attractive alternative to pricier business connectivity options like T1, MPLS, VSAT, Frame Relay, and point-to-point microwave services.
What makes Maestro so special? Like other smart devices, Maestro utilizes active technology to enhance performance. In this situation, it improves the performance of a typically passive component: the RF antenna.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>How Aircards Work For Mobile Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 17:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</guid><description>Internet access via broadband has become a standard requirement for almost all businesses and home offices. Individuals can easily find and afford DSL and Cable Internet. Businesses, on the other hand, often opt for T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, and Ethernet connections. However, challenges arise when venturing beyond the confines of a traditional workspace. Without WiFi hotspots, staying connected becomes difficult. How can tasks such as delivering presentations, accessing inventory, or entering orders at a client&amp;rsquo;s office be accomplished if they necessitate a broadband connection?</description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T HSUPA Aircards Have the Edge Over EDGE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</guid><description>Major wireless carriers, including AT&amp;amp;T, are heavily invested in upgrading their cellular data capabilities to meet the increasing demand for broadband internet access. This demand stems from the desire for constant connectivity, enabling activities like web browsing and mobile video streaming. AT&amp;amp;T is eager to capitalize on this demand and provide the desired connectivity.
Those accustomed to traditional wired broadband connections and basic cell phones may not fully grasp the advancements in mobile broadband technology.</description></item></channel></rss>