<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Arrest Warrant on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-arrest-warrant/</link><description>Recent content in European Arrest Warrant on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-arrest-warrant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Union and the Crisis in the Spanish Constitution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</guid><description>Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated both to Université Saint-Louis Bruxelles and Université libre de Bruxelles
Background
For over a month, Spain has been grappling with a constitutional crisis stemming from pro-independence sentiments in Catalonia. These sentiments culminated in an independence referendum held on October 1, 2017, orchestrated by the Catalan government under President Carles Puigdemont. Barcelona claims that 90% of the 43% voter turnout favored independence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Has the European Court of Justice shifted from being an offender to a protector of human rights in the context of the European Arrest Warrant?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Since its rushed creation after the 9/11 attacks, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) has become a cornerstone of EU criminal law. It replaces traditional extradition with a streamlined system lacking most of the usual limitations. This has worried critics concerned about potential miscarriages of justice but pleased supporters who appreciate the faster return of more fugitives to face justice.
Despite concerns from some EU countries&amp;rsquo; constitutional courts, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) has long dismissed human rights criticisms of the EAW...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finally free? Detention, the European Arrest Warrant, and Julian Assange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Lanigan case, which deals with prolonged pre-trial detention and the European Arrest Warrant (EAW), is especially noteworthy given the UN&amp;rsquo;s recent statement regarding Julian Assange&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;arbitrary detention.&amp;rdquo; Assange, who is also facing an EAW, presents a unique situation. What can we learn from each of these cases about the intersection of detention length and the EAW?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unexpected turn of events? Case C-128/18 Dorobantu: the conditions of detention and the ECHR's relevance in the EU legal system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</guid><description>Ágoston Mohay, University of Pécs Faculty of Law
Introduction
The EU legal system is often viewed as a distinct entity, separate from both international and national law. Within this system, safeguarding fundamental rights is paramount. Article 6 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) establishes a three-pronged approach to fundamental rights protection: 1) the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union, 2) the EU&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and 3) general principles of EU law derived from the ECHR and shared constitutional values of member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU is currently hearing important cases regarding the European Arrest Warrant, questioning whether mutual trust should be blind or general with exceptions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 04:32:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</guid><description>Henning Bang Fuglsang Madsen Sørensen, Associate Professor, Department of Law, University of Southern Denmark
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held a hearing on February 15th, 2016, concerning two cases, Aranyosi and Caldararu, both addressing whether surrender under a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) should be refused if there are concerns about potential inhumane prison conditions in the requesting state. These cases, originating from the same German court, delve into the balance between the principle of mutual recognition in EU criminal law and the protection of fundamental rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for prosecutors from Belgium, France, and Sweden to issue European Arrest Warrants? The CJEU provides clarification on the necessity of independent public prosecutors.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 04:27:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</guid><description>Laure Baudrihaye-Gérard, Fair Trials The European Court of Justice (CJEU) has again clarified who can issue a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). This decision is significant for this key EU judicial cooperation tool, used countless times daily to extradite individuals between member states for investigations or to serve sentences.
Courts in Luxembourg and the Netherlands recently paused EAWs from prosecutors in Belgium, France, and Sweden to seek clarification from the CJEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Evolution of EU Criminal Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 06:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2014 was significant for the European Union, marked by events such as European Parliament elections, the establishment of a new European Commission, and notable legislative and case-law developments. This post, the first in a series, reviews key developments in specific EU law areas.
The most substantial change in EU criminal law occurred on December 1st, ending the five-year transition period for EU criminal law measures enacted before the Lisbon Treaty came into effect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 2: Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights under ordinary EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Can the EU penalize its member states for consistently violating human rights and the rule of law? And if so, how?
This article, the second in a three-part series, explores this question. The first installment analyzed the official mechanism designed for this purpose: Article 7 TEU. As previously discussed, this process, which could result in the suspension of certain EU membership rights for a member state, is highly political, offers limited involvement from EU courts, and is challenging to implement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit has not resulted in any legal changes yet, as the Court of Justice of the European Union continues to rule on the execution of European Arrest Warrants issued by the UK before Brexit Day.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While there are many legal discussions surrounding the impact of Brexit, the ultimate authority on these matters, at least for the EU, is the EU Court of Justice. The Court&amp;rsquo;s first ruling on Brexit, released today, clarifies the legal standing until Brexit Day and potentially influences the approach after that.
The judgment in the case of RO addressed whether Ireland remained obligated to enforce a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) issued by the UK considering its impending withdrawal from the EU after triggering Article 50 TEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New developments in EU case law regarding extradition to non-EU countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A recent European Court of Justice (ECJ) decision in the Pisciotti case concerning the extradition of citizens from one EU Member State to a non-EU country (in this instance, the USA) provides further legal precedent in this domain and carries potential implications for Brexit. This ruling expands on the September 2016 Petruhhin judgment, which dealt with extraditing citizens from one EU Member State to Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Restrictions on extradition to countries outside the EU due to EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) is a well-known EU law that streamlined extradition between member states, EU law generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern extradition to non-EU nations. Exceptions exist in cases of pre-existing treaties, like those with the USA and Norway/Iceland, or regarding asylum seekers. The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum laws restrict extraditing asylum-seekers before determining if the requesting country intends to persecute them.
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Petruhhin case has changed this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenges to Judicial Independence in the European Arrest Warrant System and Potential Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</guid><description>Dr Leandro Mancano, Senior Lecturer in EU Law, Edinburgh Law School
This blog post builds upon Leandro Mancano&amp;rsquo;s work, ‘You’ll never work alone: A systemic assessment of the European Arrest Warrant and judicial independence’, published in Common Market Law Review, Volume 58, Issue 3 (2021) pp. 683 – 718
Introduction
The European Arrest Warrant Framework Decision (EAW FD) has significantly altered cooperation between EU states on criminal justice matters (for its effects beyond the EU, see the Court of Justice’s judgments in Petruhhin – discussed here – and IN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Impact on UK's Participation in EU Policing and Criminal Law: EU Referendum Brief 5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
This piece examines the relationship between EU membership and UK policing and criminal law, exploring potential impacts of Brexit.
Summary
The UK held veto power over EU laws in this domain before the Treaty of Lisbon (enacted December 1, 2009). Subsequently, the UK secured two opt-out mechanisms: the ability to opt into (or out of) any new EU law in this area post-Treaty, and the option to retroactively opt out of pre-existing EU laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Alice Gross case: Examining EU law implications of allowing murderers to freely move within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British readers of this blog are likely aware of the case of missing teenager Alice Gross. A Latvian man, Arnis Zalkalns, is a person of interest in her disappearance. What makes this case more complex is that Mr. Zalkalns had a prior murder conviction in Latvia before relocating to the UK. He has since vanished, possibly returning to Latvia.
This raises several questions: how was a convicted murderer able to enter the UK undetected?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Arrest Warrants and the autonomy of public prosecutors as ruled by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Julia Burchett, PhD candidate at the Université libre de Bruxelles and the University of Grenoble
Introduction
Widely recognized as a cornerstone of EU criminal law, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as one of the most, if not the most, utilized tools for judicial cooperation in criminal matters among EU member states. This streamlined cross-border surrender procedure, designed for prosecution or execution of custodial sentences and detention orders, has replaced traditional systems relying on political involvement from individual member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How committed are Member States to safeguarding fundamental rights through the EU's common rules on detention?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</guid><description>By Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
In early February 2014, the Commission released a concerning report regarding &amp;ldquo;common rules on detention.&amp;rdquo; The report revealed that a mere 18 out of 28 EU member states had implemented any of the intended instruments. This study was purely quantitative and did not assess the effectiveness of the rules or their impact on individuals.
The inadequate implementation of these fundamental commitments to enhance detainee rights is worrisome...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Arrest Warrant and the German Constitutional Court: A new development in the legal conversation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The German Constitutional Court (GCC) has issued another impactful ruling, this time concerning fundamental rights. In an order published yesterday, the GCC exercised its authority to review the implementation of a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) from Italy to Germany. The subject, a US citizen convicted in Italy in absentia, argued that his conviction lacked due process and that Italian law provided no recourse for appeal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on conflicting EU and national law obligations regarding detention time limits. Is this a Prison Break?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD candidate, Utrecht University
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed the conflict between EU and national laws regarding detention periods for individuals subject to a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). Specifically, the case considered whether a longer EU-mandated detention period overrides a shorter national one, and whether unclear national legislation on this matter violates the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The argument for the UK to remain in the European Arrest Warrant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Maria Fletcher, Senior Lecturer in Law at the University of Glasgow, and Steve Peers, Professor of Law at the University of Essex, collaborated on this piece.
As of December 1, 2014, the UK government will have to decide which pre-December 2009 EU laws on criminal law and policing to potentially rejoin. One of the most contentious issues is whether to opt back into the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. This article presents the argument for rejoining this legal framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>