<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>10Gbps on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/10gbps/</link><description>Recent content in 10Gbps on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 14:22:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/10gbps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business moves online and companies shift their IT to the cloud, the demand for WAN bandwidth continues to rise. These days, even small businesses frequently require reliable dedicated internet and inter-office network bandwidth in the range of 100 Mbps to 1 Gbps. Larger companies, particularly those dealing with tech-heavy products, services, or medical imaging, can easily saturate Gigabit connections, making a transition to 10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN a worthwhile consideration.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item></channel></rss>