<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Council on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/council/</link><description>Recent content in Council on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/council/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to suspend Schengen due to Greece? Is it necessary to do so?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</guid><description>A recent leak of a Council document proposes a potential suspension of the Schengen system for a duration of up to two years. This proposal stems from what are being termed &amp;ldquo;systemic deficiencies&amp;rdquo; in Greece&amp;rsquo;s management of its external borders, particularly concerning the influx of refugees and migrants. Such a suspension would provide any Schengen country the option to reinstate or implement border controls along their shared internal borders. While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely that every Schengen country would exercise this option, it&amp;rsquo;s anticipated that several would choose to do so, especially given that a number already have active border controls in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU establishes significant limitations on the Commission's power to initiate actions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</guid><description>Steve Peers
It is a fundamental principle of EU law, as taught to every student of the subject, that the Commission has a near-monopoly on proposing new EU legislation - it is the &amp;lsquo;motor&amp;rsquo; of EU integration. This near-monopoly is often called the Commission&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;right of initiative&amp;rsquo;. But does this right also imply a right to withdraw proposals? And if it does, are there any limitations to this power? These questions were addressed by the CJEU in a significant ruling...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cracks in the unity of EU representation are evident in the Global Compact for Migration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</guid><description>Pauline Melin, PhD, Lecturer in European Law (Maastricht University) and Researcher at the Institute for European Law (KULeuven)
The UN Global Compact for Safe, Orderly and Regular Migration is scheduled for approval at a conference in Marrakesh, aiming for adoption as a UN General Assembly Resolution in New York on December 19th, 2018. However, the political climate surrounding the Compact&amp;rsquo;s adoption has become contentious. Since Austria, an active participant in the negotiations, withdrew its support in late October 2018, multiple EU Member States have followed suit, publicly questioning or withdrawing their support every week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion of the Legal Service of the Council on the Brexit agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</guid><description>This document presents the EU Council legal service&amp;rsquo;s analysis of whether the Brexit deal requires approval from both the EU and its Member States (a &amp;lsquo;mixed agreement&amp;rsquo;), or solely from the EU. It concludes that the EU can act alone due to the deal encompassing a blend of exclusive EU competences and competences shared between the EU and its member states. This aligns with Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law, which allows the EU to enact a treaty encompassing shared competences either independently or jointly with its Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU here to rescue legal aid, or to put it to rest? Evaluating discussions on the proposed Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</guid><description>by Claire Perinaud (FREE Group Trainee)
Access to legal aid is crucial for individuals facing criminal charges, enabling them to mount a proper defense. The EU is developing legislation to address this right, but its impact remains uncertain.
Progress of the Procedural Rights Roadmap
EU legislation concerning the procedural rights of suspects and accused individuals in criminal cases has been developing gradually since late 2009, following years of unsuccessful attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new executive board of the EU-ASEAN Business Council has been elected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (EU-ABC), the leading advocate for European companies in the ASEAN region, recently selected its Executive Board for the next two years. The election took place at their annual general meeting in Hanoi, Vietnam, on June 1st.
The new board members are:
François Guibert, Executive Vice-President, President, Greater China and South Asia Region, STMicroelectronics (Chairman) Donald Kanak, Chairman, Prudential Corporation Asia (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Theodoor Bakker, Partner, ABNR Law, Indonesia; Executive Board Member, European Chamber of Commerce, Indonesia (Chamber Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Martin Hayes, President, Robert Bosch SEA (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Treasurer), and Jan B...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU visa policy driving growth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s visa policy has traditionally focused on managing illegal immigration and security threats while considering foreign policy goals. However, in recent years, promoting economic growth, particularly in the tourism sector, has become increasingly important. This shift, initiated by a 2012 Commission communication, is evident in recent updates to the EU&amp;rsquo;s visa &amp;lsquo;whitelist&amp;rsquo;. The criteria for visa liberalization now include trade and investment, leading to the inclusion of Peru and Colombia after they signed a trade agreement with the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The labeling of the European Union in the International Maritime Organization is more of a focus than the EU's actual competence.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</guid><description>Cathleen Berg, doctoral student, University of Bayreuth
Advocate General (‘AG’) Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s November 25, 2021, opinion regarding a legal challenge from the European Commission against the European Council (Case C-161/20) highlights the contrasting interests between the European Union (‘EU’) and its Member States. This disagreement centers around how they exercise their authority within the International Maritime Organization (‘IMO’), an organization where the EU currently holds neither membership nor observer status. If the Court of Justice sides with AG Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s analysis, this case could significantly impact how the EU interest is represented within IMO committees, potentially shifting power from the Commission to the Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on immigration for students and researchers a minor advancement or a significant stride?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU has been working for many years to attract highly skilled individuals from non-EU countries. However, the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s reports indicate that the existing legislation, specifically the 2005 Researchers&amp;rsquo; Directive and the 2004 Students&amp;rsquo; Directive, have not significantly increased the number of students and researchers coming to the EU.
As a result, in 2013, the Commission recommended a complete overhaul of these laws. The European Parliament (EP) and the Council recently reached an agreement on the content of this proposal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Going from bad to worse? Examining the rule of law initiatives of the Commission and the Council</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</guid><description>Dimitry Kochenov* and Laurent Pech**
*Professor of EU Constitutional Law at the University of Groningen and Visiting Professor of Private Law at the Universita degli studi di Torino
**Jean Monnet Professor of EU Public Law, Head of the Law and Politics Department at Middlesex University London
The principle of the rule of law is a cornerstone of the European Union, as stated in Article 2 of the Treaty on European Union...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving institutional equilibrium and the process of negotiating global treaties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</guid><description>Andrés Delgado Casteleiro, Lecturer at Durham Law School
Introduction
In a ruling on Case C-425/13, Commission v Council, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with clarifying the Council&amp;rsquo;s authority in providing directions to the Commission during international negotiations. This case, decided on Thursday, specifically concerned the linking of Australia&amp;rsquo;s emissions trading system with the EU&amp;rsquo;s and involved examining the balance of power between the Council and the Commission during such negotiations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU guarantees the fundamental democratic and judicial oversight of the EU's foreign policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirmed in its recent decision in European Parliament v Council that the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) is subject to a minimum standard of democratic and judicial oversight.
The case involved a challenge by the European Parliament (EP) to the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign and ratify a treaty between the EU and Mauritius. This treaty pertained to the EU&amp;rsquo;s military operations against pirates operating in the Indian Ocean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the draft UK/EU renegotiation deal considered to be 'legally binding and irreversible'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The draft agreement regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership has sparked significant debate. While some, mostly within the UK, believe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough, others, primarily from the remaining EU member states, argue it grants excessive revisions to EU law for a single member state. These are primarily substantive concerns. While I have previously addressed some immigration-related issues within the draft, I will delve into other substantive matters later...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a difference this time? The Commission's work programme for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently released its yearly plan, outlining a different approach than previous years. Beyond the typical policy revisions, this Commission aims to introduce fewer new EU initiatives and withdraw more pending proposals.
Is this approach truly different from past Commissions? Comparing this year&amp;rsquo;s plan to those of previous Commissions offers insights.
In 2005, the incoming Barroso Commission put forward 32 pages of proposals, without mentioning any withdrawals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Imprisoning bankers: the latest EU Directive on enforcing criminal penalties for market abuse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU politicians likely feel a sense of relief as they&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a group even less popular than themselves: bankers. This unpopularity has only intensified as the global financial crisis and resulting austerity measures continue to impact ordinary citizens across numerous Member States. Politicians understand that targeting disliked groups rarely hurts them in the polls, leading EU institutions to enact legislation that could imprison bankers for specific wrongdoings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU once again reinforces the EU's external role with In Vino Veritas ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While only a handful of EU countries excel in wine production, it&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed throughout the Union. This simple truth underpins the recent Germany v Council ruling, where the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) bolstered the EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign relations authority, aligning with several previous decisions.
Background
This case centers on instances where Member States act as &amp;rsquo;trustees&amp;rsquo; of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external competence. This situation arises when the EU, despite having authority over a subject, cannot join a treaty or international organization dealing with it (a frequent occurrence)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guide for Law Students: Understanding EU Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge*
EU law is a captivating field of study that offers something for everyone, particularly those interested in politics, visionary thinking, and pragmatic solutions. Even if these aren&amp;rsquo;t your primary interests, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to study EU law due to its mandatory nature. However, it&amp;rsquo;s unlike any other legal system you may have encountered, defying categorization and fitting into no single box.
Before diving in, it&amp;rsquo;s helpful to reflect on your existing political perspectives on the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council is making initial progress in reforming EU data protection law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 data protection rules, laid out in a Directive, are undergoing a major transformation. The Commission has proposed a new Regulation, sparking discussions since early 2012. While negotiations continue, June saw a significant step forward: the Council (composed of EU Member States&amp;rsquo; justice ministers) agreed on its stance regarding the proposal&amp;rsquo;s application outside the EU. This agreement, though partial, provides valuable insight into the negotiation&amp;rsquo;s trajectory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A leaked document discloses that the EU is considering suspending the Schengen agreement for a period of two years.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</guid><description>Commentary by Steve Peers
This is Council document 14300/15, from December 1, 2015, called &amp;ldquo;Integrity of the Schengen area,&amp;rdquo; and sent to Coreper (representatives of EU member states) and the Council - likely the Justice and Home Affairs ministers meeting December 3rd and 4th. (An official version of the document is available here).
The first three sections are relatively standard (see here for discussion), but section 4 proposes initiating a process to formally permit the reinstatement of internal border controls within the Schengen zone for a duration of up to two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regarding knowledge as power: the transparency of procedures for making EU laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</guid><description>Päivi Leino (University of Helsinki)
A key promise made during the adoption of the Lisbon Treaty was increased transparency in EU law-making. However, this has not yet been realized. Access to documents related to EU legislative processes, especially &amp;ldquo;trilogues&amp;rdquo; (informal meetings between the European Parliament, the Council, and the Commission), has become a significant concern. This issue is highlighted in the new Interinstitutional Agreement (IIA) on Better Regulation, the European Ombudsman&amp;rsquo;s public consultation on trilogue transparency, and a legal appeal by a former LIBE Committee Secretariat head against the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s refusal to grant full access to legislative documents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Politicians 1, Architects 0: Constructing the EU Judicial System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently suggested that the EU should double the number of judges on the General Court and eliminate the EU Civil Service Tribunal. This piece examines the reasons behind this significant proposition for restructuring the EU judicial system and evaluates its merits.
Background
The EU judicial system has consistently expanded to accommodate a growing caseload. The Single European Act of 1987 allowed for the establishment of the Court of First Instance (renamed the General Court by the Lisbon Treaty) to support the Court of Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 3: Is there a lack of democracy in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, Middlesex University
Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The European Union is frequently criticized for being undemocratic or suffering from a &amp;ldquo;democratic deficit.&amp;rdquo; One common assertion is that all EU decisions are made by the unelected bureaucrats of the European Commission. This post will demonstrate why this criticism is fundamentally flawed. It stems from a misunderstanding of both the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s actual powers within the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes and how the European Commission is appointed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Additional research is required to further explore the EU's efforts to attract a greater number of non-EU researchers and students.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU member states, similar to other economically advanced nations, require a growing number of highly skilled workers. Current EU regulations have not significantly increased the influx of students and researchers from other countries, prompting the Commission to propose revisions in 2013. Both the European Parliament (EP) and the Council have agreed on their respective stances for the proposed law and are preparing to negotiate a final version...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</a></p></description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>