<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Search on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/search/</link><description>Recent content in Search on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/search/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discover financial products in Malaysia with GoBear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</guid><description>GoBear, a metasearch engine that simplifies financial product comparison, has officially launched in Malaysia. The platform offers unbiased, side-by-side comparisons of products like travel insurance and credit cards, with over 1,000 options currently listed and more to come.
Iskandar Ezzahuddin, GoBear&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, emphasized the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: &amp;ldquo;GoBear stems from the understanding that modern consumers demand convenient access to service information and straightforward product comparisons before making financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing Search Master: The Ultimate Microsoft Dynamics GP Search Tool - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-search-master-the-ultimate-microsoft-dynamics-gp-search-tool-part-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-search-master-the-ultimate-microsoft-dynamics-gp-search-tool-part-1/</guid><description>While &amp;ldquo;search&amp;rdquo; may not be a top concern for Dynamics GP users, a recent encounter made me realize its potential. A friend, who works with a competing ERP system, introduced me to the concept of &amp;ldquo;global search,&amp;rdquo; which initially seemed irrelevant to Dynamics GP. However, witnessing it firsthand changed my perspective.
My colleague, Andrew Dean, and I collaborated to create Search Master for Dynamics GP, a .NET application that revolutionizes data retrieval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-search-master-the-ultimate-microsoft-dynamics-gp-search-tool-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-search-master-the-ultimate-microsoft-dynamics-gp-search-tool-part-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check out Rahlat.com for the best travel prices in Arabic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</guid><description>Source: Rahlat.com website. Screen capture of the home page.
Rahlat.com is an Arabic travel search website designed by Arabs, for Arabs. Its goal is to help travelers in the Middle East and Gulf region find the best prices on flights and hotels. This free, independent metasearch engine is available in both Arabic and English, making it easy for users to compare prices from numerous travel and airline websites with just one click...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking for SQL objects and data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-sql-objects-and-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:56:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-sql-objects-and-data/</guid><description>When working with Dynamics GP and SQL Server, finding a specific table, stored procedure, table column, or data value is often necessary. This is especially true when troubleshooting issues with third-party modules where the table name or database location is unknown.
Several methods exist for searching SQL Server for a specific object. One straightforward approach uses the INFORMATION_SCHEMA views. These views are helpful when the object type (table, stored procedure, etc...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-sql-objects-and-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-sql-objects-and-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the fast Phone Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</guid><description>The Phone Finder helps locate lost smartphones, even if they&amp;rsquo;re on silent mode, for up to three years. When the Phone Finder device is clicked within 15 meters of the missing phone, the phone will ring, vibrate, and flash, making it easier to find. If the phone is out of range, the Phone Finder website displays its location on a map.
Source: Kickstarter
Creator Gabsow Tom selected Bluetooth 2.1 for its forward and backward compatibility, allowing the Phone Finder to work with any smartphone, regardless of its iOS or Android version...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TalentBin by Monster searches through social networks to find potential candidates for recruitment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 16:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</guid><description>Source: Monster website.
Monster recently launched its TalentBin platform across multiple regions to help businesses locate and engage skilled professionals. Functioning as a specialized search engine for talent, the software grants recruiters access to a pool of potential candidates who might not be easily discoverable through traditional methods. This is achieved by analyzing and leveraging professional information individuals share on various social media platforms.
TalentBin not only automates and simplifies the process of identifying potential candidates through site monitoring, data interpretation, and profile matching but also makes hiring more efficient, allowing recruiters to achieve more in less time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2019 Year in Review by Yahoo highlights Singapore's obsession with celebrity, wealth, and the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 05:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s 2019 Year in Review (YIR) reveals that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s internet users were captivated by stories surrounding Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s former PM Najib Razak, NUS student Monica Baey, and the Hong Kong protests.
The YIR, which analyzes search trends on Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s platforms, highlighted Najib Razak&amp;rsquo;s connection to the 1MDB scandal as a topic of significant interest. The Orchard Towers murder case, particularly Natalie Siow&amp;rsquo;s involvement, also drew considerable attention.
Actor Aloysius Pang&amp;rsquo;s passing during reservist training prompted searches related to training safety, while his girlfriend, actress Jayley Woo, also became a top search...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In its latest update, Yahoo! introduces cutting-edge search technology to Flickr</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 10:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/</guid><description>Yahoo! has introduced several major updates to Flickr, potentially revitalizing the platform. These updates include an improved search engine and simplified access, organization, discovery, and sharing of images and videos across various devices. Over 112 million users, including businesses, will benefit from these enhancements, making it easier to manage their combined 11 billion photos on Flickr.
Tim Miller, Head of Engineering at Flickr, expressed their aspiration to create a space for lifelong memories and highlighted the new tools&amp;rsquo; role in maximizing the platform&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 GB storage capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>