<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Animal Welfare on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/animal-welfare/</link><description>Recent content in Animal Welfare on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/animal-welfare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe.</description></item><item><title>EU Animal Welfare Rules' Extraterritorial Reach</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</guid><description>By Jessica Lawrence, PhD student, VU University Amsterdam
In the Zuchtvieh-Transport case, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that Regulation 1/2005, concerning the protection of animals during transport, applies beyond EU borders. This means that even when transport starts within the EU and ends outside its borders, the regulation still governs the journey. This decision is significant as it promotes animal welfare but also reflects the CJEU’s expanding interpretation of EU jurisdiction, stretching conventional international law principles on &amp;rsquo;territorial jurisdiction'.</description></item></channel></rss>