<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dark Fiber on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dark-fiber/</link><description>Recent content in Dark Fiber on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dark-fiber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choosing Dark Fiber vs Lit Fiber Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</guid><description>When applications require the bandwidth of fiber optic transmission, businesses face a choice: use existing &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber services or establish their own transport services using purchased or leased &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; fiber.
Deciding between these options involves weighing performance, cost, and installation time. Focusing solely on cost can lead to extended installation delays, potentially impacting operational needs. While a cost-effective solution might be suitable with ample planning time, immediate bandwidth demands may necessitate prioritizing availability over cost.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit to 10 Gigabit to 100 Gigabit WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business operations transition to the cloud and remote work becomes increasingly common, the demand for robust Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth has surged. Fortunately, providers offer excellent solutions for establishing high-bandwidth connections between locations and to the internet.
Fiber Optic Ethernet WAN
Fiber optic connectivity has become the leading choice for business bandwidth. Businesses still relying on older technologies like T1 lines, ISDN PRI, or DS3 bandwidth may be facing limitations and nearing obsolescence.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections.</description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points.</description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (EoDWDM)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</guid><description>Large organizations with high bandwidth needs, such as financial institutions and research labs, often require more capacity than standard telecom services offer. Building a custom fiber network by installing owned or leased dark fiber is one solution. Another is leasing wavelengths on existing fiber infrastructure.
Your Own Fiber Installing fiber optic cable on your own property provides control over both the physical space and network assets. However, construction costs increase significantly beyond your premises, especially when obtaining right-of-way permissions.</description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Community Builds Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a narrative circulating that our infrastructure is failing. While this might be true in some areas, a massive construction project is currently underway to create a robust fiber optic network across the nation. This &amp;ldquo;nervous system&amp;rdquo; for information technology promises practically limitless, low-lag bandwidth for the foreseeable future.
This surge in fiber optic infrastructure isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by failing systems, but rather by existing infrastructure reaching full capacity. The late 20th century witnessed a fiber optic boom, which initially seemed excessive when the tech bubble burst.</description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive.</description></item><item><title>Ciena Takes New Bandwidth Technologies On The Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</guid><description>Today, June 29th, those in Waltham, MA can experience cutting-edge carrier bandwidth technology firsthand. Visit the Ciena Innovation Lab to see live demonstrations of their latest optical, Ethernet, and software solutions. The lab will move to its next location in White Marsh, MD on July 15th.
What exactly is the Ciena Innovation Lab? It&amp;rsquo;s a mobile showcase housed in a semi-trailer, packed with the most recent advancements in telecom and networking.</description></item><item><title>Fiber - Dark, Lit and Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve decided that a fiber optic connection is no longer optional for your business; it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for productivity. The next step is determining which type of fiber to get. You might be surprised to learn there&amp;rsquo;s more than one option.
One Strand, Multiple Options
The foundation of all fiber optic connections is the transmission of information through modulated light waves within a glass strand. The fiber cable entering your building will appear the same regardless of the type.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768).</description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber.</description></item><item><title>Metro and Long Haul Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies with multiple locations and many employees may find that standard internet and private lines are insufficient for their needs. At a certain point, having complete control over your network becomes desirable, allowing you to establish performance benchmarks and implement upgrades as needed.
This sounds great, but how can you maintain the same level of control over a network that extends beyond your physical premises? Should you become your own network provider and install fiber optic cable to all your locations?</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward.</description></item></channel></rss>