<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marriott on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marriott/</link><description>Recent content in Marriott on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marriott/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park in Bangkok provides a versatile indoor-outdoor option for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</guid><description>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park, Bangkok – Marriott Executive Apartments is a unique venue for gatherings in the Sukhumvit area. Combining indoor and outdoor elements, it offers a versatile space for 30 to 160 guests. High ceilings and comfortable furniture create a welcoming atmosphere.
This lounge seamlessly blends several design concepts, creating a space that is both modern and traditional, as well as casual and elegant. Featuring lawn and garden views, the Lounge covers over 400 square meters and can host a variety of events from meetings to cocktail receptions.</description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India.</description></item><item><title>The Autograph Collection is ready to make its first appearance in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</guid><description>Australian companies have a new, upscale event location. Pier One Sydney Harbour is joining the Autograph Collection, a curated group of almost 60 unique hotels globally. This harborside hotel provides a picturesque setting for meetings and events, featuring eight meeting rooms with expansive water views.
Source: Marriott International. From Sydney to San Diego - Autograph Collection set to debut in three new world class destinations, including Pier One Sydney Harbour in Sydney, Australia.</description></item></channel></rss>