<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1741DABG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1741dabg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 1741DABG4000 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1741dabg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Very Corroded New Arrival from Sweden</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the Beogram 4000 from Sweden is a mixed bag. Positively, the aluminum surfaces, platter, arm cover lettering, and panels are in good shape, though a thorough cleaning is needed to determine their true condition. The internal components appear original, and the red position indicator is intact. However, there are significant drawbacks.
The black enclosure parts have an unprecedented amount of corrosion, exceeding typical wear and tear. This corrosion is present even on the underside and has also affected the chassis&amp;rsquo;s leaf springs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Restoration and a Test Spin with Oscar Peterson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable from Sweden in very corroded condition. To address the extensive corrosion, I chose to use another 4000 unit as a donor for parts. The donor unit, while missing some components, was free of corrosion.
My restoration process started with the carriage. I disassembled and cleaned the arm lowering system, damper, carriage rods, and spindle in an ultrasonic bath. Additionally, the sensor arm assembly was removed to lubricate the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>