<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SWIFT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/swift/</link><description>Recent content in SWIFT on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/swift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing the most rapid growth for SWIFT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</guid><description>SWIFT, a financial messaging service, has announced a significant increase in new corporate clients from the Asia Pacific region between May and December 2015, with 29 new companies joining the network.
SWIFT provides a unified platform for corporations to communicate financial information with their banks globally, leading to enhanced visibility and more efficient treasury operations. This connection allows for greater automation and standardization of financial processes. Currently, over 1,500 corporate groups, representing roughly 30,000 entities, utilize SWIFT to manage their banking relationships worldwide.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>Tips for achieving success with your startup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</guid><description>Thinking about launching a business from your great idea? Fabian Vandenreydt, a leader at Innotribe and the SWIFT Institute, who has witnessed the ups and downs of fintech startups, highlights key success factors.
First, clearly define the problem you&amp;rsquo;re addressing and ensure it&amp;rsquo;s a genuine issue. Developing a fantastic product is futile without a problem to solve. Vandenreydt emphasizes that starting with a problem is crucial for success.
Second, articulate a detailed solution implementation plan and understand your target market.</description></item></channel></rss>