<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Servo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/servo/</link><description>Recent content in Servo on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:11:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/servo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Gap at the Carriage Servo Pulley Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, significant longitudinal play was discovered in the threaded rod responsible for moving the carriage. This play resulted in a &amp;lsquo;clacking&amp;rsquo; noise whenever the carriage changed direction.
The issue was resolved by removing the servo pulley, damaged locking ring, and worn plastic washer. A new, thick 2-56 nylon washer, which fit snugly on the shaft, replaced the locking ring and washer. The locking ring became unnecessary as the pulley was secured with a setscrew.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts.</description></item></channel></rss>