<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Senior on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/senior/</link><description>Recent content in Senior on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/senior/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The World Economic Forum introduces its inaugural online leadership module for professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</guid><description>Professionals can now register for the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s first online leadership program, Global Information Technology Outlook. This six-week module, created for senior executives and fast-track leadership programs, offers a comprehensive overview of important new technologies transforming industries and society.
Professor Klaus Schwab, Founder and Executive Chairman of the World Economic Forum, highlighted the challenges leaders face understanding the increasingly complex and unpredictable world, largely due to rapid technological advancements. He stated that the Forum Academy module addresses this by giving leaders a better grasp of ongoing information technology transformations.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor examines consumer opportunities for individuals aged 60 and above</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 12:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Market research firm Euromonitor International has published a new report on the growing market of older consumers. Though businesses have often overlooked this demographic— individuals aged 60 and above— due to perceptions of low spending, limited income, and resistance to marketing, this group is expanding rapidly.
In 2014, the global population aged 60 and over reached 912 million, accounting for 12.6% of the total. By 2030, this segment is projected to increase to 1.</description></item></channel></rss>