<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Balance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/balance/</link><description>Recent content in Balance on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/balance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Balancing work and play on your smartphone: Four helpful tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. View the full infographic.
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming harder to separate our work and personal lives with smartphones being used for both. For instance, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Lumia 640 and 640 XL come with an Office 365 subscription.
Dr. Mark Batey, an Organizational Psychologist at Manchester Business School in the UK, collaborated with Microsoft to offer advice on finding a good balance:
1. Capture inspiration immediately.
He says, &amp;ldquo;Make use of note-taking apps on your phone to jot down brilliant ideas as they come, anytime and anywhere.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Installing New Lamps (Unit #1)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-installing-new-lamps-unit-1-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 02:53:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-installing-new-lamps-unit-1-/</guid><description>Today, I replaced all the indicator lamps in the Beomaster 1900.
I switched out the original incandescent Bass, Treble, and Balance indicator lamps with LED/resistor lamp assemblies. This is because incandescent lamps produce more heat, which can be seen in the white spots on the red lamp lenses. LED lamp assemblies generate less heat.
The board shown here originally housed the Bass, Treble, and Balance lamps. Anticipating future needs, I created more LED replacement lamp assemblies than the required three for this project.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Zero Force Balancing and Tracking Force Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:45:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring is almost ready for its initial test run. It&amp;rsquo;s time to fine-tune the zero force balance and set the appropriate tracking force. I documented this process in a video on my YouTube channel, featuring a Beogram 4002. You can find the video and my entire Beogram 4000 playlist through the provided links.
Let me share some observations from this specific Beogram 4000 restoration. The first stage involves achieving zero force balance.</description></item></channel></rss>