<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Luggage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/luggage/</link><description>Recent content in Luggage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/luggage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US airlines may now reject your standard carry-on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</guid><description>According to George Hobica from Airfarewatchdog, several US airlines have reduced the allowed size for carry-on luggage.
Traveling Hello Kitty statue at Taoyuan Airport,
Taiwan in 2008.
American, Delta, and United Airlines now permit carry-on bags with a maximum size of 22 inches in length, 14 inches in width, and 9 inches in height. The previous allowed width was 15 inches.
A Yahoo article from March highlighted United Airlines&amp;rsquo; stricter enforcement of carry-on size regulations.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's top business travel destinations are Tokyo and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</guid><description>A recent Samsonite survey explored the preferences of Singaporean business travelers, revealing Tokyo and Bangkok as the top choices for both business and leisure.
The survey, conducted by YouGov, involved over 500 Singaporean respondents who travel for business frequently. It found that Tokyo was the top business destination overall, particularly favored by those aged 35 to 44. Bangkok was the preferred choice for those over 45. Among younger travelers (under 34), Tokyo and London tied for the top spot.</description></item><item><title>Air China is providing a 50% discount on excess baggage fees to North America if paid in advance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</guid><description>Air China is the first Chinese airline to offer a prepaid excess baggage fee service for flights to North America. Travelers on Air China flights between Beijing and North America who anticipate exceeding their baggage allowance can now pay a discounted fee in advance. This service can be accessed through Air China ticketing offices globally or by calling their Member Services hotline.
Passengers who prepay for excess baggage will save 50% compared to airport rates, paying RMB 650 per piece or the equivalent in local currency.</description></item></channel></rss>