<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Year on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/year/</link><description>Recent content in Year on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:50:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starbucks in Asia is offering merchandise for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>To commemorate the 2016 Lunar Year of the Monkey, Starbucks has introduced a special collection of limited-edition items available in Asian markets. This merchandise includes:
[Image of Starbucks Monkey Mug]
Lunar New Year Monkey Mug
This red ceramic mug features a three-dimensional white monkey. Its body wraps around the side, its tail forms the handle, and its playful expression peeks out from the mug&amp;rsquo;s surface. The design is enhanced with a glossy red glaze, a contrasting yellow interior, and gold-colored vines.</description></item><item><title>The amount of money given as gifts for Chinese New Year in 2017 was calculated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</guid><description>Source: Gift Something blog post. Survey results for monetary gifts during Chinese New Year in Hong Kong. Values are in Hong Kong dollars.
Gift Something, a Hong Kong-based online retailer specializing in premium gifts, conducted a survey to understand the practice of giving red envelopes (known as angpow or red packets in Singapore, and lai see or red pockets in Hong Kong) during Chinese New Year. Traditionally, married couples give these envelopes to unmarried individuals during the first 15 days of the Lunar New Year to bring luck.</description></item><item><title>Quick reference guide for Chinese New Year in the Year of the Water Tiger</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:44:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</guid><description>In 2022, the ox replaces the rat as the third animal in the 12-year Chinese zodiac cycle, bringing hope for positive change. Chinese New Year commences on February 1st, ushering in a period of customary greetings and well wishes.
A wish for plentiful business opportunities.
生意兴隆.
Common greetings include &amp;ldquo;Happy New Year&amp;rdquo; (新年快乐, xin nian kuai le) and &amp;ldquo;Congratulations on receiving riches and prosperity&amp;rdquo; (恭喜发财, gong xi fa cai). Prosperity holds significant value in Chinese culture, particularly during Chinese New Year.</description></item><item><title>Quick guide for Chinese New Year in the year of the rat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</guid><description>The rat is associated with a new 12-year cycle in the Chinese zodiac. Legend has it that a race among all the animals determined which twelve would be featured in the zodiac. The animals finished in the following order: rat, ox, tiger, rabbit, dragon, snake, horse, goat, monkey, rooster, dog, and pig. This sequence dictates the order of the animals in the zodiac.
The rat is generally agreed to be very clever.</description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year.</description></item><item><title>EY introduces the Entrepreneur of the Year 2016 award in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, EY has announced the launch of the Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) 2016 award in Saudi Arabia. This year, the EOY will center on medium-sized enterprises, emphasizing their successes and the significance of their expansion and prosperity. The event has been conducted internationally for 29 years in 150 cities across 60 countries.
Ahmed I. Reda, Office Managing Partner at EY, Jeddah, and Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader at EY, states, “As we celebrate the 30th anniversary of the EOY program globally, we are excited to host the Saudi Arabia EOY program again this year.</description></item><item><title>Quick guide to Chinese New Year for the Year of the Pig</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</guid><description>The Lunar New Year period is a time when Chinese communities are filled with a palpable sense of celebration. Vibrant red decorations, believed to bring good luck, are prominently displayed, and the atmosphere is alive with the melodies of traditional festive music. The Chinese New Year, which falls on February 5th in 2019, is a time when well-wishes are exchanged, particularly during the first fifteen days of the lunar year.</description></item><item><title>Spotify celebrates the year of the rooster with a fresh playlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Welcoming the lunar new year.
To celebrate the Lunar New Year on January 28th, Spotify has launched a special playlist. This playlist features popular songs by artists born in the Year of the Rooster.
Interested?
Check out Spotify&amp;rsquo;s 恭賀新年 (welcoming the new year) playlist</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Facebook highlighted the things that caught the world's interest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
Facebook recently unveiled its &amp;ldquo;Year in Review&amp;rdquo; for 2015, featuring a dedicated website and video.
The company highlighted major global conversations, with the US presidential election taking the lead. This was followed by discussions surrounding the November 13 Paris attacks, the Syrian civil war and resulting refugee crisis, the Nepal earthquakes, and the Greek debt crisis.
On the entertainment front, &amp;ldquo;Game of Thrones&amp;rdquo; reigned supreme as the most popular TV show, while &amp;ldquo;Star Wars: The Force Awakens&amp;rdquo; dominated movie discussions globally.</description></item><item><title>CulinaryOn Singapore is offering Lunar New Year dinner experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Culinaryon Singapore. Yusheng with salmon sashimi.
For this Lunar New Year, CulinaryOn Singapore is offering special dinners starting on December 26th, 2017. These dinners feature premium six-to-eight course meals and include a taste of their cooking classes with a noodle-making activity. Guests can also choose to create their own desserts.
The eight-course premium menu features dishes such as yusheng with salmon sashimi, shiitake mushrooms with broccoli, crayfish braised longevity noodles, golden shrimp with honeydew mayo, and mango ice cream with pomelo.</description></item><item><title>Kaspersky Lab is providing security tips in preparation for the Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown is prominently featuring dog decorations in celebration of the new year.
As shoppers navigate the excitement and rush of Chinese New Year shopping, Kaspersky Lab cautions that they are more susceptible to making simple errors that could jeopardize their personal information.
Sylvia Ng, General Manager of Kaspersky Lab Southeast Asia, acknowledges that holiday shopping is a top priority for consumers. However, she emphasizes that it&amp;rsquo;s also an opportune time for cybercriminals.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce.</description></item></channel></rss>