<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internal Market on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internal-market/</link><description>Recent content in Internal Market on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internal-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk.</description></item><item><title>Does the new Council of Europe treaty on match-fixing comply with EU internal market regulations?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</guid><description>Tom Serby, a Senior Law Lecturer at Anglia Law School, Anglia Ruskin University, discusses the escalating problem of betting-related match-fixing in sports. He highlights the Council of Europe&amp;rsquo;s recent Convention aimed at tackling this issue, while also pointing out Malta&amp;rsquo;s legal challenge against it at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). Malta argues that the treaty clashes with internal market rules, particularly the freedom to provide services, underscoring the difficulties in achieving a unified international response to match-fixing.</description></item><item><title>Is the Essent ruling a new milestone in the legal precedent for the free movement of goods?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</guid><description>A Reassessment of Proportionality and Discrimination in Light of the Essent Case Filippo Fontanelli, Lecturer in International Economic Law, University of Edinburgh
Introduction
The September 11, 2014, Essent case (Joined Cases C-204 to C-208/12) judgment by the Court of Justice of the EU presents a nuanced analysis of proportionality, weighing factors such as promoting free energy trade, safeguarding the environment and human health, adhering to international emission reduction agreements, bolstering local employment, and encouraging energy self-sufficiency.</description></item><item><title>Beware of the Accountability Gap in the EU's Financial Supervisory Authorities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City Law School
The year 2010 saw the creation of three European Supervisory Authorities: the European Banking Authority, the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority, and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA). These authorities were established by the European Union in response to the then-unprecedented financial crisis. On January 22, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant judgment (Case C-270/12, United Kingdom v Council &amp;amp; Parliament) concerning recent legislation granting ESMA the authority to impose legally binding measures on financial institutions in Member States when the proper functioning of financial markets or the stability of the EU financial system is threatened.</description></item><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules.</description></item><item><title>Is there Friendly Fire in the European Union? AG Sharpston's view on the revised firearms Directive's validity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</guid><description>Niels Kirst (University Paris II – Panthéon-Assas)
Advocate General Sharpston (AG) issued an opinion on April 11, 2019, regarding the legitimacy of Directive 2017/853, known as the Firearms Directive. The Czech Republic challenged this directive, arguing that the European Parliament and the Council should not have used the internal market harmonization clause (Article 114 TFEU) as the legal basis for its adoption.
This case is noteworthy for several reasons. First, it centers around the crucial aspect of legal basis, drawing considerable attention from EU legal experts.</description></item><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to remain in the single market even after exiting the EU? The proposed lawsuit regarding Article 127 of the EEA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</guid><description>Could the UK Remain in the Single Market While Exiting the EU? Steve Peers
A potential legal battle questions whether the UK can remain part of the European Economic Area (EEA) even if it leaves the EU. This situation involves both international and national legal complexities. Let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the EEA itself.
Understanding the EEA
Established in 1994, the EEA treaty aimed to expand the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market to European Free Trade Area (EFTA) nations.</description></item><item><title>Balancing Health and Trade: The Scotch Whisky Association ruling on finding the right equilibrium.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School The Court of Justice has issued its judgment regarding the legality of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s minimum alcohol pricing (MUP) measure in Case C-333/14. Both the Scottish Government and the Scotch Whisky Association (SWA), which initiated the legal challenge, have expressed satisfaction with the ruling, although the SWA might be more content as the case now returns to Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Inner House of the Court of Session, which had referred it to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling on the Legality of the Revised European Firearms Directive: Gun Control in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 22:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, PhD candidate, Dublin City University
Introduction
On December 3rd, 2019, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) delivered its final ruling on a case concerning Czech firearm regulations. This judgment, providing guidance on EU lawmaking, addressed key EU law principles and refined their interpretations. Following terrorist attacks in Paris and Copenhagen, the EU legislature utilized its single market powers (Article 114 TFEU) to pass Directive (EU) 2017/853, amending existing firearms Directives 91/477 and 2008/51/EC.</description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice of the European Union mindful of the boundaries of EU authority?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Vilija Vėlyvytė, British Academy Post-Doctoral Fellow, Somerville College, University of Oxford
Photo credit: civarmy, by wikipedia
My recently published book, ‘Judicial Authority in EU Internal Market Law: Implications for the Balance of Competences and Powers’ (Hart Publishing 2022), investigates how the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) broadens the EU’s authority through its interpretation of EU internal market law.
The expansion of EU power, often referred to as ‘competence creep’, into areas where the EU lacks explicit authority, such as public health and social security, has been extensively discussed.</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General considers the intersection of public health, trade, and competition in setting minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School Background to the Opinion Advocate General (AG) Bot provided his opinion on September 3rd, 2015, regarding Case C-333/14, which involved the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to establish a minimum price per unit (£0.50) on alcohol sales. This Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) faced legal challenges from the Scotch Whisky Association, leading to the case reaching the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The CJEU was asked to determine whether the MUP aligned with the single Common Market Organisation (CMO) and the free movement principles of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item></channel></rss>