<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Control Panel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/control-panel/</link><description>Recent content in Control Panel on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:53:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/control-panel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Slow Slide Transport Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem was encountered where the tonearm carriage would continue moving after attempting to move it in reverse. This issue stemmed from a damaged keypad switch, specifically a bent contact terminal that prevented a clean shut-off connection. This damage was likely caused by a previous repair attempt.
To address this, the control panel and circuit board were removed to access and extract the switch terminals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</a></p></description></item><item><title> Beogram 8000 Type 5613: Finishing the floating chassis components, transformer C1 replacement &amp; cleaning the control panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</guid><description>Last night, I completed work on the floating chassis parts.
I reassembled the cleaned tangential drive parts, including the spindle, spindle nut, rails, and new bracket, and installed them on the floating chassis.
Following the service manual&amp;rsquo;s instructions, I lubricated the spindle. The lubricants are very similar to those used in the Beogram 400x, which is logical given that both turntable series have comparable tangential drive systems. The Beogram 8000 lubrication chart had one intriguing item that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t previously considered: an entry for lid damping grease...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Incandescent Light Bulbs in Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, all four incandescent bulbs in the control panel were found to be non-functional. This highlighted the fragility of these bulbs and emphasized the need for a more durable solution. To address this, the original bulbs were replaced with custom-designed LED replacements.
Specifically, the two position indicator bulbs were replaced with surface-mounted LED (SMD LED) units. The two bulbs responsible for illuminating the RPM trimmers were replaced with high-intensity red LEDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>