<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tool on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tool/</link><description>Recent content in Tool on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 03:31:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aptugo develops customized web software without requiring any training</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 03:31:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</guid><description>Aptugo, a software tool designed to help individuals without coding experience build websites, is currently in beta testing. Developed by the company Aptugo, the software is expected to launch in 2015.
&amp;ldquo;Aptugo has the potential to bridge the gap between large and small businesses. Users don&amp;rsquo;t need any programming knowledge to use it,&amp;rdquo; stated Gaston Gorosterrazu, Head of Aptugo. &amp;ldquo;However, those with coding experience can further enhance what Aptugo can do, as it is designed to empower users and expand their capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Discover your leadership potential with a revolutionary tool from Hogan Assessment Systems and Sirota</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-your-leadership-potential-with-a-revolutionary-tool-from-hogan-assessment-systems-and-sirota/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-your-leadership-potential-with-a-revolutionary-tool-from-hogan-assessment-systems-and-sirota/</guid><description>On July 30th at the Oasia Hotel Singapore, Dr. Tomas Chamorro-Premuzic, CEO of Hogan Assessment Systems, a leader in personality profiling and psychometric testing, along with Lewis Garrad, Managing Director Asia Pacific at Sirota, a performance consulting firm, will preview a new employee assessment model they jointly developed.
Launching in the Asia Pacific market in October 2015, the Engaging Leader tool will help companies and brands better identify and develop leadership potential.</description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership.</description></item></channel></rss>