<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Calais on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/calais/</link><description>Recent content in Calais on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/calais/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services.</description></item><item><title>Is the Dublin Regulation coming to an end? Where should unaccompanied children seek asylum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Recent events have sparked debate concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin III Regulation, which dictates where asylum seekers must apply for asylum within the EU. A British court ruled that the UK is responsible for the asylum claims of unaccompanied children in France, particularly those in Calais, if they have family in the UK. Additionally, a press release suggested the Commission may soon propose significant changes to the Dublin rules.</description></item></channel></rss>