<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Genesys on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/genesys/</link><description>Recent content in Genesys on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/genesys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever.</description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales.</description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question.</description></item></channel></rss>