<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resellers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/resellers/</link><description>Recent content in Resellers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/resellers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Who Says You Can't Sell T1 Lines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</guid><description>While your business thrives by selling business phone systems or computer networking services, you might be missing out on providing clients a complete package. This missing piece? PBX trunk lines or WAN network connections. You&amp;rsquo;d definitely want a share of this profitable market.
You might assume this area belongs solely to phone companies. They prefer you think that way. When businesses see an available &amp;ldquo;T1&amp;rdquo; jack, they often contact their local phone provider directly.</description></item><item><title>Environmentally Friendly Hosting is Super Green</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/environmentally-friendly-hosting-is-super-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/environmentally-friendly-hosting-is-super-green/</guid><description>A growing number of website creators are seeking environmentally responsible technology solutions. Super Green hosting offers an eco-friendly approach.
Super Green Hosting prioritizes environmental responsibility, aiming to minimize their carbon footprint. Internet usage consumes electricity, often generated from non-renewable sources like coal, contributing to carbon emissions.
To mitigate this, they focus on reducing power consumption, utilizing renewable energy like wind power, and planting trees to offset remaining carbon emissions, achieving carbon neutrality.</description></item></channel></rss>