<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>78SSBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/78ssbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 78SSBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/78ssbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Lubrication of Platter Motor Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the DC motor was lubricated. This particular motor uses brushes and has simple sleeve bearings.
To access the bearings for lubrication, the pulley and outer housing were removed. The pulley is attached to the shaft with glue, allowing for easy removal. After taking out two small screws, the housing can be opened and the motor taken out.
Next, the black rubber vibration insulation boot was removed, revealing the circuit board connected to the brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>My work on restoring the 4002 continues, and today involved polishing the hood – a task that&amp;rsquo;s quite a workout! The plexiglass hood had some noticeable scratches:
I began by using 200 grit sandpaper to create a consistent surface:
Then I gradually polished it using Micromesh polishing cloths:
The final stage involved Micromesh Micro-Gloss:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable and have reached the stage of addressing cosmetic details. A common issue with this model, as with approximately 90% of them, is a worn keypad. The original coating deteriorates over time due to exposure to skin oils and acids. This results in unsightly smudges, especially on units that have seen regular use. I recently acquired some refurbished keypads from a contact in Denmark to have on hand for my restoration projects.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Infusing Oilite Brass Bearings of DC Motor with Oil Under Vacuum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-infusing-oilite-brass-bearings-of-dc-motor-with-oil-under-vacuum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-infusing-oilite-brass-bearings-of-dc-motor-with-oil-under-vacuum/</guid><description>Restoring the DC motors found in Beogram 4002/4 turntables (models 551x and 552x) presents a significant challenge. Many of these motors exhibit loud operation and inconsistent rotational speed due to their age. While lubricating the motor&amp;rsquo;s brass sleeve bearings with grease might seem like a solution, this often only yields temporary improvement.
The root of the issue lies in the use of &amp;lsquo;oilite&amp;rsquo; bearings, which are designed to operate without external lubrication.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Floating Chassis Height</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</guid><description>After adjusting the main platter bearing in a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to set the height of the floating chassis. The goal is to make sure the aluminum surface of the platter is level with the surrounding aluminum panels. You can adjust the height by turning the nuts on the leaf springs that hold the chassis and provide vibration isolation. Using an 8 mm hex wrench is recommended.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002/4004: Replacement of a Broken Cable Clamp/PCB Holder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a broken cable clamp/PCB holder presented an opportunity to test a replacement part file. A fellow Beogram enthusiast from New Zealand shared the file, and in return, received access to parts in my Shapeways store. Photos document the broken clamp, the 3D-printed replacement, and the final installation. The new clamp fits securely with the PCB, keeping the audio cable properly positioned. With the successful trial complete, the part was made available for purchase in my store for other B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a Plug-In Ready SMD LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I installed the latest iteration of my SMD LED light source for the tracking sensor.
Previously, I designed a drop-in SMD LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb fixture, which worked well. However, it still relied on the original, cumbersome tracking sensor sensitivity adjustment process. This process involves carefully positioning the light sensors relative to the light source, a task made difficult by the mechanism&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and the adjustment mechanism&amp;rsquo;s coarseness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival on Beolover's Bench - A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 13:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench-a-first-impression/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable arrived yesterday, requiring some care. My initial assessment today was positive. The deck is quite clean with minimal cosmetic issues. The customer took great care in packaging, using a double box and securing the sub-platter with high-density foam. However, the tonearm transport support clamp detached during shipping. Thankfully, the arms were also protected with foam, preventing any damage.
The presence of orange fragments suggests that the transport lock bushings crumbled during shipment, a common problem with the 5513 model.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of the Latest Version of the Beogram Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>While restoring my Beogram 4002 (5513), I decided to improve the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control I had previously designed. I added a &amp;ldquo;pairing&amp;rdquo; feature to prevent conflicts with Apple TVs and other devices that use Apple remotes. To completely eliminate the need to touch the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s delicate keypad, I also included remote switching between 33 and 45 RPM. A detailed video about the latest version explains the functions and demonstrates the remote and its pairing process:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacement of Rusty RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 14:56:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration, I swapped out the old, worn-out RCA plugs. The originals were showing their age.
I chose robust, gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs as replacements. These are excellent for transmitting the low-voltage MMC signal to the amplifier. The metal housing provides superior shielding against electromagnetic interference, ensuring signal integrity. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look after soldering:
And here they are secured:</description></item></channel></rss>