<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contract on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contract/</link><description>Recent content in Contract on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 17:33:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contract/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Salary growth is expected in Southeast Asia as there is a high demand for IT skillsets in key sectors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s IT sector is expected to experience high demand for skilled professionals and contract workers in 2018, particularly in fintech, healthcare, and technology.
Specialized skills will be highly sought after in 2018 across accounting and finance, human resources, sales and marketing, and technology sectors.
According to the 2018 Salary Survey by Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, the economic outlook for the coming year is positive. The survey anticipates that continued digitalization and market expansion in Southeast Asia will fuel salary growth.</description></item><item><title>Contract positions are the perfect solution for companies in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</guid><description>A recent survey by Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, indicates a rise in contract employment in Singapore. The Singapore Contracting Survey reveals that hiring managers are increasingly turning to skilled contract workers due to difficulties in obtaining approval for permanent positions. Many companies are implementing hiring freezes, often mandated by their headquarters, leading managers in Singapore to seek adaptable, temporary staffing solutions.
The survey, which polled over 300 professionals in Singapore with contracting experience, explored the advantages and disadvantages of contract work.</description></item><item><title>The Unified Electronic Contract will come into effect in January 2018 in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-unified-electronic-contract-will-come-into-effect-in-january-2018-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 17:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-unified-electronic-contract-will-come-into-effect-in-january-2018-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: DED. Al Zaabi.
Dubai Economy&amp;rsquo;s Commercial Compliance &amp;amp; Consumer Protection (CCCP) sector held a workshop for electronics businesses. The goal was to clarify the rules of the unified contract. Starting in 2018, this contract is required for selling or servicing electronic devices and components in the UAE.
This Unified Electronic Contract combines sales, warranty, maintenance, and spare parts agreements into a single document. It became mandatory in early January 2018 and must detail the product, serial number, and purchase date.</description></item></channel></rss>