<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Belt on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/belt/</link><description>Recent content in Belt on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/belt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Exchanging the Rubber Parts in the Tape Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</guid><description>My Beocord 9000 restoration project saw some good progress. I recently installed new rubber tires on the idler wheels of the tape drive mechanism to address a rewinding issue. The deck wasn&amp;rsquo;t rewinding smoothly, becoming very slow and sometimes even stopping at the end of the process. This seemed like a common problem attributed to hardened idler wheel rubber, as suggested by Beoworld.org.
However, upon disassembling the mechanism, I discovered that a previous repair attempt had damaged a crucial friction pad, which was the root cause of the problem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Preamplifier and the Radio Amplifier Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s review the Beocord 5000! This model contains many tantalum capacitors that, due to their age (around 35 years), should be replaced. Tantalum capacitors pose a fire risk if they short circuit because of the intense heat released when tantalum reacts with oxygen. While tantalum capacitors were favored in the 1970s due to their smaller size compared to aluminum electrolytic capacitors, advancements in manufacturing have closed the size gap. Today, modern aluminum capacitors can be just as small as the older tantalum ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Power Supply, Motor Control, Electronic Switch and Operational Control Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</guid><description>The restoration continues! Today, I replaced the remaining electrolytic capacitors on my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716). New electrolytics bring peace of mind!
The power supply board, including its reservoir and AC motor capacitors, along with the motor control, electronic switch, and operational control boards, were all addressed:
The Motor Control board, responsible for the take-up motor, had only one Tantalum capacitor that needed replacement:
Here it is after the replacement:
Next is the Electronic Switch board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating Recording Current and Bias</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</guid><description>Pleased with the seemingly functional Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape mechanism, an initial test recording was conducted using a waveform generator. Playback revealed a 3 dB channel imbalance on the Peak Program Meter (PPM), indicating a calibration issue. This was unsurprising given the deck&amp;rsquo;s age and highlighted the fortunate performance of a previously rebuilt Beocord 5000 in a Beolab 6000 setup, which operated well without calibration. To establish a solid calibration baseline, a reliable frequency response measurement was deemed essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating the Peak Program Meters (VU Meters)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</guid><description>After reassembling and successfully testing a Beocord 5000 tape deck, I decided to calibrate its Peak Program Meters (PPMs) according to the service manual.
Instead of directly inputting a 300 Hz signal into the Dolby B ICs as the manual suggested, I opted to feed a 25 mV, 300 Hz signal into the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inputs while in record mode (paused). Using a multimeter, I adjusted the recording levels to achieve the specified 740 mV RMS output at the Dolby B ICs (pin 7), allowing for the calibration of the PPMs&amp;rsquo; 0 dB level...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: First Contact and Installing New Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-first-contact-and-installing-new-belts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 10:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-first-contact-and-installing-new-belts/</guid><description>I recently received a Beocord 9000 cassette deck that needed some care. It was shipped in its original Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen box, which was then placed inside a second box for protection. However, the B&amp;amp;O box was incorrectly oriented inside the outer box, likely resulting in an upside-down journey. The original box had some water damage:
Thankfully, the Beocord 9000 itself appeared unharmed:
As a rule, I never connect devices to power immediately after unpacking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-first-contact-and-installing-new-belts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-first-contact-and-installing-new-belts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Belt Deterioration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-belt-deterioration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 13:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-belt-deterioration/</guid><description>Replacing rubber belts is a standard restoration procedure for old audio equipment. However, Beocord 8000 and 9000 tape decks often require an extra step: cleaning up the mess left behind by deteriorated belts.
Most Beocords I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered have belts degraded into a sticky, gooey substance, probably due to prolonged storage in warm conditions. Like cars, these devices suffer from lack of regular use.
This picture shows the residue found in this Beocord, a common sight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-belt-deterioration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-belt-deterioration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Exchanging the Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 12:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</guid><description>After removing the tape mechanism from the Beocord 5000 (4715) for rebuilding, I replaced the old, worn-out belts. My process was largely based on the one shown in my YouTube video.
However, I made one key improvement. I learned that the eject lever&amp;rsquo;s alignment with the tape mechanism is vital for the eject key to function correctly after reassembly. Previously, I had only marked the position of part #256 (&amp;ldquo;lever&amp;rdquo;) with a pencil, leading to time-consuming readjustments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>