<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>C2C on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/c2c/</link><description>Recent content in C2C on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:30:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/c2c/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Barter and location-based services contribute to Jualo's success in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Chaim Fetter, a Dutch programming prodigy and entrepreneur, has balanced building businesses with a spirit of exploration and philanthropy. As a teenager, he created his first online venture, developing e-commerce websites. He spent his twenties traveling in Southeast Asia before establishing the Peduli Anak Foundation in 2005 to support former street children in Lombok, Indonesia.
Source: Jualo website.
Last year, Fetter transitioned the foundation&amp;rsquo;s leadership to a local team, relocating to Jakarta to pursue a new business venture, Jualo.</description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community.</description></item></channel></rss>