<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pantone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pantone/</link><description>Recent content in Pantone on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:29:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pantone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Pantone color of the year for 2018 is Ultra Violet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pantone-color-of-the-year-for-2018-is-ultra-violet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:29:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pantone-color-of-the-year-for-2018-is-ultra-violet/</guid><description>Source: Pantone. PANTONE Ultra Violet 18-3838.
Pantone, a subsidiary of X-Rite and a leading authority on color systems and technology, declared PANTONE 18-3838, Ultra Violet, as its highly anticipated Color of the Year for 2018. According to Pantone, this shade embodies originality, creativity, and forward-thinking.
For nearly two decades, Pantone&amp;rsquo;s Color of the Year has significantly shaped product development and purchasing choices across diverse industries, including fashion, home furnishings, industrial design, packaging, and graphic design.</description></item><item><title>AkzoNobel has chosen Denim Drift as the Color of the Year for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 02:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</guid><description>Source: AkzoNobel. From left: Farhan Akhtar, Dulux Brand Ambassador; Rajiv Rajgopal, Director of Decorative Paints, AkzoNobel South Asia Cluster; Jeremy Rowe, Managing Director of AkzoNobel Decorative Paints, South East &amp;amp; South Asia, Middle East; and Shraddha Kapoor, Dulux Brand Ambassador, revealed Denim Drift as the Colour of the Year for 2017.
AkzoNobel, a global paints and coatings company, specialty chemicals producer, and the manufacturer of Dulux paints in India, has announced Denim Drift as the Colour of the Year for 2017.</description></item></channel></rss>