<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wallet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wallet/</link><description>Recent content in Wallet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 22:32:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wallet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dash, the mobile payment service by Singtel, introduces a new rewards program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 22:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</guid><description>Singtel Dash users now have a new incentive to use the app – the Dash Rewards program. This program allows users to earn points for various transactions, including payments and overseas remittances. These points can then be redeemed for rewards such as Singtel mobile services, grocery vouchers, dining options, retail discounts, and lifestyle benefits.
Source: Singtel website. Dash Rewards incentivizes Dash users for making transactions.
Dash Rewards aims to provide more value to users by awarding points for every dollar spent.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Insurance is now available through Singtel's Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash app is launching Dash EasyEarn, a new financial product offering a 2% annual return. This insurance savings plan is available exclusively through the Dash app and is backed by Etiqa Insurance.
Source: Singtel. Dash EasyEarn is a fully digital insurance product, allowing users to manage their plans entirely through the Singtel Dash app.
This innovative addition to the Dash app, which already provides various services like payments and mobile top-ups, aims to make saving simple and accessible.</description></item></channel></rss>