<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Migration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/migration/</link><description>Recent content in Migration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cracks in the unity of EU representation are evident in the Global Compact for Migration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</guid><description>Pauline Melin, PhD, Lecturer in European Law (Maastricht University) and Researcher at the Institute for European Law (KULeuven)
The UN Global Compact for Safe, Orderly and Regular Migration is scheduled for approval at a conference in Marrakesh, aiming for adoption as a UN General Assembly Resolution in New York on December 19th, 2018. However, the political climate surrounding the Compact&amp;rsquo;s adoption has become contentious. Since Austria, an active participant in the negotiations, withdrew its support in late October 2018, multiple EU Member States have followed suit, publicly questioning or withdrawing their support every week.</description></item><item><title>CA Technologies is offering a free migration tool for Windows XP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</guid><description>If you need to upgrade from Windows XP, there&amp;rsquo;s a free tool that can help. Developed by CA Technologies, CA Desktop Migration Manager (CA DMM) is a software solution designed to manage, upgrade, and maintain laptops and desktops. It can also migrate a Windows XP computer to a more secure operating system.
&amp;ldquo;Since Microsoft is no longer providing ongoing technical support and security updates for Windows XP, our customers are exposed to vulnerabilities and significant risks,&amp;rdquo; says Vic Mankotia, VP of Solution Strategy for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies.</description></item><item><title>Italian Court of Cassation: Vos Thalassa ruling clears migrants who opposed being sent back to Libya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/italian-court-of-cassation-vos-thalassa-ruling-clears-migrants-who-opposed-being-sent-back-to-libya/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/italian-court-of-cassation-vos-thalassa-ruling-clears-migrants-who-opposed-being-sent-back-to-libya/</guid><description>Yasha Maccanico, Statewatch
Photo credit: Sergio D&amp;rsquo;Afflitto, via Wikimedia commons In December 2021, Italy&amp;rsquo;s highest court overturned the convictions and prison sentences of two men who were found guilty of leading a protest on a rescue ship. The men, from Ghana and Sudan, were part of a group of 67 migrants rescued from a distressed boat in the Libyan Search and Rescue zone in July 2018. Initially, the rescue ship was instructed to take the migrants to Italy, but later received orders to return them to Libya.</description></item><item><title>Best investment migration programmes for wealthy individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</guid><description>The increased global demand for residence and citizenship-by-investment programs, particularly among wealthy investors, highlights the desire to overcome limitations posed by single jurisdictions in the wake of COVID-19. Recognizing this, Deep Knowledge Analytics and Henley &amp;amp; Partners have collaborated to create the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
Source: Henley &amp;amp; Partners website. Illustration for the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
This digital publication provides a detailed analysis, interactive tools, and unique perspectives on the efficiency of countries offering these programs during the pandemic, and their potential as future havens for longevity.</description></item><item><title>It is time for the EU to address the origins of informal agreements in EU migration law when cooperating on migration with third countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</guid><description>Dr Céline Hocquet, Teaching Fellow, Birmingham Law School, University of Birmingham
Photo credit: Issam Barhoumi, via Wikimedia Commons
As the EU proposes yet another collaboration with a non-EU nation to manage migration beyond its borders, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to critically examine the EU&amp;rsquo;s externalization policy and its use of informal cooperation. This analysis should consider the historical, legal, and political context of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external migration and asylum policy.
From the EU-Turkey to the EU-Tunisia deal?</description></item><item><title>Many Singaporeans are aware of human trafficking but underestimate its prevalence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</guid><description>The International Organization for Migration’s X Campaign (IOM X), in collaboration with USAID, the US Embassy in Singapore, and Microsoft, recently released findings from their pilot outreach program, IOM X Connect Singapore. This initiative sought to increase awareness about human trafficking in Singapore.
During the project, students from the National University of Singapore (NUS) and Singapore Management University (SMU) utilized the newly developed IOM X Learn, Act and Share App. They tested the knowledge of 100 Singaporean residents on the topic of human trafficking.</description></item></channel></rss>