<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Booking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/booking/</link><description>Recent content in Booking on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/booking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the ability to hail a cab using Hailo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</guid><description>Hailo, a highly-rated taxi app boasting more five-star reviews than any other similar service, launched in Singapore on October 29th. With a global network of over 60,000 drivers and a strong user base exceeding 1.4 million, Hailo reports a ride request every two seconds somewhere in the world.
Source: Hailo. From left: Benny Lim, Managing Director, SMRT Road Holdings; Ron Zeghibe, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Executive Chairman, Hailo Global, and Yu Hsiang Wong, General Manager, Hailo Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi cab booking app is now available in Kuala Lumpur and will soon be expanding to more countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a cab booking app, has expanded its reach to Malaysia and will be pre-installed on Celkon phones in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal.
Developed by India-based On Time Technologies, TaxiPixi launched in Malaysia this week. Celkon, a mobile phone manufacturer, will pre-install the app on its devices in several countries. Pradeep Yerraguntla, Celkon&amp;rsquo;s Head of Digital, stated that Celkon will promote the app through its app store and website, targeting consumers in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Makani numbers in Dubai assist taxi drivers in locating their customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</guid><description>Source: RTA. Dubai taxis are now connected to the city through the Makani system.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) Public Transport Agency has successfully connected 4,500 taxis operated by franchise companies to the Dubai Municipality&amp;rsquo;s Makani System. This system utilizes unique coordinates, known as Makani numbers, for precise building location.
Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems at RTA&amp;rsquo;s Public Transport Agency, highlighted the significant role of the Makani System...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can book Mwasalat taxis without using the mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Mwasalat. Taxi Butler devices will offer taxi booking
services.
Mwasalat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Taxi Butlers,&amp;rdquo; kiosks that streamline taxi bookings. This initiative is part of the public transportation company&amp;rsquo;s ongoing plan to modernize Oman&amp;rsquo;s taxi services.
Taxi Butlers eliminate the hassle of individual driver contact by allowing users to pre-book taxis. The kiosks offer the convenience of booking multiple taxis and provide passengers with real-time updates on arrival times, driver information, and vehicle arrival alerts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Journeyful has revamped its website, incorporating additional listings and enhancing rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</guid><description>Source: Journeyful. The Journeyful 2.0 website.
Journeyful, a company located in Singapore, has relaunched an updated website for its rewards-based online travel agency, Journeyful.com. The new and improved &amp;ldquo;Journeyful 2.0&amp;rdquo; website features a selection of over 200,000 hotels globally, a price-match guarantee, and Facebook integration.
The redesigned website includes Journeyful MICE, which offers comprehensive solutions for business conferences, corporate events, and incentive trips. A Journeyful representative explained that once an online inquiry is submitted, MICE consultants collaborate offline with the organization to personalize solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi is working to increase the popularity of taxis in India and other countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</guid><description>A new free taxi booking app called TaxiPixi is gaining popularity in India. Available on Android, iOS, and online, this less-than-a-year-old service offers reliable options for booking cabs, motorcycles, or auto-rickshaws for point-to-point trips or hourly packages.
TaxiPixi&amp;rsquo;s online home page
Co-founder and CEO Kajal Dubey believes that the biggest obstacles to increased taxi use are the uncertainty of finding a ride and the perception that taxis are much more expensive than driving...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>