<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smartwatch on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smartwatch/</link><description>Recent content in Smartwatch on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:07:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smartwatch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Garmin unveils a new smartwatch with GPS and music capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-unveils-a-new-smartwatch-with-gps-and-music-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-unveils-a-new-smartwatch-with-gps-and-music-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Garmin.
The vivoactive 3 Music. Garmin Singapore has launched the vívoactive 3 Music, a GPS smartwatch that incorporates both music playback and Garmin Pay contactless payments. Users can make purchases directly from their wrist using their Garmin Pay wallet, enjoying the same benefits as their physical cards but with added convenience.
According to Jimmy Chuang, Regional Product Manager at Garmin, the company aims to make its products an integral part of everyday life, and they believe music is a key feature in achieving that goal.</description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities.</description></item></channel></rss>