<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>100 Mbps on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/100-mbps/</link><description>Recent content in 100 Mbps on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/100-mbps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Corporate Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</guid><description>For medium to large businesses, a 100 Mbps connection speed is becoming the new norm. While this might seem excessive and expensive, it&amp;rsquo;s actually neither. In essence, Fast Ethernet is taking over the role of DS3.
A decade ago, a 1.5 Mbps T1 line was considered high bandwidth. Today&amp;rsquo;s need for 100 Mbps reflects the significant evolution of application requirements. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from basic video conferencing to high-definition, two-way video and telepresence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Colocation Center Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 23:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/</guid><description>Businesses frequently turn to colocation to avoid the financial burden of owning and operating their own data centers. A major advantage of colocation is access to high bandwidth at significantly reduced costs.
](http://www.etherrabbit.com/)Colocation centers, or colos, are facilities that house the data center needs of numerous businesses. Maintaining a server farm involves considerable infrastructure and resources, including servers, network equipment, racks, power, cooling, security, and round-the-clock staff. Colocation provides all these elements as a service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>