<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economy/</link><description>Recent content in Economy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hong Kong government confirms the schedule for releasing statistics from March to May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</guid><description>Companies interested in monitoring the Hong Kong economy can stay informed through press release schedules published by the Hong Kong government. These releases provide insights into various economic indicators.
A schedule of upcoming releases for March to May 2014 is provided below, starting with March 3rd.
March 2014
3rd: January 2014 Retail Sales Statistics
7th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Statistics on Vessels, Port Cargo, and Containers
10th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Quarterly Business Receipts Indices for Service Industries</description></item><item><title>Vietnam receives report card from World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economy shows resilience due to strong domestic demand and export-focused manufacturing, as highlighted in the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s recent Taking Stock report. The country&amp;rsquo;s mid-term economic outlook appears positive, with GDP projected to grow by 6% in the current year.
The report, a semi-annual assessment of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economic performance, notes that economic growth decelerated to 5.9% in the first nine months of the year. This slowdown is largely attributed to a severe drought that hampered agricultural output, reduced oil production, and weakened external demand.</description></item><item><title>What impact could Brexit have on the younger generation? EU Referendum Briefing 2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A UK exit from the European Union, or &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; could have significant implications for young people, impacting their education, travel opportunities, and economic prospects.
Education
The EU does not control educational content or matters like tuition costs. Instead, its involvement lies in cross-border educational aspects, including promoting student and teacher mobility through initiatives like the Erasmus program. Established in 1987, this EU law-based program facilitates student exchanges across various educational levels.</description></item><item><title>Strategies For The Hunkered Down Economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</guid><description>While the new year has arrived, the economic situation remains challenging. Unemployment is still high, companies are focusing on cost-cutting over revenue growth, and uncertainty about the future persists. Consumers are tightening their belts and spending less, leaving businesses with little choice but to do the same. It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to hesitate before making significant moves when the path ahead is unclear.
Does this mean your business is stuck or in irreversible decline?</description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste</description></item><item><title>The President of China promises to create a thriving society</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-president-of-china-promises-to-create-a-thriving-society/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-president-of-china-promises-to-create-a-thriving-society/</guid><description>In his New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve address in Beijing, Chinese President Xi Jinping welcomed 2020 by promising to meet the centenary goal of achieving moderate prosperity for everyone, as reported by China Daily.
Xi urged the nation to &amp;ldquo;seize the day and live it to the full.&amp;rdquo;
He highlighted several achievements:
China&amp;rsquo;s 2019 gross domestic product (GDP) is projected to be nearly US$14.37 trillion, with per-capita GDP expected to reach US$10,000. China has established diplomatic ties with 180 countries.</description></item><item><title>Schroders predicts that the second half of 2016 will be challenging, but still an improvement over the first half</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</guid><description>Schroders Investment Management believes the global economy will improve after weak growth in the first half of 2016.
Keith Wade, Chief Economist &amp;amp; Strategist at Schroders, states that there are indicators of increasing growth in the next two quarters of 2016, with previous economic obstacles diminishing. Consumer spending is also rising due to renewed credit growth. However, Wade cautions that 2016 will likely not see robust global growth.
Wade attributes much of the sluggishness to the aftermath of the global financial crisis, with various economic actors still adapting.</description></item><item><title>The IMF is analyzing the economy of the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) mission, headed by Chikahisa Sumi, has assessed the Philippine economy&amp;rsquo;s performance as positive but believes there&amp;rsquo;s room for improvement.
During their visit to Davao and Manila from June 28 to July 12, the mission engaged with various stakeholders, including the Governor of the Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP), economic ministers, high-ranking government representatives, private sector leaders, and financial experts. Sumi&amp;rsquo;s post-mission statement highlighted the following:</description></item><item><title>The Philippines' economic outlook has improved according to the World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</guid><description>The World Bank has improved its economic forecast for the Philippines from 2016 to 2018.
They now predict the Philippine economy will grow by 6.8% in 2016, up from their previous prediction of 6.4% made in October (World Bank Philippines Economic Update October 2016). This adjustment is based on stronger than expected growth in the third quarter of 2016, fueled by increased investment and private consumption. This follows robust economic performance in the first half of 2016, driven by the government’s pre-election spending.</description></item><item><title>Mergers and acquisitions in the early stages are decelerating in Southeast Asia and Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 11:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</guid><description>Announcements for early-stage mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in Q4 2016 are predicted to be similar to the same period last year. This is attributed to reduced early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity in Southeast Asia and South Korea, as per the latest Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor (DFP) report released by Intralinks Holdings. Intralinks provides software and services, including virtual data rooms (VDRs), for managing M&amp;amp;A transactions.
Southeast Asia, encompassing Singapore, Malaysia, and Indonesia, is experiencing a significant 47.</description></item><item><title>The IMF reports that Armenia's economy is improving</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-reports-that-armenia-s-economy-is-improving/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:30:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-reports-that-armenia-s-economy-is-improving/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) concluded its regular economic assessment of Armenia on June 23, 2017. The IMF noted Armenia&amp;rsquo;s satisfactory economic growth with controlled inflation, generally well-managed government finances, and increased foreign currency reserves.
The IMF observed that in 2016, Armenia&amp;rsquo;s economic output grew by a minimal 0.2%, prices continued to fall, and the budget deficit reached 5.6% of GDP. However, in 2017, economic activity showed signs of recovery, with a rise in inflation and business loans, supported by relaxed monetary policies.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank ranks the UAE in the top 10 for enhancing the business environment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-ranks-the-uae-in-the-top-10-for-enhancing-the-business-environment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:35:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-ranks-the-uae-in-the-top-10-for-enhancing-the-business-environment/</guid><description>A new World Bank Group study reveals that local businesses in the Middle East have faced difficulties over the past year. While some economies, such as the UAE—one of the top 10 global improvers—enhanced their business environments, the Middle East and North Africa region saw relatively slow regulatory reform.
According to Doing Business 2015: Going Beyond Efficiency, 55% of economies in the region implemented business regulatory reforms. This is comparable to 60% in East Asia and the Pacific but indicates that the reforms were limited in scope.</description></item><item><title>Preserve Your IT Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserve-your-it-budget/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 17:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserve-your-it-budget/</guid><description>As we enter a new year and budget cycle, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to consider how to maximize your IT budget, even if funds seem plentiful. Economic uncertainty could lead to cutbacks, making it crucial to get the most value from your spending.
Maintaining your IT budget amidst pressure for upgrades and new projects requires smart strategies. One approach is negotiating better deals for the same services or products. While this might have been challenging during prosperous times, the current economic climate means businesses are eager for sales and more likely to negotiate.</description></item><item><title>IMF provides suggestions for economic policy in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-suggestions-for-economic-policy-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 03:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-suggestions-for-economic-policy-in-japan/</guid><description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s economic growth has decelerated due to subdued private consumption and investment, leading to a loss in inflationary momentum, as per the International Monetary Fund&amp;rsquo;s (IMF) Executive Board&amp;rsquo;s assessment following a consultation in late July. Despite favorable financial conditions, declining stock prices and a strengthening yen have contributed to a slight tightening of financial conditions.
In response to the weakening domestic and global economic landscape, Japanese authorities have implemented additional monetary and fiscal measures.</description></item><item><title>Enhancing financial inclusion has the potential to boost economic growth in the Arab region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) is advocating for the development of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and greater financial inclusion in the Arab world.
During the World Government Summit in Dubai, UAE, IMF Managing Director Christine Lagarde emphasized the need for Arab countries to prioritize growth and job creation. She highlighted the significant role of SMEs in generating employment, diversifying economies, and driving overall economic growth.
Lagarde pointed out that while SMEs make up 96% of registered companies and employ half of the workforce in the Arab region, they face significant challenges in accessing finance.</description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel.</description></item><item><title>The IMF has identified key policy priorities for Cambodia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) team, led by Sonali Jain-Chandra, visited Cambodia from July 6 to July 20, 2016, for their yearly review of Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s economy. The team analyzed economic data and discussed policies with Cambodian government officials, business leaders, and other stakeholders. They concluded that Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s economy is strong, with high growth projected to continue due to exports, real estate, and construction. However, they cautioned that this growth could slow in the long term and emphasized the risk of financial instability from rapid credit growth, particularly in real estate.</description></item><item><title>Cross-disciplinary conversations are reshaping the service economy at KODW 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Pictured at the KODW 2021 opening ceremony are (from left) Lofai Lo (Director and GM, ViuTV); Dr Lay Lian Ong (Principal, Hong Kong Design Institute &amp;amp; Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education); Victor Tsang (Head of Create Hong Kong); Professor Eric Yim (Chairman of Hong Kong Design Centre); guest of honor The Honourable Edward Yau (Secretary for Commerce and Economic Development); Victor Lo (Chairman, KODW Steering Committee of Hong Kong Design Centre); Professor Kun-Pyo Lee (Dean of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Design), and Dr Edmund Lee (Executive Director of Hong Kong Design Centre).</description></item><item><title>IMF provides feedback on the economy of Laos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-feedback-on-the-economy-of-laos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-feedback-on-the-economy-of-laos/</guid><description>At the end of January, the Executive Board of the International Monetary Fund (IMF) concluded its annual Article IV consultation with the Lao People&amp;rsquo;s Democratic Republic.
The IMF reported that real GDP growth is anticipated to decrease from 7.5% in 2015 to 7% in 2016. This moderation is attributed to a less favorable external environment leading to slower domestic activity, and a reduction in credit growth from its previous high levels.</description></item><item><title>The IMF predicts a positive outcome for Pakistan's economic growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</guid><description>The IMF Executive Board finalized its regular economic assessment of Pakistan on June 14, 2017.
The IMF determined that Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic outlook is positive, with real GDP expected to reach 5.3% in FY2016/17 and rise to 6% in the medium term. This growth is attributed to increased investments from the China Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), greater energy availability, and structural reforms that support economic expansion. While inflation has gradually risen, the IMF team stated it remains manageable, and the financial sector is stable.</description></item><item><title>Singapore ranks second in global competitiveness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</guid><description>The World Economic Forum (WEF) recently published its Global Competitiveness Report for 2016.
The report determined that a global trend of decreasing openness in countries is negatively impacting growth and prosperity. Financial stimuli like quantitative easing are insufficient for sustained growth and must be paired with reforms that bolster competitiveness. For emerging markets, modernizing business practices and investing in innovation are now just as crucial as infrastructure, skilled workforces, and efficient markets.</description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age.</description></item><item><title>Emirates NBD observes improvement in Dubai's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</guid><description>Source: Emirates NBD. Emirates NBD Dubai Economy Tracker Index: Sector
summary. Seasonally adjusted, 50 = no-change.
Data from April shows a continuing upswing in private sector output. Compared to March, all three major sub-sectors reported greater new business growth. Employment figures are increasing again, but at a slower rate than the survey average. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s private sector companies reported continued recovery and growth momentum since the survey&amp;rsquo;s record low in February.</description></item><item><title>INTA: Companies that invest in trademarks make a significant contribution to the economies of ASEAN countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 22:15:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</guid><description>A new report from the International Trademark Association (INTA) reveals that industries heavily reliant on trademarks play a substantial role in the economies of five key ASEAN nations: Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, Singapore, and Thailand. The report, titled The Economic Contribution of Trademark-Intensive Industries in Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, Singapore, and Thailand, shows that these industries stimulate job growth across sectors and significantly contribute to international trade. Industries classified as &amp;ldquo;trademark-intensive&amp;rdquo; are those that file a higher number of trademarks compared to others, adjusted for the total employment within each industry.</description></item><item><title>CEOs anticipate a deceleration in economic growth in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</guid><description>Global CEOs are expressing unprecedented pessimism regarding the economic outlook for 2020, according to PwC&amp;rsquo;s 23rd Annual Global CEO Survey. 53% of CEOs anticipate a decline in economic growth, a significant increase from 29% in 2019 and a stark contrast to the mere 5% who held this view in 2018. This marks the highest level of pessimism since the survey began in 2012, with only 22% of CEOs predicting economic growth in 2020, down from 42% in 2019.</description></item><item><title>The IMF anticipates that the Kyrgyz Republic's economy will grow by 2.2% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) team, headed by Edward Gemayel, visited Bishkek, Kyrgyz Republic from July 8th to 14th. The purpose of the visit was to assess the country&amp;rsquo;s recent economic performance and lay the groundwork for the third review mission under the Extended Credit Facility (ECF), tentatively planned for late September.
Preliminary findings from the visit were presented by Gemayel, noting that these do not necessarily reflect the views of the IMF’s Executive Board:</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2018 Budget is on technology, innovation, and building capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Budget 2018 site. View of Singapore skyline.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Trade and Industry (MTI) anticipates more broad-based economic growth across sectors in 2018, albeit at a moderated pace compared to the heights of 2017, according to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Financial Minister Heng Swee Keat during his Budget 2018 speech.
Minister Heng emphasized the need for Singapore to adapt to three major shifts in the coming decade:
Asia&amp;rsquo;s increasing global economic influence.</description></item><item><title>Japan Macro Advisors introduces a new tool to assist in analyzing the Japanese economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-macro-advisors-introduces-a-new-tool-to-assist-in-analyzing-the-japanese-economy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 22:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-macro-advisors-introduces-a-new-tool-to-assist-in-analyzing-the-japanese-economy/</guid><description>Source: Japan Macro Advisors. Interactive chart and table.
Japan Macro Advisors (JMA) has introduced My Charts, a suite of online analytical tools designed to provide economists and decision-makers with up-to-date insights into the Japanese economy.
Based on JMA&amp;rsquo;s publicly available and continually updated macroeconomic database, My Charts acts as a personalized storage space where users can convert charts into PowerPoint slides. The database currently holds over 500 indicators, including some exclusively available through JMA.</description></item><item><title>IMF approves of Singapore's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its yearly assessment of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy. The IMF noted that while Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy remains strong, it is facing challenges from both global and domestic factors.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economic growth slowed to 2% in 2015, down from 3.3% in 2014, and was 2.2% in the first half of 2016. While unemployment is still low, job creation slowed significantly in 2015, and inflation has remained negative since late 2014.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia has announced the release of its 2017 budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s King Salman bin Abdulaziz recently announced the nation&amp;rsquo;s budget for 2017. The budget is set at SAR890 billion, representing an 8% rise from the previous year. It is anticipated to significantly reduce the kingdom&amp;rsquo;s deficit by a historic 33%.
King Salman emphasized the strength and resilience of the Saudi economy, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our economy is firm and it has sufficient strength to cope with the current economic and financial challenges.</description></item><item><title>South Asia has the potential to become the leading export region in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</guid><description>By implementing policies that enhance productivity, South Asia could substantially increase its global market share in electronics, motor vehicles, and apparel by 2030, according to a new World Bank report titled &amp;ldquo;South Asia’s Turn: Policies to Boost Competitiveness and Create the Next Export Powerhouse.&amp;rdquo; The report emphasizes that improving firm productivity is crucial for boosting competitiveness in Pakistan and the rest of South Asia. While acknowledging the region&amp;rsquo;s investment climate challenges, the report focuses on less-explored factors like the impact of cities and clusters, global value chains, and firms&amp;rsquo; capacity for innovation and efficient resource utilization.</description></item><item><title>The IMF emphasizes the importance of AML/CFT for maintaining stability in the financial sector of the Kyrgyz Republic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</guid><description>Despite external pressures decreasing and some positive economic signs, the recovery has been modest. Economic growth sped up towards the end of 2016, hitting 3.8% with 0.5% deflation, partly due to a currency appreciation of about 9%. The 2016 deficit was kept to 4.5% of GDP due to controlled spending on less critical items and the rescheduling of some investment projects, even though tax revenue fell short of expectations. Efforts to consolidate the budget should continue to achieve the 2017 fiscal deficit target of 3% of GDP.</description></item><item><title>Dell considers Singapore to be one of the 50 economies worldwide that are prepared for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 10:50:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</guid><description>Dell recognized Singapore as one of 50 economies worldwide prepared to flourish in an evolving, globalized future through technological integration. The _Dell Future-Ready Economies Model*, the foundation for this ranking, assesses large, rapidly growing global metropolitan areas on characteristics that allow individuals and businesses to utilize innovative tools and concepts. These factors contribute to improved connectivity, superior economic performance, and a greater capacity to attract talent.
The ranking evaluated the Global 50 cities based on three key aspects:</description></item></channel></rss>