<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hypervisor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hypervisor/</link><description>Recent content in Hypervisor on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hypervisor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>