<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fireworks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fireworks/</link><description>Recent content in Fireworks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fireworks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Special promotions for the Fireworks Celebration at the Mandarin Oriental, Macau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Macau has special Fireworks Celebration packages perfect for corporate events, team building, or client appreciation. These packages provide a unique opportunity to experience the 26th Macau International Fireworks Display Contest.
Source: Mandarin Oriental Macau website.
Available on September 8th, 13th, 20th, 27th, and October 1st, 2014, the package starts at MOP4,388 and includes:
Overnight accommodations in a room or suite with panoramic fireworks views through expansive windows. A special four-course fireworks-themed dinner for two at the Vida Rica Restaurant, showcasing Chef Dominique Bugnand’s modern take on classic French cuisine.</description></item><item><title>Fireworks will be held at Al Majaz Waterfront to celebrate Eid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</guid><description>Al Majaz Waterfront, a popular destination located in Sharjah, UAE, will be hosting a fireworks show to celebrate the beginning of Eid al-Adha.
As reported by the Emirates News Agency (WAM), a three-minute fireworks display will take place at 9pm on the first and second days of Eid. The fireworks will be launched above the Sharjah Musical Fountain, and additional entertainment will be offered.
Source: Al Majaz Waterfront website. Fireworks on Marwa Obaid Al Shamsi, the Manager of Al Majaz Waterfront, emphasized that Eid al-Adha is a joyous celebration for families and especially children.</description></item><item><title>Preview the SG50 National Day promotion at Fairmont Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-the-sg50-national-day-promotion-at-fairmont-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:04:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-the-sg50-national-day-promotion-at-fairmont-singapore/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 50th anniversary, the Fairmont Singapore is offering a special package. This package provides guests with a prime location to view the fireworks display during the National Day preview parade on August 1st.
Ranging from S$400++ to S$750++ for a one-night stay, the package includes a premium room with views of Marina Bay and the Padang. Guests will also enjoy complimentary breakfast for two and a 24-hour self-parking coupon at Raffles City Shopping Centre.</description></item><item><title>The highlight of the Downtown Dubai New Year's Eve Gala is the Burj Khalifa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</guid><description>To celebrate the arrival of 2015, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Khalifa will showcase a dazzling LED display across its 828-meter height, synchronized with a spectacular fireworks show, according to a report from the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
Emaar Properties, the developer behind Downtown Dubai, is orchestrating a six-part extravaganza for their New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Gala. The event will feature a captivating blend of fireworks, laser displays, and a light show. A highlight of the celebration will be a special tribute to Dubai, its leaders, and the UAE&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments over the past 43 years, projected onto the specially designed LED screen.</description></item></channel></rss>