<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fujitsu on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fujitsu/</link><description>Recent content in Fujitsu on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 22:14:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fujitsu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fujitsu introduces 30 new models of enterprise PCs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujitsu-introduces-30-new-models-of-enterprise-pcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 22:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujitsu-introduces-30-new-models-of-enterprise-pcs/</guid><description>Fujitsu, along with Fujitsu Client Computing, has introduced 30 new enterprise PC models across 15 product lines. These models all feature the Windows 10 Creators Update, the most recent version of the Windows 10 operating system.
Source: Fujitsu. The ESPRIMO K557/R desktop.
Within its Fujitsu Desktop ESPRIMO line, five models are being released, including the ESPRIMO K557/R. This model boasts a redesigned chassis with an integrated LCD display. The high-quality IPS LCD is available in various sizes, ranging from 19.</description></item><item><title>Fujitsu introduces new mobile products in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujitsu-introduces-new-mobile-products-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 13:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujitsu-introduces-new-mobile-products-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Fujitsu. The LIFEBOOK U7310/D.
Fujitsu and its subsidiary, Fujitsu Client Computing, have introduced new mobile devices designed to support the changing workstyles of their customers, particularly in remote work environments.
The new product lineup consists of nine FUJITSU Notebook LIFEBOOK models, four Fujitsu Tablet ARROWS Tab models (running on Windows), and a Fujitsu Workstation CELSIUS model. These devices are equipped with the latest CPUs and operating systems, with the exception of the CELSIUS model*.</description></item></channel></rss>