<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>201612KMBM8000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/201612kmbm8000/</link><description>Recent content in 201612KMBM8000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:05:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/201612kmbm8000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> Beomaster 8000: Ready for Some Bench Testing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-ready-for-some-bench-testing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-ready-for-some-bench-testing/</guid><description>After powering up the Beomaster and confirming its audio quality with an iPod and FM radio, I began the reassembly process. However, the remote control wasn&amp;rsquo;t working. Troubleshooting this will require investigating the power supply board, which houses the remote control receiver. For now, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to proceed with bench testing.
My initial test involved connecting the Beomaster to a previously restored Beocord 9000 using a DIN cable. The Beocord&amp;rsquo;s play button activated the Beomaster&amp;rsquo;s TP1 play mode, and the Beomaster&amp;rsquo;s standby button turned off both devices, confirming proper communication.</description></item><item><title> Beomaster 8000: Display Board Rebuilt</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-display-board-rebuilt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-display-board-rebuilt/</guid><description>After rigorous testing, the refurbished Beomaster 8000 display modules are ready for installation. This final stage of the restoration involves replacing several components on the display board: the four display modules, incandescent bulbs, a 10uF electrolytic capacitor, and a 4.7uF tantalum capacitor. The incandescent bulbs will be replaced with Beolover&amp;rsquo;s LED replacements, eliminating the need for four 220Ω resistors. As part of the restoration process, all board connectors will be reflowed.</description></item><item><title> Beomaster 8000: Microcomputer Board Reworked</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-microcomputer-board-reworked/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 09:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-microcomputer-board-reworked/</guid><description>I worked on the Beomaster 8000 microcomputer board today. This Beomaster is an earlier model and uses a first-generation microcomputer board, unlike later models with directly replaceable, yet distinct, boards. I&amp;rsquo;ll show an example of a later model board at the end.
One issue with the first-generation boards is the metal enclosure surrounding the processor ICs. While necessary for shielding, it makes accessing components difficult. B&amp;amp;O used soldered metal tabs to connect the upper and lower sections, but these tabs are soldered to the board&amp;rsquo;s ground plane, requiring significant heat for removal.</description></item></channel></rss>