<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free/</link><description>Recent content in Free on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration.</description></item><item><title>The Hasso Plattner Institute is offering a free six-week MOOC on the Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</guid><description>The Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) is offering a free, six-week online course in English about the fundamentals of the Internet. Starting on March 31st, HPI&amp;rsquo;s director, Professor Christoph Meinel, will teach participants about the technical basis of the Internet through a massive open online course (MOOC) titled &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Internetworking with TCP/IP.&amp;rdquo; The course is available to anyone and can be accessed through free registration.
Professor Meinel believes that anyone who uses the Internet for daily tasks like online shopping, reading news articles, or sending emails should understand the technologies that make these actions possible.</description></item><item><title>Access free Wi-Fi at more than 200,000 hotspots throughout Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 21:28:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</guid><description>Source: Wire and Wireless Company. The logo displays the Wi-Fi symbol superimposed on an image of Mt Fuji.
Wire and Wireless Company, a Japanese telecommunications provider, is celebrating the second anniversary of its free TRAVEL JAPAN Wi-Fi app. The latest update includes enhanced features and a wider range of free Wi-Fi access points.
The app provides travelers with details about nearby stores, restaurants, and attractions, along with numerous discount coupons.</description></item><item><title>Nanu, the free calling app, provides a fresh approach to connecting with customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</guid><description>Source: nanu website.
Nanu, the first entirely free mobile calling app, is experiencing rapid growth in its monthly and daily active users. Based in Singapore, the startup claims its app&amp;rsquo;s active user rates are almost twice the industry standard, with 56% monthly active users and 19% daily active users.
CEO Martin Nygate points out that many tech startups avoid disclosing these figures due to poor performance. He&amp;rsquo;s pleased to share nanu&amp;rsquo;s positive data, reflecting both strong download numbers and increasing app usage.</description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre now offers complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Guests at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) can enjoy free Wi-Fi access through the &amp;lsquo;ADNEC Free Wi-Fi&amp;rsquo; network.
Humaid Matar Al Dhaheri, Acting Group CEO of Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company, stated that providing complimentary Wi-Fi highlights ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s focus on using technology to improve visitor experiences. This service eliminates the need for visitors to seek out basic internet access, aligning with ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing its technological infrastructure and enhancing service offerings to meet the changing needs of its stakeholders.</description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after.</description></item><item><title>CA Technologies is offering a free migration tool for Windows XP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</guid><description>If you need to upgrade from Windows XP, there&amp;rsquo;s a free tool that can help. Developed by CA Technologies, CA Desktop Migration Manager (CA DMM) is a software solution designed to manage, upgrade, and maintain laptops and desktops. It can also migrate a Windows XP computer to a more secure operating system.
&amp;ldquo;Since Microsoft is no longer providing ongoing technical support and security updates for Windows XP, our customers are exposed to vulnerabilities and significant risks,&amp;rdquo; says Vic Mankotia, VP of Solution Strategy for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals, a brand that is committed to being cruelty-free, has launched a new range of eyeshadows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</guid><description>Everyday Minerals (EM) prioritizes using the purest natural ingredients to create all-natural, vegan, and cruelty-free makeup. Their products are handmade in Texas and packaged in eco-friendly, recyclable materials.
Source: Everyday Minerals blog.
Vegan makeup is characterized by its exclusion of animal-derived ingredients and its non-reliance on animal testing. Ingredients like lanolin and collagen are examples of animal-derived components. A growing number of cosmetics companies are introducing vegan product lines or, like EM, adopting a fully vegan approach.</description></item><item><title>Fuuzle offers a free news consolidation service that translates content into 26 different languages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fuuzle-offers-a-free-news-consolidation-service-that-translates-content-into-26-different-languages/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 19:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fuuzle-offers-a-free-news-consolidation-service-that-translates-content-into-26-different-languages/</guid><description>Fuuzle simplifies information retrieval by gathering and providing access to the content of countless newsletters and RSS feeds worldwide, translating them into 26 languages with a high level of accuracy. Fuuzle claims that some of this information is difficult or impossible to find using traditional search engines.
Source: Fuuzle website.
Currently in beta, the company&amp;rsquo;s database expands by over 100 million unique RSS feeds and more than 5 million newsletters monthly.</description></item><item><title>Dell has launched backup appliances for midmarket businesses, along with complimentary Windows data recovery software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</guid><description>Dell has introduced new data protection solutions tailored for small and medium-sized businesses to enhance the protection of their crucial systems, applications, and data, both on-site and in cloud environments. These solutions include data deduplication appliance models and the new Dell Data Protection | Endpoint Recovery – Free Edition.
Back up more and store less The latest additions to the Dell DR series of deduplication appliances are the Dell DR4300e, DR4300, and DR6300.</description></item><item><title>BCM Institute offers Business Continuity Management courses specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</guid><description>The BCM Institute, in collaboration with the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC), is offering a free two-day Business Continuity Management (BCM) course designed to enhance the resilience of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) against disruptions.
Taking place on October 28-29, 2014, at the Singapore Productivity Centre, this course is presented with support from the Singapore Business Federation and SPRING Singapore. Participants will engage with the following topics:
APEC-endorsed step-by-step BCM implementation guidelines Complimentary, ready-to-use BCM templates Guidance on utilizing BCM templates Insights into BCM trends affecting SMEs, shared by an APEC ASEAN BCM Working Group Committee member SMEs meeting the criteria of an annual sales turnover not exceeding S$100 million or employing 200 or fewer staff are eligible to participate.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th.</description></item><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar.</description></item><item><title>Citizens of Thailand holding ordinary passports can travel to Taiwan without a visa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 07:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</guid><description>Holders of regular Thai passports can now travel without a visa to 26 countries, along with Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau. Beginning August 1st, Taiwan initiated a year-long trial program waiving visa requirements for Thai citizens with regular passports visiting for tourism purposes.
This program permits eligible travelers to stay in Taiwan for a maximum of 30 days. To qualify, Thai nationals must possess a valid regular passport with at least six months of validity remaining, hold a return or onward ticket to another destination, and meet Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s entry requirements.</description></item><item><title>ACCA is sponsoring a MOOC on FutureLearn that grants learners an exemption from the F1 paper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) is breaking new ground as the first professional accountancy body to use massive open online courses (MOOCs) for professional recognition. They are partnering with FutureLearn, a UK-based social learning platform, to offer free online courses in accounting, finance, and business.
This partnership aims to reach a global audience, providing valuable supplementary knowledge for professionals and introducing career paths to those new to the field.</description></item><item><title>Guests staying at the Hyatt hotel can enjoy complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels Corporation is demonstrating its commitment to enhancing the guest experience by providing free Wi-Fi at all of its hotels globally starting in February 2015. This initiative aims to provide guests with convenient connectivity regardless of how they booked their stay or their loyalty program status.
Guests will have access to complimentary Wi-Fi on an unlimited number of devices, including laptops and mobile phones, in both guest rooms and common areas of Hyatt-branded hotels.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay for the Once Upon a Nightmare free street party to celebrate Halloween</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-for-the-once-upon-a-nightmare-free-street-party-to-celebrate-halloween/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-for-the-once-upon-a-nightmare-free-street-party-to-celebrate-halloween/</guid><description>Clarke Quay is hosting &amp;ldquo;Once Upon A Nightmare,&amp;rdquo; a street party they&amp;rsquo;re calling the most frightening Halloween event of the year. The event, which is free to attend, will be hosted by popular radio DJs Justin Ang and Vernon A from 98.7FM’s Muttons On The Move.
Source: Clarke Quay.
Attendees can enjoy live music from local band Enigma and participate in themed games for a chance to win prizes. Guests are encouraged to dress up in their most twisted and imaginative interpretations of fairytale characters.</description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Check Point warns that free USB devices may be carriers of malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</guid><description>Source: Victoria Police. The unmarked USB drives used are similar to these.
On September 21st, law enforcement in Victoria, Australia, issued a warning to residents of Pakenham, a Melbourne suburb, about unlabeled USB drives found in mailboxes.
According to the Victoria police statement, people have been discovering unmarked USB drives in their mailboxes. When connected to computers, these drives have exposed victims to fraudulent streaming service offers and other serious problems.</description></item><item><title>Starting on July 29, upgrades to Windows 10 will be available for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</guid><description>Source: Windows blog.
Microsoft has revealed that Windows 10 will launch on July 29th in 190 countries. The company states that Windows 10 will enhance productivity and offer a more personalized and intuitive user experience across devices. Windows 7 and 8.1 users can upgrade to Windows 10 for free, making it accessible to a majority of current Windows users.
&amp;ldquo;Windows 10 empowers users to achieve remarkable things,&amp;rdquo; says Terry Myerson, Executive VP at Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing.</description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks.</description></item><item><title>Veeam introduces a new free backup tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 06:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</guid><description>Source: Veeam video.
Veeam has introduced a cost-free solution for creating backups of Windows desktops and laptops that doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessitate any extra software or costs.
Users have the flexibility to select their backup locations, including options such as external hard drives, shared folders on the network, and more. This free software from Veeam also offers the capability to generate bootable recovery media, proving useful when addressing computer issues that hinder the operating system from starting properly.</description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community.</description></item><item><title>At Shopee University: achieving that perfect Instagram shot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-shopee-university-achieving-that-perfect-instagram-shot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 17:34:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-shopee-university-achieving-that-perfect-instagram-shot/</guid><description>To celebrate the launch of Shopee University, Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, hosted a practical Shopee University session for the media. This session gave attendees a preview of the experience Shopee sellers and the public can expect.
Each free session lasts around 60 to 90 minutes. Students must complete two basic and two advanced classes to qualify for expert classes. After that, they can attend unlimited expert sessions. The photography class showcased here is considered an advanced to expert level class.</description></item><item><title>The free WooCommerce WordPress plugin has reached 4 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 06:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</guid><description>WooThemes, a developer of WordPress themes, plugins, and shopping cart features, announced that its WooCommerce WordPress plugin has been downloaded over 4 million times. WooCommerce is WooThemes&amp;rsquo; free flagship product, officially partnered with companies like Amazon, Mastercard, and PayPal.
Source: WooThemes website.
WooCommerce enables businesses to operate e-commerce sites using WordPress as their content management system.
WooThemes uses a freemium model. The basic plugin and some add-ons are free, while more advanced extensions and themes require payment.</description></item><item><title>AC Works introduces Korean versions of free stock image websites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</guid><description>Source: AC works. Screen capture of illustAC.
AC works, a company with over 2.3 million users in Japan, is expanding globally. They recently introduced Korean versions of their popular stock image platforms: photoAC, illustAC, and silhouetteAC.
The stock image industry has historically been restrictive, often imposing fees for various uses of a single image. Costs are common for both the stock images themselves and their vector files. Purchased images typically come with limited usage rights, like a single use within a specific advertising campaign.</description></item></channel></rss>