<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PwC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pwc/</link><description>Recent content in PwC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pwc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IPO activity in Singapore is expected to exceed that of 2016 in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</guid><description>During the first half of 2017, Singapore saw a surge in initial public offerings (IPOs), attracting US$329 million in investments, as reported by PwC Singapore. This momentum is projected to continue, potentially exceeding the total funds raised in 2016. Professional services are emerging as a leading sector, with HRnetGroup and Shopper360&amp;rsquo;s IPOs securing a combined US$134 million, a significant leap from the previous year.
While Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) and business trusts, a traditional strength for the Singapore Exchange (SGX), constituted 33% of IPO proceeds, the anticipated listing of NetLink Trust, estimated at US$1.</description></item><item><title>CEOs express optimism about the global economy, according to PwC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-express-optimism-about-the-global-economy-according-to-pwc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 01:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-express-optimism-about-the-global-economy-according-to-pwc/</guid><description>Global business leaders are feeling positive about the economic climate in the near future, according to the 21st annual survey of CEOs conducted by PwC. The survey, which included approximately 1,300 CEOs from around the world, was released at the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting in Davos, Switzerland.
A significant majority (57%) of CEOs believe that global economic growth will improve in the next year. This represents a substantial increase from last year&amp;rsquo;s 29% and marks the largest surge in positive sentiment since PwC began tracking global growth projections in 2012.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is the third best city in APEC for living and conducting business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</guid><description>A new study presented at the APEC 2015 CEO Summit has positioned Singapore as the third most desirable city for living and conducting business within the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) region.
Conducted by PwC, the &amp;ldquo;Building Better Cities&amp;rdquo; study aims to provide city leaders with insights into their current standings and to encourage collaboration and knowledge sharing among APEC cities to tackle persistent challenges.
The study examines the role urban centers play in APEC&amp;rsquo;s economic and social progress, emphasizing their growing global influence.</description></item></channel></rss>