<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Telephone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephone/</link><description>Recent content in Business Telephone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goose Your Technical Service Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</guid><description>Are you seeing a decline in business lately? You might have just as many inquiries, but customers seem hesitant to commit. This is likely due to the current economic climate, not anything you&amp;rsquo;re doing wrong. However, there are ways to stimulate your business and potentially even increase your income.
While these ideas apply to many businesses, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on those offering telephone or computer networking technical services. If this describes your business, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SMB Phone System Needs Only Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</guid><description>The simplicity of traditional phone systems, where plugging in a phone provided immediate dial tone, is making a comeback with cloud-based communication systems.
This modern approach, known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, shifts the responsibility of complex switching equipment to a service provider. This means the provider manages updates, maintenance, and scalability, leaving you with only the phones to handle.
These aren&amp;rsquo;t your typical phones; they are IP phones designed for computer networks, using different electrical signals and connectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Office Hosted Telecommunications at Half Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</guid><description>Upgrading your business phone system can be pricey, but hosted telecommunications, like Packet8&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Office, offers a more affordable solution. For a limited time, they&amp;rsquo;re offering a 50% discount, making it even more budget-friendly.
Instead of buying and managing your own phone system, hosted telecommunications lets a specialized company handle the equipment and services. You simply plug in your phones wherever you need them. Packet8&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Office utilizes an internet-based PBX system, eliminating the need for on-site equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Voice Over MPLS The New PSTN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</guid><description>Packet-switched networks are undeniably replacing circuit-switched networks, so much so that the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) might be phased out by the FCC. This signals the potential end of the century-old telephone system, raising the question of what will replace it. VoIP is a strong contender, but not in its current form.
VoIP&amp;rsquo;s strengths lie in its established standards for coding, signaling, and its compatibility with Ethernet data networks. However, its widespread adoption is hampered by incompatible implementations, concerns from wireless carriers about network overload, and inconsistent voice quality on the internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Hosted PBX VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 03:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</guid><description>There are many ways to implement VoIP, with some methods being more effective than others. Your goal with VoIP is likely to reduce expenses and access enhanced features while maintaining high-quality voice communication.
Achieving this balance is possible with the right technology, though proper setup can be challenging. Getting assistance with the installation, specifically by outsourcing complex aspects to a specialized provider, can greatly increase your chances of a smooth implementation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best VoIP Providers For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</guid><description>Thinking about switching from traditional phone lines to VoIP, but unsure about its effectiveness? This guide provides insights and advice for a smooth transition.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, is also known as “network voice” because it operates on computer networks, unlike traditional phone systems. Essentially, voice becomes another service on your network, alongside data, video, and audio streaming. Each service transmits packets routed through the network.
This setup offers significant cost savings for larger businesses by consolidating telephone and data networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Communications Advantages Explained</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</guid><description>Many businesses are unsure if switching their communications to the cloud is a good idea. XO Communications, a large networking and telecom provider, explains why this change is beneficial. Their short video illustrates why this might be the right choice for your business.
XO&amp;rsquo;s Enterprise Cloud Communications provides large businesses with services similar to what hosted PBX systems offer smaller companies. Essentially, it transitions a company from managing its own phone system to simply using a sophisticated service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PRI Lines For Domestic Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are turning to domestic call centers, whether they are in-house or independent contractors. All call centers rely on telephone service, and PRI lines are the preferred choice. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, belongs to the Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) standard. ISDN aimed to transition all telephone lines from analog to digital. The basic offering, BRI (Basic Rate Interface), provides two phone lines or one phone line with either a 64 Kbps or 128 Kbps data service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why NOT to Buy a New PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</guid><description>Traditionally, businesses dealing with outdated or inadequate phone systems have opted for a complete replacement, known as a “forklift upgrade.” While this provided enhanced performance and capacity, like a brand new car, there&amp;rsquo;s a compelling alternative in today&amp;rsquo;s world: hosted PBX solutions.
Rather than investing heavily in another physical PBX system, consider a hosted PBX, also referred to as Hosted VoIP or PBX in the cloud. This service eliminates the need for a physical PBX on your premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CAS vs PRI Voice Channels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</guid><description>T1 telephone trunk lines are commonly used with PBX and IP PBX phone systems because most modern equipment can connect directly to them without a separate CSU/DSU box. There are two main types of T1 lines: CAS and PRI (also called ISDN PRI).
The original T1 line design, T1 CAS, is divided into 24 channels, each carrying a 64 Kbps digitized phone call. This digital conversion process, known as PCM, ensures clear voice quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Cell Phone IS Your Business Phone System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-your-business-phone-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-your-business-phone-system/</guid><description>Why invest in a large, expensive office phone system when you&amp;rsquo;re an independent professional constantly on the move? If your work revolves around sales or consulting, your mobile phone might be the only phone system you need.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense for clients to call your office if you&amp;rsquo;re rarely there. When they call your mobile number, you&amp;rsquo;re reachable regardless of location. You can always let calls go to voicemail, eliminating the need to rush back to the office just to check messages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-your-business-phone-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-cell-phone-is-your-business-phone-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone Offers Awareness In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The traditional office phone, once a large and stationary fixture on every desk, is becoming a relic of the past. Modern business communication has evolved into a dynamic and multifaceted process, incorporating instant messaging, online collaboration tools, file sharing, and web-based applications alongside traditional voice calls and conferencing. This evolution begs the question: are conventional PBX systems still equipped to handle the demands of today&amp;rsquo;s business environment?
As outdated phone systems increasingly hinder productivity, many companies are turning to cloud-based solutions for a more modern approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ISDN's Primary Rate Interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</guid><description>The Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) is a digital telephone standard that provided widespread voice and data services before Enterprise VoIP and MPLS networks. Notably, ISDN&amp;rsquo;s Primary Rate Interface remains in high demand due to its seamless integration with existing telephone trunk lines, which are nearly ubiquitous.
The development of ISDN was driven by the increasing use of modems on analog telephone lines for long-distance data transmission. Analog telephone networks, designed for limited voice bandwidth, only allowed for data speeds up to 56 Kbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rise Of The Cloud Hosted PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</guid><description>Traditional, in-house PBX systems might be nearing obsolescence with the emergence of cloud-hosted solutions like AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s AirePBX. This innovation signifies a return to an older model where the service provider manages the switching system, but with modern technological advancements.
This shift back to provider-managed systems, reminiscent of early telephone networks, offers significant cost advantages due to increased competition and the use of existing network infrastructure for VoIP services. Businesses no longer need to invest in separate wiring or proprietary equipment, leading to more competitive offerings and feature-rich options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is a PRI Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</guid><description>Businesses frequently use PRI lines to obtain multiple phone lines. But what exactly are PRI lines, and what choices are there?
PRI is a component of ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network), a telecommunications standard. Its goal was to replace analog phone lines with digital ones for both residential and commercial customers. When ISDN was first introduced, dial-up connections using 56 Kbps modems were the norm for internet connectivity. Many of these modems only achieved speeds of 30 to 40 Kbps due to phone line limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Does Cloud Computing Work In Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is frequently used today. But what exactly is it, and how can it benefit your business by improving efficiency, speed, and affordability? Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into it.
In business, the term &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; often carries a negative connotation, implying uncertainty and unpredictability. Naturally, clarity and predictability are preferred, especially from a financial standpoint. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable why people might be skeptical when advised to transition their business to the cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How HD Audio Will Transform VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</guid><description>People who recall the era of analog phones and physical switches often feel nostalgic about the superior audio quality of those systems. The conversations back then possessed a clarity and immediacy that has largely vanished in recent times, though this might be changing soon. A new movement is underway to enhance the fidelity of VoIP calls significantly, aiming to make current phones seem primitive in comparison.
This advancement is known as high-definition audio or HD Voice, a term used by Polycom, a manufacturer of IP phones equipped with this technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Broadband and Phone Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses require both internet and phone service. While ordering these services separately remains an option, businesses now have more choices.
Bundled services, offering both phone and internet, often make the most sense for smaller businesses with limited needs and budgets. Two primary bundled options provide cost savings compared to separate services.
The first option, known as Integrated T1 or SIP Trunking, utilizes line sharing but differs in connection methods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of Business Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Over time, business phone lines have evolved from a single analog option to a variety of choices. While you can still get traditional analog lines, various digital options offer potential cost and performance benefits.
The standard business phone line remains largely unchanged from its origins over a century ago, using a single twisted pair of copper wires to carry signals. This analog line, also called POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is the basis for multi-line phones connecting to multiple POTS lines, commonly seen in small office phone systems with one to four lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SMB Cloud Computing Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</guid><description>While large companies have widely adopted cloud computing, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) may wonder about its relevance for them. Broadview Networks offers a range of cloud services ideal for such businesses. Already a prominent communications provider in the Northeastern and Mid-Atlantic US, Broadview provides various connectivity options, including T1 lines, Ethernet, fiber optic connections, and traditional phone lines.
What distinguishes Broadview is its ability to provide both cloud services and the reliable connectivity these services require, unlike many cloud providers that only offer the infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Trunk Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines often benefit from trunk lines. But with various trunk services available, choosing the right one can be tricky. While VoIP phone systems might make SIP trunking seem like the obvious choice, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to evaluate all options before deciding.
The concept of telephone trunking originated with telephone companies. Initially, individual phone lines connected users to the local phone company. As phone usage surged, businesses adopted switchboards to manage multiple lines, leading to a tangled mess of overhead wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Voice Options for Call Quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 19:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</guid><description>For businesses reliant on phone communication, exceptional call quality is non-negotiable. This means clear, natural-sounding voices with minimal disruptions like dropped calls, echoes, or choppy audio. If this resonates, T1 voice service might be your solution.
T1 lines are a natural fit for business phone systems as they were intentionally designed for this purpose. T-Carrier technology, including T1 (1.5 Mbps) and T3 (45 Mbps), was initially developed for use by phone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>