<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PBX Telephone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-telephone/</link><description>Recent content in PBX Telephone on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-telephone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Last Mile Connections That Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</guid><description>The US is covered in a network of competing telecom companies, reaching into every major city. Businesses of all sizes are drawn to their advanced IP networks, fiber optic infrastructure, and significantly lower prices. But how can businesses connect to these networks?
The final connection to a customer&amp;rsquo;s location, often called the &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; is frequently the most critical, expensive, and limiting part of a wide area network. It gets its name from the typical distance between a business and the nearest carrier Point of Presence (POP).</description></item><item><title>T1 Broadband For Rural Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</guid><description>Government funding is being used to expand rural broadband access, as it&amp;rsquo;s generally understood that service providers have overlooked these areas due to their sparse populations. But what about businesses in these locations? Do they face similar internet limitations?
In most cases, businesses in rural areas shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be deprived of reliable internet any more than they are deprived of multi-line phone service. The existing copper telephone lines can also deliver broadband.</description></item><item><title>XO Nails Down SIP Trunking Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</guid><description>Want to discover how your business could save upwards of $88,000 annually just by switching to SIP trunking service?
Hold on a minute! To achieve this level of savings, your business needs to have a certain volume of operations and spending. This figure comes from XO Communications, a leading voice and data carrier, and their new Enterprise SIP Savings Estimator.
So, what kind of business can expect these substantial savings? In this scenario, a company with 1,000 employees spread across 10 locations, where half of their phone calls are internal.</description></item><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service.</description></item><item><title>Managed IP Services Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</guid><description>Companies are increasingly interested in cloud services because they can save money and access capabilities that they might not otherwise be able to afford. Cloud services offer a wide range of IP services and can be accessed in-house, privately, or purchased from a provider. While providers offer different services, they all deliver their services over IP networks, leading to the term &amp;ldquo;managed IP services.&amp;rdquo;
Managed services allow carriers or service providers to take responsibility for operations, a task typically handled by on-site IT staff.</description></item><item><title>Finding Information on PBX Telephone Systems Pricing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 15:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</guid><description>Planning a new office building or hotel? Upgrading your old business phone system? Finding the right PBX system at the right price is essential for a smart decision.
Instead of searching endlessly, utilize an online clearinghouse like the VAR Network. This platform connects businesses with qualified PBX and network equipment vendors.
The VAR Network focuses on these two interconnected technologies. Most businesses rely on both for internal communication and internet access.</description></item><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential.</description></item><item><title>The Ubiquitous Cloud of 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</guid><description>The year 2012 brings a shift in the business landscape, not towards a downturn, but rather a move towards cloud computing. This change benefits businesses facing uncertainty by offering flexibility and adaptability. Instead of struggling to predict the future, businesses can embrace the cloud and adjust their strategies as needed.
The current business environment is already in flux. While some businesses are stagnant, others experience constant change. This unpredictability leaves many longing for a more stable past.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking and Internet On a T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</guid><description>Many smaller companies utilize T1 lines for dedicated internet access, opting for this solution after experiencing unreliable or unavailable consumer-grade broadband options. T1 lines offer these businesses dependable, robust bandwidth at increasingly affordable prices. However, many are unaware that they can bundle their broadband and telephone services onto a single T1 line.
Traditional T1 lines offer various service options. The original format, designed for the telephone industry, provides 24 channels of digitized telephone service over two pairs of twisted copper phone wires.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems.</description></item><item><title>T1 Lease Costs Reduced Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</guid><description>In the past, T1 lines were a costly telecommunication option accessible only to large companies and the telecom sector. While competition has significantly lowered prices since then, there&amp;rsquo;s been another recent plunge. But what&amp;rsquo;s driving this trend?
Originally, T1 lines, part of the T-Carrier telephony standard, were trunk lines connecting central offices within telephone companies. Later, corporate telecom departments adopted them for PBX phone systems and internet service. They became crucial for local internet providers, particularly dial-up services.</description></item><item><title>Why, Oh Why, PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</guid><description>You might know the terms PRI, T1 PRI, Telephone PRI, PRI Trunk, or ISDN PRI, but what do they actually mean, and why choose this service?
PRI stands for Primary Rate Interface. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN or Integrated Services Digital Network and is a step up from BRI or Basic Rate Interface. Simply put, PRI is a digital line connecting to your PBX phone system. It combines numerous phone lines into a single digital line, leading to cost savings on monthly phone bills.</description></item><item><title>Using T1 Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:54:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</guid><description>T1 lines have diverse applications, including linking offices within a city or across the country. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how this is achieved and the available options.
The fundamental interoffice connection is a point-to-point T1 line, a circuit connecting two specific locations. It runs from one business site to the nearest telecom central office, then between central offices, and finally to the other location.
You might wonder why not directly connect locations with wires.</description></item><item><title>Find A T1 Line For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re unsatisfied with your current internet options like DSL or Cable due to fluctuating speeds, frequent outages, or location limitations, and find Satellite internet&amp;rsquo;s lag, bandwidth restrictions, and weather-related disruptions unacceptable, there&amp;rsquo;s a better solution: T1 lines.
T1 lines, the gold standard for business wireline services, provide a reliable solution with consistent upload and download speeds, high reliability, quick problem resolution, and widespread availability. They offer secure connections between business locations and digital phone line options for PBX systems, features absent in other digital services.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then.</description></item><item><title>T1 Telephony Has Many Flavors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</guid><description>Initially designed for high-volume call transfer between telephone exchanges, T1 technology has evolved into a leading digital phone solution for businesses. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering T1, understanding the available options is crucial.
T1 is a digital standard supporting voice, data, video, or a combination thereof. Originally, it carried 24 separate calls on individual channels called DS0s, collectively forming a T1 line or DS1. Each DS0 transmits digitized voice, call control, and signaling information.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Manufacturing Driving Faster WANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</guid><description>The recent &amp;ldquo;Great Recession&amp;rdquo; stands out not just for its severity, but also for the uneven recovery that followed. While businesses have bounced back, job growth has lagged. This unusual trend has been attributed to unexpected gains in productivity, where output increases without a proportional rise in employment. But is this sustainable or merely a blip in the current economic climate?
The saying &amp;ldquo;everything old is new again&amp;rdquo; rings true. While new applications and technologies emerge, they often echo past advancements driven by innovation.</description></item><item><title>Cut Telecom Line Expenses, Not Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</guid><description>During economic downturns, businesses often look to cut costs to stay afloat. While eliminating unnecessary expenses is a good start, managers may soon scrutinize even essential budget items.
Instead of panicking and making rash decisions, it&amp;rsquo;s best to proactively identify reasonable cost reductions. This way, you can present well-thought-out proposals and maintain some control over the process.
The key is to maintain productivity while reducing expenses. Instead of completely cutting essential services, focus on achieving the same functionality for less money.</description></item><item><title>The Cheaper T1 Line is a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cheaper-t1-line-is-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cheaper-t1-line-is-a-t1-line/</guid><description>Your telecommunications setup is vital to your business. While your current T1 lines for phone and internet are reliable, you&amp;rsquo;re searching for budget cuts. However, before you think about drastically reducing your telecom expenses, consider these points:
Switching to cheaper, consumer-grade internet and phone services will likely result in lower performance and reliability. This could mean dropped calls, outages, and a negative impact on your clients and suppliers. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to downgrade your service to save money.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI Offers Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</guid><description>If your company relies heavily on phone communication, using numerous phone lines managed by an internal system, ISDN PRI might be the solution for you. It provides excellent voice quality, quick call transfers, and additional features like Caller ID, all while potentially saving you money.
ISDN PRI, or Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is an advanced form of the traditional T1 digital phone line. While it utilizes the same T1 line infrastructure, making it widely accessible, its channel organization sets it apart.</description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country.</description></item></channel></rss>