<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Caribbean on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/caribbean/</link><description>Recent content in Caribbean on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/caribbean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join.</description></item></channel></rss>