<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hire on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hire/</link><description>Recent content in Hire on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:06:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avoid using the following words on your resume: CareerBuilder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-using-the-following-words-on-your-resume-careerbuilder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:06:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-using-the-following-words-on-your-resume-careerbuilder/</guid><description>A CareerBuilder survey found that almost 70% of hiring managers spend less than two minutes looking at resumes, meaning word choice is critical for job seekers.
Rosemary Haefner, CareerBuilder&amp;rsquo;s VP of human resources, advises using strong action verbs that highlight specific experiences, skills, and achievements. She cautions against subjective terms and clichés because they fail to convey concrete information. For example, instead of claiming to be &amp;ldquo;results-driven,&amp;rdquo; demonstrate actual results.</description></item><item><title>First Advantage reported that ten percent of job candidates in the Asia Pacific region are dishonest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-advantage-reported-that-ten-percent-of-job-candidates-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-dishonest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 14:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-advantage-reported-that-ten-percent-of-job-candidates-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-dishonest/</guid><description>First Advantage, a company that specializes in background verification, has found that over 10% of resumes from job applicants in the Asia Pacific region contain inconsistencies. This issue is particularly prominent in Australia, where 12% of candidates were found to have significant discrepancies on their resumes. The company noted a higher rate of alerts related to criminal records and employment history checks among Australian candidates compared to other countries.
First Advantage recommends that companies implement screening practices not only to comply with industry regulations, ensure employee competence, and mitigate physical, legal, and financial risks but also to safeguard their brand reputation.</description></item><item><title>"Robert Walters focuses on hiring for long-term success based on potential."</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-focuses-on-hiring-for-long-term-success-based-on-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 23:18:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-focuses-on-hiring-for-long-term-success-based-on-potential/</guid><description>In Southeast Asia, while a remarkable 94% of individuals hired for potential stay in their roles, nearly half of hiring managers remain hesitant to move away from experience-based recruitment. This resistance persists despite the significant resources wasted on unsuitable candidates.
This data comes from &amp;ldquo;Grow your Talent, Hire Based on Potential,&amp;rdquo; a guide published by Robert Walters in October 2019, which explores the benefits of hiring for potential as a sustainable talent strategy.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item></channel></rss>