<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UOB on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uob/</link><description>Recent content in UOB on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:11:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uob/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel's Dash and UOB Asset Management have collaborated to provide a mobile robo-adviser that includes an ESG option</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for UOBAM Robo-Invest.
Singtel has introduced a new digital advisor, developed by UOB Asset Management (UOBAM), on its Dash e-wallet platform. This launch expands Dash’s selection of financial services, which already encompasses payments, international money transfers, insurance, savings, and investments.
UOBAM Robo-Invest is the first robo-advisor in Singapore available on a mobile wallet and stands out by offering sustainable investing options created by UOBAM specifically for Dash users.</description></item><item><title>Vietnam, a country experiencing growth, is attracting investments from various regions, according to UOB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</guid><description>A recent study by the United Overseas Bank (UOB) suggests Vietnam will experience a surge in investments from nearby countries like Malaysia, Thailand, and Singapore over the next three to five years.
The 2016 UOB Asian Enterprise Survey found that Vietnam is a top expansion target for businesses in Malaysia (38%), Thailand (35%), and Singapore (29%). These nations are among the 28% of surveyed enterprises that selected Vietnam as their preferred expansion destination within the next three to five years.</description></item><item><title>UOB discovers misunderstandings about financing options for small and medium businesses in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: UOB infographic. Statistics gathered from the Financing for Startups and Small Businesses Survey.
A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB) revealed that a significant number of startups and small businesses in Singapore lack a comprehensive understanding of the alternative funding options available to them for early expansion. These businesses are also uncertain about how to effectively utilize options such as venture capital, venture debt, and debt and equity crowdfunding.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's International Enterprise (IE) and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to collaborate on connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</guid><description>International Enterprise (IE) Singapore, a government agency promoting international trade, and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have established a partnership to boost trade and international expansion for Singaporean companies. This agreement, solidified in a memorandum of understanding (MoU), marks IE Singapore’s first strategic partnership with a Singaporean bank.
The collaboration between IE Singapore and UOB aims to support 200 Singaporean companies in expanding overseas within the next three years. Their focus is primarily on Southeast Asia, China, Japan, and Europe.</description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year.</description></item><item><title>The initial business transformation program in Malaysia has achieved notable success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</guid><description>UOB Malaysia and The FinLab have reported that the small- and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) participating in the _Jom Transform Programme_1 could experience productivity gains of up to 30% through digitalization.
Jom Transform is the first program in Malaysia dedicated to helping local businesses digitize their operations, aiming to increase productivity and revenue growth.
Over the three-month program, the 16 participating SMEs acquired digital transformation expertise in areas such as business re-engineering and digital marketing.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia emerges victorious in the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, an Indonesian artist has earned the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award. This year, the United Overseas Bank (UOB) recognized 36-year-old Gatot Indrajati for his relief acrylic painting, Right or Wrong My Home. This artwork also garnered him the 2016 UOB Painting of the Year, Indonesia award.
Judges praised Indrajati&amp;rsquo;s innovative combination of wood, a traditional Indonesian art material, with paint. This creates a visually captivating and modern piece of art.</description></item></channel></rss>