<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-wireless/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Wireless on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:06:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Daddy Wants a BlackBerry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</guid><description>With Father&amp;rsquo;s Day around the corner, forget the usual tie or car-related gifts. This year, give Dad what he truly desires: a cutting-edge BlackBerry Bold for both work and personal use. And here&amp;rsquo;s a secret: you can find it online at a great price.
The BlackBerry Bold combines style and functionality. Its sleek black design exudes professionalism and practicality. This BlackBerry boasts an impressive email client with the renowned &amp;ldquo;push&amp;rdquo; email feature, seamlessly integrating up to 10 accounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry's Bold Move to HSDPA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</guid><description>BlackBerry, the company known for its wireless devices, is launching a new model called &amp;ldquo;Bold&amp;rdquo; with enhanced features like a sharper display, increased storage, a faster processor, and a 2-megapixel camera. However, the most significant advancement lies in its connectivity. The Bold surpasses standard EDGE data services by incorporating tri-band HSDPA and Wi-Fi, catering to the growing demand for desktop-like web browsing and video streaming among professionals.
Adding to the excitement, rumors are circulating about Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone selling out in anticipation of a new model featuring HSDPA technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I'm Not Paying For That Aircard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 07:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</guid><description>Fast and dependable office internet connections are great when you&amp;rsquo;re stationary, but mobile work demands solutions like WiFi hotspots or cellular broadband. While these options are suitable, not all laptops are equipped for cellular broadband.
Aircards, sometimes called wireless modems, bridge this gap. Similar to WiFi access cards, these devices allow laptops to connect to cellular broadband networks. In the past, laptops primarily used built-in modems, requiring separate cards for WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>