<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Herbalife on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/herbalife/</link><description>Recent content in Herbalife on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/herbalife/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Herbalife introduces a new skincare line to the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Herbalife, a nutrition company, has expanded its product line with the launch of Herbalife SKIN, a new skincare collection available in Asia Pacific markets. This line complements Herbalife&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;outer nutrition&amp;rdquo; range, which focuses on achieving healthy, youthful skin through a blend of natural ingredients, botanicals, extracts, and scientific formulation.
[Image of Herbalife logo]
Herbalife SKIN products are designed to create softer, smoother, and more radiant skin while minimizing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Herbalife has found that women in Singapore who work are less active than men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</guid><description>Herbalife, a worldwide nutrition company, has found some differences in the health outlooks and routines of working men and women in Singapore. Their Nutrition at Work survey showed that, compared to men, women in Singapore tend to stay at their desks longer, eat lunch at their desks more, and have more difficulty being active during a typical workday.
“Our aim as a global nutrition company is to provide members and customers with high-quality nutrition products that support healthy eating and active lifestyles,” said Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Making small changes to your lifestyle can lead to a healthier you in the long run, according to Herbalife</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</guid><description>People in Asia are interested in expanding their fitness routines beyond traditional practices like yoga and tai chi. However, Samantha Clayton, Director of Worldwide Fitness Education at Herbalife, notes that they face unique challenges, such as extreme weather and demanding work schedules, and need to adapt their fitness routines accordingly.
She emphasizes the importance of integrating fitness into everyday life, especially when environmental factors like air quality, heat, and humidity can be obstacles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>