<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Connections on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Gigabit Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Metropolitan and wide area networks are getting faster. Undersea cables are moving from 10 to 40 and even 100 Gbps, and land-based fiber lines are already at 100 Gbps. This means large companies, healthcare organizations, and video producers are starting to find their networks inadequate. The good news is that there are more affordable options than ever before.
There are several practical ways to boost your MAN or WAN bandwidth beyond one Gigabit per second, up to 10 Gbps.</description></item><item><title>Why Choose Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet has transitioned from a novelty to a necessity, as indispensable as electricity or heat. However, its unreliability can be a source of frustration, especially given its immense potential for businesses. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to enhance Internet stability and dependability.
Internet vs Internet
Internet experiences are not universal, despite discussions about net neutrality claiming otherwise. While some enjoy superior performance, others face limitations. How is this possible?</description></item><item><title>DS3 Over Copper Avoids Fiber Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</guid><description>Businesses desire fiber optic connections for their high bandwidth capabilities, but the installation costs can be prohibitive, ranging from tens of thousands to even hundreds of thousands of dollars. However, there&amp;rsquo;s an alternative solution worth considering: DS3 over Copper.
Although DS3 is often associated with fiber optic lines, it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a 45 Mbps TDM protocol that can operate on various carriers. Originally, DS3 was delivered using T3 coaxial copper lines, waveguides, or microwave transmissions.</description></item><item><title>Tysons Corner Gets Wireless Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tysons-corner-gets-wireless-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 19:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tysons-corner-gets-wireless-network-connections/</guid><description>Washington D.C., a major hub for technology in government, military, and business, has been a key market for XO Communication&amp;rsquo;s competitive network services. Their newest offering is high-capacity broadband wireless for the Tysons Corner area of Virginia, with speeds ranging from 10 Mbps to 1 Gbps for various services including VoIP, Ethernet, and private lines.
This surpasses WiFi capabilities, offering speeds from 10 Mbps to 1 Gbps, exceeding what&amp;rsquo;s available through standard consumer wireless options like WiFi and WiMAX.</description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability.</description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds.</description></item><item><title>A Graphical Introduction to Big Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</guid><description>Confused about the hype surrounding Big Data? This infographic might help clear things up&amp;hellip;
Feeling limited by your current internet connection when dealing with large amounts of data, cloud services, backups, or file transfers? Upgrading might be more affordable than you expect. Get immediate pricing on cost-effective copper and fiber internet options for your business.
Credit to Wikibon Infographics for this infographic on Big Data.</description></item><item><title>Why Colo Bandwidth Pricing Is Lowest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</guid><description>Intrigued by the idea of significantly cheaper bandwidth? Take a look at the pricing for colocation bandwidth and see for yourself.
It&amp;rsquo;s tempting, right? The cost per Mbps at a colocation center is often much lower than standard bandwidth costs for your servers, even with a discounted rate from a telecom broker. While this might seem unfair, it&amp;rsquo;s simply a matter of economics.
Colocation facilities can offer these reduced costs for a couple of reasons.</description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle.</description></item><item><title>Copper While Waiting For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</guid><description>Fiber optic connections are the optimal choice for high bandwidth, offering speeds from 10 Mbps to 10 Gbps using either SONET or Carrier Ethernet protocols. However, accessing these options requires &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber service, which can take several months or more due to potential construction delays. So, how do you maintain connectivity in the meantime?
While waiting for fiber activation was once the only option, many carriers now offer a two-stage solution for businesses needing immediate bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity For Multi-Business Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</guid><description>Instead of constructing their own offices, many businesses rent space in large buildings like office complexes, shopping centers, or strip malls. This shared situation offers a unique opportunity to secure better bandwidth at lower costs by joining forces with other tenants in the building.
There are a few approaches to leverage the collective bandwidth requirements of multiple businesses. One method is for the building owner to become an ISP, providing bandwidth to all tenants.</description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading.</description></item><item><title>What Real Estate Developers Need to Know About Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-real-estate-developers-need-to-know-about-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 23:03:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-real-estate-developers-need-to-know-about-ethernet/</guid><description>High-speed internet is becoming as essential as other utilities like electricity, water, and phone services. Businesses rely on it, and those working from home expect it. Developers of office spaces, industrial parks, and new housing divisions should incorporate broadband internet into their plans, rather than making it the responsibility of buyers or renters. Broadband access is not just a desirable feature, but a potential revenue source, and Ethernet is the best technology for the job.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs.</description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>Many Flavors of Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting your business to the internet is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world. It&amp;rsquo;s practically impossible to operate without a broadband connection. Customers, cloud services, backups, suppliers, and even connections to home offices or remote locations rely on it. The question is, how can you establish the best connection for your business?
Businesses have numerous options for internet service, but the variety can be overwhelming. Choosing the cheapest option might leave you frustrated if it can&amp;rsquo;t handle your needs.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines.</description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines, a technology dating back to the telegraph, have evolved to offer businesses speeds ranging from 1.5 Mbps to 100 Gbps. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the characteristics of leased lines and how they stand apart from conventional broadband.
What is a Leased Line?
Similar to leasing a property, leased lines involve an agreement and regular payments that grant you exclusive access to a dedicated communication line.
In its simplest form, a leased line consists of a pair of copper wires, linking your location to your provider, often through a local telephone company (ILEC).</description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs T1 in Under 3 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Ethernet bandwidth services are generating a lot of interest, but are they truly superior to traditional T1 lines? Is switching from copper to fiber a wise decision financially? This brief comparison of Ethernet and T1 services will provide clarity.
Interested in determining which connectivity and hosted services best meet your business needs? Get instant pricing and availability for Ethernet, T1, and other connectivity options.</description></item><item><title>Looking For A Lit Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</guid><description>When seeking high-speed internet for your business, you need more than just a building with lights on at night. You need a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; – one connected to a fiber optic network.
Fiber optic connectivity is crucial for high bandwidth. While most buildings have copper wiring for traditional phone lines and T1 connections, these offer limited bandwidth (1.5 Mbps per line). Fiber optics, on the other hand, provide significantly faster speeds (10 Gbps or more per fiber) using light to transmit data.</description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards.</description></item><item><title>What is VPLS Bringing to MPLS Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous branches have embraced MPLS networks for their affordability and high performance in connecting multiple locations. However, they may be overlooking a superior connectivity solution: Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS).
Essentially, VPLS is an Ethernet transport service operating over existing MPLS networks, enhancing rather than replacing them.
What sets VPLS apart is its ability to unify all your individual LANs into a single, company-wide network. This network transcends geographical limitations, enabling international connections for globally distributed businesses.</description></item></channel></rss>