<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Real Time on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/real-time/</link><description>Recent content in Real Time on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/real-time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The TomTom City portal offers real-time traffic and travel updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</guid><description>TomTom (TOM2) introduces TomTom City, a digital platform providing real-time traffic data and travel details to both individuals and traffic management professionals.
This new service showcases the wide array of traffic information available for specific cities and acts as a hub for connecting traffic authorities, businesses, and citizens to collaborate on sustainable and efficient mobility solutions. Building on the traffic information already available through TomTom navigation devices and partners in automotive, consumer, and government sectors, TomTom City expands upon the historical congestion data provided in reports like the TomTom Traffic Index...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Haul Voice, Video and Data via MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses need to transmit voice, video, and data across long distances, whether between cities, across the country, or even internationally. While both the internet and dedicated private lines are viable options, there&amp;rsquo;s another solution you might not be familiar with: MPLS networks. This article will explore why MPLS is a strong option for long-distance data transport and how to decide which solution best suits your needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Word Lens assists travelers in translating signs instantly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</guid><description>Quest Visual, the company behind the augmented reality app Word Lens, has decided to offer the app and all of its language packs for free for a limited time. This includes languages like English, French, Italian, Portuguese, and Russian. This gesture of thanks to their users comes as the company transitions to new ownership under Google.
Source: Word Lens page on Play Store.
You can download the Glass, Android, and iOS versions of Word Lens from the Quest Visual website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>