<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2004/38 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2004/38/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2004/38 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2004/38/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the free movement of people in the European Economic Area (EEA) distinct from that in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Karin Fløistad: PhD Candidate, European University Institute; practicing lawyer at Norwegian law firm Simonsen Vogt Wiig
The UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit relationship with the EU often involves discussions about the free movement of people, with the EEA Agreement frequently cited as a potential model. This piece will analyze two key distinctions between the EEA Agreement&amp;rsquo;s approach to the free movement of people and that of full EU membership.
The EEA Agreement integrates the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market with three members of the European Free Trade Association (EFTA): Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to deport and prohibit unemployed EU citizens from returning?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Germany&amp;rsquo;s recent exploration of expelling unemployed EU citizens has sparked interest among critics of EU free movement in the UK. As this topic gains traction, it&amp;rsquo;s timely to clarify the circumstances under which EU citizens can be expelled.
While the EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive empowers Member States to expel citizens for reasons related to public policy, security, or health, it explicitly prohibits using these grounds for economic reasons. Consequently, the rules for expelling unemployed EU citizens lie elsewhere within the Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An important Irish ruling on compensation for violation of EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) affirmed the right of individuals to sue Member States for damages resulting from breaches of EU law over two decades ago in the Francovich case, most subsequent lawsuits have been initiated by businesses seeking compensation for financial losses. The CJEU has yet to address a case involving damages claims related to the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The historical context of the Dano judgment: Free movement and social benefits for economically inactive EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 12:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Géraldine Renaudière, Trainee at the CJEU, within the cabinet of the Court Vice-President, Koen Lenaerts. (This post reflects the author&amp;rsquo;s view only).
The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s recent ruling in Elisabeta Dano and Florin Dano v Jobcenter Leipzig revisits the sensitive issue of national laws that prevent economically inactive EU citizens from receiving special non-contributory benefits, even though those benefits are available to nationals in similar situations. Issued a year after the controversial Brey decision, this judgment aims to clarify the connection between Directive 2004/38, which concerns the free movement of EU citizens, and Regulation 883/2004, which deals with coordinating social security systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's judgment on divorce and free movement law poses a problem.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Singh case tackles a crucial question: what happens to a non-EU spouse&amp;rsquo;s residency rights when their EU citizen partner, who moved to another EU country, leaves that country after their marriage ends? This case highlights a conflict within the EU Citizens’ Directive, where rules concerning divorce and departure clash. Unfortunately, the court chose a simplistic interpretation, aligning with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s prior suggestion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-judgment-on-divorce-and-free-movement-law-poses-a-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the UK's limitation on EU workers' eligibility for benefits lawful - and if not, should it be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK government recently established a new income requirement for EU citizens from other Member States to be classified as &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and access certain benefits. This raises the question of whether these rules align with EU law regarding the free movement of workers and if modifications are necessary.
Under these regulations, EU citizens must earn a minimum of £150 weekly for at least three months to be considered &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and qualify for benefits such as child benefit, child tax credit, job-seekers&amp;rsquo; allowance, and housing benefit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union rejects benefit tourism by EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant ruling in the case of Dano, which dealt with the ability of EU citizens to access social welfare benefits when they relocate to another Member State. The Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the laws in this case (and other rulings earlier this year involving EU citizens with criminal histories) suggests a stricter approach, possibly reflecting the ongoing political discussions regarding the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CS and Rendón Marín: Are Union Citizens and their Third-Country National Parents Experiencing a Revival of the Ruiz Zambrano Ruling?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</guid><description>Maria Haag, PhD Researcher, European University Institute (Florence, Italy) &amp;amp; Michigan Grotius Research Scholar, University of Michigan Law School (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
Background
Five years ago, a significant ruling in the case of C-34/09 Ruiz Zambrano was delivered by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The court found that national measures that hinder EU citizens from genuinely enjoying their rights as citizens are prohibited under Article 20 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial stances on the status of UK and EU citizens in the Brexit negotiations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Introduction
A crucial Brexit issue with potentially significant consequences for many is the fate of UK citizens in the EU and EU citizens in the UK post-Brexit. Addressed early in Brexit negotiations, both sides have established positions: the EU through a Council decision outlining the mandate for Commission negotiators on May 22, and the UK through a government proposal on June 26. Despite claims to the contrary, the UK&amp;rsquo;s proposal didn&amp;rsquo;t precede the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Love triumphs in the CJEU: Equal Marriage and EU Freedom of Movement Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling on same-sex marriage within the framework of EU free movement law in the case of Coman. This case involved a Romanian citizen, Mr. Coman, who married his American husband in Belgium while residing there. When they attempted to return to Romania, the Romanian government, which does not legally acknowledge same-sex marriage, refused residency to Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gathering of EU citizens residing in their home country: Understanding the Surinder Singh and Carpenter rulings for family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
This article examines when an EU citizen residing in their home country can assert rights under EU law for family members to join them. This analysis stems from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressing judgments in the Surinder Singh and Carpenter cases. These cases involve family reunification for EU citizens who return to their home country after residing in another Member State and for EU citizens who provide services in another Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The rights of pregnant workers and the free movement rights of EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Jessy Saint Prix, a young woman from France, relocated to Britain in 2006 to pursue a teaching career. Her experience led her to learn much more about EU law and the English legal system than she expected.
After working in the UK as a teaching assistant for a year, she began a teacher training program (PGCE). During the program, she became pregnant and decided to pause her studies to register with a teaching agency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New mothers who are self-employed and the EU free movement law: the CJEU reaches the expected decision.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
* For further information on EU free movement law issues, refer to the upcoming second edition of the commentary on the EU Citizenship Directive, authored by Elspeth Guild, Steve Peers, and Jonathan Tomkin – available soon
A pertinent question arises when an EU citizen relocates to another Member State and gives birth: do new mothers risk losing their rights under EU free movement law?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Following the Dano ruling, under what circumstances can unemployed EU citizens be deported?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Dano case focused on benefit applications, not deportation. Therefore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly affect deportation. However, due to the Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the EU citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive, it might indirectly impact deportation.
Earlier this year, I published a blog post about when unemployment could justify deporting or banning EU citizens. This post expands on that analysis, considering the Dano judgment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Alice Gross case: Examining EU law implications of allowing murderers to freely move within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British readers of this blog are likely aware of the case of missing teenager Alice Gross. A Latvian man, Arnis Zalkalns, is a person of interest in her disappearance. What makes this case more complex is that Mr. Zalkalns had a prior murder conviction in Latvia before relocating to the UK. He has since vanished, possibly returning to Latvia.
This raises several questions: how was a convicted murderer able to enter the UK undetected?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are the new proposals for simplifying Schengen visa applications for third-country national family members of EU citizens comprehensive enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU citizens with family members who are non-EU citizens often face obstacles to free movement, especially when those family members are from Asia, Africa, or the Caribbean. Traveling outside of the Schengen area with these family members often requires obtaining visas, adding complexity to their trips.
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent proposals on visas, if adopted, could bring some relief. One proposal focuses on revising the existing &amp;ldquo;Schengen visa&amp;rdquo; rules, which permit travel across Schengen countries for three months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Handbook on Marriages of Convenience by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
In September 2014, the Commission introduced a Handbook designed to guide Member States in addressing marriages of convenience between EU citizens and non-EU nationals. The goal is to combat these marriages without unduly restricting the free movement rights of EU citizens. The Commission emphasizes that the guidelines, developed in collaboration with Member States, are not legally binding and don&amp;rsquo;t supersede existing EU law or its future interpretations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anticipating the ECJ Decision in Coman: Progressing Towards EU-wide Recognition of Same-Sex Marriages across Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Photo: Mr Adrian Coman (right) with his spouse, Mr Claibourn Robert Hamilton (left)
(picture from PinkNews http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/29/romania-goes-to-court-over-whether-to-recognise-gay-couples-marriage/)
Introduction
The question of legal recognition for same-sex relationships has become a major topic in recent decades, sparking intense discussions globally in legislative bodies, courts, and the media, with strong opinions on both sides. This complex and delicate issue intersects with human rights, religious beliefs, moral perspectives, traditions, and constitutional principles like equality, personal freedom, and inherent human worth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipating-the-ecj-decision-in-coman-progressing-towards-eu-wide-recognition-of-same-sex-marriages-across-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on domestic violence and the free movement of EU citizens is disgraceful.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU freedom of movement laws don&amp;rsquo;t directly apply to non-EU citizens. Instead, they gain rights through family ties with EU citizens. This poses a problem in domestic violence situations where the abuser is an EU citizen and the victim is not. Leaving the abuser could lead to expulsion, forcing victims to choose between their safety and remaining in the country, potentially separated from their children.
EU law attempts to mitigate this risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's 'emergency brake' preserving or abolishing the free movement of people?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Steve Peers
If British pro-Europeans could travel back in time, their priority should be returning to 2004. They should focus all efforts on persuading the then-British government to reconsider granting immediate free movement of workers from new EU member states. While economically advantageous, this decision has severely damaged public support for EU membership in the UK, as well as for the UK Labour Party.
Today, the free movement of people is often framed as a fundamental flaw within the EU, prompting calls for the UK to either leave or renegotiate its terms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unemployed EU citizens may benefit from the CJEU's decision, potentially complicating David Cameron's renegotiation strategy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ability of EU citizens to move freely between Member States, often referred to as ‘immigration,’ has sparked significant political debate, particularly in the UK. Access to benefits for these individuals remains a point of contention. The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has an opportunity to provide clarity on key aspects of this issue in the upcoming case of Alimanovic. An Advocate-General recently issued a non-binding opinion on this case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union provides clarification on the Singh and Carpenter rulings for EU citizens' family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Typically, EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant residency rights to non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in their own home country. However, recent court rulings have clarified two key exceptions to this rule, albeit with unexpected outcomes. These rulings stem from Advocate-General Sharpston&amp;rsquo;s December 2013 opinion, as discussed in a prior blog entry.
The O and B case: Revisiting Singh
In 2007, O, a non-EU citizen, and their Dutch partner, sponsor O, moved to Spain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has upheld the temporary free movement rights of third-country family members of EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent ruling from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the McCarthy case addresses a crucial question about EU free movement law in the UK: can the UK restrict the ability of family members (who are third-country nationals) of UK (and other EU) citizens to visit the UK?
The case involved a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual British and Irish citizen)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>