<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Online on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online/</link><description>Recent content in Online on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hasso Plattner Institute is offering a free six-week MOOC on the Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</guid><description>The Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) is offering a free, six-week online course in English about the fundamentals of the Internet. Starting on March 31st, HPI&amp;rsquo;s director, Professor Christoph Meinel, will teach participants about the technical basis of the Internet through a massive open online course (MOOC) titled &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Internetworking with TCP/IP.&amp;rdquo; The course is available to anyone and can be accessed through free registration.
Professor Meinel believes that anyone who uses the Internet for daily tasks like online shopping, reading news articles, or sending emails should understand the technologies that make these actions possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Purchase online and make your payment at a nearby convenience store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</guid><description>MOLPay, a Southeast Asian online payment provider, is partnering with 7-Eleven Malaysia to introduce a new e-commerce payment method.
This service, called MOLPay CASH, will launch first in select Klang Valley 7-Eleven stores, with 735 stores currently offering this option and plans for further expansion. By July 2014, all 1,569 Malaysian stores will provide this service.
MOLPay CASH allows merchants to accept cash payments from customers at their nearest 7-Eleven. After an online purchase, a barcode is generated for the customer to use for payment at a 7-Eleven location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KKday has launched in Singapore and is introducing the #taiwantrippin promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</guid><description>Source: KKday. Ming Chen, CEO of Asia’s leading travel experience e-commerce platform KKday celebrates Singapore launch, and the #taiwantrippin digital campaign.
KKday, an Asian e-commerce platform specializing in travel experiences, has launched in Singapore. Based in Taiwan, KKday links users with local tours globally. Following its 2014 debut, KKday expanded to Hong Kong, Korea, and Japan, with Singapore as its fourth market.
“Establishing a presence in Singapore was a logical step...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Viva La Fleur has launched online sales of its durable, all-natural floral arrangements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</guid><description>Since its establishment in October 2013, Viva La Fleur Floral Boutique has impressed businesses with its enduring, all-natural floral arrangements and bouquets. The company holds the exclusive distribution rights for LavieFlo, a technology that makes flowers appear freshly cut for months, eliminating the need for water or sunlight.
Sourced globally, fresh flowers from countries like Japan and China undergo a meticulous preservation process. This process substitutes the plant&amp;rsquo;s sap with a solution that retains the natural appearance and texture of the petals and leaves...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air France provides complimentary newspapers and magazines for tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</guid><description>Air France has launched a new app, Air France Press, allowing Flying Blue members to enjoy complimentary digital media offline.
Flying Blue members can download a selection of French and international newspapers and magazines at no cost. This content is accessible offline before, during, and after their Air France flights. Passengers can download publications with their ticket, starting 24 hours before their flight until departure.
Access to the service is granted by logging into the app using Flying Blue credentials or a reservation number...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Facebook claims that only native and video advertisements provide substantial value</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Head of Ad Tech, Dave Jakubowski, recently stated that exchanges and banners lack significant value in a blog post. He highlights that Facebook conducted a test using &amp;ldquo;a buying platform&amp;rdquo; within Atlas, their ad solution. The test revealed that despite reaching real people accurately, many ads were low-quality or fraudulent.
Although effective in removing these poor ads, Facebook was surprised by the sheer volume of ineffective inventory. The test also demonstrated that only native and video ad formats yielded substantial value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brief Lab introduces new online certification program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</guid><description>The Brief Lab, an organization that trains professionals to be concise communicators, is marking its one-year anniversary with a redesigned website and the introduction of its first online certification program, Brief Practitioner.
Source: The Brief Lab website.
The Brief Practitioner program is geared towards professionals who want to embrace conciseness and become certified in a structured approach to lean communication. The online course is designed for those who aim to champion these methodologies within their organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Men's Chorus debuts virtual choir performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-chorus-debuts-virtual-choir-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:33:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-chorus-debuts-virtual-choir-performance/</guid><description>Sing! Men’s Chorus (SMC), an all-male choir in Singapore, has launched its first virtual choir project, &amp;ldquo;Why We Sing,&amp;rdquo; marking the return of arts performances in the country. The music video, available on SMC&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel, was created over two months and conveys a message of hope: that the arts community can adapt to a new normal where the arts, especially music, are recognized for their essential role in community development...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-chorus-debuts-virtual-choir-performance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-chorus-debuts-virtual-choir-performance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A digital sales training platform that enables users to engage in role-playing exercises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 19:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</guid><description>Role-playing is crucial for sales training, allowing two people to act out real-life sales scenarios.
While businesses utilize meeting software for training remote sales teams, this technology often lacks features for practicing pitches online.
uniRow&amp;rsquo;s TrainingCloud.com is designed specifically to facilitate online role-playing during sales training. Trainers can conduct, record, and share role-plays for evaluation and learning purposes.
Nimit Kumar, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of uniRow, emphasizes the importance of hands-on practice in sales training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pi1M Training Programme offered by Digi provides benefits to small business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Participants of the Pi1M Training Programme gathered for a group photo.
Digi Telecommunications recently conducted a training program for community members residing near the company-managed Pusat Internet 1 Malaysia (Pi1M) centers. This tailored program reflects Digi&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering online entrepreneurship within its Pi1M communities. Currently, Digi manages 34 Pi1Ms across Pahang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Johor, Melaka, and Sarawak, with plans to establish 70 more centers by year&amp;rsquo;s end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jumei expands its online beauty offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</guid><description>Source: Jumei website.
Jumei International Holding, a Chinese online retailer specializing in beauty products, has formed several strategic alliances with international brands. The company revealed that Max Factor and OPI Products have joined its Authentic Beauty Product Alliance (ABPA) and that it has established a partnership with American fashion designer Jill Stuart.
Through its website and mobile app, the company provides a variety of products, including branded beauty items, fashionable apparel, and other lifestyle goods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to GfK, Singaporean travelers frequently plan their trips with less than a month's notice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</guid><description>A Jetstar aircraft at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Companies can potentially reduce travel expenses by adopting strategies used by individual travelers. A study by GfK revealed that roughly 76% of trips originating in Singapore were booked no more than one month before the travel date.
Laurens van den Oever, Global Travel Director at GfK, suggests that this trend of booking close to the travel date is likely due to airlines offering discounted fares for last-minute flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Journeyful has revamped its website, incorporating additional listings and enhancing rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</guid><description>Source: Journeyful. The Journeyful 2.0 website.
Journeyful, a company located in Singapore, has relaunched an updated website for its rewards-based online travel agency, Journeyful.com. The new and improved &amp;ldquo;Journeyful 2.0&amp;rdquo; website features a selection of over 200,000 hotels globally, a price-match guarantee, and Facebook integration.
The redesigned website includes Journeyful MICE, which offers comprehensive solutions for business conferences, corporate events, and incentive trips. A Journeyful representative explained that once an online inquiry is submitted, MICE consultants collaborate offline with the organization to personalize solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA has entered into a partnership with Careem for ride-hailing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</guid><description>Source: RTA. HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of RTA and Mudassir Sheikha, Founder and Managing Director of Careem, signed the agreement on behalf of the two respective entities. RTA executives attending the signing included Mohammed Obaid Al Mulla, Member of Board of Executive Directors, Abdullah Yousef Al Ali, CEO of Public Transport Agency, and Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems. Bassel Al Nahlaoui, VP of Business Development &amp;amp; Government Relations attended on behalf of Careem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Buyer (or Surfer) Be Cautious!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 21:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</guid><description>Over the past week, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a few situations that highlight the internet&amp;rsquo;s potential, both good and bad, for software troubleshooting and learning, especially with Microsoft Dynamics GP.
For instance, I came across a Summit Group Software Blog post about recent changes to US Payroll for form 941. This was perfect timing, as I had just seen an internal email chain about it. The blog had valuable information from a reliable source that I could share, which was a great find...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</a></p></description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Monitoring social media shows the sentiments towards Formula One in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>In July, Microsoft launched Microsoft Social Listening in eight Asia Pacific markets. This service is designed to help professionals in sales, marketing, and customer care understand and engage with customers on social media more effectively. Microsoft Social Listening provides tools for analyzing market intelligence from social conversations, including sentiment analysis across multiple platforms. It also allows users to monitor products, brands, competitors, and campaigns globally in real time to gain a comprehensive understanding of their customers and their business in the social media landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kluje.com is enhancing its property management bidding e-platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kluje-com-is-enhancing-its-property-management-bidding-e-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 07:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kluje-com-is-enhancing-its-property-management-bidding-e-platform/</guid><description>Kluje.com, pronounced &amp;ldquo;clue-jay&amp;rdquo;, has expanded its online contractor platform to include over 30,000 property agents and facility managers. The platform allows users to easily find qualified contractors for various tasks, such as electrical work, plumbing, and flooring.
Jamey Merkel, CEO of Kluje.com, explains that the platform addresses the time constraints faced by real estate and facilities professionals responsible for property upkeep. By streamlining the process of finding and hiring contractors, Kluje...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kluje-com-is-enhancing-its-property-management-bidding-e-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kluje-com-is-enhancing-its-property-management-bidding-e-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lark Technologies is providing a free collaboration tool for businesses in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:59:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Lark Technologies, headquartered in Singapore, is now offering its comprehensive, enterprise-level collaboration platform, Lark, free of charge across Southeast Asia. This includes Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, the Philippines, Thailand, and Vietnam. Lark provides a range of features, including unlimited video calls and online collaboration tools, to facilitate seamless teamwork remotely. Users can view colleagues&amp;rsquo; schedules, initiate video calls directly from calendar events, and collaborate on documents during video meetings.
Joey Lim, APAC Commercial Lead at Lark, highlighted that with an estimated 90% of Asia Pacific employees currently working remotely, the company aims to empower teams to maintain productivity regardless of physical location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kramnik will face Alcántara in a rematch on Chessarena.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</guid><description>Source: World Chess. Vladimir Kramnik (pictured left) is set to have a rematch against José Alcántara (Jospem, pictured right) in August 2024.
World Chess, an organization dedicated to increasing the popularity of chess worldwide, is organizing &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims 2.&amp;rdquo; This event is a rematch following a controversial first &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims&amp;rdquo; match between chess players Vladimir Kramnik and José Alcántara. The event will be broadcasted live with commentary from well-known chess personalities and include interactive elements for viewers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>