<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alignment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/alignment/</link><description>Recent content in Alignment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/alignment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Final Adjustments, Repair of a Damaged Pinth Corner and Test Drive with Bobby Hutcherson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration is nearing completion. Following the installation of new gold-plated RCA plugs, I made adjustments to the sub-chassis, platter height, and meticulously cleaned the aluminum surfaces. To prevent the needle from contacting the platter ribs if the record detection mechanism fails, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit.
Subsequently, I calibrated the tracking weight scale and enhanced the counterweight adjustment mechanism. The original flimsy circlip was replaced with a more durable M3 nut and washer setup, enhancing its resistance to transport-related stress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Final Touches - AC Motor Calibration, Adjusting Platter and Sub-Chassis and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration is nearly complete. After deep cleaning the aluminum panels and platter, I adjusted the sub-chassis and platter height, tonearm lowering limit, and tracking weight.
There are videos on my YouTube channel demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, similar for the 4000 and 4002 models. Another video covers the crucial adjustment of lowering limits, essential because the 4002&amp;rsquo;s system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent damage from photosensor failure. Proper adjustment acts as a safeguard, potentially saving an expensive cartridge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments, a New Solenoid, and Test Drive with Christoph Spendel &amp; Wolfgang Schlüter Group on MPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</guid><description>The final steps of restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) involved replacing the sensor arm light bulb with an LED assembly and performing standard adjustments. These included calibrating the tracking feedback, platter height, level, sub-chassis height, and arm lowering limit, which prevents stylus damage.
To ensure accurate tracking weight calibration, the C-clip securing the counterweight adjustment screw was replaced with an M3 nut and washer for permanent fixation. This guarantees that the calibration remains consistent during shipping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's "The Love Connection"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project is finished after some final tuning. I made adjustments to the platter height and sub-chassis alignment, documenting the process for my YouTube channel. While my videos feature a Beogram 4000, the method for adjusting the platter bearing and sub-chassis are quite similar for the 4002 model.
The arm lowering limit was the next step, a crucial adjustment to safeguard the cantilever if the record detection malfunctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter Height, Tonearm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>After successfully positioning the top aluminum plates, I could adjust the sub-chassis and platter. This step is crucial as it sets the foundation for adjusting the arm lowering limits and, ultimately, the tracking force. This Beogram will be ready for an initial test run once this is completed. I&amp;rsquo;ve previously provided detailed explanations of the chassis and platter adjustment process on my blog and YouTube channel. Two videos demonstrate the platter bearing adjustment and the subchassis adjustment (using a Beogram 4000 as an example, although the procedure is almost identical for the 4002)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Final Adjustments, Some Odds and Ends and a Test Drive with Cal Tjader</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</guid><description>After switching the original black plinth with a teak one from a Beogram 4002, it was time for the final adjustments and a test run of the Beogram 4000 turntable. I started by setting the platter height, tilt, and alignment with the surrounding aluminum panels. Next, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowest point to make sure the needle wouldn&amp;rsquo;t touch the black ribs on the platter if the platter detection system malfunctioned...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Chico Hamilton on Auto-Repeat!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</guid><description>It was time for the final adjustments on the Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration project. Adjusting the platter and sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking force is always a satisfying part of the process. It means the turntable is ready for its initial post-restoration playback. Observing the intricate mechanics in motion, bringing out the best in vintage vinyl, is always captivating.
This Beogram presented a unique sub-chassis and platter adjustment challenge. The platter was positioned too close to the front right edge of the aluminum plate cutout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Fit and Finish Rework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</guid><description>Restoring Beogram 4002 turntables is a fulfilling endeavor, though it often necessitates revisiting steps multiple times. Despite getting this particular Beogram functioning properly, I was dissatisfied with the fit of some components.
The tonearm cover wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting flush, as evidenced by its crooked appearance in the photo, with the center divider visibly off-center between the fixed arm and tonearm.
A head-on perspective further highlights this issue, along with the misaligned deck trim, showing an undesirably wide gap between the panels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddy Hubbard's 1975 Album "Polar AC"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable to its former glory is always fulfilling. This particular restoration involved several meticulous adjustments before I could relish Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s music.
The first crucial step was aligning the platter and arms flawlessly. Next, I had to align the platter with its surrounding aluminum panels while ensuring the chassis remained suspended, delicately balanced on its spring-loaded arms. This procedure requires precision as the tolerances for these adjustments are minimal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's Liquid Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</guid><description>Following the installation of the Beolover 4002 Commander remote control and internal RIAA pre-amplifier, it was time for final adjustments before testing the turntable. The first step was tracking feedback adjustment. A blue trimmer on the tracking sensor LED light source simplified the fine-tuning of the feedback after the coarse mechanical adjustment of the sensor housing.
Next, the subclasses and platter height were adjusted, followed by the arm lowering limit. The lowering limit ensures the needle can descend below the record surface without hitting the platter ribs if the record detection fails...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustments, Cleaning the Aluminum Surfaces and a First Spin with Freddie Hubbard!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</guid><description>Following the installation of a new gold-plated DIN 5 plug, the Beogram 4000 was ready for its initial test. The RPM was fine-tuned using a custom Beolover RPM device, aided by the recently installed precision multi-turn trimmers. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that allowing the unit to warm up for approximately 15 minutes before this adjustment is recommended, as the RPM can fluctuate slightly during this period. For fellow enthusiasts, the Beolover RPM device is available upon request via email or the contact form and includes a separate base for convenient setup and occasional RPM checks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Platter, Sub-Chassis, Arm Lowering Limit and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>To prepare the Beogram 4002 (5513) for testing, several mechanical adjustments were required. The platter needed to be perfectly aligned with the surrounding aluminum plates. This involved balancing the floating sub-chassis within its support brackets. After aligning the chassis and platter, the arm lowering limit was addressed. Finally, the tracking force was calibrated to match the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s weight dial.
Prior to adjusting the sub-chassis, damaged cabinet guidance washers, crucial for securing the top aluminum plates, were replaced with 3D-printed replicas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Idris Muhammad (KU-17) After Platter and Tonearm Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day at the shop, where another Beogram 4002 (5513) is looking and sounding fantastic! The finishing touches involved adjusting the sub-chassis and platter to ensure they float freely and sit flush with the deck&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface. My YouTube channel features two videos demonstrating these adjustments for a Beogram 4000, which are very similar to the 4002 model.
Afterward, the tonearm lowering limit was adjusted, a crucial procedure given the 4002&amp;rsquo;s control system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent photosensor malfunctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter and Tonearm Weight and Limits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</guid><description>The final stage of restoring the Beogram 4002 (5503) involved balancing the sub-chassis, setting the correct platter height, and adjusting the tonearm. To ensure the best range of motion, the sub-chassis must be carefully positioned between the transport lock clamps. The platter height and vertical alignment need to be set so that the platter sits level with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s aluminum covers. This allows for the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit to be established and the tracking weight to be calibrated against the adjustment dial located on the arm weight housing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Floating Chassis, Arm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>The next steps were to make adjustments to the platter, sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking weight. Additional information on this process is available on my Beogram 4000 page, which includes posts and videos. Before starting, I needed to replace the cabinet guiding washers because they were either damaged or replaced with unsuitable substitutes.
[Image of a missing cabinet guidance washer]
A video demonstrating this process is available in my Beogram 4002 playlist on my YouTube channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Chassis, Platter, Tonearm Limits and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. After adjusting the sub-chassis and platter, I set the tonearm limits and calibrated the tracking force. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to finalize the platter height before adjusting the arm, ensuring the correct arm-to-platter distance. My YouTube channel has videos demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, particularly for the Beogram 4000, but the 4002 process is similar.
Here’s the result:
The platter is now centered and level within the main aluminum plate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>