<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UK Withdrawal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-withdrawal/</link><description>Recent content in UK Withdrawal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-withdrawal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union considered valid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart
Introduction
The Treaty of Lisbon introduced Article 50 to the Treaty on European Union (TEU), establishing the legal framework for exiting the European Union (EU). This article acknowledges the possibility of withdrawal, a concept many legal experts believed existed even before the Treaty of Lisbon. Article 50 TEU outlines the withdrawal procedure. However, some argue that it contradicts the EU&amp;rsquo;s fundamental nature and weakens member states&amp;rsquo; commitment to European integration, raising questions about the ideal withdrawal mechanism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit Redux: Exploring the legal complexities of retracting the EU departure notification and subsequently re-notifying the intention to leave.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law, University College London
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Wightman case offers valuable insights into the Brexit process. The Court affirmed that the UK could unilaterally withdraw its intention to leave the EU, without needing approval from the remaining 27 EU members.
While this is a significant development that could empower those advocating for a second referendum with the option to remain in the EU, the CJEU ruling is ultimately inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it appropriate to question the credibility of research conducted by academics whose institutions receive funding from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 08:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Some Eurosceptics suggest that research should be disregarded if the academics involved or their institutions have received EU funding, especially if that research contradicts Eurosceptic viewpoints. This tactic has been used against both recent research on the positive impacts of free movement of EU citizens and me personally. While it&amp;rsquo;s tempting to ignore these accusations, they are frequently used to discredit objective evidence supporting pro-European arguments, particularly in the context of a potential referendum on British exit from the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mastering the art of releasing control - the Charter of Fundamental Rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Eduardo Gill-Pedro, Post-Doctoral Researcher, Faculty of Law, Lund University: Eduardo.gill-pedro@jur.lu.se
The UK Government&amp;rsquo;s proposition to exclude the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights (the Charter) from UK law after Brexit (clause 5(4) of the EU Withdrawal Bill) has drawn criticism from opposition parties. The Labour party views this as a non-negotiable issue and refuses to endorse any bill that doesn&amp;rsquo;t integrate the Charter into UK law. Keir Starmer, the Shadow Brexit Secretary, previously stated that Labour would only back a deal that meets its &amp;ldquo;six tests,&amp;rdquo; one being the preservation of &amp;ldquo;rights and protections&amp;rdquo; to avoid a decline in standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The process of withdrawing from the EU: Examining the uses and abuses of Article 50 TEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</guid><description>If the UK decides to hold a referendum on leaving the EU, also known as &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; Article 50 of the Treaty on the European Union (TEU) will be a focal point. This article outlines the exit process for member states. While some suggest using Article 50 to renegotiate UK membership, its legal and political limitations make this challenging.
The Details of Article 50 Article 50 allows any EU member state to withdraw according to its constitution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit: You have the option to change your mind. The CJEU ruling in Wightman allows for a U-turn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The recent definitive ruling by the Full Court concerning the Wightman case reaffirms the UK&amp;rsquo;s ability to independently revoke its withdrawal notification from the EU under the most flexible terms. This judgment aligns with the non-binding opinion given the previous week by an Advocate-General.
The judgment
The Court dismissed the UK government&amp;rsquo;s claim of the case being hypothetical, emphasizing the imminent involvement of some litigants (who are MPs) in voting on the proposed withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial stances on the status of UK and EU citizens in the Brexit negotiations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Introduction
A crucial Brexit issue with potentially significant consequences for many is the fate of UK citizens in the EU and EU citizens in the UK post-Brexit. Addressed early in Brexit negotiations, both sides have established positions: the EU through a Council decision outlining the mandate for Commission negotiators on May 22, and the UK through a government proposal on June 26. Despite claims to the contrary, the UK&amp;rsquo;s proposal didn&amp;rsquo;t precede the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Failed Gamble: Brexit Election aftermath and the future steps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent UK election concluded with an unexpected &amp;lsquo;hung Parliament,&amp;rsquo; where no single party secured a majority in the House of Commons. This raises questions about the future of Brexit.
Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s Conservative party undeniably faced a major setback. The Prime Minister called for this election three years ahead of schedule, seeking a stronger majority to solidify her Brexit plan. Instead, voters reduced her majority, resulting in a minority government...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Paying tribute to Catalonia: The impact of EU law on movements for independence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:39:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent surge in support for pro-independence parties in Catalonia has revived discussions about the connection between EU law and independence movements within member states. This issue was previously discussed in the context of the Scottish independence referendum, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth revisiting now. There are three interconnected questions: Firstly, what happens if a region within a member state declares independence unilaterally, a potential scenario in Catalonia? Secondly, if a newly independent state, formerly part of an EU member, seeks continued EU membership, what are the implications?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Analysis of Article 50(1) TEU: Member States' Right to Decide on Withdrawal from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) outlines the process for a Member State to withdraw from the European Union (EU). While seemingly straightforward, the first paragraph of this article raises questions about its interpretation.
Can a Member State unilaterally decide to withdraw under Article 50(1) TEU?
The primary question surrounding the first paragraph of Article 50 TEU is if it permits a unilateral withdrawal decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can the EU be reformed without making changes to the Treaties?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is about to begin renegotiating its European Union membership, a process some call &amp;ldquo;EU reform.&amp;rdquo; However, several member states have already rejected the idea of treaty changes. So, is a renegotiation or reform package even possible?
While amending secondary EU legislation (or convincingly promising to do so) without altering the treaties is possible, there&amp;rsquo;s always a risk that such changes won&amp;rsquo;t happen or could be reversed later...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will Brexit be unavoidable? The UK's EU membership post-General Election.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Conservative majority win in the UK brings up significant questions regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued membership in the European Union. This piece will initially address concerns surrounding the referendum and the renegotiation process.
The Brexit Referendum
What are the main issues surrounding the approaching referendum?
The new government&amp;rsquo;s plan to renegotiate the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership followed by a referendum (Brexit) based on the renegotiation&amp;rsquo;s results by the end of 2017 is paramount...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The lives of UK nationals living in other EU Member States have been significantly altered by Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah McCloskey and Tamara Hervey, Sheffield Law School
Following a string of significant political shifts, many can relate to the feelings of unease and worry stemming from the resulting instability. Currently, those hit hardest are individuals who have exercised their right to free movement without fear of it being revoked. This is the essence of Brexit: a source of discontent for some, a daily news item for others, but for EU citizens in the UK and UK citizens residing in other Member States, it holds the power to drastically alter their lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What would be the effect on the UK's relations with the EU if Scotland gained independence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:31:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the Scottish independence referendum approaches, with the &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; campaign gaining momentum and even leading some polls, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to analyze the potential impact of Scottish independence on the European Union (EU). This analysis will focus on the EU membership of both an independent Scotland and the remaining UK (rUK).
Scottish independence would trigger four significant, near-simultaneous events: negotiations between Scotland and rUK about their future relationship; negotiations for Scotland to rejoin the EU; renegotiation of the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership; and a UK general election...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for humans to make a legally binding commitment to Treaty change?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British Prime Minister David Cameron has surprised many by securing concessions from the EU, such as a smaller EU budget and a Conservative majority in the House of Commons. However, his goal of renegotiating the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership raises the question: are his demands even achievable?
This question arises from Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recently confirmed intention to secure not immediate Treaty changes, but rather a &amp;ldquo;legally binding&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;irreversible&amp;rdquo; agreement that would commit to future Treaty changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phase 2 of Brexit negotiations: analysis of the EU27's stance in negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 02:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU Council is anticipated to establish its negotiating directives for the second stage of Brexit discussions on January 29th. These talks will primarily focus on a transition period after Brexit Day, during which existing EU law would still be applicable in the UK. A leaked version of these directives has surfaced, providing an opportunity to analyze them in detail. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is subject to change pending final approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and the Protection of EU Transnational Rights - Part II The Stance of the Supreme Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:43:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
This piece expands on a previous one concerning the High Court&amp;rsquo;s stance on protecting EU Law-based transnational rights within the context of the Miller case. It examines the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the High Court&amp;rsquo;s position and the resulting implications for EU law. The significance of transnational rights persists for two primary reasons. Firstly, beyond the immediate impact on EU and UK citizens facing Brexit-related disruptions, it highlights the fundamental nature of individual rights within the EU legal framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Charter of Rights post Conservative party amendments to UK human rights legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many drivers have encountered the unfortunate experience of hitting a small animal that darted across the road at the wrong moment. Reactions vary from distress to indifference, but some feel a sense of triumph, having removed an obstacle from their path.
This last reaction mirrors the Conservative party&amp;rsquo;s stance on EU law within their UK human rights law reform proposals. They aim to diminish EU law&amp;rsquo;s influence, much like a driver indifferent to roadkill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU/Canada free trade deal and investor protection disputes a blessing in disguise or a cause for concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent news suggests the EU/Canada free-trade agreement (CETA) faces obstacles due to the German government&amp;rsquo;s opposition to rules concerning investor/state dispute settlement. This situation carries potential implications for various aspects, including the EU/Canada and EU/USA trade deals, the EU&amp;rsquo;s broader trade and investment policies, and even the UK&amp;rsquo;s potential departure from the EU (&amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;).
Background
After commencing negotiations in 2009, the EU and Canada reached a preliminary agreement in 2013, pending finalization of technical points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's 'emergency brake' preserving or abolishing the free movement of people?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Steve Peers
If British pro-Europeans could travel back in time, their priority should be returning to 2004. They should focus all efforts on persuading the then-British government to reconsider granting immediate free movement of workers from new EU member states. While economically advantageous, this decision has severely damaged public support for EU membership in the UK, as well as for the UK Labour Party.
Today, the free movement of people is often framed as a fundamental flaw within the EU, prompting calls for the UK to either leave or renegotiate its terms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A revival of the Brexit negotiations? Theresa May's address in Florence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s recent speech was largely seen as an effort to jumpstart the Brexit negotiations, which have hit a roadblock, particularly regarding financial matters. The question is whether her speech will be successful, or if its underlying goal of appeasing Leave voters in the UK, especially those in the cabinet and the media, will undermine its effectiveness. Additionally, it prompts questions about the future relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Does repealing the Human Rights Act comply with EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK&amp;rsquo;s new government plans to revoke its Human Rights Act (HRA), a move with legal and political ramifications. While the overlap with EU law is complex, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to examine the potential conflicts and consequences.
Assuming the UK remains part of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and doesn&amp;rsquo;t intend to disapply the EU Charter of Rights domestically, the government&amp;rsquo;s objective seems to be weakening domestic human rights protection and separating it from the ECHR, potentially impacting groups considered undesirable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to unilaterally revoke an Article 50 notice of withdrawal from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 14:31:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Currently, there are no indications that either the UK government or the opposition Labour party are contemplating the reversal of the UK&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal from the EU. Neither party seems interested in initiating another referendum concerning EU membership. Nevertheless, spurred by Nigel Farage&amp;rsquo;s recent attempt to garner attention, the possibility of an additional Brexit referendum, which inherently implies the revocability of the Article 50 notice, remains a topic of public discourse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit Negotiations: A Comprehensive Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 05:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK formally initiated the Brexit process by sending the Article 50 withdrawal letter to the EU on March 29th. The EU responded with its draft Brexit negotiating guidelines.
This post offers a thorough analysis of the EU&amp;rsquo;s draft guidelines, comparing them to the UK&amp;rsquo;s stance as articulated in Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s Chatham House speech last January. Although subject to potential modifications before their final adoption on April 29th, significant alterations to the draft guidelines are improbable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dispute resolution between the EU and UK after Brexit in the context of the White Paper.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Emilija Leinarte*
*Professor of EU law, University of Cambridge and PhD student, University of Cambridge. This research has received support from the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme.
A recent publication by UK in a Changing Europe examined various governing structures that could be used to manage the UK-EU relationship following Brexit. The released White Paper offers a glimpse into the institutional structure that the UK envisions for its future dealings with the EU after withdrawal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>