<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pioneer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pioneer/</link><description>Recent content in Pioneer on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pioneer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>