<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beogram on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beogram/</link><description>Recent content in Beogram on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beogram/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>My work on restoring the 4002 continues, and today involved polishing the hood – a task that&amp;rsquo;s quite a workout! The plexiglass hood had some noticeable scratches:
I began by using 200 grit sandpaper to create a consistent surface:
Then I gradually polished it using Micromesh polishing cloths:
The final stage involved Micromesh Micro-Gloss:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Replacement of Carriage Position Sensor Photocell</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</guid><description>Over many years of working with the Beogram 400x, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a wide array of issues, but these turntables never cease to present new challenges. In this instance, a Beogram 4002 exhibited inconsistent behavior when attempting to locate the record&amp;rsquo;s setdown point after pressing start. This pointed to a potential fault in the carriage position sensor.
Initially, I suspected the IR LED, a common culprit in later models like this 5513 Type.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Final 3D Printed Part Added</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</guid><description>I have completed the final 3D printed component for my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control system. This piece fits into a 10mm opening on the remote control receiver board, allowing it to be secured using one of the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s screws. The image below shows the part with the screw in place:
Once the remote control board is in place, the original screw can be used to fasten it. The cylindrical portion is designed to prevent the remote board from pressing against the component pins on the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main PCB while ensuring a secure fit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Main Capacitor Array with Integrated Efficient 24V Power Supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 is known to get quite hot, primarily due to its outdated voltage regulator-based power supply. To address this, a modern PCB design with a buck converter-based 24V supply was created as a replacement for the original power supply and capacitors.
The new design features high-quality Panasonic electrolytic capacitors, Samsung ceramic capacitors for the motor phase, and a buck converter for the 24V power supply. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to be easily installed in place of the original components.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Repair of an Intermittent Sensor Arm Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously restored in May 2022, recently came back to my workshop due to a malfunctioning sensor arm LED. This was concerning because I had implemented a redesigned LED assembly for this particular unit.
To my relief, the LED functioned correctly when I powered up the turntable in my workshop. This suggested an intermittent problem that resolved itself during transport.
I tried manipulating the plugs and cables, but the LED remained illuminated.</description></item><item><title>Bang &amp; Olufsen MMC Cartridge Protector: Dimensionally True Reproduction with Stereolithography</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 05:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</guid><description>I recently decided to test out the clear resin (sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;maker juice&amp;rdquo;) on my Formlabs Form 1 printer. I chose to design a replica of a Multi Media Card (MMC) cartridge protector, as they always seem to go missing. While I own multiple MMC cartridges, I only had one remaining protector.
As you can see in the images, the finished product is pretty good! The term &amp;ldquo;transparent&amp;rdquo; might be subjective, as the 3D-printed clear material doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite match the real thing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a 3D Printed Installation Tray</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control upgrade, specifically the receiver board insulation. My previous solution, using plastic foil, wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal aesthetically.
To address this, I designed a plastic tray that safeguards the receiver board from the main circuit board&amp;rsquo;s solder points. The tray is designed to click into place without additional screws.
Here are some photos:
Tray and board before assembly:
The tray features three rectangular cutouts to provide clearance for the solder points.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Choppily Rotating AC Platter Motor - Repair of Wien-Bridge Oscillator Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-choppily-rotating-ac-platter-motor-repair-of-wien-bridge-oscillator-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 12:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-choppily-rotating-ac-platter-motor-repair-of-wien-bridge-oscillator-circuit/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project presented a recurring issue: a malfunctioning oscillator circuit responsible for powering the AC platter motor. This was unusual, as previous 4002 and 4000 models hadn&amp;rsquo;t shown this problem. Although the light bulbs managing the circuit&amp;rsquo;s Automatic Gain Control (AGC) weren&amp;rsquo;t visually illuminated during motor operation, suggesting a longer lifespan compared to indicator bulbs, this unit proved otherwise. It&amp;rsquo;s likely that factors like mechanical vibrations, particularly during transport, could have damaged the bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This article details the installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control Module into a Beogram 4002 (Type 5504) turntable. This particular unit was restored for a customer in Australia and also features an internal Beolover RIAA phono pre-amplifier.
The Commander Module, seen here before installation, allows for remote control of the turntable:
The module includes an IR receiver (black wire at the bottom), an adapter board (narrow board on the right), a wiring harness (white wires), and an auto-repeat indicator (red wire at the top).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Wiring Sleeve of Carriage Harness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable, previously restored in 2020, was brought in for repairs due to an oscillating solenoid issue. However, upon inspection, a more critical problem was discovered: the wiring harness sleeve was severely damaged, exposing the wires.
This level of damage had never been encountered before. Thankfully, the wires themselves were still intact. The timing of the solenoid problem was fortunate, as further use could have led to wire damage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Restored Keypad and Plinth, a New Hood and Installation of the Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I finished restoring the functionality of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513), a project detailed in this post. Here&amp;rsquo;s how the unit appeared at that stage:
Although functionally restored, there were two noticeable cosmetic issues: a bleached area on the plinth and typical keypad wear from finger contact. It appears that skin oils negatively affect the keypad coating:
My client opted for a refurbished keypad. Additionally, the RPM panel&amp;rsquo;s plastic securing clamps were cracked, a common issue causing the panel to detach.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Awesome Refurbished Keypads in the House!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</guid><description>I received two refurbished Beogram 4002 keypads from Denmark today. My friend, who did the repainting, said the weather conditions were perfect for the job, and he was right! The picture shows how fantastic they look.
He&amp;rsquo;s incredibly talented! The keypads look brand new, as if they were just made in 1975. He did a phenomenal job. I had sent him a worn-out keypad from a Beogram 4002 I recently restored, and he even found another one!</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor Video Published - Check It Out!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finished my Beogram DC motor restoration video due to high demand! This video will show you how to disassemble the motor and revitalize the Oilite brass bearings by infusing oil under a vacuum. If your Beogram&amp;rsquo;s RPM is inconsistent, this video is for you! Have a look:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Installation Video</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 &amp;ldquo;Commander&amp;rdquo; remote control system has recently seen a surge in popularity, with multiple orders coming in over a short time. This could be linked to the Commander&amp;rsquo;s new compatibility with a specific Apple TV remote, allowing it to integrate with Apple devices in the same space. Designed for later models of the 4002 turntable with the keypad connector on the main circuit board (types 551x and 552x), I recently built three receivers over the weekend and shipped them out today, each packaged with a compatible Apple remote:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a Brand New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</guid><description>Before returning the recently restored Beogram 4002 (5513) to its owner, one final detail needed attention: the original dust cover showed early signs of cracking around the hinges.
The owner opted for a brand new replacement dust cover from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These reproduction dust covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, resulting in a seamless look, unlike previous versions made by fusing laser-cut panels. The result is indistinguishable from the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a Professionally Made PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</guid><description>I recently had a professionally made circuit board manufactured for the remote control receiver in my Beogram 4002 (5513). It was exciting to see the new board arrive and start assembling it.
The biggest changes in this design were simplifying the assembly by placing all the components on the top side and repositioning the ISP port to avoid interference with the aluminum top panel fixture. I also removed the reset button and made more space for the keypad connector.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Newly Adapted Beolover RIAA Pre-Amp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</guid><description>Following the recent redesign of the Beolover internal RIAA pre-amplifier for DC-motor Beogram 4002/4 turntables and its adaptation for the Beogram 4000, the final stage of the design process involved adjusting the circuit for the AC-motor Beogram 4002. The owner of a recently restored 4002 (5504) requested the RIAA installation, making his Beogram the first AC-motor 4002 to feature a Beolover RIAA.
The new board features an input jack that connects to a replicated Beogram-style plug through a multi-lead wiring harness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Keyboard Repair - Detached Backstops</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 11:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</guid><description>Following the AC motor hood restoration on a Beogram 4002 (5503), the next cosmetic issue addressed was the loose keypad backstops. Some keys were protruding and functioned erratically, requiring multiple presses.
Upon removing the keypad and its PCB, it was discovered that several plastic backstops had detached. A previous attempt to reattach them using double-sided tape proved unsuccessful, causing an uneven keypad surface.
The remaining backstops were easily removed, but precisely reattaching them posed a challenge.</description></item><item><title>Bang&amp;Olufsen MMC20EN Vintage Cartridge Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</guid><description>The MMC20EN cartridge that came with my recently restored Beogram 4004 parts was tested using my evolving cartridge testing methodology.
My approach involves evaluating the frequency range and trackability of a cartridge. For this, I utilize three test records: the Analogue Audio Ultimate Test LP for checking frequency response up to 20kHz, the Fisher Test &amp;amp; Performance Standard Quadradisc to observe 30kHz carrier frequency reproduction, and the Clearaudio Trackability Test Record to assess the cantilever suspension&amp;rsquo;s condition at different groove amplitudes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair and Exploration of an Intermittently Oscillating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</guid><description>This section details the work done on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s oscillating solenoid, and what was learned about winding solenoid coils and comparing them to the original.
The arm lowering mechanism is shown here:
When the control logic initiates arm lowering, the solenoid pushes the solenoid lever forward. The lever opens the solenoid switch when fully extended, decreasing the current flowing through the solenoid to a level just enough to keep it engaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Arm, Replacement of the Damper Gasket and Re-Glueing of a Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 required a few final adjustments before it could be returned to its owner following a wiring sleeve replacement on the carriage harness and a fix for an intermittent solenoid.
During its initial restoration in 2020, I was unfamiliar with some common problems that these turntables develop. One such issue involves the damper gasket, which tends to harden over time. This hardening can lead to uneven arm lowering due to inconsistent airflow around the gasket.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Exploration of Photocell Function in Sensor Arm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:24:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is going well, but it appears someone attempted repairs before. The sensor arm insert, containing the light bulb and photocell for record detection, was in disarray.
Upon inspection, a photocell wire was disconnected, another was damaged from being forced back into the aluminum profile, and the lens insert had heat damage, likely from improper soldering. Thankfully, the lenses were unharmed.
After reconnecting the wire, replacing the non-standard light bulb with a Beolover LED insert, and adjusting the TR14 bias to 1.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Apple Remote Controls All Functions of Turntable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</guid><description>After several weeks of testing, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my latest creation: a remote control receiver designed specifically for the Beogram 4002 (5513 model) turntable. This receiver seamlessly integrates with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s existing keypad connector without affecting its functionality.
The receiver board is compatible with the latest Apple TV remote, chosen for its sleek aluminum design that complements the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic. The remote&amp;rsquo;s minimalist button layout also aligns perfectly with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Worn Keypad Restoration - My Process Finally Appears Reproducible...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a common issue: a worn-out keypad. The start button, in particular, was in rough shape due to frequent use.
After a multi-month endeavor, I successfully restored the keypad to an almost-new appearance. My refined restoration method finally produces consistent results, marking a significant step forward in the 4002&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation.
During the process, I discovered another problem: a broken RPM panel clamp. This prevented the RPM panel from staying securely in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Packaging for Shipping: An Update on How to Secure the Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</guid><description>This article outlines a packaging update for the Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 turntables. Instead of taping the arm cover to the platter, the author now advises using an M3 screw to secure the carriage directly to the chassis.
This change is due to the risk of damaging the arm cover&amp;rsquo;s labeling with tape during shipping. While the author previously suggested using paper to protect the lettering, damage continued to occur.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander MkII: Remote Control for Beogram 4002 Now With Integrated Auto-Repeat Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable and planned to install my 4002 Commander Remote control system. This system is great because it keeps the keypad pristine and allows for operation without touching it. You can find demonstration and installation videos on my blog if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in upgrading your own 4002. The Commander board is compatible with all models equipped with a DC motor.
This restoration project inspired me to create an updated MkII version of the 4002 Commander, featuring an auto-repeat function similar to the Beogram 8000 and 8002 turntables.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Signal Path between DIN5 Plug and Cartridge, Plug Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</guid><description>I recently decided to update my Beogram 4002 turntable for the 21st century. While it was functional, the DIN 5 plug was noticeably worn and corroded. To address this, I swapped it out with a modern, high-quality Neutrik AG Rean NYS 322G plug featuring gold-plated pins, aiming for a reliable, long-lasting connection with my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s auxiliary input. The old plug was in rough shape, leaving me curious about its past.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of the Latest Version of the Beogram Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>While restoring my Beogram 4002 (5513), I decided to improve the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control I had previously designed. I added a &amp;ldquo;pairing&amp;rdquo; feature to prevent conflicts with Apple TVs and other devices that use Apple remotes. To completely eliminate the need to touch the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s delicate keypad, I also included remote switching between 33 and 45 RPM. A detailed video about the latest version explains the functions and demonstrates the remote and its pairing process:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Keypad with a Worn Through Start Button</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:47:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 keypad, showing signs of wear, was recently sent from New Zealand. The start button&amp;rsquo;s coating was entirely worn down:
This is a common problem for Beogram keypads. The combination of skin acids and friction wears away the coating.
Fortunately, this is fixable. Here is the keypad after being restored:
It looks great! The coating will be left to harden further before being returned to New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Newly Designed Beolover RIAA Pre-Amplifier Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</guid><description>Due to demand, I designed an internal RIAA pre-amplifier board for the Beogram 4000, adapting the circuit from my recent redesign for the DC motor Beogram 4002 and 4004. I installed this new board in a Beogram 4000 that was in for a warranty repair. This post details the installation process; for technical data, refer to my previous post about the 4002/4 version&amp;rsquo;s performance, as the circuits are identical.
The current prototype board has some features that will be absent in the final version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacement of Rusty RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 14:56:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration, I swapped out the old, worn-out RCA plugs. The originals were showing their age.
I chose robust, gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs as replacements. These are excellent for transmitting the low-voltage MMC signal to the amplifier. The metal housing provides superior shielding against electromagnetic interference, ensuring signal integrity. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look after soldering:
And here they are secured:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Afternoon Exploring the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem arose with its record detection system. While it functioned correctly at the 12-inch LP position, it frequently failed to detect records at the 7-inch singles position. This malfunction was observed when the turntable, starting without a record on the platter, bypassed the LP position but stopped at the singles position.
An examination of the circuit diagram revealed the signal path of the detection system.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Stability Test and an Updated Display on the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>I dedicated time to program the compact display integrated into my BeoloverRPM device. This enhancement enables precise RPM adjustments and long-term RPM stability analysis. The display now includes minimum and maximum values, along with the total measurement duration. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the display:
The display boasts high resolution and excellent contrast. However, those of us who are getting older might need reading glasses to decipher the small font. Is perfection ever attainable?</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of Short Circuited Solenoid Coil and Repair of Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-short-circuited-solenoid-coil-and-repair-of-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-short-circuited-solenoid-coil-and-repair-of-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently received a faulty solenoid coil and the main circuit board from a Beogram 4002 turntable belonging to a customer in Texas. I requested the circuit board be sent along with the coil because there&amp;rsquo;s usually an underlying reason why these coils fail, especially in later models of the Beogram 4002 and 4004 turntables.
The components arrived as shown in the image:
My first step was to measure the coil&amp;rsquo;s resistance to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s diagnosis:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Evening Exploring the Differential Stop Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</guid><description>Before returning a refurbished unit to a customer, we put it through rigorous real-world testing. This involves playing music for several weeks to ensure consistent functionality. This listening process is a delightful part of working with Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen equipment, as our workshop is always filled with music! A recent case involving a restored Beogram 4000 turntable highlights the value of this testing phase.
During playback, I noticed the arm occasionally failed to return to its resting position after reaching the record&amp;rsquo;s end.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of 4002 Commander MkII Remote Control and Internal RIAA Preamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</guid><description>I recently completed a Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration, and the customer requested two upgrades I developed: the Beolover 4002 Commander MkII remote control receiver and the internal RIAA pre-amplifier. These upgrades are detailed further on my blog, along with installation instructions. Both are available for purchase; feel free to contact me for more information.
This image showcases both boards:
The lower board is the Commander MkII. This version includes a repeat function, indicated by the CD4 light on the keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beo4 Enabled Commander Remote Control: Seamless Integration of Beogram 4002 or 4004 with More Recent B&amp;O Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</guid><description>Dirk, a Beolover from Berlin, recently reached out about controlling his Beogram 4004 turntable with a Beo4 remote. He wanted to seamlessly integrate the turntable with his existing Beosound 9000 system.
I found his idea intriguing and decided to modify the Beolover Commander remote to make it compatible. This involved adding a 455kHz IR receiver for Beo4 communication and deciphering the Beo4&amp;rsquo;s code system to rewrite the Commander&amp;rsquo;s firmware accordingly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Mass Production!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 02:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</guid><description>More orders for the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control have been placed. The Commander is now compatible with a designated Apple TV remote, eliminating interference with other Apple devices in the same room. Designed specifically for later models of the 4002 turntable (types 551x and 552x) that feature the keypad connector on the main circuit board, the Commander offers a simple plug-and-play installation process. Today, five new units were assembled.</description></item></channel></rss>