<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Investment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/investment/</link><description>Recent content in Investment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:39:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Attend Walton's Cashflow Night to learn how to break free from your routine and achieve significant success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attend-walton-s-cashflow-night-to-learn-how-to-break-free-from-your-routine-and-achieve-significant-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attend-walton-s-cashflow-night-to-learn-how-to-break-free-from-your-routine-and-achieve-significant-success/</guid><description>A board game can help you start aligning your life goals by reassessing how you approach cash flow and investment. The website for Cashflow the Boardgame, which was created by Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki, states that &amp;ldquo;You could learn to be wealthy and that would be life changing. You could also learn to be wealthy by playing a game and that would be amazing.&amp;rdquo; The game was first played in 1996 in Singapore and has since gained global popularity, with a community of 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attend-walton-s-cashflow-night-to-learn-how-to-break-free-from-your-routine-and-achieve-significant-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attend-walton-s-cashflow-night-to-learn-how-to-break-free-from-your-routine-and-achieve-significant-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB Bank increases interest rates for fixed deposits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 18:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/</guid><description>CIMB Bank is marking its ninth anniversary by offering a special interest rate increase for online fixed deposits throughout September. This gesture is a thank you to customers for their ongoing support.
During this promotional period (September 1st to 30th, 2018), individuals who open a Singapore CIMB Fast Fixed Deposit account online will enjoy an extra 0.09% per annum on top of the existing online promotional rates.
These combined rates are highly competitive, positioning CIMB among the top options available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investing in corporate bonds will be made more accessible for Singaporean investors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has launched two new regulations aimed at making it easier for retail investors – individuals who purchase securities for personal investment purposes – to participate in corporate bond offerings. These changes are part of MAS&amp;rsquo;s broader strategy to expand retail investors&amp;rsquo; investment choices by providing access to simpler, lower-risk investment products.
Corporate issuers typically rely on the wholesale bond market for funding due to the higher expenses associated with reaching retail investors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore investors who are accredited can transition to digital investing with Jachin Capital</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</guid><description>Jachin Capital, a Singapore-based independent fund manager, is now authorized to offer its digital investment platform, iAdvisor, to accredited investors in Singapore after receiving a Capital Markets Services Licence from the Monetary Authority of Singapore. The company specializes in providing investment management solutions, including discretionary and non-discretionary options, to accredited investors and private family offices throughout the Asia-Pacific region. Jachin Capital uses a transparent, rules-based approach to build and regularly rebalance investment portfolios around specific themes or ideas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash and UOB Asset Management have collaborated to provide a mobile robo-adviser that includes an ESG option</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for UOBAM Robo-Invest.
Singtel has introduced a new digital advisor, developed by UOB Asset Management (UOBAM), on its Dash e-wallet platform. This launch expands Dash’s selection of financial services, which already encompasses payments, international money transfers, insurance, savings, and investments.
UOBAM Robo-Invest is the first robo-advisor in Singapore available on a mobile wallet and stands out by offering sustainable investing options created by UOBAM specifically for Dash users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-and-uob-asset-management-have-collaborated-to-provide-a-mobile-robo-adviser-that-includes-an-esg-option/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vietnam, a country experiencing growth, is attracting investments from various regions, according to UOB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</guid><description>A recent study by the United Overseas Bank (UOB) suggests Vietnam will experience a surge in investments from nearby countries like Malaysia, Thailand, and Singapore over the next three to five years.
The 2016 UOB Asian Enterprise Survey found that Vietnam is a top expansion target for businesses in Malaysia (38%), Thailand (35%), and Singapore (29%). These nations are among the 28% of surveyed enterprises that selected Vietnam as their preferred expansion destination within the next three to five years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian venture capital investments have remained stable in the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Venture capital (VC) investment experienced a global decline in 2016, following a strong 2015, according to the Venture Pulse Q4 2016 report by KPMG Enterprise.
Global VC investment decreased by 24% year-over-year, totaling US$127.4 billion. Despite a promising start to the year, investor confidence waned in the latter half of 2016 due to uncertainties in the market. Events like Brexit and the US presidential election furthered this uncertainty.
Chia Tek Yew, Head of Financial Services Advisory at KPMG in Singapore, noted that this period of uncertainty allowed VCs to refine their portfolios, focus on high-potential deals, and guide their portfolio companies towards further growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The annual Berkshire Hathaway Shareholders Meeting timing for 2021 has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-annual-berkshire-hathaway-shareholders-meeting-timing-for-2021-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 06:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-annual-berkshire-hathaway-shareholders-meeting-timing-for-2021-has-been-announced/</guid><description>For the sixth consecutive year, Yahoo Finance will exclusively livestream the Berkshire Hathaway Shareholders Meeting. Due to the ongoing pandemic, this will be the second year the event will be held virtually.
Source: Yahoo Finance. Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s Annual Shareholder&amp;rsquo;s Meeting will be streamed live by Yahoo Finance.
This significant event for the global business community features insights from Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s leaders: Chairman and CEO Warren Buffet, Vice Chairman Charlie Munger, Vice Chairman of Non-Insurance Operations Greg Abel, and Vice Chairman of Insurance Operations Ajit Jain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-annual-berkshire-hathaway-shareholders-meeting-timing-for-2021-has-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-annual-berkshire-hathaway-shareholders-meeting-timing-for-2021-has-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawksford has released the latest data on new business formations in Singapore for the fourth quarter of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 09:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</guid><description>Source: Hawksford report. Data represents the shareholder&amp;rsquo;s country of origin. Although the final quarter of 2015 saw a decrease in new Singaporean company formations compared to the previous quarter and the same period last year, international investors continue to set up companies and subsidiaries in Singapore, according to Hawksford, a provider of corporate, private client, and fund administration services.
Hawksford notes this decline is typical for the fourth quarter. Private limited companies made up the largest portion of new formations at 48...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment commitments in Singapore remain in a positive trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</guid><description>Global companies continued to view Singapore as a crucial base in Asia for expansion and innovation in 2016, with investment commitments meeting or exceeding the Economic Development Board (EDB)&amp;rsquo;s projections. The EDB remains committed to pursuing opportunities in thriving sectors to foster sustained economic growth and create quality employment prospects for Singaporeans.
Attracting S$9.4 billion in fixed asset investments, Singapore exceeded its forecast of S$8 billion to S$10 billion. Total business expenditure reached S$8...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Term deposits from ICBC are available through Alipay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</guid><description>ICBC, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest bank by assets, now offers three-year term deposit services through Alipay, a popular digital lifestyle platform.
This collaboration between Alipay and ICBC began in 2005 with online payment services. In January 2020, ICBC introduced a one-year term deposit service on Alipay, allowing customers to make deposits directly through the platform. This service has seen a sevenfold increase in size since May.
The new three-year term deposit option, called Anxin Cun (Secure Deposits), offers a 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The economy has an impact on retirement and emergency savings plans in Singapore, according to OCBC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/</guid><description>Source: OCBC. Average retirement ages by age cohorts.
Retirement and emergency planning have taken a backseat in Singapore. OCBC&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that &amp;ldquo;planning for retirement&amp;rdquo; experienced the most significant decline among financial priorities, with the index score dropping from 47 in 2022 to 40 this year. This finding comes from the fifth edition of the annual OCBC Financial Wellness Index, which surveyed 2,000 working adults in Singapore aged 21 to 65 in August 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Kazakhstan are working together to enhance their bilateral trade relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/</guid><description>Singapore and Kazakhstan have signed a bilateral investment treaty designed to encourage greater investment between the two nations.
This agreement is intended to safeguard investors from both Singapore and Kazakhstan, giving them more confidence to pursue investment opportunities in each other&amp;rsquo;s countries. The treaty ensures that Singaporean companies operating in Kazakhstan will have additional protection for their investments beyond what is provided by Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s domestic laws, and the same applies to Kazakh companies in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers of CIMB in Singapore have the option to apply for fixed deposits in Singapore dollars through the online platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 10:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/</guid><description>CIMB Bank is the first bank in Singapore to offer online applications for Singapore dollar fixed deposits.
This new service, called CIMB Fast Fixed Deposit (FD), allows new customers to apply for a Singapore dollar FD account and a CIMB FastSaver account online. The CIMB FastSaver account is used for deposits and withdrawals related to the FD account.
“In today’s fast-paced world, people want services that are convenient, quick, and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alternatives play a crucial role in investor portfolios</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternatives-play-a-crucial-role-in-investor-portfolios/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 08:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternatives-play-a-crucial-role-in-investor-portfolios/</guid><description>Intralinks partnered with Global Fund Media to conduct a global survey of Limited Partners (LPs) to understand their views on General Partners (GPs) they entrust with their funds. The survey analyzes trends and provides statistics on various themes.
A key takeaway is that alternative investments continue to play a significant role in investor portfolios. Over a third (35%) of LPs reported allocating more than 30% of their portfolio to alternative investments, with 20% allocating up to 10%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternatives-play-a-crucial-role-in-investor-portfolios/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternatives-play-a-crucial-role-in-investor-portfolios/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BERI considers Taiwan to be a top candidate for establishing its Asia Pacific headquarters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 09:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</guid><description>Is your business searching for a new Asia-Pacific regional headquarters? Taiwan might be the ideal location.
Business Environment Risk Intelligence (BERI) released its third &amp;ldquo;Report on the Evaluation of Environmental Risks of Investment&amp;rdquo; for 2013 in December 2013. The report ranks 50 countries and territories based on their &amp;ldquo;Profit Opportunity Recommendation&amp;rdquo; metric. Switzerland secured the top position, followed by Singapore and then Taiwan.
Taiwan holds the second position globally, just behind Singapore, for operational risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, ASEAN received the highest amount of foreign direct investment (FDI) among developing countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The latest ASEAN Investment Report examines the growth of foreign direct investment (FDI) into the ASEAN region, particularly the influence of corporations on infrastructure expansion and regional integration.
In 2014, ASEAN emerged as the top recipient of FDI among developing nations. FDI inflows to the region experienced a third consecutive year of growth, reaching US$136.2 billion, a rise from US$117.7 billion in 2013. This achievement occurred despite a 16% global decline in FDI and inconsistent global economic progress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should you consider investing in cryptocurrency?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: Statista. Bitcoin price index from November 2016 to November 2018 (US$).
Cryptocurrencies experienced substantial growth in 2017, followed by a less impressive 2018. This raises the question: Are we witnessing a classic boom and bust cycle? Several experts in the field share their insights.
Source: Dash. Taylor.
“The total market value of all cryptocurrencies combined is currently at the same level as in September 2017. However, what often gets overlooked is the continued growth in actual usage and the constant innovation happening in the sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AC Ventures is investing in women-led businesses in Indonesia, with a total value of US$421 billion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</guid><description>Source: AC Ventures. Wong speaks at the Women’s CEO Forum.
Helen Wong, Managing Partner at AC Ventures, a venture capital firm focused on early-stage investments, urged for concrete actions to support women investors. She highlighted that investing in female founders in Indonesia presents a significant opportunity exceeding US$421 billion annually.
Wong made these remarks during her address at the Women’s CEO Forum held in Jakarta. This event was an officially recognized side event of the ASEAN Business &amp;amp; Investment Summit (ABIS) 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best investment migration programmes for wealthy individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</guid><description>The increased global demand for residence and citizenship-by-investment programs, particularly among wealthy investors, highlights the desire to overcome limitations posed by single jurisdictions in the wake of COVID-19. Recognizing this, Deep Knowledge Analytics and Henley &amp;amp; Partners have collaborated to create the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
Source: Henley &amp;amp; Partners website. Illustration for the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
This digital publication provides a detailed analysis, interactive tools, and unique perspectives on the efficiency of countries offering these programs during the pandemic, and their potential as future havens for longevity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investors demonstrate trust in the cryptocurrency investment platform CoinMENA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</guid><description>CoinMENA, a cryptocurrency exchange based in Bahrain, has successfully raised US$9.5 million in its initial seed funding round. Major investors included BECO Capital, Kenetic, Arab Bank Switzerland, and others.
Founded in early 2021 by Dina Saman, Talal Tabbaa, and Yazan Barghuthi, CoinMENA aimed to simplify and enhance the safety of cryptocurrency investments in the region. The platform is officially licensed by the Central Bank of Bahrain and has partnered with the Dubai World Trade Centre to establish a prominent blockchain and cryptocurrency hub in the UAE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmoney proudly displays impressive first-year results</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</guid><description>The remarkable first-year performance of Harmoney, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s sole peer-to-peer (P2P) lending platform, highlights a substantial unmet need for crowdfunded microloans.
Established on September 10, 2014, with NZ$100 million in committed capital from prominent institutions like Blue Elephant Capital Management and Heartland Bank, Harmoney has facilitated NZ$100 million in personal loans within its inaugural year. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid expansion has resulted in the creation of 65 new jobs across New Zealand, Australia, and Fiji, with plans underway for an Australian launch...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Henley &amp; Partners has been selected as the worldwide concessionaire for the Thai residency program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</guid><description>Henley &amp;amp; Partners, a global firm specializing in residence and citizenship advisory, has been chosen to promote Thailand&amp;rsquo;s residence visa program, Thailand Elite. This program allows foreigners to reside in Thailand for up to 20 years.
Thailand&amp;rsquo;s welcoming atmosphere has made it a desirable destination in Southeast Asia. Individuals and families from affluent nations are increasingly drawn to its climate, scenery, and recreational opportunities. The 2017 &amp;ldquo;Best Countries&amp;rdquo; report highlighted Thailand as a prime location for starting a business due to its affordability, efficient bureaucracy, and accessible capital...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dalio Market Principles Online Program has been launched on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalio-market-principles-online-program-has-been-launched-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 02:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalio-market-principles-online-program-has-been-launched-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Wealth Management Institute (WMI) has introduced the Dalio Market Principles (DMP) Online Program to provide accessible, high-quality investment education globally.
This program, grounded in Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s five decades of experience and research, aims to help participants grasp the interconnected forces influencing markets and economies. Using advanced technology like generative AI, it delivers an engaging learning journey accessible from anywhere, at any time.
Dalio, Founder, CIO Mentor and Member of the Board at Bridgewater Associates, emphasizes the unprecedented changes the world is witnessing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalio-market-principles-online-program-has-been-launched-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalio-market-principles-online-program-has-been-launched-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goldbell Evolution Network has secured almost S$1 million in funds for floor stock financing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goldbell-evolution-network-has-secured-almost-s-1-million-in-funds-for-floor-stock-financing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:18:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goldbell-evolution-network-has-secured-almost-s-1-million-in-funds-for-floor-stock-financing/</guid><description>Goldbell&amp;rsquo;s private debt investment platform, Goldbell Evolution Network (GEN), has successfully secured S$900,000 in funding to launch its latest product: floor stock financing. GEN, pronounced &amp;ldquo;ghern,&amp;rdquo; offers alternative investment opportunities in private debt, catering to accredited investors, family offices, business owners, and professionals.
Floor stock financing is a revolving line of credit designed for automotive dealers. This short-term financing solution, backed by assets, allows dealers to purchase vehicles for their showroom floors (or lots)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goldbell-evolution-network-has-secured-almost-s-1-million-in-funds-for-floor-stock-financing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goldbell-evolution-network-has-secured-almost-s-1-million-in-funds-for-floor-stock-financing/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>