<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>World on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/world/</link><description>Recent content in World on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vietnam receives report card from World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economy shows resilience due to strong domestic demand and export-focused manufacturing, as highlighted in the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s recent Taking Stock report. The country&amp;rsquo;s mid-term economic outlook appears positive, with GDP projected to grow by 6% in the current year.
The report, a semi-annual assessment of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economic performance, notes that economic growth decelerated to 5.9% in the first nine months of the year. This slowdown is largely attributed to a severe drought that hampered agricultural output, reduced oil production, and weakened external demand.</description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank will provide assistance for a geothermal energy project in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-will-provide-assistance-for-a-geothermal-energy-project-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-will-provide-assistance-for-a-geothermal-energy-project-in-indonesia/</guid><description>The World Bank is providing $55.25 million in grants to bolster Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s Geothermal Energy Upstream Development Project, which promotes investment in geothermal energy production.
The Clean Technology Fund (CTF) is supplying $49 million for infrastructure and exploratory drilling, while the Global Environment Facility (GEF) is providing an extra $6.25 million to build geothermal exploration expertise, including due diligence safeguards. The Indonesian Ministry of Finance and PT Sarana Multi Infrastruktur, a state-owned infrastructure financing firm, will match the CTF funding.</description></item><item><title>World Heritage Map now for sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 01:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</guid><description>Source: UNESCO website.
The UNESCO World Heritage Centre and National Geographic Maps have released the most recent edition of the World Heritage map. This project received generous support from Turkey, and the map can be purchased on the World Heritage Centre website.
The map features an image of Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Historic Areas of Istanbul, the location of the next World Heritage Committee meeting in July 2016.
The poster-sized map displays all 1,031 World Heritage sites, along with pictures and detailed captions.</description></item><item><title>New sites have been added to the World Heritage List for 2017 by the World Heritage Committee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sites-have-been-added-to-the-world-heritage-list-for-2017-by-the-world-heritage-committee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sites-have-been-added-to-the-world-heritage-list-for-2017-by-the-world-heritage-committee/</guid><description>Source: UNESCO. Kulangsu: a Historic International Settlement, China. © Cultural Heritage Conservation Center of THAD / Qian Yi | Image Source: Nomination File (Update).
The World Heritage Committee designated 21 new locations to UNESCO’s World Heritage List in 2017. Additionally, the boundaries of five existing sites were expanded or adjusted. These additions bring the total number of sites on the World Heritage List to 1,073.
The Asia Pacific region saw the addition of these new natural sites:</description></item><item><title>The domain name "Dot World" is now in the sunrise period for Chinese, Japanese, and Korean languages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-domain-name-dot-world-is-now-in-the-sunrise-period-for-chinese-japanese-and-korean-languages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-domain-name-dot-world-is-now-in-the-sunrise-period-for-chinese-japanese-and-korean-languages/</guid><description>Stable Tone&amp;rsquo;s DotWorld_IDN Registry has started the sunrise period for its Chinese, Japanese, and Korean top-level domain (TLD). This period, ending on November 10, 2015, allows trademark holders with prior rights to register DotWorld_IDN domain names before the public launch.
Starting November 17, 2015, anyone can register these domains on a first-come, first-served basis.
The two-character domain extension, 世界, translates to &amp;ldquo;world&amp;rdquo; in all three languages (pronounced &amp;ldquo;shijie&amp;rdquo; in Chinese, &amp;ldquo;seikai&amp;rdquo; in Japanese, and &amp;ldquo;segye&amp;rdquo; in Korean).</description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization has declared the Ebola outbreak a global public health emergency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) declared the West African Ebola outbreak a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) on August 8th.
As of August 4, 2014, there were 1,711 cases (1,070 confirmed, 436 probable, and 205 suspected) of Ebola virus disease (EVD), resulting in 932 deaths. Between August 5th and 6th, 2014, 68 new EVD cases (including confirmed, probable, and suspected) and 29 deaths were reported across Guinea, Liberia, Nigeria, and Sierra Leone.</description></item></channel></rss>