<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vc/</link><description>Recent content in VC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asian venture capital investments have remained stable in the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Venture capital (VC) investment experienced a global decline in 2016, following a strong 2015, according to the Venture Pulse Q4 2016 report by KPMG Enterprise.
Global VC investment decreased by 24% year-over-year, totaling US$127.4 billion. Despite a promising start to the year, investor confidence waned in the latter half of 2016 due to uncertainties in the market. Events like Brexit and the US presidential election furthered this uncertainty.
Chia Tek Yew, Head of Financial Services Advisory at KPMG in Singapore, noted that this period of uncertainty allowed VCs to refine their portfolios, focus on high-potential deals, and guide their portfolio companies towards further growth.</description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures.</description></item></channel></rss>