<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Earbud on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earbud/</link><description>Recent content in Earbud on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earbud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Altec Lansing Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds come with noise isolation and GPS tracking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>Source: Altec Lansing. The Freedom True Wireless
Bluetooth Earbuds have rechargeable lithium
ion batteries.
Altec Lansing&amp;rsquo;s new Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds offer a truly wireless experience, featuring rechargeable lithium-ion batteries integrated into the earbud housings.
These innovative earbuds boast a six-hour battery life, IPX7-rated waterproof construction for sweat resistance, and Bluetooth-based GPS tracking to easily locate misplaced earbuds.
Expected to launch in the second quarter of 2016 with a manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s suggested retail price of US$149...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JVC introduces new sports in-ear headphones that are waterproof and washable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 03:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</guid><description>Source: JVC.
JVC introduces four new sports headphone options designed to stay securely in place during physical activity, with some models offering waterproof and washable features.
The lineup includes two models in both the JVC Gumy Sport and Extreme Fitness series. The Gumy Sport headphones, HA-EN10 and HA-ENR15, utilize a Nozzle Fit earpiece constructed from soft silicone. This unique shape ensures a secure and comfortable fit, preventing the headphones from falling out during workouts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>X-mini expands its audio portfolio with the addition of earbuds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/x-mini-expands-its-audio-portfolio-with-the-addition-of-earbuds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/x-mini-expands-its-audio-portfolio-with-the-addition-of-earbuds/</guid><description>X-mini, a company known for its portable audio devices, is expanding its product line in Singapore with the introduction of four new wired earbud series: NOVA, XYRIUS, XTLAS, and RAY. These additions aim to provide audio lovers with a variety of choices to suit their preferences and needs.
Each earbud series is crafted with X-mini&amp;rsquo;s audio expertise, incorporating carefully chosen sound drivers to deliver their signature sound quality. All earbuds come equipped with microphones, allowing users to seamlessly switch between music and calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/x-mini-expands-its-audio-portfolio-with-the-addition-of-earbuds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/x-mini-expands-its-audio-portfolio-with-the-addition-of-earbuds/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>