<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Broadband Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband-access/</link><description>Recent content in Broadband Access on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages.</description></item><item><title>Symmetrical Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</guid><description>The majority of internet users consume content rather than create it. While content has shifted from primarily text to images and video, broadband internet access remains asymmetrical, favoring downloads over uploads.
Why is this the case? Consider how you browse the internet: you click or type to select content, which uses minimal bandwidth. However, receiving the content, like web pages with text, images, and videos, requires significant bandwidth for timely delivery.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Access Wireless Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</guid><description>Wireless internet isn&amp;rsquo;t just for mobile devices. Businesses can also benefit from fixed wireless services.
One affordable option utilizes existing cell towers to provide broadband similar to a T1 line at nearly half the cost. Accel Networks, for instance, partners with major carriers to leverage their bandwidth, achieving 99.9% reliability and quick installation times. This solution is ideal for businesses requiring PCI-compliant connections, like convenience stores or gas stations, especially those in areas with limited wired options.</description></item><item><title>You Are A WiFi Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-a-wifi-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 03:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-a-wifi-finder/</guid><description>ThinkGeek is offering the ultimate in internet geekiness: a t-shirt that lights up to show the strength of nearby WiFi signals. This shirt will make internet addicts follow you everywhere. You could even become a hotspot yourself and have people at your beck and call – or at least within range of your signal.
The Wi-Fi Detector Shirt from ThinkGeek is a black cotton t-shirt featuring a removable decal of a tower emitting signal lines.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Puts Your Complete Office In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:47:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>You might be interested in cloud services, but the process of ordering and integrating them can be overwhelming. Now, a new solution offers a comprehensive bundle of IT services tailored for small businesses at an affordable price.
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
Small businesses often don&amp;rsquo;t need or can&amp;rsquo;t afford large-scale IT infrastructure. Expensive VoIP phone systems and on-site data centers are impractical for companies with limited staff and resources. While cost savings were previously linked to scale, hosted solutions have revolutionized this.</description></item></channel></rss>