<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Securities on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/securities/</link><description>Recent content in Securities on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/securities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?</description></item><item><title>New OCBC Securities app and Android OCBC app now offer fingerprint security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 08:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ocbc-securities-app-and-android-ocbc-app-now-offer-fingerprint-security/</guid><description>Source: OCBC. The iOCBC TradeMobile app allows users to perform in-depth technical analyses of stocks using standard indicators.
OCBC Securities has introduced a new mobile app called iOCBC TradeMobile for iPhone users. Existing OCBC Securities customers can now conveniently monitor their stock portfolios and access real-time market data for their stocks using Apple&amp;rsquo;s Touch ID technology. This fingerprint authentication feature, known as OneTouch, offers both OCBC Bank and OCBC Securities customers a secure and convenient way to access their banking and brokerage accounts.</description></item><item><title>Crowdonomic is now a registered e-facility for equity crowdfunding in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 14:03:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Crowdonomic. Crowdonomic was one of just a few operators approved as a Registered Electronic Facility (Equity Crowdfunding Platform) by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Securities Commission. From left: Nicola Castelnuovo, Co-founder and Chief Commercial Officer of Crowdonomic; Datuk Ranjit Ajit Singh, Chairman, Securities Commission Malaysia and Leo Shimada, Co-Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Crowdonomic.
Crowdonomic, a leading crowdfunding platform in Southeast Asia, was designated as a registered electronic facility by the Securities Commission Malaysia (SC).</description></item></channel></rss>