<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speed on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/speed/</link><description>Recent content in Speed on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/speed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides an explanation of mobile performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</guid><description>Singtel contributed to the Infocomm Development Authority&amp;rsquo;s (IDA) MyConnection SG study, highlighting connectivity, speed, and coverage as crucial aspects of user experience.
Singtel emphasized that, based on study feedback, users prioritize network coverage, call stability, customer service, and reliable data connections over pure speed. Consistent speed across a broad coverage area is key for a positive user experience. This feedback helps Singtel pinpoint areas for service enhancement.
Connectivity, as defined by Singtel, is the server connection response time, measured in milliseconds.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Speed Indictor Light Bulbs with RGB LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 11:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</guid><description>During the wait for a 3D-printed part for a Beogram 4002 turntable restoration, the author decided to upgrade its speed indicator lights. Using a method from a previous video, they replaced the incandescent bulbs with RGB LEDs for a more authentic look.
The original setup with incandescent bulbs was documented before the upgrade.
The new setup utilizes both the red and green diodes of an RGB LED for a natural appearance, addressing the issue of amber LEDs failing to illuminate red scale markers properly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Unit Switches Immediately to 45 RPM After Pressing Start</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable being restored exhibited a peculiar issue during initial testing. Upon starting, the tonearm moved as expected but the speed immediately switched to 45 RPM. Pressing the 33 RPM button temporarily resolved the issue, but the speed reverted back upon release.
This unusual behavior pointed to a potential problem with transistors TR3 or TR2. Examining the circuit diagram, we can see how speed selection operates:
The speed control mechanism utilizes a flip-flop circuit with transistors TR3 and TR4.</description></item><item><title>StarHub, offering the quickest 3G and 4G network in Singapore, introduces the World's Fastest Band</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</guid><description>StarHub, a telecommunications company, has unveiled the &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Fastest Band&amp;rdquo; to celebrate its recognition in OpenSignal&amp;rsquo;s Speed Awards 2018 for having Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fastest 4G and 3G speeds. OpenSignal, a global wireless coverage mapping specialist, awarded StarHub based on network quality. StarHub&amp;rsquo;s VP of Segment &amp;amp; Marketing, Donovan Kik, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to network quality and customer satisfaction. He stated their dedication to meeting customer needs and expectations despite achieving this recognition.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit.</description></item></channel></rss>