<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>French on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/french/</link><description>Recent content in French on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/french/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fragrance Du Bois opens a temporary store at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Fragrance Du Bois.
Fragrance Du Bois has opened a temporary boutique at TANGS, a major department store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road shopping area, until September 4, 2015. This marks their second appearance at TANGS this year. The pop-up offers customers a direct encounter with niche perfumery and showcases Fragrance Du Bois&amp;rsquo; fragrances, all made with 100% pure, natural oud.
Nicola Parker, Brand Director of Fragrance Du Bois, noted a rising interest in niche perfumery.</description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center.</description></item><item><title>A more nutritious choice of French-Vietnamese cuisine in Tanjong Pagar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz. The L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz sautéed beef and spring rolls vermicelli salad (bún bò xào chả giò).
L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz, a Vietnamese eatery located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Tanjong Pagar financial area, serves both lunch and dinner.
The name &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz&amp;rdquo; is a clever fusion of &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;euphorie&amp;rdquo; (French for &amp;ldquo;euphoria&amp;rdquo;), &amp;ldquo;phở&amp;rdquo; (the famous Vietnamese noodle soup), and &amp;ldquo;riz&amp;rdquo; (French for &amp;ldquo;rice&amp;rdquo;), hinting at the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s French-Vietnamese roots.
With origins in Saigon, Vietnam, the restaurant later established itself in Paris and played a key role in the three-decade success of Parisian Vietnamese restaurant Dong Huong.</description></item><item><title>Toyo Koda will enhance the menus at Le Passage Mohkan Shan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</guid><description>Source: Le Passage Mohkan Shan website.
Le Passage Mohkan Shan, a French-style hotel and restaurant nestled in its own private tea plantation at the base of Moganshan* mountain in China, has appointed Toyo Koda as its new head chef. This strategic hire emphasizes the hotel&amp;rsquo;s aim to become a premier culinary destination in Asia.
Chef Toyo, previously recognized as one of Asia&amp;rsquo;s top chefs by the San Pellegrino Restaurant Awards in 2013 for his role at Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French restaurant Franck, is poised to transform the hotel&amp;rsquo;s culinary offerings.</description></item></channel></rss>