<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hair on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hair/</link><description>Recent content in Hair on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:25:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We are all increasing the frequency of washing our hair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</guid><description>The increasing prevalence of hair problems and pollution has led people to shampoo their hair more often, either daily or every other day. This trend has fueled the growth of the shampoo industry, as noted in Technavio&amp;rsquo;s report on the global hair shampoo market from 2015 to 2019. The report highlights that shampoos held over 40% of the global hair care market share in 2014.
Source: Technavio.
The global shampoo market is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 4.</description></item><item><title>Kérastase Résistance Thérapiste offers amazing results for hair that has been over-processed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oréal.
The Résistance line was launched by Kérastase in 1995 to provide women with superior hair care and repair solutions. Two decades later, the brand expanded with Résistance Thérapiste, specifically addressing the needs of over-processed hair.
Kérastase claims that this innovation, driven by a breakthrough discovery in hair structure, harnesses the power of an ancient plant and incorporates a novel sensory experience, allowing women to achieve complete renewal of damaged hair in just one use.</description></item><item><title>Eating facai may have negative health effects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eating-facai-may-have-negative-health-effects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eating-facai-may-have-negative-health-effects/</guid><description>A vegetarian dish commonly enjoyed during Chinese New Year often features &amp;ldquo;facai&amp;rdquo; fungus, which resembles hair and symbolizes prosperity due to its name sounding like &amp;ldquo;gaining prosperity&amp;rdquo; in Chinese. However, facai, scientifically known as nostoc flagelliforme, is a type of toxic bacteria.
Excessive harvesting led to a ban on facai in China, resulting in most facai today being primarily made from starch. A 2009 study published in Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis revealed that authentic nostoc flagelliforme was rare in commercially available facai, and those genuine samples contained a toxin called beta-N-methylamino-L-alanine (BMAA).</description></item></channel></rss>