<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PBX Phone Systems on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-phone-systems/</link><description>Recent content in PBX Phone Systems on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-phone-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrated Access Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>T1 lines can be used for broadband data or digital phone lines. However, needing separate lines for voice and data was expensive for smaller businesses. Integrated T1 offered a solution by combining voice and data on a single line, proving cost-effective for a while. But now, Integrated Access using Ethernet over Copper is an even better option.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a strong competitor to T1 lines. Both use existing copper telephone wiring, offering reliability and dedicated bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How HD Audio Will Transform VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</guid><description>People who recall the era of analog phones and physical switches often feel nostalgic about the superior audio quality of those systems. The conversations back then possessed a clarity and immediacy that has largely vanished in recent times, though this might be changing soon. A new movement is underway to enhance the fidelity of VoIP calls significantly, aiming to make current phones seem primitive in comparison.
This advancement is known as high-definition audio or HD Voice, a term used by Polycom, a manufacturer of IP phones equipped with this technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So, What Does ISDN Stand For?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</guid><description>If your business uses telephone systems, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the term ISDN. This piece explains what ISDN is and how it can benefit your company.
ISDN, or Integrated Services Digital Network, is a digital telephone standard initially intended to replace analog lines for both residential and business users. While DSL, cable broadband, and VoIP surpassed ISDN in the residential market with their higher bandwidths and lower costs, ISDN found its niche as a popular trunking service for business PBX telephone systems and a few specialized applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>