<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Information Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/information-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Information Technology on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:59:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/information-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IT Departments are Wearin' the Green</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</guid><description>Maintaining IT budgets requires more than just good fortune these days. Many companies are discovering that environmentally friendly practices can save them money. These eco-conscious choices benefit both the planet and their bottom line.
One of the first areas to examine is electricity consumption. Power usage can be deceptive because it often occurs in small, unnoticeable increments. Every desktop computer, even when idle, contributes to the overall energy use, measured in watt-hours and kilowatt-hours.</description></item><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data.</description></item><item><title>From CAPEX to OPEX In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The cost model for Information Technology is shifting from capital expenditure (CAPEX) to operational expenditure (OPEX) due to economic uncertainty and the rise of cloud computing.
Traditionally, businesses invested heavily in on-site data centers with servers, storage, and network equipment. This approach, while effective, requires substantial upfront capital and incurs ongoing operational costs like electricity, bandwidth, staffing, and software maintenance.
While this capital-intensive model was the norm, the economic downturn made businesses more cost-conscious.</description></item><item><title>XO Nails Down SIP Trunking Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</guid><description>Want to discover how your business could save upwards of $88,000 annually just by switching to SIP trunking service?
Hold on a minute! To achieve this level of savings, your business needs to have a certain volume of operations and spending. This figure comes from XO Communications, a leading voice and data carrier, and their new Enterprise SIP Savings Estimator.
So, what kind of business can expect these substantial savings? In this scenario, a company with 1,000 employees spread across 10 locations, where half of their phone calls are internal.</description></item><item><title>The Ubiquitous Cloud of 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</guid><description>The year 2012 brings a shift in the business landscape, not towards a downturn, but rather a move towards cloud computing. This change benefits businesses facing uncertainty by offering flexibility and adaptability. Instead of struggling to predict the future, businesses can embrace the cloud and adjust their strategies as needed.
The current business environment is already in flux. While some businesses are stagnant, others experience constant change. This unpredictability leaves many longing for a more stable past.</description></item><item><title>What Becomes Of The Broken Hardware?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</guid><description>_While troubleshooting a LAN for faulty wiring, I&amp;rsquo;m haunted by thoughts of server failures. The concept of uptime seems like a cruel joke, and I&amp;rsquo;m desperate for a solution.
What happens to malfunctioning equipment that dies prematurely? I need to determine the root cause of this outage.
The list of underlying issues is extensive, and the network is collapsing. The pressure mounts daily, becoming unbearable.
I examine server logs, looking for answers while facing the frustrated stares of the staff who demand updates.</description></item><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services.</description></item><item><title>Make Mine Green Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/make-mine-green-hosting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/make-mine-green-hosting/</guid><description>Two major challenges impacting data centers today are power demands and the associated costs, limiting the expansion of online services. Large server farms are often located not for staff convenience, but near ample power sources due to their significant energy consumption.
Information technology requires vast amounts of electricity, particularly for processing large datasets at high speeds. Servers generate significant heat, demanding substantial cooling systems, which further increase energy consumption. Data centers, with their massive energy needs, face challenges as we grapple with power generation limitations.</description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Deals for MSPs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</guid><description>Managed Service Providers (MSPs) can provide more value to their clients by helping them find better deals on WAN bandwidth, in addition to their existing IT services. Many companies are unaware of the changes in the telecommunications market and the cheaper options now available.
A basic bandwidth service that businesses should consider is T1, which offers reliable voice and/or data services with a service level agreement. T1 prices have significantly decreased this decade, often by 50% or even 67%.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item><item><title>Workaholic and Proud of IT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 22:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re deeply involved in technology, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you might identify as a workaholic. Did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a day specifically for acknowledging workaholics? It&amp;rsquo;s not an official holiday, of course, as that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t align with the workaholic spirit. Workaholics Day falls on July 5th, the day after most people are recovering from their Fourth of July festivities.
While others are recovering from fireworks or tending to minor burns, you might find yourself busy with crucial hardware upgrades in a server room.</description></item></channel></rss>