<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Collection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/collection/</link><description>Recent content in Collection on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 09:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/collection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mary Katrantzou, known as the "Queen of Prints," is featured in the adidas Originals fall/winter collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mary-katrantzou-known-as-the-queen-of-prints-is-featured-in-the-adidas-originals-fall-winter-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 09:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mary-katrantzou-known-as-the-queen-of-prints-is-featured-in-the-adidas-originals-fall-winter-collection/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Shoes from the Mary Katrantzou collection.
Renowned fashion designer Mary Katrantzou, often called the “Queen of Prints,” has partnered with sportswear giant adidas. Their collaboration, the adidas Originals by Mary Katrantzou collection, features apparel and footwear inspired by Katrantzou&amp;rsquo;s signature style.
Katrantzou&amp;rsquo;s designs are known for their fusion of vibrant graphics, structural silhouettes, and cutting-edge technologies, resulting in a contemporary and feminine aesthetic. For this collection, she drew inspiration from classic adidas shoe designs, incorporating elements like outsoles, laces, and iconic brand details into her unique pieces.</description></item><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile.</description></item><item><title>Accor makes a comeback in Myanmar with The Lake Garden in Nay Pyi Taw</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw.
Accor, a leading international hotel operator in the Asia-Pacific region, has established its first hotel in Myanmar: The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw. This recently constructed, upscale establishment is part of the MGallery Collection and is conveniently located a short distance from both the Myanmar International Convention Centre (MICC) and Nay Pyi Taw International Airport.
Patrick Basset, Chief Operating Officer for Accor in multiple Southeast Asian nations, highlighted the significance of this opening as it marks Accor&amp;rsquo;s return to Myanmar.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals, a brand that is committed to being cruelty-free, has launched a new range of eyeshadows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</guid><description>Everyday Minerals (EM) prioritizes using the purest natural ingredients to create all-natural, vegan, and cruelty-free makeup. Their products are handmade in Texas and packaged in eco-friendly, recyclable materials.
Source: Everyday Minerals blog.
Vegan makeup is characterized by its exclusion of animal-derived ingredients and its non-reliance on animal testing. Ingredients like lanolin and collagen are examples of animal-derived components. A growing number of cosmetics companies are introducing vegan product lines or, like EM, adopting a fully vegan approach.</description></item><item><title>The Fall/Winter 2015 Collections have been launched by CH Carolina Herrera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</guid><description>CH, a subsidiary brand under the Carolina Herrera fashion house, has launched their Fall/Winter 2015 collections for both men and women. The Women’s Collection uses vibrant pops of color like reds, sky blues, and fuchsias, which stand out against a darker color scheme with white and ivory accents.
Formal evening wear is designed using luxurious fabrics like silks, lace, and jacquard. The feminine looks are completed with signature CH Carolina Herrera details like bows and ruffles.</description></item><item><title>Rodenstock is bringing back vintage shapes and sizes in eyewear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rodenstock-is-bringing-back-vintage-shapes-and-sizes-in-eyewear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rodenstock-is-bringing-back-vintage-shapes-and-sizes-in-eyewear/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, fashion icon Claudia Schiffer and German eyewear company Rodenstock debuted their first collaborative eyewear collection. Later, in September, they launched an autumn/winter collection, featuring fresh color variations for several styles.
&amp;ldquo;Sunglasses are a simple yet impactful way to define a look,&amp;rdquo; explains Schiffer, who serves as Creative Director for the collection. &amp;ldquo;Paired with the right coat, bag, or jeans, the right pair can make a real statement.</description></item><item><title>InPost has officially started its operations in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: InPost.
InPost, a global leader in automated parcel locker networks, has expanded its services to Malaysia. The launch was accompanied by a roadshow, themed &amp;ldquo;Malaysia E-commerce Day (MED) 2015,&amp;rdquo; aimed at raising awareness about the latest advancements in e-commerce, e-payments, and logistics.
According to InPost Malaysia Managing Director Rosland Mohd Jannes, the initiative seeks to connect with businesses and individuals, boosting consumer confidence in online shopping and alleviating delivery-related anxieties.</description></item></channel></rss>