<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Starhub on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/starhub/</link><description>Recent content in Starhub on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/starhub/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bookmate has teamed up with StarHub for its initial launch in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Bookmate. Pictured at the December 17 launch of Bookmate in Singapore are (from left): Simon Dunlop, Bookmate Founder, Andrew Baev, Bookmate Managing Director, and Michael Sim, StarHub Lead Futurist, i3 (Innovation, Investment, Incubation).
Bookmate, a social platform for reading e-books, has launched in Singapore, its initial entry point into the Southeast Asian market. The service offers subscribers unlimited reading for a fixed monthly price, drawing from a library of over half a million e-books provided by 600 publishers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In January, StarHub will be featuring high-definition Korean movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</guid><description>StarHub TV customers will be the first in Asia to enjoy the latest and greatest Korean films in high definition (HD), 24 hours a day. The company announced that tvN Movies HD, Asia’s first channel dedicated to Korean films, will launch on StarHub TV (channel 818) on January 11, 2017. For added convenience, the channel will also be available on demand as tvN Movies VOD HD. Customers can watch it anytime on StarHub TV Channel 819, or stream it via StarHub Go, StarHub&amp;rsquo;s online streaming service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces WeChat SIM card for tourists from China visiting Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced two new prepaid SIM cards, named &amp;ldquo;StarHub WeChat Go SIM&amp;rdquo;, specifically designed for Chinese tourists visiting Singapore. This launch is a collaboration between StarHub and WeChat.
The StarHub WeChat Go SIM aims to meet the connectivity needs of the increasing number of Chinese tourists. Data from the Singapore Tourism Board shows a 36% rise in tourists from China in 2016 compared to the previous year. A 2017 Hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces digital remittance services for Mobile Prepaid customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 21:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile Prepaid users can now send money internationally to over 40 countries within a day using the updated StarHub Prepaid app. This new feature is possible through a partnership with Singapore fintech company and licensed major payment institution, Pay2Home.
Digital remittances through the app eliminate the need for physical queues or appointments. The StarHub Prepaid app allows users to conveniently manage everything from identity verification and checking updated currency rates to transferring funds and managing prepaid accounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub is offering a deal of 3GB for S$3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</guid><description>StarHub is offering a new &amp;ldquo;3GB-for-$3&amp;rdquo; data upsize option for its mobile postpaid customers. For a limited time, customers who sign up for or renew their StarHub 4G plans can get an extra 3GB of data for S$3 per month. This promotional price will increase to S$6 per month for customers who sign up on or after April 1, 2016.
Here are the details for StarHub&amp;rsquo;s two-year mobile postpaid plans:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub shows appreciation for loyal customers during iPhone launch by offering rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-shows-appreciation-for-loyal-customers-during-iphone-launch-by-offering-rewards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-shows-appreciation-for-loyal-customers-during-iphone-launch-by-offering-rewards/</guid><description>Four loyal StarHub customers were treated to an exclusive experience: becoming the first in Singapore to own and activate the new iPhone. They enjoyed a luxurious supercar ride to StarHub&amp;rsquo;s flagship store in Plaza Singapura for the launch event.
At the store, they were greeted by StarHub executives, including Chief Executive Peter Kaliaropoulos. At precisely 8 am, the four customers activated their new iPhones, marking them as the first users in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-shows-appreciation-for-loyal-customers-during-iphone-launch-by-offering-rewards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-shows-appreciation-for-loyal-customers-during-iphone-launch-by-offering-rewards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub reintroduces 12GB mobile data bundles and additional features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced a new, budget-friendly package called SurfHub, combining mobile and home internet services.
For a starting price of S$96.56 per month on a 24-month contract, SurfHub customers receive a 4G mobile plan with a minimum of 12GB of data and a 1Gbps fiber broadband connection for their homes. This combined offer costs roughly half the price of a standalone 12GB mobile plan. SurfHub also includes generous benefits like up to 700 minutes of local calls, 1,500 local SMS/MMS messages, and a subsidy for a new mobile phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get your hands on StarHub's flyers for CEE 2017 by downloading them now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</guid><description>Source: StarHub.
StarHub, recognized as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s most environmentally friendly telecommunications company, will participate in the 2017 Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE).
Details about StarHub&amp;rsquo;s mobile, television, broadband, and bundled services are available in online promotional flyers. These flyers, which include information about the Business Fibre Broadband Bundle, are specifically designed for business customers.
The 2017 CEE will take place at Suntec from June 1st to June 4th. The event will be open from 11 am to 9 pm on levels 1 and 3, and from 12 pm to 9 pm in Halls 403 to 406 on level 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub now offers mobile phone aftersales care to customers who have SIM-only plans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced SmartSupport Lite, a new mobile phone aftersales service designed to be incredibly user-friendly. This service is specifically for customers with SIM Only plans, allowing them to quickly address any unexpected issues with their phones.
Source: StarHub SmartSupport Lite offers mobile phone aftersales care to SIM Only customers.
Signing up is simple - customers can register their existing phones digitally using the My StarHub app without needing any paperwork or activation fees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel customers enjoy the top roaming experience in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Opensignal. 4G download speed experience in Mbps for Singapore roamers in Malaysia compared to the experience for Malaysian mobile users.
A 2019 Opensignal study on Singaporean 4G users roaming in Malaysia revealed that Singtel subscribers had the best download speeds, upload speeds, and latency.
M1 and StarHub users experienced comparable download and upload speeds while in Malaysia. However, StarHub users enjoyed better latency compared to M1. Although both StarHub and M1 users faced significantly slower latency than Malaysian domestic users, indicating a poorer experience, Singtel users only lagged behind domestic Maxis users by 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub, offering the quickest 3G and 4G network in Singapore, introduces the World's Fastest Band</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</guid><description>StarHub, a telecommunications company, has unveiled the &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Fastest Band&amp;rdquo; to celebrate its recognition in OpenSignal&amp;rsquo;s Speed Awards 2018 for having Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fastest 4G and 3G speeds. OpenSignal, a global wireless coverage mapping specialist, awarded StarHub based on network quality. StarHub&amp;rsquo;s VP of Segment &amp;amp; Marketing, Donovan Kik, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to network quality and customer satisfaction. He stated their dedication to meeting customer needs and expectations despite achieving this recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub announces pricing for newest iPhone models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 14:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone 11 Pro and iPhone 11 Pro Max are available in midnight green, space grey, silver, and gold finishes.
StarHub has quickly released pricing for the newly announced iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, and iPhone 11 Pro Max. The iPhone 11 Pro and iPhone 11 Pro Max represent a new generation of iPhones offering high-level performance.
According to Apple, the pro line boasts a new Super Retina XDR display, the brightest ever seen on an iPhone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting from 26 September, StarHub is excited to welcome buyers of the iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 18:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Source: StarHub. Customers waiting in line inside the newly renovated StarHub Shop in VivoCity, one of 38 StarHub stores serving pre-order customers on September 25th.
On September 25th, pre-orders for Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus became available for pickup at 38 StarHub stores across Singapore. To ensure a smooth pickup process, customers who pre-ordered were given specific locations and time slots when they booked their appointments.
Starting September 26th, customers can visit any StarHub Shop or participating authorized retailers to purchase the phones directly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub simplifies mobile customers' ability to browse and travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile postpaid customers can now subscribe to a Mobile DataTravel plan for S$15. This plan offers 2GB of data valid for 30 days, usable in a single country or across multiple destinations.
DataTravel eliminates the need to manually select or lock phones to specific mobile networks, unlike traditional roaming plans. StarHub highlights this as a unique advantage among Singaporean telcos and plans to expand its list of supported destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>