<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SOC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/soc/</link><description>Recent content in SOC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/soc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data.</description></item><item><title>Earth to Cloud Network Security Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 18:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</guid><description>Information technology specialists understand the need for secure corporate networks, including enterprise-level security for cloud computing services in remote data centers. However, maintaining security across the entire network, especially when extending the LAN remotely, poses a significant challenge.
Level 3 Communications offers a solution with its “Earth to Cloud” comprehensive global security suite. This multi-layered protection strategy aims to secure every aspect of the network from potential threats.
A key factor in this approach is having a single provider for both connectivity and network security, a role Level 3 is well-equipped to fill.</description></item></channel></rss>