<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Journalism on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/journalism/</link><description>Recent content in Journalism on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 02:25:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/journalism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The European Commission introduces an anti-SLAPP initiative known as 'Daphne's Law'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-introduces-an-anti-slapp-initiative-known-as-daphne-s-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 02:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-introduces-an-anti-slapp-initiative-known-as-daphne-s-law/</guid><description>Professor Justin Borg-Barthet, University of Aberdeen*
*Advisor to a coalition of press freedom NGOs on the introduction of SLAPPs, co-author of the CASE Model Law, lead author of a study commissioned by the European Parliament, and member of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s Expert Group on SLAPPs and its legislative sub-group
Background
At the time of her assassination on October 16, 2017, Maltese journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia faced 48 defamation lawsuits across various courts.</description></item><item><title>Can The Big Amazon Kindle DX Save The Newspapers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-big-amazon-kindle-dx-save-the-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 03:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-big-amazon-kindle-dx-save-the-newspapers/</guid><description>The recent debut of the larger Amazon Kindle DX has been hailed by some as a potential savior for the struggling newspaper industry. However, this nearly $500 device, while innovative, is unlikely to reverse the decline of print newspapers.
It&amp;rsquo;s simply too late and too expensive a solution for an industry facing dire financial straits. Had newspapers embraced electronic delivery methods a decade ago, the outcome might have been different. Now, many are on the brink of collapse, and technology alone cannot salvage them.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the European Democracy Action Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 04:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
The European Democracy Action Plan (EDAP) is one piece of a larger effort to regulate the online world. Unveiled as a key initiative by Commission President von der Leyen, it joins upcoming legislation like the Digital Services Act (DSA) and Digital Markets Act (DMA). These measures signal a change in how the EU approaches internet regulation and raise questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority in this space.</description></item><item><title>The ECHR provides clarification on the use of hidden cameras in relation to human rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Bremner v Turkey provides clarity on the use of hidden cameras by journalists and potential human rights violations. The case involved an Australian citizen, Bremner, who was secretly filmed in his apartment discussing Christianity for a documentary about &amp;ldquo;foreign peddlers of religion&amp;rdquo; in Turkey. The program aired footage of Bremner with his face unblurred.</description></item></channel></rss>