<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backhoe Fade on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backhoe-fade/</link><description>Recent content in Backhoe Fade on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backhoe-fade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet Service Without The Outages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</guid><description>The internet has become an essential tool for accessing information, connecting with others, and conducting business. It offers a vast repository of knowledge, real-time services, and entertainment options. However, internet outages can occur, causing frustration and disruption.
While complete internet blackouts are rare, local outages can still happen. These outages can be planned maintenance, accidental disruptions, or natural disasters. For businesses and individuals who rely heavily on the internet, these outages can be costly.</description></item><item><title>Winter Of Our Disconnect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winter-of-our-disconnect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winter-of-our-disconnect/</guid><description>The Challenges of Disconnection in the Digital Age
While we live in an era defined by instant communication, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for businesses to prepare for disruptions. This is similar to the wisdom of anticipating challenges, even during seemingly stable times.
Take, for instance, the recent incident in the Mediterranean where several underwater cables were severed. This caused significant internet outages in Egypt and India, with slower speeds experienced across Europe and Asia.</description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?</description></item><item><title>TelePacific Takes Business Continuity Seriously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications, a telecommunications company serving California and Nevada, emphasizes a thorough approach to disaster preparedness and business continuity.
Their Business Continuity Services aim to keep your voice and data operational, even if a trunk line or your entire facility goes down. But how is this achieved?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with telephone service. Many businesses utilize digital trunk lines like T1 PRI and SIP Trunks, which offer cost savings compared to individual lines but pose a single point of failure risk.</description></item></channel></rss>