<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MBA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mba/</link><description>Recent content in MBA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:20:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asian students are focusing on hospitality management programs at LHE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</guid><description>Asian students make up a significant portion of the student population at the four hospitality schools operated by Laureate Hospitality Education (LHE): Glion Institute of Higher Education, Les Roches International School of Hotel Management, Kendall College, and Blue Mountains International Hotel Management School.
Source: LHE. From left, Hou, Tatar, Williams Knight.
Judy Hou, CEO of Glion Institute of Higher Education, noted a growing demand for LHE&amp;rsquo;s programs (offered in Switzerland, the US, and their branch campuses) throughout the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AMBA accreditation awarded to India's IIMC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/</guid><description>The Indian Institute of Management Calcutta (IIMC) has received a five-year accreditation from the Association of MBAs (AMBA) for its MBA and MBM programs.
Anindya Sen, Dean of IIMC, stated that the institute aims to secure a distinct global standing. &amp;ldquo;AMBA accreditation will enhance our international visibility and establish us as a global institution, enabling us to attract more international students. We will also receive valuable guidance for continuous improvement,&amp;rdquo; he explained...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>16% of the top 100 MBAs from the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Business schools in Asia may be overlooking the potential of online MBAs. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s first ever Online MBA Rankings for 2014, which came out in March, contained no Asian business schools in its list of the top 15 programs.
However, the region performs better in the traditional MBA format. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s Global MBA Rankings for 2014, published in January 2014, features a number of Asian schools within its top 50...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>