<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Radiation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/radiation/</link><description>Recent content in Radiation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:14:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/radiation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There is debate over whether mobile phones can cause cancer, with some believing they can and others disagreeing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</guid><description>There have been many concerns about mobile phones and cancer risks. Since the first mobile phone&amp;rsquo;s debut in 1984 and their rise in popularity in the 1990s, it&amp;rsquo;s taken time to study the long-term effects of mobile phone radiation, as some cancers take years to manifest. We might only now be starting to see the impact.
A recent study in Pathophysiology suggests that radiation from mobile and cordless phones could contribute to a specific brain tumor called glioma.</description></item><item><title>The main focus of Kickstarter is iFind, which is powered by ambient electromagnetic radiation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</guid><description>WeTag&amp;rsquo;s iFind tags use Bluetooth to connect with iOS or Android devices and don&amp;rsquo;t require charging. Like similar tracking devices, the tag is attached to an item and located using a smartphone.
If the item goes out of range, the &amp;lsquo;Rope&amp;rsquo; feature notifies the owner. The &amp;lsquo;UHelp&amp;rsquo; feature leverages nearby phones to help find the lost object through Bluetooth. WeTag highlights a unique feature: shaking the iFind tag will cause the paired phone to vibrate.</description></item></channel></rss>