<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet Service Provider on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-service-provider/</link><description>Recent content in Internet Service Provider on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-service-provider/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dedicated Symmetric Internet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you unhappy with how the internet performs for your business? Do you think it&amp;rsquo;s more for entertainment and casual use than for getting work done quickly and efficiently? You need the internet to function, though. Your customers and suppliers, along with important information, are online. Even your software and communication tools might be cloud-based. What you likely need is a business-grade broadband connection with better performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic ISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</guid><description>Internet service used to rely on dial-up connections, but it has advanced significantly since then. Today, medium-sized businesses are now transitioning to fiber optic internet service providers, a technology already embraced by larger corporations.
Residential fiber optic internet, like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS, offers high speeds, with Google soon to introduce even faster Gigabit service. Business broadband connections, however, have already surpassed Gigabit speeds, with 10 Gbps becoming increasingly common. The technology is well-established, leaving businesses to determine their bandwidth needs and locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>