<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Movement of Goods on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-goods/</link><description>Recent content in Free Movement of Goods on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-goods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The alignment of Ireland's Public Health (Alcohol) Bill with EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Ollie Bartlett, Maynooth University
After nearly three years of discussion, the Irish Public Health (Alcohol) Bill has been passed by the Irish Parliament. The Bill aims to address Ireland&amp;rsquo;s significant alcohol-related harm through five key measures: minimum alcohol pricing; stricter labeling; advertising restrictions; separating alcohol from other retail products; and limitations on alcohol sales and supply.
While lauded as &amp;ldquo;groundbreaking&amp;rdquo; by Health Minister Simon Harris, some argue that elements of the Bill, particularly those related to the free trade of alcohol within the European Union, might not be legal.</description></item><item><title>Is the Essent ruling a new milestone in the legal precedent for the free movement of goods?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</guid><description>A Reassessment of Proportionality and Discrimination in Light of the Essent Case Filippo Fontanelli, Lecturer in International Economic Law, University of Edinburgh
Introduction
The September 11, 2014, Essent case (Joined Cases C-204 to C-208/12) judgment by the Court of Justice of the EU presents a nuanced analysis of proportionality, weighing factors such as promoting free energy trade, safeguarding the environment and human health, adhering to international emission reduction agreements, bolstering local employment, and encouraging energy self-sufficiency.</description></item><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services.</description></item><item><title>Is there Friendly Fire in the European Union? AG Sharpston's view on the revised firearms Directive's validity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</guid><description>Niels Kirst (University Paris II – Panthéon-Assas)
Advocate General Sharpston (AG) issued an opinion on April 11, 2019, regarding the legitimacy of Directive 2017/853, known as the Firearms Directive. The Czech Republic challenged this directive, arguing that the European Parliament and the Council should not have used the internal market harmonization clause (Article 114 TFEU) as the legal basis for its adoption.
This case is noteworthy for several reasons. First, it centers around the crucial aspect of legal basis, drawing considerable attention from EU legal experts.</description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34.</description></item><item><title>The case of Scotch Whisky Association v Lord Advocate [2017] UKSC 76 demonstrates the appropriateness and necessity of implementing minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-scotch-whisky-association-v-lord-advocate-2017-uksc-76-demonstrates-the-appropriateness-and-necessity-of-implementing-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-scotch-whisky-association-v-lord-advocate-2017-uksc-76-demonstrates-the-appropriateness-and-necessity-of-implementing-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Law School, Lancaster University (@AngusMacCulloch)
The UK Supreme Court, in a long-awaited decision on SWA v Lord Advocate, dismissed the Scotch Whisky Association&amp;rsquo;s (SWA) appeal, allowing the Scottish Government to proceed with its Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) policy on alcohol sales. This policy, setting a minimum price of £0.50 per unit of alcohol under the 2012 Alcohol (Minimum Pricing)(Scotland) Act, faced a five-year delay due to legal challenges arguing its conflict with EU law.</description></item><item><title>AG Kokott dismisses challenges to the legality of the Tobacco Products Directive - what does this mean for standardized packaging laws in Member States?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</guid><description>Jonathan Griffiths, Reader in Intellectual Property Law, Queen Mary University of London
The Tobacco Products Directive (Directive 2014/40/EU, revising Directive 2001/37/EC) implements strict rules for selling tobacco products. This includes requiring larger image and text health warnings on cigarettes and rolling tobacco, tighter marketing regulations for tobacco products (including e-cigarettes), and a ban on marketing tobacco products with &amp;ldquo;characterizing flavors,&amp;rdquo; such as menthol cigarettes.
On December 23rd, Advocate General Kokott presented her Opinions on three cases regarding the validity of specific parts of the Directive.</description></item><item><title>Balancing Health and Trade: The Scotch Whisky Association ruling on finding the right equilibrium.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School The Court of Justice has issued its judgment regarding the legality of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s minimum alcohol pricing (MUP) measure in Case C-333/14. Both the Scottish Government and the Scotch Whisky Association (SWA), which initiated the legal challenge, have expressed satisfaction with the ruling, although the SWA might be more content as the case now returns to Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Inner House of the Court of Session, which had referred it to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling on the Legality of the Revised European Firearms Directive: Gun Control in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 22:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, PhD candidate, Dublin City University
Introduction
On December 3rd, 2019, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) delivered its final ruling on a case concerning Czech firearm regulations. This judgment, providing guidance on EU lawmaking, addressed key EU law principles and refined their interpretations. Following terrorist attacks in Paris and Copenhagen, the EU legislature utilized its single market powers (Article 114 TFEU) to pass Directive (EU) 2017/853, amending existing firearms Directives 91/477 and 2008/51/EC.</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General considers the intersection of public health, trade, and competition in setting minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School Background to the Opinion Advocate General (AG) Bot provided his opinion on September 3rd, 2015, regarding Case C-333/14, which involved the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to establish a minimum price per unit (£0.50) on alcohol sales. This Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) faced legal challenges from the Scotch Whisky Association, leading to the case reaching the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The CJEU was asked to determine whether the MUP aligned with the single Common Market Organisation (CMO) and the free movement principles of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item></channel></rss>