<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hybrid on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hybrid/</link><description>Recent content in Hybrid on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hybrid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HPE has reduced the entry threshold for its storage portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</guid><description>Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) recently improved its entry storage products to help budget-conscious customers leverage their data and speed up applications. These new HPE MSA Storage options deliver the most budget-friendly dual-controller hybrid flash array from a major vendor while the new HPE StoreEasy 1650 Expanded makes storing large amounts of information more economical.
Being able to quickly and effectively use information is crucial for success. &amp;ldquo;Agility and speed are critical for staying competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s economy, no matter the business size,&amp;rdquo; said Manish Goel, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Storage at HPE.</description></item><item><title>IWG: The Transformation of the World of Work in 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 19:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</guid><description>This image, created using the AI tool Dream by WOMBO, depicts a concept of modern office work.
As the leading global provider of flexible workspaces, IWG, known for brands like Regus and Spaces, has identified ten significant workplace trends anticipated to influence global work dynamics in 2024. The company predicts the continuation of hybrid work models, citing ongoing research by institutions like Stanford University that suggests a significant portion of white-collar workers will maintain this approach.</description></item><item><title>HP has released the HP Helion OpenStack Community Edition for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 09:24:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</guid><description>As part of its new HP Helion portfolio, HP is launching cloud products and services. These include:
HP Helion OpenStack Community Edition: This commercially available OpenStack product line is delivered, tested, and supported by HP. This free edition, available now, is perfect for proofs of concept, pilot projects, and basic production workloads. HP&amp;rsquo;s OpenStack Technology Indemnification Program: This safeguards eligible customers who use HP Helion OpenStack code from claims of patent, copyright, and trade secret infringement by third parties.</description></item><item><title>Cisco: The adoption of hybrid work has enhanced the quality of life for many individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-the-adoption-of-hybrid-work-has-enhanced-the-quality-of-life-for-many-individuals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-the-adoption-of-hybrid-work-has-enhanced-the-quality-of-life-for-many-individuals/</guid><description>A recent global Cisco study indicates that hybrid work arrangements in Singapore have led to improvements in overall employee well-being, work-life balance, and performance. While companies have seen gains in employee productivity, there&amp;rsquo;s room for improvement in fostering an inclusive work environment and fully implementing hybrid work models to enhance employee experience and preparedness.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s study, titled &amp;ldquo;Employees are ready for hybrid work, are you?&amp;rdquo;, revealed that 56% of Singaporean employees believe their work quality has risen, and 60% reported increased productivity.</description></item><item><title>The Business of Design Week 2021 is open to participants from all over the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Officiating guests join Business of Design Week 2021’s opening ceremony.
The 19th edition of Business of Design Week (BODW) 2021 has begun. This major Asian design, innovation, and brand event, organized annually by the Hong Kong Design Centre (HKDC) since 2002, will run for a week. The summit showcases a diverse range of speakers and television programs centered around the theme of Global Design Reset.
The event adopts a hybrid format this year, broadcast simultaneously online, on ViuTV, and at various partner venues such as the PMQ in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Part 12: 2023's Work Trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</guid><description>Source: Deel playbook. 12 work
trends for 2023.
Deel, a provider of payroll and compliance solutions for global teams, has identified twelve emerging workplace trends for 2023:
Overemployed
Deel found that remote workers are increasingly taking on multiple jobs simultaneously, leveraging flexible schedules and asynchronous communication tools.
The Chief Remote Officer (CRO)
The role of CRO is gaining traction, with companies seeking individuals to oversee all aspects of remote work, including in-person events, time-zone management, compensation, and communication tools.</description></item><item><title>HP has improved MSA Storage for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP is introducing new features for its MSA Storage solutions to benefit startups, SMBs, and customers with small sites. These enhancements aim to increase competitiveness.
The improved MSA 2040 Storage offers significantly faster application performance, up to 45% faster, without extra costs through firmware updates. Additionally, new MSA 2040 bundles provide cost savings of up to 45% for hybrid flash deployments. Furthermore, the introduction of Serial Attached SCSI (SAS) connectivity to the MSA 1040 Storage positions it as the most budget-friendly shared storage option from a major vendor.</description></item></channel></rss>