<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Human Resources on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/human-resources/</link><description>Recent content in Human Resources on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 05:37:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/human-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exciting Updates Ahead for HR and PR in Dynamics GP 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic to hear about the exciting updates coming to the Human Resources and Payroll modules in Dynamics GP 2013, as shared by Terry Heley from Microsoft. Here are a few highlights:
A significant improvement is the direct integration of tools for managing deductions, benefits, and pay code modifiers. This user-friendly approach will make it much easier to modify pay codes, deduction codes, and benefit codes, enhancing user satisfaction.
Another valuable enhancement for users is the ability to choose whether or not to print alignments on checks and earnings statements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Payroll System Continues to Grow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 11:48:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</guid><description>Over the last few months, many clients have asked me about additional modules for Payroll in Dynamics GP. While the base payroll module works well, companies seeking better efficiency and streamlined processes are looking for ways to expand its capabilities. For example, they might need to automate a previously manual process or switch from paper-based delivery to electronic methods like email or portals.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to share some options for improving payroll processing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>