<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cisco on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cisco/</link><description>Recent content in Cisco on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cisco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, Singaporean small and medium-sized businesses are leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</guid><description>Source: Cisco ebook. This Cisco report, the APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, evaluates digital maturity based on four key aspects.
· Singaporean SMBs achieved the highest ranking on the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index.
· Cybersecurity is the primary technology that Singaporean SMBs are investing in, followed by cloud computing and analytics.
· The most significant challenges cited by SMBs across Singapore are a shortage of digital skills and talent within their organizations and a lack of understanding of operational and customer data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco's Unified Computing Cuts Costs and Power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-unified-computing-cuts-costs-and-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:57:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-unified-computing-cuts-costs-and-power/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Unified Computing technology aims to make data centers more efficient. Recognizing the enduring role of virtualization, Cisco fully embraces it to enhance performance and cut expenses, leading to reduced power usage.
You might be reminded of Unified Communications (UC) when hearing about Unified Computing. UC aims to combine all forms of business communication, such as phones, emails, faxes, voicemails, and instant messaging, into a single infrastructure. A good example is Kall8&amp;rsquo;s feature that sends faxes and voicemails to your email...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-unified-computing-cuts-costs-and-power/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-unified-computing-cuts-costs-and-power/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco Steps In Front Of The Video Parade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-steps-in-front-of-the-video-parade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 19:52:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-steps-in-front-of-the-video-parade/</guid><description>John Naisbitt, a renowned futurist, once said that true leadership involves recognizing a trend and positioning oneself at its forefront. Cisco seems to have taken this to heart by acquiring Flip Video, the company behind the wildly popular camcorder line. It appears Cisco sees consumer-generated video as a growing trend and intends to lead the charge. But what exactly are their plans?
To understand Cisco&amp;rsquo;s strategy, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to examine the Flip video camera&amp;rsquo;s impact on the camcorder market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-steps-in-front-of-the-video-parade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-steps-in-front-of-the-video-parade/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco has launched new personal hardware to improve collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</guid><description>At Cisco Live! 2014 in the US, Cisco unveiled new personal collaboration tools. The company recognizes that teamwork often spans continents, demanding tools that enable seamless and immediate collaboration, regardless of location.
Source: Cisco. The Cisco DX80 in action.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution comes in the form of the DX70 and DX80 desktop collaboration devices. These Android-based devices act as hubs for collaboration tools and applications. Featuring large touch screens, the DX70 and DX80 combine Cisco&amp;rsquo;s expertise in HD video, high-quality audio, and web conferencing with integrated business applications and web browsing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaller companies can benefit from Cisco's advanced firewall security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</guid><description>Source: Cisco website. Some members of the Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services family.
Cisco has introduced new Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services models designed for small to mid-sized businesses and branch offices. These models offer the same advanced malware protection and threat detection used by larger organizations.
A recent study by PwC revealed a 64% increase in security breaches among mid-sized organizations in 2014. These organizations face similar security challenges as larger enterprises when safeguarding their network and data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>