<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fair on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fair/</link><description>Recent content in Fair on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region.</description></item></channel></rss>