<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ICT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ict/</link><description>Recent content in ICT on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ict/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India is enhancing its intellectual property infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</guid><description>The Indian government has decided to continue its efforts to improve its intellectual property (IP) offices. This initiative, part of the 12th Plan (2012-2017), will cost Rs309.6 crore, with Rs258 crore allocated for the 12th Plan and Rs51.6 crore for the 13th Plan.
This decision recognizes the increasing importance of IP in a globalized economy, India&amp;rsquo;s recent membership in the Madrid Protocol (April 2013), and the Controller General of Patents, Designs, and Trademarks (CGPDTM) office&amp;rsquo;s new role as an International Searching and Preliminary Examining Authority (ISA/IPEA) under the Patent Cooperation Treaty (starting October 2013).</description></item><item><title>Singapore is dedicated to developing talent in the infocomm sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, addressed the rising demand for infocomm professionals in the country. This surge is attributed to the growth of the ICT sector and Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation initiatives. Dr. Yaacob emphasized the need to fill 30,000 infocomm positions by 2020.
He acknowledged the challenge of meeting this demand solely with local talent, stating that while relying on non-Singaporeans might be necessary, the focus should be on equipping Singaporeans with highly competitive skills.</description></item><item><title>Tourists are disappointed with shopping in Singapore, while locals are loyal to their telecommunications companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tourists-are-disappointed-with-shopping-in-singapore-while-locals-are-loyal-to-their-telecommunications-companies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tourists-are-disappointed-with-shopping-in-singapore-while-locals-are-loyal-to-their-telecommunications-companies/</guid><description>A study by the Institute of Service Excellence (ISES) at Singapore Management University reveals a drop in customer satisfaction within Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retail and info-communications sectors.
The 2014 Q1 Customer Satisfaction Index of Singapore (CSISG) indicates a 2.5 point (3.5%) decrease to 69.6 points for retail and a 0.9 point (1.3%) decrease to 66.8 points for info-communications, both compared to the previous year.
Eight retail aspects were evaluated, with supermarkets as the only sector showing improvement:</description></item><item><title>This year in the Philippines, the focus is on mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</guid><description>In the Philippines, technology is synonymous with mobile technology.
According to Jubert Alberto, Research Manager at IDC Philippines, &amp;ldquo;The younger generation is entering the workforce, and they have a strong desire to be connected, informed, and entertained. They also tend to have fewer dependents. These factors indicate a growing demand for all things mobile, including devices, services, and applications.&amp;rdquo; IDC predicts that the Philippines will experience a 22% rise in smartphone spending and a 40% increase in tablet expenditure in 2014, fueled by a positive economic outlook.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the opportunity to apply for government grants to assist with their studies in infocomm, media, and design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</guid><description>Singaporeans working in Infocomm, Media, and Design can apply for the SkillsFuture Study Awards until June 14, 2016.
Announced during the Ministry of Communications and Information’s Committee of Supply Debate for 2016, the SkillsFuture Study Award encourages Singaporeans to enhance their skills in sectors crucial for future economic growth. Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, stated that 310 awards will be granted to Singaporeans in the early or middle stages of their careers who are looking to advance their skills in these sectors.</description></item></channel></rss>