<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Leadership on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/leadership/</link><description>Recent content in Leadership on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/leadership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encouraging an open workplace culture: the role of leaders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</guid><description>Open communication and strong relationships are essential for a thriving workplace. UK-based sales and marketing firm Forrest Bell emphasizes that openness involves respectful and constructive dialogue about needs, opinions, and concerns. It also means actively listening to and considering new ideas, questions, and feedback.
Forrest Bell believes that a culture of openness fosters trust and facilitates collaboration on projects. It also promotes transparency and streamlines processes in dynamic business environments.</description></item><item><title>Flight Experience Singapore and McGallen &amp; Bolden offer unique leadership workshops that stand out from the rest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</guid><description>Source: McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden.
Flight Experience Singapore, the first flight simulator open to the public in Asia, has partnered with the consulting firm McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden to offer leadership workshops.
Their program, Leadership Secrets at 30,000 Feet, is designed for business leaders and executives. It uses a realistic cockpit setting to teach leadership skills. The customized, four-hour workshop draws on decades of experience from Captain Michael Caston, a pilot with experience flying Boeing 747 and 737 jets for British Airways and Singapore Airlines.</description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is leading the way in digital transformation and digital leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</guid><description>Source: SAP. Agree or disagree? Management and staff in Southeast Asia and globally share their thoughts in the Leaders 2020 study.
Almost 25% of Southeast Asian companies are considered digital leaders, according to a recent study by SAP and Oxford Economics. This figure surpasses the global average of 16% reported in the Leaders 2020 study.
This new category of high-achieving companies reports greater profit increases, improved employee engagement, and more inclusive workplace environments.</description></item><item><title>Discover your leadership potential with a revolutionary tool from Hogan Assessment Systems and Sirota</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-your-leadership-potential-with-a-revolutionary-tool-from-hogan-assessment-systems-and-sirota/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-your-leadership-potential-with-a-revolutionary-tool-from-hogan-assessment-systems-and-sirota/</guid><description>On July 30th at the Oasia Hotel Singapore, Dr. Tomas Chamorro-Premuzic, CEO of Hogan Assessment Systems, a leader in personality profiling and psychometric testing, along with Lewis Garrad, Managing Director Asia Pacific at Sirota, a performance consulting firm, will preview a new employee assessment model they jointly developed.
Launching in the Asia Pacific market in October 2015, the Engaging Leader tool will help companies and brands better identify and develop leadership potential.</description></item><item><title>Flightleaders.com will enhance its programs in 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</guid><description>Source: Flightleaders.com website. An aircraft cockpit.
Flightleaders.com, an aviation-inspired leadership training provider and part of the McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden Group, intends to expand its program offerings throughout 2018.
Dr. Seamus Phan, a Leadership Trainer with Flightleaders.com specializing in corporate leadership and philosophical approaches, believes corporate training will be highly sought after due to generational gaps in the workplace. He argues this need goes beyond technological advancements and other disruptive trends, as managing people and leadership will remain critical challenges.</description></item><item><title>The World Economic Forum introduces its inaugural online leadership module for professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</guid><description>Professionals can now register for the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s first online leadership program, Global Information Technology Outlook. This six-week module, created for senior executives and fast-track leadership programs, offers a comprehensive overview of important new technologies transforming industries and society.
Professor Klaus Schwab, Founder and Executive Chairman of the World Economic Forum, highlighted the challenges leaders face understanding the increasingly complex and unpredictable world, largely due to rapid technological advancements. He stated that the Forum Academy module addresses this by giving leaders a better grasp of ongoing information technology transformations.</description></item><item><title>Various approaches to talent management in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: ECN.
Attracting and retaining skilled managers in Asia has become increasingly crucial for business leaders.
A recent survey by the Economist Corporate Network (ECN) of 550 member companies in Asia revealed that 95% of CEOs actively engage in talent management practices. However, their level and type of involvement differ significantly.
The report, Aligned for Success? Strategy, talent management and the role of the CEO in Asia, indicates that CEOs primarily focus on the strategic aspects of human capital, such as forecasting future workforce needs and organizational design.</description></item></channel></rss>