<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projector on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/projector/</link><description>Recent content in Projector on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/projector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BenQ introduces new digital signage, projectors, and interactive flat panels, creating a buzz</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</guid><description>BenQ, a leading provider of visual display technology, has introduced a range of new projectors, digital signage, and interactive flat panels, all emphasizing high quality and innovative design. The company highlighted its commitment to delivering excellent visual experiences across various sectors, including business, retail, and food &amp;amp; beverage.
Business The MX666+ projector.
The MX666+ is the first wireless business projector to feature Near Field Communication (NFC) technology and USB connectivity, making it ideal for bring-your-own-device environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces an affordable WUXGA projector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-an-affordable-wuxga-projector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-an-affordable-wuxga-projector/</guid><description>Epson, a leading manufacturer of projectors, is introducing a new line of affordable Widescreen Ultra Extended Array (WUXGA) projectors. These projectors are designed for business use and offer high-resolution images that surpass Full HD video quality.
Siew Jin Kiat, General Manager of Epson Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s Visual Instruments Division, highlighted the significance of this release. For the first time, businesses can access Epson&amp;rsquo;s renowned high color and brightness projection at competitive prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-an-affordable-wuxga-projector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-an-affordable-wuxga-projector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore introduces high-brightness projectors designed for large venues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-introduces-high-brightness-projectors-designed-for-large-venues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 20:33:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-introduces-high-brightness-projectors-designed-for-large-venues/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. The white EB-G7000.
Epson Singapore recently introduced the EB-G7000 series, their newest high-brightness projectors designed for large venues. These projectors provide high-quality images with quiet operation, making them suitable for various settings like meeting rooms, lecture halls, and museums.
Featuring the latest 4K enhancements, the projectors produce brighter, more vivid images with up to 8,000 lumens of both color and white brightness. They offer three times the color brightness compared to similar single-chip projector models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-introduces-high-brightness-projectors-designed-for-large-venues/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-introduces-high-brightness-projectors-designed-for-large-venues/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson's portable projectors are designed for on-the-go presentations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</guid><description>Source: Epson website. The EB-1780W.
Epson has introduced the EB-1700 series, its lightest line of 3LCD projectors yet. This series prioritizes portability without sacrificing image quality or connectivity options, making it ideal for business presentations on the go.
The projectors in the EB-1700 series weigh under 4 pounds and are less than 2 inches thick, making them easy to carry in a laptop bag. Grip lines on the sides add to their portability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new family of interactive projectors with 3LCD technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-family-of-interactive-projectors-with-3lcd-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-family-of-interactive-projectors-with-3lcd-technology/</guid><description>Source: Epson website; The EB-696Ui.
Epson recently released the EB-600 series*, a new line of 3LCD projectors with advanced features. These features include ultra short throw projection at resolutions exceeding full HD, PC-free interactivity, and the first-ever seamless dual-screen interactivity.
Designed for classrooms and businesses, the new EB-600 series projectors (EB-696Ui, EB-695Wi2, EB-685Wi, EB-685W3, and EB-680) provide a vibrant viewing experience.
The series boasts WUXGA resolution (1,920 x 1,200), surpassing full HD, and a heightened brightness of 3,800 lumens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-family-of-interactive-projectors-with-3lcd-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-family-of-interactive-projectors-with-3lcd-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new smart gaming projector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 01:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the EH-TW6250 Smart Gaming Projector, the most budget-friendly option in their 4K PRO-UHD lineup. This projector delivers an impressive home theater experience with a screen size up to 500&amp;quot;, brightness up to 2,800 lumens, and an input lag* under 20 ms, making it ideal for movie nights and casual gaming.
This all-inclusive entertainment solution features scene-adaptive gamma correction, frame interpolation, HDR10/HLG support, and 3LCD technology. These features combine to provide smooth, color-accurate, high-resolution images with balanced white and color light output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BenQ has recently introduced a new series of digital laser projectors that offer precise color accuracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 21:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</guid><description>The BenQ LU9715 digital laser projector.
BenQ, a leading brand in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, has introduced a new series of laser projectors designed for large venues in corporate, professional, and academic settings.
BenQ highlights that the 24/7 operational capabilities will be particularly valuable in large business settings, museums, exhibition spaces, and boardrooms. Daren Low, Senior Product Manager at BenQ Singapore, emphasized the advantage of minimal maintenance, especially since these projectors are often mounted in high, hard-to-reach locations where scaffolding would be necessary for each maintenance session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asus introduces a portable LED projector with a 4K display</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</guid><description>The PB287Q is a 28-inch monitor with 4K ultra high definition.
At CES last week, Asus, known for its consumer notebooks and motherboards, introduced new products designed for content creators and mobile professionals seeking enhanced performance and affordability. The company emphasized delivering bigger, better, and faster solutions. Among their offerings is the PB287Q, a 28-inch display with 4K ultra high definition (UHD) resolution. This slim-profile monitor features a full range of adjustments including swivel, tilt, pivot, and height, along with Splendid Plus video intelligence technology for optimal viewing comfort...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asus-introduces-a-portable-led-projector-with-a-4k-display/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new smartphones and audio-visual solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications (Sony Mobile) has introduced new consumer experiences centered around innovation.
“Xperia Touch represents a groundbreaking interface,&amp;quot; stated Hiroki Totoki, President and CEO of Sony Mobile Communications. &amp;ldquo;A year after revealing our updated brand direction and vision for the future of communications, we are not only introducing the Xperia XZ Premium, packed with cutting-edge technologies to improve core smartphone features, but also creating entirely new interactive communication experiences with our Xperia Smart Products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>