<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Water on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/water/</link><description>Recent content in Water on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/water/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin.</description></item><item><title>Guests are invited by Jumeirah Dhevanafushi to discover the house reef</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-invited-by-jumeirah-dhevanafushi-to-discover-the-house-reef/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-invited-by-jumeirah-dhevanafushi-to-discover-the-house-reef/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. Underwater view of a reef.
Jumeirah Dhevanafushi, a secluded resort at the southernmost point of the Maldives, has launched a new &amp;ldquo;Underwater Snorkeling Adventure&amp;rdquo; experience, allowing guests to explore the resort&amp;rsquo;s own reef.
This package provides a guided opportunity to discover some of the planet&amp;rsquo;s most impressive coral reefs. Led by Jumeirah Dhevanafushi&amp;rsquo;s resident marine biologist, guests can explore the reefs surrounding the heart-shaped Meradhoo island, situated on the Gaafu Alifu Atoll.</description></item><item><title>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental Hong Kong has become more environmentally friendly than ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</guid><description>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong is implementing environmentally friendly practices to offer guests sustainable luxury, including producing its own eco-friendly water and starting a rooftop garden.
The hotel is the first in Hong Kong to work with Nordaq FRESH, a Swedish company, to provide filtered and purified water in reusable glass bottles. This system reduces plastic waste and carbon emissions associated with traditional bottled water. Guests can also refill BPA-free bottles at the hotel.</description></item></channel></rss>