<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Users on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/users/</link><description>Recent content in Users on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/users/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Users of Forecaster and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>Have you ever encountered a problem where you vaguely recall a solution but can&amp;rsquo;t seem to locate the specific article or link? This happened to me recently with a client attempting to use their Dynamics GP user ID for Forecaster 7. As expected, it was unsuccessful due to GP&amp;rsquo;s encryption method when generating user IDs in SQL. This encryption prevents the same ID from functioning in Forecaster, even with proper database permissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who is it, what is it, forecaster?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-it-what-is-it-forecaster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-it-what-is-it-forecaster/</guid><description>To help new Forecaster users understand its intricacies, let&amp;rsquo;s break down the relationships between Forecaster, its users, data sources, and FRx.
The Forecaster database, created after installation using the Forecaster Database Creation Wizard, stores all the relevant data. During creation, a database owner is assigned, who can then manage periods within the Forecaster application itself.
Users can interact with Forecaster through either the web interface or the client application. While both offer data access, input, and reporting functionalities, the client application provides additional features for administrators...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-it-what-is-it-forecaster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-it-what-is-it-forecaster/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>