<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Malaysia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/malaysia/</link><description>Recent content in Malaysia on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 10:05:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/malaysia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Entrepreneurs in South Malaysia are receiving support from BAHTERA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-in-south-malaysia-are-receiving-support-from-bahtera/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 10:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-in-south-malaysia-are-receiving-support-from-bahtera/</guid><description>The Malaysian Ministry of Finance (MoF) has revealed that the upcoming BAHTERA series will be held on October 14th and 15th at the PERSADA Convention Centre in Johor Bahru.
BAHTERA aligns with the Malaysian government&amp;rsquo;s 11th Malaysia Plan to strengthen the Bumiputera economy. The event aims to equip Bumiputera entrepreneurs with valuable business insights, effective branding techniques, and relevant technology. This year, BAHTERA anticipates over 6,000 attendees.
Themed Bumipreneurs of Tomorrow, BAHTERA (Southern Edition) is tailored for entrepreneurs and Bumiputera businesses in Southern Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement was initiated in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: GEM Facebook page.
The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) launched officially in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia today. This non-governmental organization (NGO) aims to create a platform for entrepreneurs from various sectors like social entrepreneurship, technology, and halal to connect.
“This NGO brings together community leaders from different networks who will cultivate strong partnerships for Malaysia and our entrepreneurs,&amp;quot; shared YBhg. Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah, GEM patron and Secretary General Treasury, Ministry of Finance.</description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement provides a platform for new entrepreneurs to thrive on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) has been chosen to develop, curate content for, and design the strategy of the Global Entrepreneurship Community (GECommunity) for 2016. The soft launch of this initiative took place at the World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF) in Jakarta, Indonesia. The Finance Ministry, through the National Entrepreneurs Development Office (NEDO) and the Malaysian Global Innovation and Creativity Centre (MaGIC), is hosting GECommunity 2016.
GECommunity aims to establish Malaysia as a global hub for connectivity and innovation.</description></item><item><title>The best beauty products chosen by Shopee Malaysia for the month of July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</guid><description>Shopee, a Southeast Asia-focused mobile marketplace designed for simple and secure online buying and selling, monitors top-selling items across various categories. Here are some of the best-selling beauty products on Shopee Malaysia during July:
Source: Shopee Malaysia portal. Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream.
Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream
According to its Shopee description, this cream is enriched with natural organic herbs to provide an immediate whitening effect that can last up to 12 hours.</description></item><item><title>Bank Simpanan Nasional has launched virtual teller machines in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Bank Simpanan Nasional (BSN) is the first bank in Malaysia to introduce virtual teller machines (VTMs). These machines allow bank tellers to assist customers in different locations throughout Malaysia remotely, through a live virtual banking system.
BSN&amp;rsquo;s adoption of VTMs was inspired by kiosk banking already in place in other countries, including those in Europe, China, Canada, and the US. The project is a collaboration between BSN and Vastcomp to develop a specialized system.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces three new exclusive routes with a 20% discount on all flights until February 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</guid><description>AirAsia is the sole airline offering flights for three new routes: Johor Bahru to Tawau, Singapore to Kota Bharu, and Singapore to Terengganu. The airline is currently promoting these routes with fares as low as RM69* for travel between Johor Bahru and Tawau. This offer is valid for bookings made before February 16th, 2014, for travel dates between April 18th, 2014 and January 31st, 2015.
Welcome banners at Changi Airport</description></item><item><title>Uber Malaysia users now have the option to request a driver who speaks Mandarin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia.
Uber Malaysia is introducing UberMANDARIN, a new service in Johor Bahru, Kota Kinabalu, and Penang that connects riders with Mandarin-speaking UberX drivers.
According to Warren Tseng, GM of Uber Malaysia and Singapore, the Ministry of Tourism and Culture projects a significant increase in Chinese tourists, from 3 million this year to potentially 8 million by 2020. UberMANDARIN aims to support the government&amp;rsquo;s tourism initiatives by offering Mandarin-speaking visitors a more comfortable and convenient experience, aligning with Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s renowned hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Purchase online and make your payment at a nearby convenience store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</guid><description>MOLPay, a Southeast Asian online payment provider, is partnering with 7-Eleven Malaysia to introduce a new e-commerce payment method.
This service, called MOLPay CASH, will launch first in select Klang Valley 7-Eleven stores, with 735 stores currently offering this option and plans for further expansion. By July 2014, all 1,569 Malaysian stores will provide this service.
MOLPay CASH allows merchants to accept cash payments from customers at their nearest 7-Eleven. After an online purchase, a barcode is generated for the customer to use for payment at a 7-Eleven location.</description></item><item><title>Global marketing summit for Malaysian entrepreneurs hosted by INSKEN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-marketing-summit-for-malaysian-entrepreneurs-hosted-by-insken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-marketing-summit-for-malaysian-entrepreneurs-hosted-by-insken/</guid><description>Source: INSKEN. Firdaus delivered
welcome remarks at GMS 2018.
Now in its second year, the Institut Keusahawanan Negara&amp;rsquo;s (INSKEN) annual Global Marketing Summit (GMS) seeks to cultivate innovative leaders within the Malaysian entrepreneurial landscape.
Malaysian Minister Datuk Seri Mohd Redzuan Yusof highlighted the ongoing emphasis on fostering the expansion of entrepreneurs and small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), particularly those in the B40 and M40 income brackets. He stated that the Ministry of Entrepreneur Development (MED) will leverage allocated funds to execute a targeted and comprehensive entrepreneur development strategy in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region.</description></item><item><title>Avis inaugurates a new branch in Malacca, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:31:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</guid><description>Avis Car Rental has expanded its presence in Malaysia by opening its eighth branch at the Holiday Inn Melaka on Jalan Syed Abdul Aziz, Malacca.
The new location offers a range of recent car models, including the economical Toyota Passo, the compact Honda City, the full-size Toyota Camry, and the Nissan X-Trail SUV. In addition to vehicles, Avis provides renters with options for GPS navigation, child safety seats, and fuel services.</description></item><item><title>The goal of the Digestive Health Malaysia Society is to increase awareness of the importance of maintaining a healthy gut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-digestive-health-malaysia-society-is-to-increase-awareness-of-the-importance-of-maintaining-a-healthy-gut/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-digestive-health-malaysia-society-is-to-increase-awareness-of-the-importance-of-maintaining-a-healthy-gut/</guid><description>The Malaysian Ministry of Health&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Health Facts report reveals that digestive diseases are the fifth leading cause of hospital deaths in Malaysia, prompting the establishment of the Digestive Health Malaysia Society.
Dato&amp;rsquo; Dr Muhammad Radzi, Chairman of the Digestive Health Malaysia Society, highlighted that while colon cancer is widely recognized, awareness of other digestive diseases like irritable bowel syndrome, diverticulitis, gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD), and Crohn&amp;rsquo;s disease remains low. These conditions are often chronic and challenging to diagnose and manage.</description></item><item><title>Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (IBFC) is initiating roadshows across the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-international-business-and-financial-centre-ibfc-is-initiating-roadshows-across-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 15:46:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-international-business-and-financial-centre-ibfc-is-initiating-roadshows-across-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Labuan IBFC, a prominent international business and financial hub in the Asia Pacific region, has initiated a series of roadshows throughout ASEAN.
The 2016 Labuan IBFC ASEAN Roadshow will cover major ASEAN countries and, for the first time, will include both events and private briefings in the developing markets of Cambodia, Laos, Vietnam, and Myanmar. The roadshows, which began in Jakarta, Indonesia, will run until the end of July.
Danial Mah Abdullah, Chief Executive Officer of Labuan IBFC, stated, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s roadshow is unique in that we are focusing on regional businesses seeking to internationalize or expand regionally.</description></item><item><title>Western Union has extended its contract to provide its services at Hong Leong Bank branches in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Western Union, a company specializing in money transfers, has extended its partnership with Hong Leong Bank (HLBB) for another three years. This agreement allows Western Union to continue providing its services across all 283 HLBB branches in Malaysia.
Chew Mei Ling, Western Union&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, highlighted the increasing demand for both inbound and outbound remittances in the country. She emphasized that the renewed partnership with HLBB will support this growth by offering customers fast, reliable, and convenient money transfer services.</description></item><item><title>IdeaLab gives power to startups in ASEAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</guid><description>IdeaLab 2016, a focused two-day startup conference, will highlight ASEAN startup collaboration and the Malaysian startup scene. It also features the Malaysian Business Angels Network (MBAN) Summit, attracting investors globally. The organizers aim to bring together 500 top startups, investors, and corporations from the ASEAN ecosystem.
Attendees can participate in various stages. The Ideation Stage features industry leaders discussing critical issues faced by startups in ASEAN. At the IdeaPad Stage, the best ASEAN startups compete before a panel of judges.</description></item><item><title>Digi has teamed up with Telenor to provide its subscribers with a complimentary image storage service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</guid><description>Telenor, through Digi, has launched Capture, a free mobile app and cloud storage service for backing up images and videos.
Capture allows users to automatically save and back up photos and videos from their devices, safeguarding memories if their phone is lost or needs to be replaced. It also provides additional storage, especially useful for entry-level devices with limited capacity.
Non-Digi customers can download and utilize Capture with 2GB of free storage space.</description></item><item><title>The Adya Hotel Langkawi provides meeting rooms and a ballroom for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: Adya Hotel Langkawi website. Interior of a junior suite.
The four-star Adya Hotel Langkawi, situated in the Kuah town center on Langkawi Island in Malaysia, is marketed as a perfect starting point for exploring the natural wonders and rich culture of Langkawi, a designated UNESCO Global Geopark.
The hotel boasts 207 rooms and suites, each featuring a private bathroom with a bath and shower, along with a balcony that offers scenic views of the sea and town.</description></item><item><title>ProtectSecure Prime life plan is now available from AmMetLife Insurance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 08:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</guid><description>AmMetLife Insurance has introduced ProtectSecure Prime, a whole life insurance plan with guaranteed premiums starting as low as RM150 each month. The plan offers three premium payment term choices: 10 years, 20 years, or until age 60. After the chosen payment period, no further payments are needed to maintain the policy.
Source: AmMetLife website.
Furthermore, policyholders will receive an automatic 10% increase in their initial sum assured annually from the end of the first policy year until the end of the tenth year.</description></item><item><title>GwaKu offers tasty and budget-friendly dishes in the center of Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>Source: Gwaku&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This is their famous ayam percik.
GwaKu, a restaurant situated in Q Sentral close to KL Sentral, offers a rotating menu that keeps nearby office workers surprised about their lunch options. For example, one week could feature ayam perchik, while the following week might offer lamb stews.
Mike Ibrahim, the founder of GwaKu, emphasizes their commitment to using fresh, seasonal, and locally sourced ingredients. He explains, &amp;ldquo;By using in-season produce, we can ensure quality and freshness while also benefiting from lower prices.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese New Year promotion by Digi highlights the importance of family and tradition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</guid><description>Source: Digi website.
For many Chinese individuals, the Chinese New Year signifies the only opportunity to reconnect with distant family members. Malaysian telecommunications company Digi is capitalizing on this tradition with a new promotional campaign designed for a global audience.
Recognizing that in today&amp;rsquo;s world, many individuals simply use titles like &amp;lsquo;aunt,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;uncle,&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cousin&amp;rsquo; for relatives beyond their immediate family, Digi&amp;rsquo;s campaign encourages the use of more precise family titles within Chinese families.</description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020.</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Labuan is excited to welcome an increased number of financial services firms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-labuan-is-excited-to-welcome-an-increased-number-of-financial-services-firms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-labuan-is-excited-to-welcome-an-increased-number-of-financial-services-firms/</guid><description>The Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC) has continued to attract financial services companies globally in 2020. Over 800 licensed entities currently operate in this midshore jurisdiction due to a more than 50% increase in licensing application approvals in the first half of the year.
Offshore jurisdictions typically provide advantageous tax rates and other benefits that onshore jurisdictions may not. Midshore jurisdictions like Labuan IBFC provide a balance between client confidentiality, compliance with international standards and best practices, a business-friendly environment, a straightforward and attractive tax system, and a strong, modern, and internationally recognized legal framework enforced by its regulator, Labuan Financial Services Authority (Labuan FSA).</description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>KLGCC will be hosting a dinner buffet during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Last year&amp;rsquo;s Ramadan dinner buffet at the Kuala Lumpur Golf and Country Club (KLGCC) was very successful. The culinary team is bringing it back this year with a Selera Nostalgia theme.
The Selera Nostalgia buffet will feature dishes from over 100 cuisines. It will be set up in an open-air, stall-style setting by the pool and will include live cooking and performances. Some menu highlights, prepared by approximately 60 chefs, include nasi Arab, tom yam nelayan, kambing panggang, various pizzas and pastas, and local favorites.</description></item><item><title>GuocoLand will be responsible for overseeing the management of both Sofitel Singapore City Centre and Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Tanjong Pagar
Centre.
GuocoLand will oversee the operation of two new AccorHotels establishments: the Sofitel Singapore City Centre at Tanjong Pagar Centre in Singapore and the Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara in Damansara City, Kuala Lumpur. These additions contribute a total of 534 rooms to AccorHotel’s luxury brand.
Raymond Choong, President and CEO of GuocoLand Group, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership with AccorHotels, highlighting the shared vision for creating modern, convenient spaces within bustling business districts.</description></item><item><title>Hong Leong Group has decided to establish its global headquarters at Damansara City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</guid><description>Source: Damansara City website.
GuocoLand Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s key project, Damansara City, will soon house the Hong Leong Group&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters. The 33-story, top-tier office building, situated on the southwest side of this notable development, will be a major tenant within Damansara City when fully occupied by the second quarter of next year.
The Hong Leong Group is a prominent Malaysian conglomerate with interests in banking, financial services, manufacturing, distribution, property development, investment, hospitality, leisure, and principal investment.</description></item><item><title>The second edition of Food and Hotel Penang is back!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</guid><description>Source: FHP 2016 website.
The second Food and Hotel Penang (FHP 2016) event is poised to solidify its standing as the premier trade-only platform in Northern Malaysia. This event will host a curated buyer program, offering access to key figures in the food and hospitality sectors within Penang and nearby northern states like Kedah, Perak, and Perlis.
Supported by the Penang state government and the Malaysian Association of Hotels, FHP aims to build upon the achievements of its 2014 edition, which saw participation from 240 companies spanning 30 countries.</description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC places a strong emphasis on ensuring compliance and transparency in all business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 11:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</guid><description>Following the release of the Panama Papers, the Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC) has reaffirmed its commitment to facilitating cross-border trade and investment, especially within the ASEAN region. The organization emphasizes its dedication to maintaining strict transparency and regulatory standards for all business activities conducted within the centre.
In a statement, the organization highlighted its continuous efforts to strengthen its regulatory framework and supervisory system. These efforts aim to meet international standards and practices related to transparency and regulatory compliance.</description></item><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news.</description></item><item><title>Celcom users now have the option to subscribe to iflix</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</guid><description>iflix, a Southeast Asian internet TV provider, has teamed up with Malaysian mobile network operator Celcom Axiata to offer TV series, movies, and other content to Celcom&amp;rsquo;s over 12 million subscribers in Malaysia.
Starting March 15, 2016, all Celcom subscribers will get two free months of iflix, allowing them to stream content seamlessly on Celcom&amp;rsquo;s 4G network (a value of RM20). After the two-month promotional period, customers can continue enjoying iflix for a discounted rate of RM9 per month.</description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 has been met with an enthusiastic and positive reception</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</guid><description>Source: 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. The 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, was officially opened by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah.
Source: _1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. _Pictured from left to right (back row): Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah, Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, alongside Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Bin Abdullah, Secretary General of Treasury, Malaysia. They are joined by 10 children, each representing a different ASEAN nation.</description></item><item><title>Digi introduces 4G LTE service in Johor Bahru, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Pictured at the launch of Digi&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE service in Johor Bahru are (from left): Tuan Haji Rizal B. Abd Malek, Regional Head of the Malaysian Communications and Multimedia Commission (SKMM) Southern Region; Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer; YB Datuk Ir Haji Hasni B Haji Mohammad, Chairman of the Johor Executive Council for Public Works, Rural and Regional Development; Digi’s Chief Network Officer Kesavan Sivabalan; and Ng Chak Khin, Digi’s Head of Southern Region.</description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces Malaysia's tonton to its CAST app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</guid><description>Singtel has added Media Prima&amp;rsquo;s tonton, a popular Malaysian streaming platform, to its CAST video streaming app. This partnership, along with existing offerings on Singtel TV, makes Singtel a leading provider of Malay entertainment content in Singapore.
This is the first time tonton is available outside of Malaysia. Through CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus pack, subscribers will have access to over 23,000 hours of Malay entertainment, including content from TV3, TV9, and tonton originals.</description></item><item><title>Xpress Money introduces a daily raffle for customers sending money in 11 countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</guid><description>Xpress Money, a money transfer company, has introduced a 49-day promotion called &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday.&amp;rdquo; This program is open to customers sending money from Malaysia and ten other countries, including several in the Middle East.
Source: Xpress Money website.
The World Bank reported that in 2012, individuals sent $2.3 billion from Malaysia to other countries. Xpress Money anticipates a 15% increase in money transfers during Ramadan. Sudhesh Giriyan, Xpress Money&amp;rsquo;s Vice President and Business Head, stated that the &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday&amp;rdquo; program is a gesture of goodwill towards customers during Ramadan.</description></item><item><title>Experience the enchanting Arabian nights under the stars at the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar until July 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</guid><description>From June 21st to July 16th, 2015, the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar is excited to present a delectable Ramadhan buffet. The culinary team at LINK All Day Dining has crafted a special &amp;ldquo;Starry Arabian Nights&amp;rdquo; themed dinner, featuring a wide selection of traditional Arab and Malay dishes. The restaurant will be adorned with exotic, Arabian-inspired starry lights, and live ‘ghazal’ performances will entertain guests throughout their meal.
Source: Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar.</description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5.</description></item><item><title>This year, come to DiverseCity in KL to experience a diverse range of performing and visual arts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</guid><description>DiverseCity 2016, also known as the Kuala Lumpur International Arts Festival, ran from August 31st to October 2nd, 2016. The festival showcased a diverse range of artistic expressions, including visual arts, crafts, music, dance, and literature at various locations around Klang Valley in Malaysia. Many events were free to attend.
Taking place annually for five weeks at multiple venues in and around Kuala Lumpur, DiverseCity highlights the rich cultural tapestry of Malaysia and explores the country&amp;rsquo;s close relationship with the ASEAN community.</description></item><item><title>Bangi Golf Resort reintroduces the beloved Buffet Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: BGR.
From June 21st to July 15th, 2015, Bangi Golf Resort Restaurant (BGR) will be offering its special Buffet Ramadhan in honor of the holy month.
Executive Chef Kamaruddin highlights the Buffet Ramadhan&amp;rsquo;s popularity, stating that it has always been a top pick for gatherings of family, friends, and colleagues during Ramadhan. He emphasizes the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a diverse menu with new offerings while upholding the quality and authentic flavors of classic dishes.</description></item><item><title>Signature Market offers Chinese New Year corporate gifts for Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signature-market-offers-chinese-new-year-corporate-gifts-for-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 01:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signature-market-offers-chinese-new-year-corporate-gifts-for-malaysia/</guid><description>Signature Market is offering corporate gift bundles for the Lunar New Year, starting from RM30, with a focus on wellness.
The &amp;ldquo;Chinese New Year 2023 Collection&amp;rdquo; features festive packaging adorned with lucky symbols like the number eight, pistachio nuts, mandarin oranges, and spring flowers. Special edition sets come in an exclusive festive box sleeve. Signature Market can advise companies on creating gift packages and offers bulk discounts. They provide over 700 product options and custom packaging solutions.</description></item><item><title>Three new routes have been announced by Air Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</guid><description>AirAsia is expanding its network in Indonesia and the Philippines with three new routes starting on March 27th. The airline will now offer flights from Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia to Pontianak, Indonesia, from Johor Bahru, Malaysia to Medan, Indonesia, and from Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia to Cebu, Philippines.
The Indonesian routes will operate twice a week, while the Kota Kinabalu to Cebu route, operated by AirAsia Zest, will operate four times a week.</description></item><item><title>Malaysia to identify energy-efficient government buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</guid><description>Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Energy Commission, under the Ministry of Energy, Science, Technology, Environment and Climate Change (MESTECC), has introduced the National Building Energy Intensity (BEI) Labelling for Government Buildings.
This program strives to enhance energy efficiency in government-owned buildings within Malaysia, encouraging building owners to prioritize and improve energy conservation. Buildings are assigned a star rating based on their energy efficiency, with a five-star rating indicating the highest level of efficiency.
The initial phase, concluding in late 2018, encompasses 100 buildings belonging to ministries, departments, and agencies under MESTECC and the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Department.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>40% of employees in Malaysia are willing to change jobs if they do not receive a bonus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-employees-in-malaysia-are-willing-to-change-jobs-if-they-do-not-receive-a-bonus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 05:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-employees-in-malaysia-are-willing-to-change-jobs-if-they-do-not-receive-a-bonus/</guid><description>Randstad, a global staffing and HR services firm, recently conducted its second annual Bonus Expectations survey in Malaysia. The purpose of this survey was to gain insights into employee perspectives on year-end bonuses and how they influence their commitment to their employers. This year&amp;rsquo;s survey also included, for the first time, feedback from companies on their bonus plans to determine if employer and employee expectations are aligned.
The survey revealed that while 98% of employees believe receiving a bonus is important for their engagement, 59% stated that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only reason they would consider a job change.</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Canopy Power is making Southeast Asia more environmentally friendly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</guid><description>Source: Canopy Power. This image shows solar panels installed on the roof of a beachfront pavilion at Batu Batu resort. This installation was part of a larger project by Canopy Power.
Despite the economic downturn of 2020, Canopy Power has announced several accomplishments within the Asia Pacific region.
One such accomplishment was the completion of a renewable energy microgrid in the third quarter of 2020. This microgrid, located on Batu Batu, a sustainable island resort 16 km from Mersing, Malaysia, will allow the 22-villa resort to decrease its reliance on diesel and lower carbon emissions.</description></item><item><title>The Pi1M Training Programme offered by Digi provides benefits to small business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pi1m-training-programme-offered-by-digi-provides-benefits-to-small-business-owners/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Participants of the Pi1M Training Programme gathered for a group photo.
Digi Telecommunications recently conducted a training program for community members residing near the company-managed Pusat Internet 1 Malaysia (Pi1M) centers. This tailored program reflects Digi&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering online entrepreneurship within its Pi1M communities. Currently, Digi manages 34 Pi1Ms across Pahang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Johor, Melaka, and Sarawak, with plans to establish 70 more centers by year&amp;rsquo;s end.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces new flights between Penang and Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</guid><description>AirAsia has launched direct flights connecting Penang to Yangon, Myanmar, making it the airline&amp;rsquo;s seventh international destination accessible from its northern hub. Penang also offers direct flights to other international destinations, such as Ho Chi Minh City, Singapore, Medan, Jakarta, Surabaya, and Bangkok.
This new route will operate three times a week, starting on March 22, 2016. The flight schedule for Penang, Malaysia (PEN) – Yangon, Myanmar (RGN) is as follows:</description></item><item><title>Foh San provides mooncake corporate orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</guid><description>Foh San, a restaurant originally known for its dim sum, has become a popular provider of both dim sum and mooncakes. They offer a diverse selection of halal mooncakes, with both baked and non-baked options available. Customers can purchase these mooncakes in elegant presentation boxes designed to hold either two or four mooncakes. Additionally, there is a premium box option which includes four mooncakes and a special gaharu (agarwood or oud) tea.</description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay.</description></item><item><title>Singtel customers enjoy the top roaming experience in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Opensignal. 4G download speed experience in Mbps for Singapore roamers in Malaysia compared to the experience for Malaysian mobile users.
A 2019 Opensignal study on Singaporean 4G users roaming in Malaysia revealed that Singtel subscribers had the best download speeds, upload speeds, and latency.
M1 and StarHub users experienced comparable download and upload speeds while in Malaysia. However, StarHub users enjoyed better latency compared to M1. Although both StarHub and M1 users faced significantly slower latency than Malaysian domestic users, indicating a poorer experience, Singtel users only lagged behind domestic Maxis users by 2.</description></item><item><title>The fourth bootcamp for 1Malaysia Entrepreneurs has begun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-bootcamp-for-1malaysia-entrepreneurs-has-begun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 15:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-bootcamp-for-1malaysia-entrepreneurs-has-begun/</guid><description>Source: 1MET. Over 500 participants attended the 1MET bootcamps in Kota Kinabalu.
The 1Malaysia Entrepreneur (1MET) program, an initiative of the National Entrepreneurship Development Office (NEDO) within the Malaysian Ministry of Finance, has initiated its fourth round of two-day entrepreneurial bootcamps. Utilizing an experiential model, these bootcamps offer a six-month mentoring and coaching opportunity for 500 chosen business concepts. The first group to benefit from this follow-up program commenced in August 2016.</description></item><item><title>Preorders for GoPro HERO5 cameras and Karma drones are now available at Shopee Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorders-for-gopro-hero5-cameras-and-karma-drones-are-now-available-at-shopee-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorders-for-gopro-hero5-cameras-and-karma-drones-are-now-available-at-shopee-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a popular online marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is now offering preorders for the new GoPro HERO5 cameras.
Source: GoPro. The HERO5 series.
GoPro&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO, Nicholas Woodman, introduced the HERO5 on September 19th, alongside a cloud-based software platform and the Karma drone.
Woodman emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to easy storytelling: &amp;ldquo;With these new products, we&amp;rsquo;re making it simpler to capture and share compelling stories. HERO5&amp;rsquo;s automatic photo and video uploads to GoPro Plus streamline the entire process of editing, sharing, and enjoying your experiences on the go.</description></item><item><title>Digi is sponsoring customers to participate in the Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</guid><description>Source: Digi Telecommunications.
Digi Telecommunications is sponsoring 200 customers to join the WWF-Malaysia Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk in Penang and Sunway Pyramid. This event coincides with the Earth Hour 2015 celebration on March 28, 2015.
As the Night Walk@Sunway&amp;rsquo;s corporate sponsor, Digi has donated RM35,000 to support WWF-Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s environmental conservation efforts.
Digi is sponsoring 200 walk packs, costing RM60 each, for its customers. 100 packs are designated for Night Walk@Sunway and 100 for Night Walk@Penang.</description></item><item><title>Firefly is back in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firefly-is-back-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firefly-is-back-in-singapore/</guid><description>Firefly Airlines has resumed flights between Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport in Subang, Malaysia, and Seletar Airport in Singapore.
Source: Firefly. Firefly reinstates Malaysia-Singapore route.
Firefly&amp;rsquo;s first flight on this route to Seletar took place in April 2019, but flights were put on hold in March 2020 due to the pandemic. Now, the airline will offer two flights every day between Kuala Lumpur and Singapore, operating out of Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport and Seletar Airport.</description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>In May 2015, Digi prepaid customers have the chance to win smartphones, tablets, and cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Thrane.
Digi Telecommunication (Digi) is celebrating its 20th anniversary by giving back to its prepaid customers. Throughout May, Digi will be offering prizes like smartphones, tablets, and even cars.
From May 1st to May 31st, customers who top-up their prepaid credit are eligible to win prizes. Every day, 20 smartphones will be given away, with 200 tablets awarded weekly. Two lucky winners will even drive home a Ford Ranger.</description></item><item><title>Direct your attention to the ASEAN approach: Prime Minister of Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 06:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
During his opening speech at the 27th ASEAN Summit and other related meetings in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysian Prime Minister Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Mohd Najib Tun Abdul Razak urged members to embrace the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN way.&amp;rdquo;
He emphasized the importance of prioritizing community and collaborative solutions over individual pursuits and self-serving goals. This approach, he stated, favors non-violent resolutions, moderation over extreme viewpoints, and respect for all, including adversaries. He stressed that true strength lies in pursuing peace and building bridges instead of fueling conflicts.</description></item><item><title>80% of Singaporeans living abroad are interested in returning to work in their home country</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 07:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</guid><description>A new report from Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, suggests that competition for skilled workers in Singapore will increase in 2016. This demand will likely lead to more attempts to recruit Singaporeans working abroad. Hiring managers believe that these experienced professionals could help alleviate the tight labor market, benefiting both companies and the &amp;ldquo;Fair Consideration Framework,&amp;rdquo; which promotes local hiring.
Returning Singaporeans are desirable candidates because they often have international experience and a broader range of skills compared to their counterparts who haven&amp;rsquo;t worked overseas.</description></item><item><title>The initial business transformation program in Malaysia has achieved notable success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</guid><description>UOB Malaysia and The FinLab have reported that the small- and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) participating in the _Jom Transform Programme_1 could experience productivity gains of up to 30% through digitalization.
Jom Transform is the first program in Malaysia dedicated to helping local businesses digitize their operations, aiming to increase productivity and revenue growth.
Over the three-month program, the 16 participating SMEs acquired digital transformation expertise in areas such as business re-engineering and digital marketing.</description></item><item><title>AppShack is a reality show that connects investors with startups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appshack-is-a-reality-show-that-connects-investors-with-startups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 03:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appshack-is-a-reality-show-that-connects-investors-with-startups/</guid><description>Source: AppShack. The official launch was officiated by Bhg. Dato’ Jailani Johari, Deputy Minister of Communications and Multimedia Malaysia.
AppShack, a Malaysian company that connects startups with organizations seeking mobile application innovation, has officially launched.
This platform supports startups in developing their ideas by providing mentorship, technical expertise, business structure assistance, legal advice, and financial funding opportunities. Successful applicants can connect with investors and partners, including consortiums, venture capitalists, and bankers.</description></item><item><title>BNM releases commemorative coins in honor of RTM's 70th anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bnm-releases-commemorative-coins-in-honor-of-rtm-s-70th-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 20:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bnm-releases-commemorative-coins-in-honor-of-rtm-s-70th-anniversary/</guid><description>Source: BNM. Detail of the silver commemorative coin.
The Central Bank of Malaysia has released special coins to mark the 70th anniversary of Radio Televisyen Malaysia (RTM). RTM, established on April 1, 1946, is Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s pioneer broadcaster, introducing radio in 1946 and television on December 28, 1963.
These commemorative coins are available in silver and Nordic gold. Nordic gold, a gold-free alloy, is composed of 89% copper, 5% zinc, 5% aluminum, and 1% tin.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Vuclip Global Video Insights reveals that Malaysian consumers are seeking uncomplicated entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Vuclip, a leading mobile video-on-demand (VOD) service in emerging markets, has published its Global Video Insights (GVI) 2015 Survey. The study examines video consumption trends and device preferences among Malaysian consumers.
Source: Vuclip. Prakash.
Malaysian consumers value several features in an over-the-top (OTT) content player. The most important are a seamless user interface (61%), uninterrupted viewing experience (58%), high-definition video quality (56%), and access to the newest videos (54%). Other desirable features include adjustable streaming quality (47%), video downloads (46%), and simultaneous multiple video downloads (45%).</description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service.</description></item><item><title>The Malaysia election, #GE14, generated more than 7.3 million tweets on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 22:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</guid><description>During the short Malaysian election campaign period, over 7.3 million tweets using the hashtags #GE14 and #MalaysiaElection established Twitter as a key platform for political discourse.
On May 9th, election day discussions dominated Twitter in Malaysia, exceeding all other topics. Over 4.2 million #GE14 tweets were sent globally in just 24 hours. The hashtag topped Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s trending list, joined by other politically charged terms like #MalaysiaMemilih and #PakatanHarapan in the top ten.</description></item><item><title>CIMB introduces a program to enhance the skills of non-executive employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</guid><description>CIMB Group, the second-largest financial services provider in Malaysia, has initiated a program to enhance the skills, productivity, career advancement prospects, and earning potential of its non-executive employees. This program, known as the CIMB Accelerated Career Enhancement Programme (CIMB ACE), was officially launched by Dato’ Sri Richard Riot Anak Jaem, the Minister of Human Resources.
The CIMB ACE program aligns with PR1ME (Program Majudiri 1Malaysia), a national initiative launched by the Prime Minister of Malaysia in November 2013.</description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt provides insights on Malaysia's perspective in the Total Compensation Measurement study</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</guid><description>Aon Hewitt, a global human resource consulting firm, has published their Total Compensation Measurement (TCM) 2015 Study. This comprehensive report analyzes compensation data from 25,000 positions in 180 countries.
Salary increase by industry sector in Malaysia
While the global GDP is projected to grow from 3.1% in 2015 to 3.6% in 2016, regional economic conditions play a vital role in employee compensation decisions. In Southeast Asia, the Philippines and Vietnam led in 2015 with 6% and 6.</description></item><item><title>Spotify creates playlists for foggy weather</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 18:01:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has curated a playlist specifically for the hazy conditions currently affecting Singapore and Malaysia. You can listen to the playlist below.
Interested in learning more?
Stay informed about the hourly air quality readings in Singapore.
Read this WorkSmart Asia blog article about Spotify&amp;rsquo;s mobile-first approach.
Hashtag: #SGHaze</description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia and Pos Malaysia are working together for order fulfillment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</guid><description>Shopee Malaysia has partnered with Pos Malaysia, the national courier service, to offer free shipping to all sellers on its platform.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace with a strong regional presence of over 12 million users, operates as a free online customer-to-customer (C2C) platform. Launched in December 2015, Shopee aims to empower both individual and business entrepreneurs to conduct secure buying and selling transactions on their mobile devices. In Malaysia alone, Shopee&amp;rsquo;s app has been downloaded over a million times within a six-month timeframe.</description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey.</description></item><item><title>Uber has expanded its services to Seremban, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 08:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Uber. UberX is arriving in Seremban in December
Uber is expanding its services to Seremban, the eighth city in Malaysia to have Uber. Starting December 1, 2016, residents of Seremban can hail a ride via the UberX service. This launch comes after the successful introduction of UberX in Melaka on October 27, 2016.
Uber also presents earning opportunities for driver-partners using their own vehicles. Drivers have the flexibility to set their own schedules and determine their earnings.</description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities.</description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks.</description></item><item><title>Sunway's Resort Cafe provides a range of dining options from breakfast to dinner, perfect for business meetings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</guid><description>Source: Sunway.
The recently opened Resort Cafe, situated on the lobby level of the luxurious Sunway Resort Hotel and Spa, accommodates 362 guests and showcases the diverse culinary heritage of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Malay, Chinese, and Indian populations.
Spanning 17,588 square feet, the restaurant presents eight distinct culinary themes: the impressive Monumental Fruit and Salad Towers, Malay Archipelago (featuring dishes from Malaysia, Singapore, and Indonesia), Indo-Chine (showcasing cuisine from Thailand and Vietnam), Oriental Far East (highlighting dishes from Japan, Korea, and China), Spices of India, Mirage of the Gulf (offering dishes from the Middle East), Best from the West (featuring Western comfort food, grills, rotisserie, and churrasco), and a dedicated dessert section.</description></item><item><title>The KL Journal provides a unique boutique option for accommodations in Kuala Lumpur, as an alternative to traditional hotel chains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 01:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</guid><description>Source: The KL Journal. This hotel blends industrial design, diverse local touches, and vintage pieces to create a stylishly modern yet retro atmosphere.
Located near Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s primary shopping and entertainment area, the Kuala Lumpur Journal (KL Journal) is a boutique hotel designed for the modern traveler seeking an alternative to large chains. It offers all the necessary modern amenities while retaining a unique sense of style and personality.</description></item><item><title>Viu, a service provided by Vuclip, delivers an average of 20 videos per month to viewers in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:44:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Vuclip, a PCCW Media company, has released key engagement data for its OTT service, Viu, based on an analysis of app and desktop viewership.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOh1EZVWoEhfM9h_KB5E2oDQtVX9NIYnObrOM6oWpK6xB_fWBVmqMwQv5MQtoq5jTe338bKg_10JMMP4wDeSWDCbwHwC8jKXx1VMXkYHCYTrGVSsm8QO-dG0eKaUelNE4fQSA8esO5InKk/s1600/image.png)
Source: Viu Malaysia website.
In the two months since its launch in Malaysia, Viu has seen average user engagement of 20 videos per month. Peak viewing times are after work hours, with Wednesday to Sunday being the most popular days.
Korean dramas, Bollywood films, and Malaysian TV series rank among the top ten most-watched content, highlighting the strong demand for Asian entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*.</description></item><item><title>Discover more about Malaysia's demographics by reading a book on the population of Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: ISEAS website.
The second edition of The Population of Malaysia, authored by Saw Swee-Hock, former Professor of Statistics at the National University of Singapore and Chairman of the National Statistical Commission of Singapore from 1971 to 1975, has been released.
This updated analysis of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s diverse population offers valuable insights for businesses interested in the Malaysian market. Dr. Saw leverages his extensive knowledge of the country, gained through his upbringing, teaching experience at the University of Malaya, and involvement in population census planning, to provide unique perspectives.</description></item><item><title>UMW Toyota Motor has expanded its Special Service Campaign to include almost 30,000 cars in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:57:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Toyota Motor Corporation (TMC) issued global recalls related to airbag inflators in some vehicle models on April 11, 2013, and May 13, 2015, and expanded the recall on June 25, 2015.
Responding to this, UMW Toyota Motor is expanding its Special Service Campaign in Malaysia. UMW Toyota Motor has confirmed with TMC that this campaign affects 29,985 Toyota Vios, Corolla Altis, and Yaris models manufactured between April 2007, and December 2008.</description></item><item><title>The Great Women Connect Series begins with Great Women Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Great Women Malaysia. Puan Nadira Yusoff.
The Great Women Connect Series debuted today in Malaysia. This new program seeks to provide a space for women in business worldwide to connect and exchange ideas and experiences related to trade. It also aims to foster international partnerships, helping women, especially those in Malaysia, build networks and realize their full potential.
Great Women Malaysia (GMW) is an initiative that strives to empower Malaysian women, particularly those in underserved and rural areas.</description></item><item><title>Crowdonomic is now a registered e-facility for equity crowdfunding in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 14:03:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Crowdonomic. Crowdonomic was one of just a few operators approved as a Registered Electronic Facility (Equity Crowdfunding Platform) by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Securities Commission. From left: Nicola Castelnuovo, Co-founder and Chief Commercial Officer of Crowdonomic; Datuk Ranjit Ajit Singh, Chairman, Securities Commission Malaysia and Leo Shimada, Co-Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Crowdonomic.
Crowdonomic, a leading crowdfunding platform in Southeast Asia, was designated as a registered electronic facility by the Securities Commission Malaysia (SC).</description></item><item><title>InPost has officially started its operations in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: InPost.
InPost, a global leader in automated parcel locker networks, has expanded its services to Malaysia. The launch was accompanied by a roadshow, themed &amp;ldquo;Malaysia E-commerce Day (MED) 2015,&amp;rdquo; aimed at raising awareness about the latest advancements in e-commerce, e-payments, and logistics.
According to InPost Malaysia Managing Director Rosland Mohd Jannes, the initiative seeks to connect with businesses and individuals, boosting consumer confidence in online shopping and alleviating delivery-related anxieties.</description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan.</description></item></channel></rss>