<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MICE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mice/</link><description>Recent content in MICE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The launch of Fairfield by Marriott Belitung has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its Fairfield by Marriott brand with the opening of a new hotel in Belitung, Indonesia.
Source: Fairfield by Marriott Belitung website. The Fairfield by Marriott Belitung.
Mike Fulkerson, Vice President of Brand &amp;amp; Marketing for Marriott International Asia Pacific, stated that Fairfield by Marriott is experiencing rapid growth in the region, with 47 properties in development in Asia Pacific and over 400 globally. He highlighted the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing a relaxing and dependable experience at a good value, enhanced by Indonesian hospitality, making the Belitung location an ideal retreat for travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Azerai offers affordable luxury in Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Azerai invites discerning travelers to experience attainable luxury in Vietnam through a collection of acclaimed boutique resorts. Founded by Adrian Zecha, the visionary behind Aman Resorts, the Azerai concept is already present in the culturally rich destinations of Ke Ga, Can Tho, and Hue.
Source: Azerai. Each Azerai resort is designed to envelop guests in sophisticated, understated luxury.
Every Azerai resort aims to immerse guests in refined yet understated luxury. At Azerai Can Tho, this translates to seclusion within low-rise structures on a private islet in the Hau River, reachable only by boat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Vines Resort &amp; Country Club introduces a new garden venue for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</guid><description>Source: The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club. The Pavilion.
The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club, located near Perth, Australia, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Pavilion.&amp;rdquo; This new event space is a specially designed garden structure situated at the front of the resort, offering scenic views of the golf course and surrounding gardens. It&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for events such as conference gatherings or product launches.
The open-air venue, capable of hosting 100 guests, has three sides open to the elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Country Holidays is introducing new Signature Departures for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Luxury travel agency Country Holidays has launched new &amp;ldquo;Signature Departures&amp;rdquo; trips for discerning travelers based in Singapore. Established in 2011, Signature Departures offers a fresh approach to group travel, steering clear of crowded buses, generic hotels, large-scale dining, and tourist traps.
Theng Hwee Chang, Managing Director of Country Holidays, explains: &amp;ldquo;We created Signature Departures four years ago to address the increasing demand for more enriching group travel experiences that go beyond the ordinary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Choose from a variety of MICE packages available in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Three travel companies — Chōsen, The Slate, and Samujana — have designed productivity programs for businesses and workgroups. These programs offer a variety of environments to help teams achieve their best results.
For adventure junkies Source: Chosen website. A view of Bali.
Chōsen provides experiences tailored for teams that thrive on new adventures and challenges:
Activities include cliff jumping, canyoning, surfing, and cooking classes. Accommodation is available at their estate in Bali and other locations, including New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reserve a magical Disney experience aboard the Disney Adventure through Traveloka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</guid><description>Starting in the fourth quarter of 2024, travelers can book voyages with Disney Cruise Lines departing from Singapore through the Traveloka app, according to an announcement from the Southeast Asian travel platform. This addition to Traveloka&amp;rsquo;s offerings reinforces the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to showcasing the diverse experiences and attractions available in Singapore.
Launching in late 2025, the Disney Adventure will call Singapore its home port. The ship boasts seven themed areas with Disney-themed dining and exciting onboard activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor Plus is the latest paid loyalty program offered by Accor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</guid><description>Source: Accor.
Accor Advantage Plus, the paid loyalty program from Accor with more than 350,000 members in 17 countries, has been renamed and enhanced. Now known as Accor Plus, this 21-year-old program allows members to enjoy enhanced experiences at over 600 Accor properties in the Asia Pacific region. The company stated that members can benefit from substantial discounts on accommodations, dining at over 800 restaurants, and access to various VIP events and partner offers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Food tours are available in Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo through Eating Adventures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</guid><description>Source: Eating Adventures website.
Eating Adventures has expanded its food tour services to Hong Kong. The company, already established as the leading provider of food tours in Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo, China, aims to provide travelers with an authentic cultural and culinary experience by guiding them through local neighborhoods.
Wai Zhou, owner of Eating Adventures Food Tours, highlights that while Hong Kong has existing food tour operators, most are not run by locals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is the inaugural Hyatt hotel in the Jiangsu province</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</guid><description>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou has officially opened in Suzhou, a city renowned for its historic canals, stone bridges, and UNESCO-recognized classical gardens.
Source: Hyatt. The hotel boasts a 29-floor atrium, the tallest in Suzhou.
&amp;ldquo;The launch of Hyatt Regency Suzhou is a significant move for Hyatt as we expand our brand presence in China,&amp;rdquo; stated Christopher Koehler, Vice President of Operations for Hyatt in China. &amp;ldquo;We aim to create valuable connections among global business and leisure travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Gold Coast, Australia will be home to the first Hyde location outside of the US</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</guid><description>Accor is expanding its partnership with sbe beyond the US, selecting Australia as the first Asia Pacific location. Hyde, their luxury lifestyle brand known for its Los Angeles Sunset Strip inspiration, will debut Hyde Paradiso on the Gold Coast in March 2019. This venue promises an all-day experience, transforming into a sophisticated lounge and dining destination in the evening.
Simon McGrath, COO of Accor Pacific, highlights the partnership&amp;rsquo;s goal to deliver unique lifestyle experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests are now welcomed at The Murray, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Wharf Hotels. The Murray,
Hong Kong.
Wharf Hotels is pleased to announce the launch of The Murray, Hong Kong, a new Niccolo Hotel. This addition represents the group’s newest flagship Niccolo property and joins their luxury contemporary chic collection.
The Murray boasts a rich history, standing as one of eight historic landmarks protected by the Conserving Central initiative, launched by the Hong Kong government in 2013. Situated in the city’s vibrant Central district, the building has been recognized for its pioneering approach to sustainability throughout its nearly 50 years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ramada Abu Dhabi introduces Lebanese fine dining for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>The Ramada Abu Dhabi, a new hotel in the city&amp;rsquo;s central business district, is now home to Karamna Beirut, an upscale Lebanese dining experience. The restaurant is the brainchild of Tony Karam, a restaurateur whose family owns and operates the Karam restaurant chain.
Source: Ramada Abu Dhabi Hotel. The Karamna Beirut restaurant.
Rene Vincent, General Manager of the Ramada Abu Dhabi, highlights the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s impressive menu, curated to delight guests seeking refined Lebanese cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Special promotions for the Fireworks Celebration at the Mandarin Oriental, Macau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Macau has special Fireworks Celebration packages perfect for corporate events, team building, or client appreciation. These packages provide a unique opportunity to experience the 26th Macau International Fireworks Display Contest.
Source: Mandarin Oriental Macau website.
Available on September 8th, 13th, 20th, 27th, and October 1st, 2014, the package starts at MOP4,388 and includes:
Overnight accommodations in a room or suite with panoramic fireworks views through expansive windows. A special four-course fireworks-themed dinner for two at the Vida Rica Restaurant, showcasing Chef Dominique Bugnand’s modern take on classic French cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor plans to introduce the ibis Styles brand to Singapore later this year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</guid><description>Source: Accor. The ibis Style in the Macpherson area, Singapore, will be launched this year.
Accor plans to open an ibis Styles hotel in Singapore by the last quarter of 2015, introducing a trendy, lifestyle-focused brand to the country. Situated within the same complex as the MacPherson shopping mall, the hotel is conveniently located at the intersection of MacPherson and Aljunied Roads, a short 20-minute drive from the airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Today marks the grand opening of Singapore's most Instagram-worthy nightclub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</guid><description>MARQUEE Singapore, a massive new nightclub, is launching at Marina Bay Sands on April 12, 2019. The opening weekend will feature world-renowned DJs Tiësto and Afrojack, with a special appearance by American rapper A$AP Rocky.
The 8K screen serves as a backdrop for TAO&amp;rsquo;s
co-founders Tepperberg (left) and Strauss (right).
This marks the first expansion into Asia for MARQUEE, a brand with clubs in New York, Las Vegas, and Sydney. The Singapore location is also the 35th project for TAO Group, the nightlife and hospitality company partnering with Marina Bay Sands on this venture...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in September, Ulu Cliffhouse will be providing a clifftop beach club playground</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</guid><description>Source: Ulu Cliffhouse.
Opening in September 2017, Ulu Cliffhouse, a &amp;ldquo;clifftop playground&amp;rdquo; created by a group of artists, is ready to change what it means to be a beach club in Bali, Indonesia.
The 50,000 square foot clifftop retreat will provide a stylish area with a 25-meter infinity pool, an on-site spa, a boutique, private beach access, and a variety of food and beverage options, including a terraced restaurant and a cliffside bar, all with breathtaking panoramic views...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has reopened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has finished renovating all guest rooms, bathrooms, and suites, offering visitors a revitalized stay in the heart of the city.
Source: Holiday Inn website. The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders.
Every room was completely emptied to give the architect a fresh start in designing a space with the modern traveler&amp;rsquo;s needs in mind. Striking new interiors are highlighted by floor-to-ceiling windows, equipped with electronically controlled blackout blinds that can be adjusted from the bedside...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park in Bangkok provides a versatile indoor-outdoor option for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</guid><description>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park, Bangkok – Marriott Executive Apartments is a unique venue for gatherings in the Sukhumvit area. Combining indoor and outdoor elements, it offers a versatile space for 30 to 160 guests. High ceilings and comfortable furniture create a welcoming atmosphere.
This lounge seamlessly blends several design concepts, creating a space that is both modern and traditional, as well as casual and elegant. Featuring lawn and garden views, the Lounge covers over 400 square meters and can host a variety of events from meetings to cocktail receptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exciting pre-game activities at Shangri-La hotels before the Hong Kong Sevens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 03:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</guid><description>Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Shangri-La Group is offering rugby enthusiasts special hotel and experience packages for the Hong Kong Sevens. Fans can choose to stay at the Island Shangri-La, Kowloon Shangri-La, or Kerry Hotel, with each offering exclusive day passes to the event. Packages include pre-game accommodations and breakfast. Additional breakfast and day passes are available for a bundled price.
Source: Shangri-La Group Hong Kong. The Hong Kong Rugby Sevens.
Island Shangri-La, Hong Kong..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>23 lessons I picked up during my Royal Caribbean voyage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 03:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</guid><description>Tips for Enjoying Your Royal Caribbean Cruise Here&amp;rsquo;s a view from the Viking Crown Lounge on Deck 14.
And here are some tips for your cruise:
Pack light on sunscreen, heavier on cleanser. Remember that everything onboard caters to US standards: food portions, electrical outlets, and currency. Your daily cruise newsletter is your best friend. Delivered to your room every afternoon, it highlights all activities and indicates which ones require payment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Adya Hotel Langkawi provides meeting rooms and a ballroom for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: Adya Hotel Langkawi website. Interior of a junior suite.
The four-star Adya Hotel Langkawi, situated in the Kuah town center on Langkawi Island in Malaysia, is marketed as a perfect starting point for exploring the natural wonders and rich culture of Langkawi, a designated UNESCO Global Geopark.
The hotel boasts 207 rooms and suites, each featuring a private bathroom with a bath and shower, along with a balcony that offers scenic views of the sea and town...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Palawan @ Sentosa provides eight lifestyle entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 02:42:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Shangri-La Group has introduced its first lifestyle and entertainment hub, spanning 183,000 square feet on Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Sentosa Island. This complex boasts eight unique experiences, including dining options.
Chan Kong Leong, Regional CEO for the Shangri-La Group in Southeast Asia &amp;amp; Australasia, Hong Kong, Japan and Middle East, Europe, Indian Ocean &amp;amp; The Americas, emphasized the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing enjoyable experiences and Asian hospitality. He stated that this venture aims to create excitement and bring more enjoyment to guests beyond their traditional hotel settings, allowing them to create their own memorable moments through diverse leisure and dining experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-palawan-sentosa-provides-eight-lifestyle-entertainment-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay offers a competitive advantage for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay website. The Grand Ballroom, theatre-style.
The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, a premier five-star resort in Phu Quoc and a flagship property in Vietnam, provides a range of meeting spaces suitable for various event sizes.
The resort is committed to crafting unforgettable events and immersive experiences for all attendees. Phu Quoc is an up-and-coming destination, now linked by direct flights to major cities like Ho Chi Minh City, Bangkok, and Guangzhou...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Golf introduces special promotions for Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Golf website.
During Ramadan, Dubai Golf has several special iftar and suhoor packages perfect for corporate events.
QD&amp;rsquo;s
QD&amp;rsquo;s has a special Ramadan tent where they serve both iftar and suhoor. The daily iftar buffet features a variety of traditional hot and cold Arabic mezze, soups, Middle Eastern and international main dishes, and desserts. This comes with your choice of juice and traditional Arabic sweets and dates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at Avani+ Samui can take advantage of a complimentary longtail boat ride</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/</guid><description>Source: Minor Hotels. Avani+Samui Resort beachfront villa.
Guests at Avani+ Samui can enjoy a complimentary trip to Koh Madsum on a traditional longtail fishing boat.
Departing daily at 10 am and returning at 1 pm, the excursion allows ample time for a leisurely lunch at the resort&amp;rsquo;s Essence restaurant. For those seeking a full day of exploration, additional longtail boat trips for island hopping and snorkeling can be arranged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort introduces its new private villas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort has introduced new villas that provide enhanced privacy and luxury for guests. These villas overlook the Gulf of Thailand and the resort&amp;rsquo;s lotus lagoon. Their spaciousness makes them perfect for hosting private events, parties, or intimate gatherings, with amenities like a private chef, outdoor barbecues, and more.
Situated in a secluded part of the resort, the four three-bedroom and one four-bedroom villas offer direct access to the Club InterContinental Lounge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rasel offers artisanal catering services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</guid><description>Rasel Catering Singapore, a top-tier halal catering service, has enhanced its offerings to become a leader in the industry.
Alan Tan, Co-Founder and Managing Director of Rasel Catering Singapore, highlighted the company’s focus on meeting the evolving needs of a global clientele. He stated, “Rasel caters to international events and weddings, recognizing the sophisticated tastes of today’s customers and their demand for high-quality halal food. Our service goes beyond just the food itself—we leverage our expertise to elevate the entire experience for our customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the street food of Taiwan at Tea Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</guid><description>Tea Valley: Bringing Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Street Food Flavors to Singapore [Image of Tea Valley Downtown East outlet]
Tea Valley (茶食坊), a casual Taiwanese dining chain in Singapore, has ambitious plans for expansion. At a tasting event held at their first location in Downtown East, Director Lawrence Lim shared his vision for growing the brand beyond just new locations, but also in the variety of services they offer.
[Image of Lawrence Lim, Director of Tea Valley]..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Foodie Tour introduces a new tour to Tai Po Market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</guid><description>Source: Hong Kong Foodie.
Hong Kong Foodie has created a food tour in Tai Po Market. This is their third food tour, and it will take people to six family-owned restaurants in Tai Po Market that serve authentic Hong Kong cuisine.
Cecilia Leung, the Founder and Director of Hong Kong Foodie, believes that Tai Po Market is the perfect location for their newest tour because it has many beloved local restaurants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kinoya in Dubai has been awarded the One to Watch Award for 2022 by MENA's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Kinoya restaurant has been awarded the One To Watch Award 2022 by Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. This recognition is given to up-and-coming restaurants in the region that have the potential to earn a spot on the 50 Best list in future years.
Kinoya&amp;rsquo;s founder, Neha Mishra, also known as the Ramen Queen, opened the restaurant after the success of her home-based supper club, A Story of Food...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels Group plans to open Holiday Inn Osaka Namba by the end of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: IHG. The Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) and Japan Hotel Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) Investment Corporation (JHR) are collaborating on the Holiday Inn Osaka Namba, marking the REIT&amp;rsquo;s first venture with IHG. Scheduled to launch by the end of 2016, the hotel, presently known as Hotel Vista Grande Osaka, will be rebranded as Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
The 314-room hotel, joining the globally recognized Holiday Inn brand, will leverage IHG&amp;rsquo;s extensive global reservation systems, sales network, and the substantial IHG Rewards Club loyalty program, boasting almost 94 million members...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor expands its footprint in regional Queensland with the addition of Mercure Rockhampton</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</guid><description>The Travelodge Hotel in Rockhampton has transitioned to the Mercure brand as part of a new franchise agreement with Accor. This addition expands Mercure&amp;rsquo;s presence to over 50 properties in Australia and New Zealand, and more than 810 globally.
Conveniently located in the city center and a short distance from the airport, the Mercure Rockhampton underwent renovations in 2008. The eight-story hotel boasts 74 rooms, views of the Fitzroy River, six conference rooms, an outdoor pool, a fitness center, a 24-hour reception, and convenient access to attractions like Great Keppel Island...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bhaya Cruises has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for five consecutive years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</guid><description>Source: Bhaya Cruises website.
The luxury cruise company Bhaya Cruises, which operates in Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Halong Bay, has received TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Certificate of Excellence award for 2015. This recognition was given to three of their brands: Bhaya Classic, The Au Co, and Legend Halong. This marks the fifth year in a row that Bhaya Cruises has been acknowledged for its exceptional service.
The Certificate of Excellence is a prestigious award within the hospitality industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Mercure makes its first appearance in Myanmar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</guid><description>AccorHotels has launched its first Grand Mercure hotel in Myanmar. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire, with its 175 guest rooms and suites, provides a view of the Schwedagon Pagoda. Local artist Pyar Dade designed the accommodations.
Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire. Patrick Basset, COO of AccorHotels, Upper Southeast and Northeast Asia and the Maldives, stated, “This is our first Grand Mercure in Myanmar and the opening of Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire reflects the cultural touchstone of the destination and heritage in bringing local stories to life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wyndham brand has entered the UAE market with its presence in Dubai Marina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</guid><description>Source: The First Group. The new Wyndham
Dubai Marina.
Wyndham Dubai Marina, the first hotel solely developed by leading Dubai-based property developer, The First Group, has officially opened. This launch signifies the Wyndham brand&amp;rsquo;s entrance into the UAE market.
This four-star deluxe Wyndham Dubai Marina, managed by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, the largest hotel management company globally, represents a significant achievement for The First Group. The developer has established a strong reputation for creating high-quality serviced apartments and &amp;ldquo;aparthotels&amp;rdquo; in Dubai...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience Silom in a whole new way at the newly elevated ibis Styles Bangkok Silom</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</guid><description>Accor Hospitality Group has launched a stylish hotel, ibis Styles Bangkok Silom, in Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s lively Silom neighborhood. The hotel boasts a playful design inspired by Thai festivals and features a vibrant mural by Thai artist Tikkywow, reflecting Silom&amp;rsquo;s rich history.
Located near Sala Daeng BTS Skytrain and Silom MRT subway stations, the hotel provides convenient access to the city. Garth Simmons, CEO of Accor Southeast Asia, Japan &amp;amp; South Korea, expressed excitement for the opening, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s fit with Silom&amp;rsquo;s dynamic atmosphere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tandoor restaurant will be reopening on February 14th at the Holiday Inn Singapore Orchard City Centre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/</guid><description>Source: Holiday Inn Singapore Orchard City Centre. Selected highlights from Tandoor&amp;rsquo;s menu.
The Indian restaurant Tandoor will reopen its doors on February 14, 2023, after a two-year hiatus. Established in 1985, the restaurant boasts a refreshed, modern interior and serves authentic North Indian cuisine.
Chef Sunder, an award-winning chef, leads the culinary team at Tandoor, offering both à la carte and set menus. The menu reflects India&amp;rsquo;s diverse culinary traditions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has launched the Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp; Residences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</guid><description>Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences, the largest five-star hotel in Kolkata, is now open in the city’s New Town precinct.
Source: Accor Hotels. The Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences. The hotel has 347 guest rooms and suites. It is located near the airport and offers the city&amp;rsquo;s first serviced apartments. Guests can enjoy amenities such as a flat-screen LED TV, coffee and tea maker, in-room safe, refreshment center, and complimentary internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The doors of Wanda Realm Fuyang are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts has expanded its portfolio with the opening of Wanda Realm Fuyang in the bustling business district of Fuyang, Anhui province, China. This addition marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 78th hotel, the 42nd under its ownership and management, and the 30th property under the Wanda Realm brand.
André Liu, General Manager of Wanda Realm Fuyang, highlighted the strategic importance of the location, stating, &amp;ldquo;Fuyang city is a rapidly developing hub with the largest population and fourth-largest size in Anhui province...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae will be available starting in March 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:23:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</guid><description>Source: BWH Hotels. A standard room at the Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, which boasts contemporary rooms with a full range of amenities.
Starting March 13, 2024, BWH Hotels (BWH), the international hospitality group that includes WorldHotels, Best Western Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, and SureStay Hotels, will introduce a newly renovated and rebranded hotel.
The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, formerly the Best Western Nagoya, was one of the city&amp;rsquo;s most well-liked international mid-scale hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new Canopy outlet is now open for corporate dining and events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-canopy-outlet-is-now-open-for-corporate-dining-and-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-canopy-outlet-is-now-open-for-corporate-dining-and-events/</guid><description>Canopy has expanded its presence with a third location at Changi City Point. This new outlet offers both indoor dining and an alfresco terrace, bringing a touch of nature to the urban landscape.
A key feature of the Changi City Point location is the introduction of corporate dining and event packages. Designed specifically for businesses in the Changi Business Park area, Canopy aims to bridge the gap between traditional function rooms and restaurants, with a capacity of up to 200 guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-canopy-outlet-is-now-open-for-corporate-dining-and-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-canopy-outlet-is-now-open-for-corporate-dining-and-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wego collaborates with the Saudi Tourism Authority to boost tourism interest in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Wego, a leading online travel platform in the Middle East and North Africa, has partnered with the Saudi Tourism Authority to promote tourism in Saudi Arabia.
The collaboration will focus on attracting travelers from the region to destinations like Riyadh and Jeddah, showcasing Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s diverse landscapes, including deserts, mountains, and coastlines. Wego has observed significant interest in travel to Saudi Arabia, with a surge in flight and hotel bookings since travel restrictions were lifted...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring new destinations in 2021: Bawah Reserve and Cedar Lodge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</guid><description>Several properties, such as Bawah Reserve in Indonesia and Cedar Lodge in New Zealand, are getting ready for the return of travel.
Bawah Reserve
Source: Bawah Reserve website. Lodges at Bawah Reserve.
Located in Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s remote Anambas Islands, Bawah Reserve encompasses six tropical islands, thirteen white sand beaches, and three lagoons. The Anambas Islands are reachable by private seaplane from Bintan Island, Indonesia.
Along with its existing 36 lodges, Bawah will debut six new cliffside lodges on Elang, a previously undeveloped island, this year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport reveals its fresh new appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has finished renovations, adding new rooms, a new Italian restaurant called Allora, another function room, an updated Club Lounge, and a revitalized fitness center.
The new design creates a calming oceanic atmosphere. Natural wood finishes on the furniture bring a feeling of warmth and comfort. This is enhanced by a color scheme of beach tones and ocean shades. Light gray couches, navy blue, and yellow accents contribute to a modern and welcoming feel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton introduces a new MICE venue in Hainan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and its DoubleTree by Hilton brand have opened a new resort in China called the DoubleTree Resort by Hilton Hainan - Qixianling Hot Spring. Situated within the Qixianling Hot Spring National Rainforest Park, the 254-room hotel is conveniently located 50 km from Lingshui Railway Station and 90 km from Sanya Phoenix International Airport.
John Greenleaf, Global Head of DoubleTree by Hilton, emphasized the brand&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding guest expectations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the new Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. This hotel, the Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel, aims to create a beach resort atmosphere.
The recently opened Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel is a 72-room boutique hotel located in the city center. Its convenient location provides guests with easy walking access to shopping, dining, and entertainment. Designed around a nautical theme, the hotel offers 60 Deluxe rooms, eight Baraquda Suites, and four Baraquda Grand Suites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The MICE industry in KSA is expanding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</guid><description>In 2017, Saudi Arabia held more than 10,129 business events that were approved by the Saudi Exhibition and Convention Bureau (SECB), reflecting a 16% rise from the previous year.
The healthcare, education, technical, and communications industries made up the largest portion of business events within the 22 targeted economic sectors in 2017. The Riyadh region hosted 47% of these events, claiming the most business activity for the year. Following Riyadh, the Makkah region held 32% of events and the Eastern Province hosted 17%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Four Seasons Private Jet offers a luxurious flying experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</guid><description>Source: Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts.
Luxury hospitality company Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts has launched the Four Seasons Private Jet, signifying a major shift in luxury travel. This offering highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding the evolving desires of modern luxury travelers.
Every aspect of the private jet journey, both in flight and on the ground, has been redesigned through the Four Seasons perspective to provide a fully immersive experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai hotels are at the top of the list of top meeting hotels according to Cvent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 03:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</guid><description>Dubai, UAE, boasts seven out of the top 10 hotels in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region for Meetings, Incentives, Conferences, and Exhibitions (MICE), according to a new ranking. The list was released by Cvent, a leading technology provider for meetings, events, and hospitality.
These rankings are based on data from the Cvent Supplier Network (CSN), a comprehensive database with information on over 260,000 hotels, resorts, and event spaces in more than 175 countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Elite Havens is proud to announce the addition of three new properties in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: Elite Havens. Caption: Elite Havens expands its Bali Collection with three new villas.
Elite Havens, a high-end villa rental and management company in Asia, has expanded its Bali offerings with three new properties:
Sol Y Mar - Uluwatu, Bali, Indonesia
Situated on Nunggalan Beach, Sol y Mar is a four-bedroom villa featuring a private pool.
Villa Dhanika - Badung, Bali, Indonesia
Nestled amidst Balinese rice paddies, Villa Dhanika is a five-bedroom retreat with an Olympic-sized swimming pool and an outdoor jacuzzi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hilton Singapore Orchard introduces the Smart Oasis meeting space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 22:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</guid><description>Hilton Singapore Orchard Unveils &amp;lsquo;Smart Oasis&amp;rsquo; Meeting Space
Hilton Singapore Orchard is excited to announce the opening of Smart Oasis, a new meeting space located on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fifth floor. The space features seven function rooms, two breakout areas, and incorporates advanced technology with natural elements inspired by the area&amp;rsquo;s plantation history.
Cedric Nubul, General Manager of Hilton Singapore Orchard, emphasized the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing cutting-edge meeting facilities. He believes Smart Oasis will become a leading venue in Asia, promoting sustainable and impactful event experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Journeyful has revamped its website, incorporating additional listings and enhancing rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</guid><description>Source: Journeyful. The Journeyful 2.0 website.
Journeyful, a company located in Singapore, has relaunched an updated website for its rewards-based online travel agency, Journeyful.com. The new and improved &amp;ldquo;Journeyful 2.0&amp;rdquo; website features a selection of over 200,000 hotels globally, a price-match guarantee, and Facebook integration.
The redesigned website includes Journeyful MICE, which offers comprehensive solutions for business conferences, corporate events, and incentive trips. A Journeyful representative explained that once an online inquiry is submitted, MICE consultants collaborate offline with the organization to personalize solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CULINARYON has opened a cooking studio in Singapore for classes and parties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/</guid><description>A workstation equipped with eggs and two varieties of flour, ready for preparing homemade tagliatelle.
CULINARYON, the largest culinary edutainment studio in Europe, established in Moscow in 2012, has expanded to Singapore. Their 7,000 square foot studio at One Raffles Place, inaugurated in October 2015, is their second location and holds the title of the biggest cooking studio in Asia.
The CULINARYON studio has a capacity of 200 people and can be reconfigured into a conference room and four distinct event spaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp; Spa is offering meeting packages for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa. Executive team members at Hyatt Regegncy Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa will help event planners make any meeting a success.
Located on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Hoi An coastline and close to Danang, the Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa has announced new meeting packages for 2017.
The resort offers a wide range of event and meeting spaces, both indoors and outdoors on the beachfront. These venues can accommodate up to 250 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's tourism numbers have increased thanks to MICE travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</guid><description>During the first six months of 2014, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s hotels received a record-breaking 5.8 million guests, as reported by Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
DTCM attributes this surge in tourism to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s prominent position as a regional center for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events (MICE). A prime example was the incentive trip in April that brought in over 14,500 delegates from China alone. Significant business events hosted in the first half of 2014 included Gulfood, the Arabian Travel Market, and Intersec, a major trade show for safety, security, and fire protection in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore Sports Hub has successfully adapted during the pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Sports Hub. Plans for 2021.
The Singapore Sports Hub has adjusted its focus in 2021 to deliver impactful experiences, building on the lessons learned from 2020. This includes their earlier efforts, from providing safe housing for migrant workers during the peak of COVID-19 to creating new event formats for local audiences.
Despite the global pandemic impacting the Hub&amp;rsquo;s ability to host its typical lineup of large-scale sporting and entertainment events, it shifted gears to become a source of support for the community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BDMS Connect Center in Bangkok now offers a wider range of MICE options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</guid><description>Source: Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok. BDMS Connect Center.
The BDMS Wellness Campus is proud to introduce its latest addition, the BDMS Connect Center. This cutting-edge facility, spanning over 3,400 square meters in the heart of Bangkok, is set to redefine the standards of meeting and event spaces.
Dan Smith, General Manager of Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok, expressed his enthusiasm for the new facility, stating that the BDMS Connect Center is a one-of-a-kind space, emphasizing both functionality and a commitment to wellness and sustainability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dusit Thani Bangkok will reopen in September 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</guid><description>Dusit Hotels and Resorts, a prominent Thai hotel and property development company, will reopen the famous Dusit Thani Bangkok on September 27, 2024, as a key component of Dusit Central Park.
Starting May 1, 2024, reservations for the new Dusit Thani Bangkok can be made through their website, with early birds receiving a US$75 nightly credit for dining and spa treatments, among other benefits. Rates begin at US$330++ per night. Bookings made by October 31, 2024, for stays between September 27, 2024, and March 31, 2025, are eligible for this promotion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CruCycle brings a fresh perspective to the fitness scene in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</guid><description>Krewfit recently introduced CruCycle, a new spin studio concept in Singapore, to fitness and fun enthusiasts. The studio&amp;rsquo;s classes operate on the principle of &amp;ldquo;Riding with the Pack,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing group workouts, teamwork, and camaraderie. This makes CruCycle&amp;rsquo;s workouts perfect for corporate team-building events.
Source: Crucycle.
The Ding siblings – Valerie, Calvin, and Beatrice – founded, own, and operate CruCycle. The inspiration for the studio came from their upbringing in Los Angeles, California...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Teardrop Hotels is introducing three new tea plantation experiences in Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Teardrop Hotels is expanding its portfolio in 2018 with the addition of three renovated tea planters&amp;rsquo; houses: Goatfell, Nine Skies, and Pekoe House. These vintage managers&amp;rsquo; bungalows, located along the tea country route, will offer a modern take on traditional tea plantation accommodations.
Opening in April 2018, Goatfell is a former superintendent’s residence situated on a working tea estate above Nuwara Eliya. This four-bedroom main house, with two additional standalone chalets, boasts living and dining rooms and a swimming pool...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the unique Kampong culinary specials at the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>This June, the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur in Malaysia is offering a special deal for gatherings with colleagues, business contacts, and potential clients. The promotion is valid in their newly renovated ballrooms and private function rooms.
Source: Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur website.
For every ten paying guests, one person can attend for free. The Selera Kampong package is priced at RM155 nett per adult, while the Kampong Boys Special is RM172 nett per adult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the successful first year of Hyatt Regency Suzhou with our Anniversary Meeting Package</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Suzhou.
The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is commemorating its first anniversary with various special offers as a thank you to its loyal and valued guests for their support throughout the year.
Having opened its doors on August 24, 2014, in the Suzhou Industrial Park (SIP), the conveniently located Hyatt Regency Suzhou boasts 355 rooms and suites. Amenities include a Regency Club, five dining options, and over 15,000 square feet of space for events...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Autograph Collection is ready to make its first appearance in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</guid><description>Australian companies have a new, upscale event location. Pier One Sydney Harbour is joining the Autograph Collection, a curated group of almost 60 unique hotels globally. This harborside hotel provides a picturesque setting for meetings and events, featuring eight meeting rooms with expansive water views.
Source: Marriott International. From Sydney to San Diego - Autograph Collection set to debut in three new world class destinations, including Pier One Sydney Harbour in Sydney, Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CulinaryOn Singapore is offering Lunar New Year dinner experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Culinaryon Singapore. Yusheng with salmon sashimi.
For this Lunar New Year, CulinaryOn Singapore is offering special dinners starting on December 26th, 2017. These dinners feature premium six-to-eight course meals and include a taste of their cooking classes with a noodle-making activity. Guests can also choose to create their own desserts.
The eight-course premium menu features dishes such as yusheng with salmon sashimi, shiitake mushrooms with broccoli, crayfish braised longevity noodles, golden shrimp with honeydew mayo, and mango ice cream with pomelo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Shanghai is set to make its debut in late 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</guid><description>Source: HKRI. The Sukhothai Shanghai.
HKR International will soon expand its Sukhothai Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts portfolio with a second hotel – The Sukhothai Shanghai. This new addition, situated in the Nanjing Road West central business district, is set to launch in late 2017.
Designed by Neri &amp;amp; Hu, The Sukhothai Shanghai is a contemporary luxury boutique hotel. It offers 168 guest rooms and 33 suites, ranging from 44 to 172 square meters in size...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Suzhou is gaining more recognition in the MICE industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</guid><description>The Suzhou Culture and Expo Centre Company (SCECC), which manages the Suzhou Culture and Arts Centre and the Suzhou International Expo Centre, claims that Suzhou is arguably the top Meetings, Incentives, Conferences and Exhibitions (MICE) destination in China.
SCECC highlights Suzhou&amp;rsquo;s success in hosting significant events, such as the 53rd World Table Tennis Championships earlier this year and Armani&amp;rsquo;s selection of the city&amp;rsquo;s Humble Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Garden as the venue for the global debut of its Pivoine Suzhou perfume...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Group discounts are available for the iftar buffet at Coral Beach Resort Sharjah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 12:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</guid><description>Source: Coral Beach Resort Sharjah website.
The Coral Beach Resort Sharjah, having just finished a full update of its rooms and amenities, is offering an iftar buffet at its Al Bahar Restaurant. The buffet will feature a variety of traditional Arabic and international dishes, with options like mixed grills, shawarma, hot and cold mezze, stews and biryani, in addition to soups, salads, snacks, and customary Ramadan beverages.
Jean Pierre Simon, the Regional General Manager for Northern Emirates at Coral Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, highlighted Al Bahar restaurant as the perfect location for gatherings to break the fast, suggesting guests round off their dining experience with classic Ramadan sweets like the ever-popular umm Ali and mouhalabia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TCEB commemorates achievements in Thailand's MICE Venue Standard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</guid><description>Forty-two venues in Thailand have now received the Thailand MICE Venue Standard award from the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB). The announcement was made at the Thailand MICE Venue Standard Certification Ceremony held last month.
This standard is a key element of a robust plan to accelerate the growth of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s MICE industry. Emphasizing Thailand&amp;rsquo;s prominent role in the region, TCEB underscored the need to utilize the expertise of MICE operators...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hyatt Regency is back in Sydney and is now focusing on positioning the hotel for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels announced that a hotel situated at 161 Sussex Street, previously operating under the Four Points by Sheraton brand, will transition to Hyatt Regency Sydney starting November 30, 2016. This change signifies the return of the Hyatt Regency brand to Sydney. The company is strategically positioning the Hyatt Regency Sydney as a prime location for conferences.
The introduction of Hyatt Regency Sydney aligns with the growing demand for business, meetings, incentives, conferences and exhibitions (MICE), as well as leisure travel within the Australian market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sunway's Resort Cafe provides a range of dining options from breakfast to dinner, perfect for business meetings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</guid><description>Source: Sunway.
The recently opened Resort Cafe, situated on the lobby level of the luxurious Sunway Resort Hotel and Spa, accommodates 362 guests and showcases the diverse culinary heritage of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Malay, Chinese, and Indian populations.
Spanning 17,588 square feet, the restaurant presents eight distinct culinary themes: the impressive Monumental Fruit and Salad Towers, Malay Archipelago (featuring dishes from Malaysia, Singapore, and Indonesia), Indo-Chine (showcasing cuisine from Thailand and Vietnam), Oriental Far East (highlighting dishes from Japan, Korea, and China), Spices of India, Mirage of the Gulf (offering dishes from the Middle East), Best from the West (featuring Western comfort food, grills, rotisserie, and churrasco), and a dedicated dessert section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The opening date for Six Senses Kaplankaya is May 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</guid><description>![Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEg6jRBaFFB8FLc8GWUouGmkRpZIrrVyWlKYCZ1pRPjPgJhTMuDR2tOLPpVhKP-eWibrLG1ZGt42dmOjjJoSeU_SwAl_HlA8BkuquNMt_lQ5P90CQTn7bDyCDPtU74R2ApXfx4oJxuNUaZo/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;Six Senses hotel in Turkey opens May 1.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.
The Six Senses Kaplankaya resort, which became part of Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas on May 1, 2017, commences its new season on May 1, 2018. The property now aligns with Six Senses&amp;rsquo; standards of design, sustainability, and wellness, offering a distinct guest experience focused on achieving equilibrium and well-being by engaging all the senses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indulge in Glamour at the Bund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</guid><description>The renowned &amp;lsquo;M&amp;rsquo; Restaurant Group, led by Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s celebrated entrepreneur Michelle Garnaut, has unveiled Glam, a chic new dining lounge and bar in Shanghai. Situated at 5 on the Bund, the location previously housed the iconic M on the Bund restaurant.
Michelle Garnaut, known for establishing new dining benchmarks in Asia, began her restaurant empire with M at the Fringe in Hong Kong in 1989. She later spearheaded Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s return to sophistication with M on the Bund in 1999 and elevated the city&amp;rsquo;s nightlife with The Glamour Bar in 2006...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing a new food tour by Isan Explorer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</guid><description>Source: Isan Explorer website.
Isan Explorer, a tour operator specializing in Northeast Thailand, has launched a culinary tour showcasing the cuisine of the lesser-known Isan region.
The day-long tour starts with a visit to a bustling fresh market to gather ingredients for lunch and dinner. Afterward, the tour proceeds to a nearby village.
Participants will enjoy a tasting menu featuring 20 main dishes, such as bamboo shoot curry, sour fish, grilled chicken, steamed mushrooms, green bean salad, and eggplant dipping sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is gaining traction as a top choice for hosting business events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</guid><description>Source: TCEB.
Thailand, with the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB) at the helm, is establishing itself as a prime location for business events. As the Thai government&amp;rsquo;s primary representative for this sector, TCEB plays a vital role in solidifying Thailand&amp;rsquo;s leading position in the Asian business events industry and Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a top-tier destination for international business events.
The Thai business events sector is projected to experience robust growth in 2015, anticipating over a million visitors and generating approximately US$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>