<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 92/85 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-92/85/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 92/85 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-92/85/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU's decision on the importance of parenthood in EU law slips away from us.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Most EU laws and court decisions on sex discrimination focus on improving women&amp;rsquo;s job opportunities and ensuring equal treatment in the workplace. A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Maistrellis case tackles these issues from a different perspective: a father&amp;rsquo;s access to parental leave when the mother isn&amp;rsquo;t employed or looking for work. This judgment brings up important questions about how EU employment and discrimination laws affect family life.</description></item><item><title>Contemplating EU Gender Equality Law on Surrogate Mothers' Day in Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:57:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contemplating-eu-gender-equality-law-on-surrogate-mothers-day-in-court/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The desire to have children has always been deeply understood, especially for women facing medical obstacles to childbirth. Adoption was the traditional solution, but recent decades have introduced alternatives like IVF and surrogacy.
While the EU doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly regulate these practices, it does address maternity leave through the Pregnant Workers&amp;rsquo; Directive. The Directive on Sex Discrimination in Employment further tackles the employment aspects of pregnancy. This directive prohibits discrimination against women undergoing IVF treatment even before pregnancy, as established by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Mayr case.</description></item><item><title>The rights of pregnant workers and the free movement rights of EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Jessy Saint Prix, a young woman from France, relocated to Britain in 2006 to pursue a teaching career. Her experience led her to learn much more about EU law and the English legal system than she expected.
After working in the UK as a teaching assistant for a year, she began a teacher training program (PGCE). During the program, she became pregnant and decided to pause her studies to register with a teaching agency.</description></item></channel></rss>