<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Congestion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-congestion/</link><description>Recent content in Network Congestion on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-congestion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Low Latency WAN Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</guid><description>Businesses are increasingly demanding low latency in their WAN connections. But why is latency suddenly so important, and how can you achieve it?
Latency is the time it takes for data packets to travel between two points. While insignificant on local networks, latency can pose major problems on long-distance WAN connections, especially for applications where speed is critical.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that latency and bandwidth are not directly related. You can have slow connections with minimal latency and blazing-fast connections with terrible latency.</description></item><item><title>So Much Network Congestion You Could Just Burst</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-much-network-congestion-you-could-just-burst/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-much-network-congestion-you-could-just-burst/</guid><description>Even with a struggling economy, workloads remain heavy. Your teams might be working harder to keep existing clients and gain new ones. This increased activity could be straining your Wide Area Network (WAN). When speed and efficiency are crucial, a slow and unreliable network becomes a problem, especially if a bandwidth upgrade is not feasible.
Don&amp;rsquo;t assume you can&amp;rsquo;t get a better bandwidth deal. Your current provider and plan might not be the most cost-effective.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing business internet services, bandwidth is important, but understanding the difference between dedicated and shared connections is crucial.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated bandwidth is exclusively for your use. This might seem obvious, but the recent rise of shared bandwidth makes it worth clarifying. The cost-effectiveness of shared bandwidth often makes businesses reconsider their need for a dedicated line.
Cost Considerations
Shared bandwidth is significantly cheaper than dedicated bandwidth at similar speeds.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Symmetric Internet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you unhappy with how the internet performs for your business? Do you think it&amp;rsquo;s more for entertainment and casual use than for getting work done quickly and efficiently? You need the internet to function, though. Your customers and suppliers, along with important information, are online. Even your software and communication tools might be cloud-based. What you likely need is a business-grade broadband connection with better performance.</description></item><item><title>Why The WAN Lags The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</guid><description>Corporate networks are often set up to ensure smooth data flow within the organization (LAN), but the real bottleneck often lies in the connection to the outside world (WAN).
LANs typically use Ethernet standards with speeds of 10/100/1000 Mbps, while WAN connections like T1 or DS3 lines operate at much slower speeds (1.5 Mbps to 45 Mbps). This disparity in speed results in significant slowdowns when transferring files outside the organization.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables.</description></item><item><title>Maxed Out On Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your business pushing the limits of its WAN bandwidth? Are you facing network congestion during peak hours? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are solutions to improve your situation.
Start by evaluating your network efficiency. Are you using quality of service management, or are you simply hoping for the best? Prioritizing voice packets can resolve issues with VoIP calls without impacting other processes.
Consider the timing of bandwidth-heavy tasks. Running backups to remote sites during peak hours can hinder employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth on Demand Complements Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:50:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
One of the biggest advantages of cloud services over traditional IT infrastructure is their flexibility. With a vast pool of virtual servers and storage, businesses can adjust resources on demand, significantly improving productivity and resource usage.
However, connectivity hasn&amp;rsquo;t quite caught up with this shift. Connecting to the cloud often relies on fixed-capacity connections. Upgrading these connections is typically a complex and time-consuming process, creating a bottleneck in an otherwise agile system.</description></item><item><title>Cure The Bulging T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</guid><description>Not too long ago, you got your first T1 line. It was impressive with its 1.5 Mbps speed for both uploading and downloading. The connection was reliable, and there was a guarantee for quick assistance if any issues arose. Though a bit pricey, it was worth it, and you believed it would last forever. However, lately, that once-speedy connection has slowed to a crawl. So, what now?
Many businesses are facing the issue of overloaded T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>The Value of Low Latency Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-value-of-low-latency-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 20:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-value-of-low-latency-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow network speeds, particularly when connecting to the internet or other company sites, could point to a latency problem. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how businesses and organizations can achieve faster network connections:
For businesses that rely on high-speed network performance, like high-frequency financial trading, minimizing latency is crucial. Some companies even choose to be in the same building as stock exchanges to be just feet away from servers.
While most applications aren&amp;rsquo;t that demanding, factors like bandwidth, latency, packet loss, and jitter still matter.</description></item><item><title>Unlimited Internet's Days are Numbered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</guid><description>Remember the golden age of air travel? You could stroll into an airport right before your flight, effortlessly purchase a ticket, and enjoy luxurious treatment onboard. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a different story. We endure long lines and cramped seats, a far cry from the preferential treatment of the past. Sadly, this shift from luxury to cattle car is coming soon to the internet.
You might be skeptical. After all, the internet has felt limitless for over a decade.</description></item><item><title>Will Ethernet Crush DS3?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</guid><description>Companies needing more bandwidth than a 1.5 Mbps T1 line often upgraded to DS3, but its 45 Mbps speed was often more than they needed. A newer option, Carrier Ethernet (also known as Metro Ethernet), offers a more practical solution with scalable bandwidth at a often lower cost.
Ethernet services are significantly less expensive than DS3 in some markets, costing up to 50% less. However, in areas where Ethernet isn&amp;rsquo;t widely available, prices may be comparable to DS3.</description></item></channel></rss>