<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ISDN PRI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/isdn-pri/</link><description>Recent content in ISDN PRI on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/isdn-pri/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get Ready For The Recovery With Bandwidth on Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>The economy is recovering, benefiting some businesses while others struggle. Maintaining earnings through cost-cutting instead of increased sales won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable. When the economy fully recovers, rapid adaptation will be crucial, but increased expenses are only justifiable with increased revenue. Bandwidth on demand offers a solution.
Bandwidth on demand allows businesses to access and pay for only the bandwidth they currently need, scaling usage up or down as required. This differs from the traditional approach of installing full capacity in advance, which poses financial risks if projected growth doesn&amp;rsquo;t materialize.</description></item><item><title>600,000 Inquiries, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</guid><description>Purchasing important items can be a hassle, especially telecommunications services. It&amp;rsquo;s a maze of confusing calls, endless hold music, and tedious forms with long wait times.
But imagine getting a price for a T1 line or finding nearby Metro Ethernet services in under a minute, any time, day or night. That&amp;rsquo;s where GeoQuote (tm) comes in. This innovative telecom pricing application is changing how businesses buy voice and data services.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>Telephony In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>When we think about cloud networking, we often picture data networks moving information between locations. However, many businesses are also transitioning their phone systems to the cloud. This shift brings both benefits and hurdles.
The traditional phone network is essentially a large cloud network. This system is designed for reliability and high-quality service, handling countless users at once. Users connect to this cloud through a direct line to their nearest local central office, unconcerned with the complexities of the system.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider.</description></item><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs ISDN PRI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses have moved past analog phone lines, embracing PBX systems and ISDN PRI for their communication needs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: SIP Trunking. This technology offers potential cost and performance benefits for companies looking to enhance their voice services. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SIP Trunks with ISDN PRI to understand the best choice for your organization.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that both technologies rely on digital telephony, eliminating analog transmission.</description></item><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options.</description></item><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Cost Reduction Ideas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</guid><description>Getting the best price on everything your business buys is crucial for success, and bandwidth is no exception. Telecom expenses can be significant, but there are ways to save without sacrificing productivity.
One surprisingly simple step is to get updated competitive quotes. Bandwidth prices change rapidly, so your current understanding might be outdated.
While gathering quotes used to be time-consuming, online tools like GeoQuote by Telarus have simplified the process. This automated engine collects pricing from various providers, delivering budgetary quotes for services like T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and Ethernet connections almost instantly.</description></item><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Hosted PBX VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 03:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</guid><description>There are many ways to implement VoIP, with some methods being more effective than others. Your goal with VoIP is likely to reduce expenses and access enhanced features while maintaining high-quality voice communication.
Achieving this balance is possible with the right technology, though proper setup can be challenging. Getting assistance with the installation, specifically by outsourcing complex aspects to a specialized provider, can greatly increase your chances of a smooth implementation.</description></item><item><title>Can SIP Trunking Supplant ISDN PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses that require multiple phone lines can benefit from digital trunks. While previously only large companies with numerous lines saw advantages with digital trunks, advancements in technology now make them a viable option for businesses with just a few lines and internet access.
What exactly constitutes a telephone trunk? Essentially, it is a collection of phone lines bundled together. Unlike individual analog lines, which consist of a twisted pair of copper wires, a trunk combines multiple lines.</description></item><item><title>How Many T1 Lines Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</guid><description>For small businesses dissatisfied with DSL or Cable broadband, a professional T1 line might seem like the ideal solution. The superior reliability and dedicated bandwidth make T1 lines the popular choice for business voice and data services. However, as your business expands, you might encounter the bandwidth limitations of your once-sufficient T1 line. What then?
Similarly, high-tech businesses, such as Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) or video production companies, might find the 1.</description></item><item><title>Voice over Internet Protocol Phone Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) suggests it will likely replace traditional phone services, including landlines and ISDN PRI. This shift is primarily driven by the transition from traditional telephone networks to computer-based networks, further complicated by the emergence of wireless voice and data services.
Telephone networks, largely analog during their long history, were initially designed solely for voice communication. While attempts were made to use them for data transfer with analog modems, the limited bandwidth of these networks proved insufficient for anything beyond low-speed data.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly.</description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines might be leaving money on the table if they haven&amp;rsquo;t explored T-1 digital phone lines. Even businesses already using T1 service might be unaware of potential savings from newer options.
Digital telephony emerged in the 1950s as phone companies sought efficient ways to handle large call volumes. Analog phone lines carried a single conversation per wire pair. While analog multiplexing (carrier telephony) allowed multiple calls on a single wire pair, it suffered from quality issues over long distances.</description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>Copper Thrives In The 21st Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</guid><description>For over a century, copper wire has been the backbone of telecommunications, connecting homes and businesses. While fiber optic technology has advanced, copper remains dominant, even in the 21st century.
Despite the rise of fiber optics, copper persists due to its widespread availability and established infrastructure. Connecting to existing copper is often more cost-effective than installing new fiber optic lines.
While copper-based systems were designed for analog signals, they can still handle today’s high-speed digital demands.</description></item><item><title>XO Nails Down SIP Trunking Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</guid><description>Want to discover how your business could save upwards of $88,000 annually just by switching to SIP trunking service?
Hold on a minute! To achieve this level of savings, your business needs to have a certain volume of operations and spending. This figure comes from XO Communications, a leading voice and data carrier, and their new Enterprise SIP Savings Estimator.
So, what kind of business can expect these substantial savings? In this scenario, a company with 1,000 employees spread across 10 locations, where half of their phone calls are internal.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking Providers Want Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 12:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>The telephone industry is undergoing a transformation. Previously, businesses typically relied on in-house PBX systems to manage their phone networks and utilized ISDN PRI trunk lines for external calls. However, this is changing rapidly.
Two significant trends are emerging: cloud-based hosted PBX telephone systems and SIP trunking. While these technologies complement each other, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to implement SIP trunking without cloud services.
A telephone trunk consists of multiple phone lines grouped together, either physically or electronically.</description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer.</description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Obsolete?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you been relying on a T1 line for a long time? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable, given their long history. When the Internet was new, a T1 line provided businesses with a dependable, high-bandwidth connection that made dial-up modems seem incredibly slow. These days, similar bandwidth options are available at comparable prices, making those old T1 lines appear slow in comparison. So, are T1 lines still a viable business solution, or are they outdated?</description></item><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service.</description></item><item><title>Local Telephone Service Provider Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</guid><description>All homes and businesses require some form of local phone service. While this was once as simple as calling the phone company, more choices are now available, requiring careful consideration for the best deal.
Traditional analog phone service, or &amp;ldquo;dial tone&amp;rdquo; service, uses century-old technology. With its established infrastructure and widespread availability, customers can still walk into a local phone company for service. However, exploring offers from both traditional and newer competitive carriers can lead to better options.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Dedicated T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 20:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</guid><description>Although a traditional service, point-to-point dedicated T1 lines remain popular. This article examines their functionality and applications.
](http://www.t1t3today.com/) Initially designed for internal use, telephone companies used T1 lines to combine 24 individual analog phone lines into a single digital connection. Their key characteristics included serial digital transmission via a maximum of two twisted pair wires, regeneration to extend transmission distance, fixed private connections between two points, a multiplexing method to separate concurrent calls, and a 1.</description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable.</description></item><item><title>PRI Lines For Domestic Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are turning to domestic call centers, whether they are in-house or independent contractors. All call centers rely on telephone service, and PRI lines are the preferred choice. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, belongs to the Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) standard. ISDN aimed to transition all telephone lines from analog to digital. The basic offering, BRI (Basic Rate Interface), provides two phone lines or one phone line with either a 64 Kbps or 128 Kbps data service.</description></item><item><title>Dynamically Allocate T1 Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a reliable choice for transmitting voice and data for many years. Traditionally, it was believed that the purpose of the line (voice or data) needed to be determined before installation. For voice communication, a channelized T1 line or ISDN PRI configuration was used, with each of the 23 or 24 channels dedicated to a single phone call. Conversely, a clear channel T1 line was used for point-to-point data transmission or dedicated internet access, allowing for the full 1.</description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses.</description></item><item><title>CAS vs PRI Voice Channels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</guid><description>T1 telephone trunk lines are commonly used with PBX and IP PBX phone systems because most modern equipment can connect directly to them without a separate CSU/DSU box. There are two main types of T1 lines: CAS and PRI (also called ISDN PRI).
The original T1 line design, T1 CAS, is divided into 24 channels, each carrying a 64 Kbps digitized phone call. This digital conversion process, known as PCM, ensures clear voice quality.</description></item><item><title>Integrated Access Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>T1 lines can be used for broadband data or digital phone lines. However, needing separate lines for voice and data was expensive for smaller businesses. Integrated T1 offered a solution by combining voice and data on a single line, proving cost-effective for a while. But now, Integrated Access using Ethernet over Copper is an even better option.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a strong competitor to T1 lines. Both use existing copper telephone wiring, offering reliability and dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines.</description></item><item><title>Why, Oh Why, PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</guid><description>You might know the terms PRI, T1 PRI, Telephone PRI, PRI Trunk, or ISDN PRI, but what do they actually mean, and why choose this service?
PRI stands for Primary Rate Interface. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN or Integrated Services Digital Network and is a step up from BRI or Basic Rate Interface. Simply put, PRI is a digital line connecting to your PBX phone system. It combines numerous phone lines into a single digital line, leading to cost savings on monthly phone bills.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century.</description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs.</description></item><item><title>PRI over Cable Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 01:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</guid><description>Many businesses use ISDN PRI, a technology that bundles multiple phone lines onto a single digital cable, for cost-effective phone service. While initially implemented with T1 lines, offering 23 usable voice channels after reserving one for signaling, ISDN PRI can now be delivered over cable networks.
Modern phone systems, including PBX and key systems, typically support ISDN PRI, allowing businesses to scale their phone lines up to 46, 69, 92, or more.</description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Buying Ernest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations often struggle to manage their telecommunications across the board. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t a single, national provider that understands local needs be ideal? While that might seem contradictory, Ernest Communications offers precisely that solution.
Ernest specializes in serving businesses with widespread locations, such as chain stores, hotels, and restaurants, by providing phone lines, data connections, and wireless services. Essentially, any company with franchises, branches, or service centers across various regions fits their model.</description></item><item><title>Find A T1 Line For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re unsatisfied with your current internet options like DSL or Cable due to fluctuating speeds, frequent outages, or location limitations, and find Satellite internet&amp;rsquo;s lag, bandwidth restrictions, and weather-related disruptions unacceptable, there&amp;rsquo;s a better solution: T1 lines.
T1 lines, the gold standard for business wireline services, provide a reliable solution with consistent upload and download speeds, high reliability, quick problem resolution, and widespread availability. They offer secure connections between business locations and digital phone line options for PBX systems, features absent in other digital services.</description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>T1 vs SIP For Business Telephone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</guid><description>Large businesses with high call volumes require different telecommunications solutions compared to small offices. While T1 lines have been the traditional choice, SIP Trunking is emerging as a strong alternative. This article explores the pros and cons of each technology to help businesses make informed decisions.
T1 lines were initially developed by telephone companies to connect central offices and handle numerous calls simultaneously. This technology, using T-carrier standards (T1 and T3), enabled high-capacity call transportation.</description></item><item><title>T1 Telephony Has Many Flavors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</guid><description>Initially designed for high-volume call transfer between telephone exchanges, T1 technology has evolved into a leading digital phone solution for businesses. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering T1, understanding the available options is crucial.
T1 is a digital standard supporting voice, data, video, or a combination thereof. Originally, it carried 24 separate calls on individual channels called DS0s, collectively forming a T1 line or DS1. Each DS0 transmits digitized voice, call control, and signaling information.</description></item><item><title>Private Branch Exchange Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</guid><description>PBX telephone systems are the preferred business phone technology for medium and large businesses, though recent advancements have made them affordable for smaller companies as well, replacing outdated hardwired or key systems. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a new PBX system, reaching out to VAR Network can provide insights into pricing and available options.
Beyond hardware, PBX systems require connectivity, with various options offering different cost and performance benefits. The most basic connection is an FXO, or analog phone line, connecting to a central office.</description></item><item><title>T1's for Business Parks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</guid><description>Most businesses require reliable communication services, but options can be limited outside of major city centers. While downtown areas boast a variety of high-speed internet providers, businesses in industrial parks often face fewer choices.
Similar to essential utilities, reliable internet access is crucial for modern businesses. However, many older industrial parks were developed before the internet&amp;rsquo;s prominence, lacking the infrastructure for high-speed connections.
Despite this, businesses in these areas still have reliable options.</description></item><item><title>PRI vs POTS Telephone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 11:04:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</guid><description>Business telephone systems come in various sizes, from single-line setups to large enterprise systems with thousands of phones. This article aims to help you determine the right system size for your business needs.
The most basic phone service is known as POTS, or Plain Old Telephone Service, although it&amp;rsquo;s often marketed as a business line or dial-tone service. This service provides an analog connection to the nearest telephone company&amp;rsquo;s Central Office (CO).</description></item><item><title>What Is a PRI Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</guid><description>Businesses frequently use PRI lines to obtain multiple phone lines. But what exactly are PRI lines, and what choices are there?
PRI is a component of ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network), a telecommunications standard. Its goal was to replace analog phone lines with digital ones for both residential and commercial customers. When ISDN was first introduced, dial-up connections using 56 Kbps modems were the norm for internet connectivity. Many of these modems only achieved speeds of 30 to 40 Kbps due to phone line limitations.</description></item><item><title>Cable, T1 and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have three primary broadband options today: Cable, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper (EoC). While their costs are relatively similar, each offers distinct advantages. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options further.
T1 lines, a long-standing choice for SMBs, utilize half-century-old telephone industry technology. This technology transmits digital signals across standard copper telephone wiring. A T1 line consists of two copper pairs, one for uploads and the other for downloads, achieving a consistent speed of 1.</description></item><item><title>Converting From Regular Phone Lines to T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/converting-from-regular-phone-lines-to-t1/</guid><description>Your business is thriving, and your team is expanding, but your phone system isn&amp;rsquo;t keeping pace. The limited lines, tangled mess of wires, and sky-high bills are holding you back. There&amp;rsquo;s a better solution than relying on outdated analog lines.
T1 lines are the answer for businesses ready for a professional phone system. This technology allows multiple calls on a single line using your existing copper wiring. It&amp;rsquo;s like consolidating numerous lines into one connection for your phone system.</description></item><item><title>Plain Old Telephone Service For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get a reliable phone service? Surprisingly, it might be POTS – Plain Old Telephone Service.
While the name might sound outdated, POTS offers dependable, high-quality phone service at an affordable price. Why is this the case?
POTS, technically known as analog telephone service over copper wiring, is a direct descendant of the original telephone system. This system, developed and refined over a century by companies like the Bell Telephone System, became incredibly efficient and standardized.</description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards.</description></item><item><title>EarthLink Offers Healthcare IT Resources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</guid><description>The potential for healthcare automation to significantly reduce costs in healthcare settings like doctor&amp;rsquo;s offices, clinics, and hospitals is substantial. However, not all healthcare providers have the necessary IT capabilities to modernize and leverage these new technologies. They might also struggle to meet privacy regulations like HIPAA. This is where large network service providers such as EarthLink Business can bridge the gap. An example of this can be seen in how EarthLink supports Monadnock Community Hospital in Peterborough, New Hampshire, as shown in this video.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual.</description></item><item><title>Types of Business Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Over time, business phone lines have evolved from a single analog option to a variety of choices. While you can still get traditional analog lines, various digital options offer potential cost and performance benefits.
The standard business phone line remains largely unchanged from its origins over a century ago, using a single twisted pair of copper wires to carry signals. This analog line, also called POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is the basis for multi-line phones connecting to multiple POTS lines, commonly seen in small office phone systems with one to four lines.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI Offers Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</guid><description>If your company relies heavily on phone communication, using numerous phone lines managed by an internal system, ISDN PRI might be the solution for you. It provides excellent voice quality, quick call transfers, and additional features like Caller ID, all while potentially saving you money.
ISDN PRI, or Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is an advanced form of the traditional T1 digital phone line. While it utilizes the same T1 line infrastructure, making it widely accessible, its channel organization sets it apart.</description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system.</description></item><item><title>Signaling for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signaling-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signaling-for-call-centers/</guid><description>Every phone call involves two parts: the conversation itself and the signaling that manages the phone network. While signaling might seem purely technical, its implementation significantly impacts call center efficiency.
Traditional analog phone lines use the same copper wires, called the local loop, for both voice and signaling. Touchtone dialing, handset lifting, and ringing all rely on electrical signals sent over this shared connection. This method, known as in-band signaling, has limitations.</description></item><item><title>So, What Does ISDN Stand For?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</guid><description>If your business uses telephone systems, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the term ISDN. This piece explains what ISDN is and how it can benefit your company.
ISDN, or Integrated Services Digital Network, is a digital telephone standard initially intended to replace analog lines for both residential and business users. While DSL, cable broadband, and VoIP surpassed ISDN in the residential market with their higher bandwidths and lower costs, ISDN found its niche as a popular trunking service for business PBX telephone systems and a few specialized applications.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Trunk Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines often benefit from trunk lines. But with various trunk services available, choosing the right one can be tricky. While VoIP phone systems might make SIP trunking seem like the obvious choice, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to evaluate all options before deciding.
The concept of telephone trunking originated with telephone companies. Initially, individual phone lines connected users to the local phone company. As phone usage surged, businesses adopted switchboards to manage multiple lines, leading to a tangled mess of overhead wires.</description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country.</description></item><item><title>T1 Phone Lines Offer More For Less</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-phone-lines-offer-more-for-less/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 09:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-phone-lines-offer-more-for-less/</guid><description>When your business expands and your phone bills become a significant expense, it might be time to consider a service that offers higher volume at a lower cost. This is especially relevant if you&amp;rsquo;ve established a dedicated customer contact center or if your business has grown to require a dozen or more external phone lines.
The service that aligns with this need is a T1 telephone line. Unlike a single phone line, a T1 &amp;ldquo;line&amp;rdquo; is a digital trunk line.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?</description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Contact Center On Demand in the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The sophistication of cloud communications services is constantly increasing, representing a logical progression in the cloud computing revolution. With data servers already transitioned to the cloud, numerous businesses are questioning the necessity of maintaining costly and aging PBX phone systems.
Transitioning business phone systems to the cloud is becoming increasingly practical. Beginning with Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, this shift eliminates the need for substantial hardware and traditional phone lines. Instead, handsets connect to the company network and a high-bandwidth WAN connection links to the provider.</description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs EoC vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</guid><description>Not long ago, businesses seeking a dedicated, symmetrical bandwidth line had only one option: T1. However, the landscape has changed with the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and SIP Trunks. While options like DSL, Cable, satellite, and 3G wireless offer shared and asymmetrical bandwidth, and DS3, SONET, and Ethernet over Fiber provide higher bandwidths at higher costs, they fall outside the scope of this comparison.
Similar to their copper-based counterparts, Ethernet over Fiber, DS3, and SONET are higher bandwidth alternatives to EoC, T1, and SIP Trunks, respectively.</description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions.</description></item><item><title>Business VoIP Solution Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about switching your business phone system from the traditional analog or PBX setup to VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), it&amp;rsquo;s wise to explore the various business VoIP options available before making a complete overhaul. The best choice for you depends on your specific needs and, by selecting wisely, you can maximize your telephony investment.
The main reasons to consider VoIP are cost savings, enhanced calling features, or a combination of both.</description></item><item><title>T1 Voice Options for Call Quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 19:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-voice-options-for-call-quality/</guid><description>For businesses reliant on phone communication, exceptional call quality is non-negotiable. This means clear, natural-sounding voices with minimal disruptions like dropped calls, echoes, or choppy audio. If this resonates, T1 voice service might be your solution.
T1 lines are a natural fit for business phone systems as they were intentionally designed for this purpose. T-Carrier technology, including T1 (1.5 Mbps) and T3 (45 Mbps), was initially developed for use by phone companies.</description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</guid><description>Traditional business bandwidth solutions, typically offering low to moderate speeds, have long relied on T1 lines and their bonded counterparts. However, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) solutions are rapidly replacing these older technologies, delivering enhanced bandwidth at a lower cost.
We&amp;rsquo;re focusing on services ranging from 1 to 20 Mbps, encompassing both dedicated point-to-point private lines and dedicated internet connections. Ethernet standards also enable private LAN services, facilitating connections between multiple business locations.</description></item></channel></rss>