<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service Manual Adjustments on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/service-manual-adjustments/</link><description>Recent content in Service Manual Adjustments on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/service-manual-adjustments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Service Manual Adjustments &amp; Preparing for Use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</guid><description>In the previous post, I finished cleaning and deoxidizing the keypad and RPM panel. The keypad is now responsive, but the cueing up and down button is overly sensitive and needs further attention.
The RPM panel re-installation was put on hold because the plastic mounting fixtures were cracked, a common issue with Beogram 4002 turntables. I was fortunate that the cracks weren&amp;rsquo;t severe and the fixtures were still usable. To repair them, I used acrylic repair fluid while pressing the pieces together.</description></item><item><title> Beogram 8000 Type 5613: Wisconsin project is ready for record play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-wisconsin-project-is-ready-for-record-play/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-wisconsin-project-is-ready-for-record-play/</guid><description>The Beogram 8000 turntable has undergone service manual checks and adjustments. The power supply voltages are within acceptable ranges, and the forward/reverse scanning LDR adjustments and tracking force are calibrated. A test play confirms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s readiness for listening tests after component reinstallation.
The supply voltage readings at the filter capacitors and regulator outputs are as follows: +15 VDC, -15 VDC, and +5 VDC.
The forward and reverse scanning sensors (LDR devices) have been adjusted to an idle voltage of around 650 mVdc using a three-pin test connector.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Adjusting/Calibrating the Detector Arm Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-adjustingcalibrating-the-detector-arm-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-adjustingcalibrating-the-detector-arm-circuit/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 turntable is nearly ready for use, with most of the necessary adjustments and calibrations finalized.
As planned, the record detection circuit needed adjustment due to a low measurement. Utilizing insights from Beolover&amp;rsquo;s blog post on the Beogram 4002 record detection circuit, the circuit was calibrated to align with the service manual&amp;rsquo;s specifications.
Two components on the main board, 1R26 (a 1MΩ resistor) and 1TR3 (an NPN BC548C transistor), are key in fine-tuning the signal from the record detection circuit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: First Listening Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-first-listening-test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-first-listening-test/</guid><description>I finished the mechanical adjustments on the Beogram today. After turning on my digital scale, I calibrated and locked the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s tracking force counterweight. Following Beolover&amp;rsquo;s method, I secured the calibrated setting by replacing the M3 counterweight adjustment screw on the back of the tonearm with a tightening nut. This prevents accidental changes during transport or handling.
With the counterweight set, I secured the locking nut and added a touch of glue for extra stability.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Service Manual Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-service-manual-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-service-manual-adjustments/</guid><description>The replacement platter motor from Beolover has arrived, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be putting it through its paces soon. Meanwhile, I&amp;rsquo;ve nearly finished the service manual adjustments on this Beogram turntable.
The most time-consuming adjustments on these turntables involve the platter height and leveling. This particular Beogram wasn&amp;rsquo;t level, and the platter height, measured from the top of the fixed arm, was less than the specified 23mm.
To fine-tune these, the platters are removed, and the central threaded bearing is adjusted vertically as needed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going Through the Service Manual Checks and Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-through-the-service-manual-checks-and-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 11:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-through-the-service-manual-checks-and-adjustments/</guid><description>This past weekend, I began working on some of the checks and adjustments outlined in the Beogram 4002 service manual. The manual details both electrical and mechanical procedures.
On the electrical side, my primary focus is to ensure that the photo sensors generate strong signals when activated by their light sources. Maintaining correct voltages is crucial for the proper function of the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s analog control system.
Mechanically, I&amp;rsquo;ll be aligning both the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s fixed arm and tonearm.</description></item></channel></rss>