<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cruise on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cruise/</link><description>Recent content in Cruise on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cruise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reserve a magical Disney experience aboard the Disney Adventure through Traveloka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</guid><description>Starting in the fourth quarter of 2024, travelers can book voyages with Disney Cruise Lines departing from Singapore through the Traveloka app, according to an announcement from the Southeast Asian travel platform. This addition to Traveloka&amp;rsquo;s offerings reinforces the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to showcasing the diverse experiences and attractions available in Singapore.
Launching in late 2025, the Disney Adventure will call Singapore its home port. The ship boasts seven themed areas with Disney-themed dining and exciting onboard activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</a></p></description></item><item><title>23 lessons I picked up during my Royal Caribbean voyage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 03:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</guid><description>Tips for Enjoying Your Royal Caribbean Cruise Here&amp;rsquo;s a view from the Viking Crown Lounge on Deck 14.
And here are some tips for your cruise:
Pack light on sunscreen, heavier on cleanser. Remember that everything onboard caters to US standards: food portions, electrical outlets, and currency. Your daily cruise newsletter is your best friend. Delivered to your room every afternoon, it highlights all activities and indicates which ones require payment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bhaya Cruises has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for five consecutive years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</guid><description>Source: Bhaya Cruises website.
The luxury cruise company Bhaya Cruises, which operates in Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Halong Bay, has received TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Certificate of Excellence award for 2015. This recognition was given to three of their brands: Bhaya Classic, The Au Co, and Legend Halong. This marks the fifth year in a row that Bhaya Cruises has been acknowledged for its exceptional service.
The Certificate of Excellence is a prestigious award within the hospitality industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bahrain becomes a member of the Cruise Arabia Alliance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</guid><description>Bahrain has joined the Cruise Arabia Alliance, solidifying the organization&amp;rsquo;s presence in the region. Other members include Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Sharjah, Qatar, and Oman. The alliance promotes collaboration among its members to maintain high standards of service for cruise lines and their passengers.
This announcement took place at the Seatrade Middle East Cruise Forum in Doha, Qatar, hosted by the Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA). Alongside this news, Bahrain also shared that the 2015/2016 cruise season will include 68,000 passengers and 32 visits from major cruise lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emperor Cruises provides day cruises in Nha Trang</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</guid><description>Source: Emperor Cruises website.
Emperor Cruises is introducing day cruises departing from the coastal city of Nha Trang, with plans to offer overnight trips in the future. The company highlights Nha Trang&amp;rsquo;s expanding range of attractions, including the Vinpearl Golf Club and upscale hotels like the Intercontinental, Best Western Premier, and Amanoi.
&amp;ldquo;Emperor Cruises wants to provide tourists with the opportunity to admire the sunset, enjoy cocktails, and savor romantic dinners while cruising on one of the world&amp;rsquo;s 29 most beautiful bays,&amp;rdquo; stated Allister Esguerra, Branch Director of Emperor Cruises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>