<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DSL on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dsl/</link><description>Recent content in DSL on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dsl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shop For DSL and Other Broadband Options Easily</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shop-for-dsl-and-other-broadband-options-easily/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shop-for-dsl-and-other-broadband-options-easily/</guid><description>Frustrated with unreliable internet or sluggish dial-up? Now&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to explore new DSL and broadband choices, thanks to an improved online tool.
Shop for DSL, the innovative search engine, has been enhanced for user-friendliness and comprehensiveness. This real-time tool pinpoints broadband options specific to your location and neatly categorizes them for easy browsing.
What makes this service stand out is its location-based approach. Broadband availability, particularly for DSL and Cable, hinges on your exact location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shop-for-dsl-and-other-broadband-options-easily/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shop-for-dsl-and-other-broadband-options-easily/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s The Best Business Internet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</guid><description>Is your new business in need of internet service for the first time, or does your existing business require better access? You might suspect you could be getting more for your money, and you&amp;rsquo;d probably be right. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the current business internet service options to determine the best fit for you.
The long-standing favored business internet connection for professionals has been the T1 line, recognized for its high reliability and consistent 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Access Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</guid><description>Consumers access the internet in various ways, and businesses have similar options, along with some exclusive ones. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the choices available for companies at their business locations.
Popular consumer broadband choices include DSL and cable for stationary setups, and 3G for mobile use. 4G wireless is emerging, with providers like CLEAR offering it for both fixed and mobile applications. In remote areas, satellite broadband delivers connectivity where wires can&amp;rsquo;t reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why T1 Is Available Where Other Line Services Aren’t</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:47:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</guid><description>Businesses located outside of city centers may struggle to obtain the same quality of network services as their downtown counterparts. While it may seem like options are limited, a reliable and affordable digital telecom service called T1 is often accessible in these areas.
Contrary to outdated beliefs, T1 lines are no longer prohibitively expensive or geographically restricted. They are widely available for businesses, though they may not be suitable for residential use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HughesNet Special Deals on Satellite Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</guid><description>Living remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to be disconnected. Just like you get your TV via satellite, you can get internet access the same way. You&amp;rsquo;ll need a specialized dish that transmits and receives data, connect it to your power source and computer, and you&amp;rsquo;re online!
HughesNet is one provider catering to both homes and businesses. Plans start at $59.99 per month, with download speeds up to 700 Kbps and upload speeds up to 128 Kbps, similar to many DSL or cellular broadband services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Bandwidth Dissimilar Line Bonding From Mushroom Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</guid><description>Want to create your own high-bandwidth internet connection without the exorbitant cost of dedicated services like SONET OC3? Combining consumer-grade options like DSL, cable, or wireless might seem appealing, but achieving a reliable, high-speed connection this way is practically impossible with standard routers.
Instead of another router, consider the Truffles appliance from Mushroom Networks. This innovative device combines multiple internet connections, regardless of type, into a single, high-bandwidth connection.
While traditional &amp;ldquo;T1 bonding&amp;rdquo; offered by carriers has limitations in terms of speed and requiring identical lines from a single provider, Truffles takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WiMAX 2 Will Challenge Fiber For Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</guid><description>The idea that copper and wireless technologies are outdated in terms of bandwidth is circulating. While copper has found new life as a last-mile solution for Metro Ethernet services, and wireless stands out for its unmatched mobility, a new wireless technology is emerging that might surpass even fiber optic speeds.
It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to think that wireless could outpace fiber in terms of bandwidth.
While not all fiber optic services offer top speeds of 10 GigE, with many customers receiving 50 to 100 Mbps, especially in the case of Fiber To The Home (FTTH), the prospect of achieving 100 to 300 Mbps wirelessly anywhere in a city is enticing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Are T1 Lines Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of unreliable DSL and cable internet for your business, consider a T1 line. While DSL and cable are suitable for home use, T1 offers a different level of service. As a regulated telecommunications service, T1 ensures consistent bandwidth and reliable uptime, unlike the consumer-grade alternatives.
T1 lines are widely accessible for businesses and function similarly to utilities. If your business has electricity, water, and phone service, you can likely get a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Redundant Business Internet Connection Using Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Large companies have avoided using consumer-grade broadband services due to concerns about their reliability and performance. While it is prudent to use dedicated circuits with service level agreements for critical business operations, there is a cost-effective solution available for backing up telecom services and enhancing internet speed.
Cable broadband has grown rapidly and seen continuous technological advancements, primarily due to its popularity as a consumer internet service. While alternatives like satellite, wireless, dial-up, and fiber optic exist, they often come with limitations in bandwidth, high installation costs, or limited availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is There Business Fiber Optic Internet Near Me?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:29:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you still dealing with slow internet service plagued by low speeds, network congestion, high latency, packet loss, or all of the above? It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, right? You&amp;rsquo;re likely spending more on subpar service than you would on a high-performance fiber optic broadband upgrade. The question is: &amp;ldquo;Is business fiber optic internet available in my area?&amp;rdquo;
Times Have Changed
When broadband first became an option, choices were limited. DSL was once the leading technology, with even basic ADSL shared connections offering a significant speed boost over previous options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet Broadband For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>When considering broadband, we usually think of DSL, cable internet, or cellular wireless. However, these options are typically consumer-grade and might not be suitable for business needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why these services might be frustrating for businesses and examine a promising alternative.
Cellular wireless, including 3G and 4G, relies on cell towers with limited bandwidth shared among many users. Smartphones consume significant bandwidth, and a high concentration of devices can overload the network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>