<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Single Currency on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/single-currency/</link><description>Recent content in Single Currency on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/single-currency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Battle of the Legal Giants: Can the Euro endure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The German Federal Constitutional Court (BVerfG) has finally submitted a legal question to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on a critically important issue: the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) policy. This policy is widely credited with saving the EU&amp;rsquo;s single currency. If either court finds the policy unlawful, the euro&amp;rsquo;s continued existence could be in jeopardy.
In simple terms, the OMT is a 2012 commitment by the ECB to buy government bonds from struggling eurozone countries on secondary markets (from banks and financial institutions).</description></item><item><title>Preserving the euro: Gauweiler's challenge to the legality of the OMT program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
On June 16th, the Court of Justice ruled in the Gauweiler case, declaring the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program legal under EU law. This decision has significant implications for the ECB&amp;rsquo;s authority, the EU Economic and Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s constitutional structure, and the relationship between the Court of Justice and the referring court, the German Federal Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario.</description></item><item><title>Judicial review of monetary policy and banking supervision by the European Central Bank.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</guid><description>Introduction
The European Union has experienced widespread political and economic consequences due to the financial crisis. These effects extend to the legal realm, leading to the European Central Bank (ECB) not only creating debatable new methods for involvement in monetary policy but also acquiring new authority in banking supervision. Additionally, the ECB, alongside the European Commission and the International Monetary Fund (forming the &amp;lsquo;Troika&amp;rsquo;), has become engaged in austerity measures within Member States requiring financial support.</description></item><item><title>What lies ahead for Greece and the Eurozone: catharsis or catastrophe?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent victory of the anti-austerity party Syriza in the Greek elections raises questions about its potential effects on the EU&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union. Syriza&amp;rsquo;s objective is not to withdraw from the EU or the single currency but to renegotiate Greece&amp;rsquo;s debt and austerity measures. Their goal is to secure debt forgiveness and renegotiate terms, including the removal of austerity demands associated with previous bailouts.
However, this program might encounter legal obstacles due to limitations on debt forgiveness and ending austerity outlined in EU Treaties and Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural report of the European Fiscal Board and the outlook for the EU's fiscal framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-report-of-the-european-fiscal-board-and-the-outlook-for-the-eu-s-fiscal-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 05:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-report-of-the-european-fiscal-board-and-the-outlook-for-the-eu-s-fiscal-framework/</guid><description>Paul Dermine (PhD candidate in EU institutional law, Maastricht University) and Diane Fromage (Assistant Professor of European Law, Faculty of Law, Maastricht University)
EU Fiscal Governance after the Crisis: A Time for Reflection and the European Fiscal Board&amp;rsquo;s First Report
Recent developments suggest that the Eurozone may be entering a new phase. With the sovereign debt crisis subsiding and economic growth gradually returning, discussions about reforming the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) are resurfacing at both the EU and member state levels.</description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the Euro's downfall? EU regulations on exiting EMU or defaulting on debts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The stability of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) is once again in question after a period of relative calm. This follows the announcement of early elections in Greece. Should the anti-austerity party, Syriza, gain control of the government, the consequences could be significant.
It is crucial to note that such an outcome is not guaranteed. Syriza holds a small lead in the polls, and even if they become the leading party, they might not secure enough seats to hold a majority.</description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro.</description></item><item><title>Mario's feet were pulled out from under him by the BVerfG and the ECB's OMT programme.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</guid><description>By Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster
The German Constitutional Court (BVerfG) is set to make a significant decision on the European Union&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union on June 21st. The court will rule on the Gauweiler case, which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. This program, designed to stabilize struggling Eurozone economies, was challenged by plaintiffs questioning its legal foundation.</description></item><item><title>Legal Challenges of Implementing the Digital Euro by the Central Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:21:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</guid><description>Dr. (Annelieke) Anne Marieke Mooij, Tilburg University
The European Central Bank (ECB) is preparing to introduce a digital euro, a central bank digital currency (CBDC). The ECB has explored several design options, ranging from restricted access for financial institutions to broad accessibility for all consumers via national central banks. While a final design hasn&amp;rsquo;t been chosen, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s statements suggest a preference for broader accessibility. This blog post will examine the primary legal hurdles associated with each design option.</description></item></channel></rss>