<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Service Providers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-service-providers/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Service Providers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-service-providers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Service Providers Colocate With Customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</guid><description>A new trend is emerging, and it&amp;rsquo;s not just about companies moving their data to the cloud. Now, cloud service providers are moving into the same facilities as their customers.
Why is this happening? Companies are realizing that running applications on distant servers can&amp;rsquo;t match the speed of having them on-site. While this can be addressed by investing in high-bandwidth, low-latency connections, it&amp;rsquo;s often more cost-effective to simply be in the same location as your provider.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>SDN Performance Takes a Leaf of Faith</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cloud computing has highlighted the importance of reliable internet connections, known as WANs (Wide Area Networks). In the past, slow file transfers or unreliable internet were acceptable because crucial tasks were handled within the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network. However, now that businesses rely on cloud services, the performance of the WAN is just as crucial as the internal network (LAN).
WAN Challenges
The main challenge with WANs is that businesses don&amp;rsquo;t control them like they do their internal networks.</description></item></channel></rss>