<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infrastructure/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infrastructure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India and Bangladesh have initiated connectivity projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</guid><description>The Prime Ministers of India and Bangladesh, Narendra Modi and Sheikh Hasina, respectively, along with West Bengal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Minister, Mamata Banerjee, inaugurated multiple connectivity initiatives between the two nations.
These projects include the inauguration of the second Bhairab and Titas Railway Bridges, situated on the 320-km Dhaka-Chittagong railway line in Bangladesh. Additionally, the International Rail Passenger Terminus in Kolkata, India, was also inaugurated.
The dignitaries also launched the first run of the Bandhan Express, connecting Kolkata to Khulna in southwest Bangladesh, covering a distance of over 150km.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure as a Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</guid><description>Cloud computing is widely understood to have three main levels: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS). The most fundamental of these is IaaS, which forms the basis for the other two. IaaS essentially refers to providing basic hardware and operating system software over the internet.
Infrastructure is fairly self-explanatory: it&amp;rsquo;s the foundational hardware and software needed for computing. When considering cloud infrastructure, the comparison is often made with having your own data center.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</guid><description>The current focus on infrastructure often overlooks a critical element: fiber optic broadband. While roads, bridges, and utilities are essential, fiber optic networks are the backbone of the 21st-century economy. Just as electricity revolutionized the 20th century, fiber optics will define this one.
We&amp;rsquo;ve outgrown the limitations of traditional wireline systems. Fiber optic technology, with its capacity for high bandwidth, is the only way to meet the growing demand for data-intensive applications.</description></item><item><title>The Yokohama Convention &amp; Visitors Bureau extends a warm welcome to Muslim travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 12:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</guid><description>Source: Yokohama Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau
The Yokohama Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau (YCVB) reports that its specialized Muslim Tourist Information microsite, part of the official Yokohama Visitors&amp;rsquo; Guide website, is gaining traction with Muslims in Southeast Asia.
Launched in December 2013, the Muslim Tourist Information website highlights tourist attractions, dining, halal shops, and mosques, all recommended by Yokohama&amp;rsquo;s Muslim residents. A survey of Southeast Asian Muslims revealed that over 90% found the information on restaurants, mosques, and recommended itineraries helpful.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Five Ways to Squeeze More ROI Out of Your Server Room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-ways-to-squeeze-more-roi-out-of-your-server-room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 19:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-ways-to-squeeze-more-roi-out-of-your-server-room/</guid><description>Servers are crucial for modern businesses as they manage internal and external data. While this service requires investment, a strategic approach to your server infrastructure can lead to long-term cost savings without affecting performance. Here are five methods to maximize your server room&amp;rsquo;s ROI.
Prioritize Cooling: Efficient cooling is vital for managing server room energy costs. Servers generate significant heat, demanding more than just internal fans. Several factors, both inside and outside the cabinet, can impact cooling efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market.</description></item><item><title>Airswift Holdings, a global recruiting company, operates in 57 locations worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 05:20:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Airswift Holdings. From left, Duncan Gregson, CEO of Air Energi; Janette Marx, COO, Airswift, Ian Langley, Chairman, Airswift; Peter Searle, CEO, Airswift; and Tobias Reed, CEO of Swift Worldwide Resources.
Air Energi Group and Swift Worldwide Resources combined to establish Airswift Holdings, a global staffing company. Airswift specializes in placing contract and permanent employees, providing resource consultation, assisting with global mobility, and developing managed solutions for companies in the energy, process, and infrastructure sectors.</description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process.</description></item><item><title>Is There a Broadband Stimulus Job For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</guid><description>The U.S. government is investing an additional $795 million in broadband stimulus funding to address the country&amp;rsquo;s lag behind nations like Japan and Korea in providing affordable, high-speed internet. This investment presents a potential win-win situation, offering both short-term job creation and long-term economic benefits.
One study projects the creation of approximately 5,000 immediate jobs from these high-speed internet projects. While seemingly small compared to the number of job seekers, it&amp;rsquo;s a step in the right direction.</description></item><item><title>Can You Benefit From New Cloud Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about cloud computing and might be wondering if it can help your small or medium-sized business (SMB). While it seems like cloud services are designed for large corporations, they offer significant potential for businesses of all sizes.
The cloud can be even more beneficial for SMBs because it levels the playing field. Large companies often have the resources to build their own private clouds, while smaller companies may struggle with the cost and staffing required for such an undertaking.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Community Builds Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a narrative circulating that our infrastructure is failing. While this might be true in some areas, a massive construction project is currently underway to create a robust fiber optic network across the nation. This &amp;ldquo;nervous system&amp;rdquo; for information technology promises practically limitless, low-lag bandwidth for the foreseeable future.
This surge in fiber optic infrastructure isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by failing systems, but rather by existing infrastructure reaching full capacity. The late 20th century witnessed a fiber optic boom, which initially seemed excessive when the tech bubble burst.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>T1's for Business Parks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</guid><description>Most businesses require reliable communication services, but options can be limited outside of major city centers. While downtown areas boast a variety of high-speed internet providers, businesses in industrial parks often face fewer choices.
Similar to essential utilities, reliable internet access is crucial for modern businesses. However, many older industrial parks were developed before the internet&amp;rsquo;s prominence, lacking the infrastructure for high-speed connections.
Despite this, businesses in these areas still have reliable options.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery.</description></item><item><title>Thailand is gaining traction as a top choice for hosting business events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</guid><description>Source: TCEB.
Thailand, with the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB) at the helm, is establishing itself as a prime location for business events. As the Thai government&amp;rsquo;s primary representative for this sector, TCEB plays a vital role in solidifying Thailand&amp;rsquo;s leading position in the Asian business events industry and Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a top-tier destination for international business events.
The Thai business events sector is projected to experience robust growth in 2015, anticipating over a million visitors and generating approximately US$3.</description></item></channel></rss>