<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cybercrime on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cybercrime/</link><description>Recent content in Cybercrime on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cybercrime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Caution: Superman is poisonous</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</guid><description>According to a McAfee blog post, Superman poses a significant online threat. The company argues that the widespread presence of superheroes beyond comic books allows hackers and scammers to exploit them for cybercrime.
McAfee&amp;rsquo;s survey, which used their SiteAdvisor site ratings, revealed that Superman is the &amp;ldquo;Most Toxic Superhero.&amp;rdquo; The study found that searches combining &amp;ldquo;Superman&amp;rdquo; with terms like &amp;ldquo;free torrent download,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;watch,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;free app,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; have a 16.5% chance of leading to websites containing threats like spyware, adware, spam, phishing, viruses, and other malware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure Any Public WiFi Hotspot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: you&amp;rsquo;re away from your secure office network or home WiFi, relying on public WiFi that makes you uneasy. While convenient, unsecured WiFi hotspots present a security risk. How can you be sure someone isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring your activity with malicious software when you send private emails or sensitive data?
](http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-1726600-11129503)
It&amp;rsquo;s a valid concern. Cybercrime is rampant, and tools for intercepting data on public WiFi are readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Undercover Laptop Sleeve Computer Cloaking Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a legendary product in computer security that&amp;rsquo;s not a fancy gadget but a simple, low-tech solution: a dirty old bag disguised as a laptop sleeve. This &amp;ldquo;Undercover Laptop Sleeve&amp;rdquo; from Lazybone uses clever disguise as its security mechanism.
The sleeve&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness lies in its unappealing appearance. To a potential thief, it looks like an ordinary, grubby mailing envelope, not a valuable laptop&amp;rsquo;s hiding place. This is crucial considering the potential loss of expensive hardware and sensitive data stored on most laptops...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need A Managed Security Services Provider?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 05:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</guid><description>Cybercrime has evolved from mere mischief into a substantial threat focused on financial gain. If your network holds valuable data, cybercriminals will see it as a target, making network security essential.
Protecting your digital assets isn&amp;rsquo;t optional; the choice lies in managing it yourself or outsourcing it to managed security services, also known as Security as a Service (SaaS).
MegaPath, a prominent carrier, provides comprehensive managed security services, including firewalls, intrusion prevention, malware and virus protection, web filtering, anti-spam measures, application control, data leak prevention, log management, vulnerability assessments, security information management, and file integrity monitoring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Before you decide to check out Ronaldo, reconsider your decision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</guid><description>A study by McAfee, a part of Intel Security, reveals that cybercriminals often use popular figures like Cristiano Ronaldo to lure unsuspecting users to malicious websites. These websites, designed to look like legitimate fan pages, can infect devices with malware capable of stealing personal information. McAfee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Red Card Club&amp;rdquo; list highlights the top eleven footballers whose names are most frequently used in these scams, with Ronaldo topping the list, followed by Lionel Messi and Iker Cassillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing financial consequences of cybercrime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</guid><description>Source: HP infographic.
HP recently released the findings of their sixth annual study, conducted in partnership with the Ponemon Institute, exploring the financial effects of cyberattacks on both public and private sectors.
The study shows a substantial rise in the total cost of cybercrime, indicating that smaller companies bear a proportionally larger cost than larger ones.
The 2015 Cost of Cyber Crime Study, carried out by the Ponemon Institute and supported by HP Enterprise Security, calculates the yearly cost of cybercrime for businesses across seven countries: the US, UK, Japan, Germany, Australia, Brazil, and Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>