<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Leave on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/leave/</link><description>Recent content in Leave on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 01:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/leave/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DBS launches improved paternity leave program in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-launches-improved-paternity-leave-program-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 01:19:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-launches-improved-paternity-leave-program-in-singapore/</guid><description>DBS Bank will enhance its paternity leave policy in Singapore, following Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong&amp;rsquo;s call to extend such leave during the National Day Rally on August 23. This new policy, announced on August 26, allows fathers employed by the bank to take two weeks of paternity leave, retroactive to January 2015.
Cheong Meng Foong, DBS Group Head of Rewards, emphasized the bank&amp;rsquo;s commitment to its employees&amp;rsquo; well-being: &amp;ldquo;At DBS, people are our most important resource, and we consistently seek to support them.</description></item><item><title>If you are a voter who is undecided or uncertain, here is why you should consider remaining in the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 05:40:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
As the referendum campaign concludes, undecided voters should consider the arguments for remaining in the European Union. This piece outlines the reasons for staying, addressing counter-arguments from the Leave campaign.
Why Remain?
Staying in the EU offers several advantages: economic benefits, security, improved workers&amp;rsquo; rights, and environmental protection. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine each.
Economic Benefits
EU membership grants the UK access to the world&amp;rsquo;s largest market, along with trade deals with 50 additional countries.</description></item></channel></rss>