<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article 7 TEU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-7-teu/</link><description>Recent content in Article 7 TEU on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-7-teu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights under ordinary EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Can the EU penalize its member states for consistently violating human rights and the rule of law? And if so, how?
This article, the second in a three-part series, explores this question. The first installment analyzed the official mechanism designed for this purpose: Article 7 TEU. As previously discussed, this process, which could result in the suspension of certain EU membership rights for a member state, is highly political, offers limited involvement from EU courts, and is challenging to implement.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU issues its first ruling on interim measures regarding the rule of law in Poland.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-issues-its-first-ruling-on-interim-measures-regarding-the-rule-of-law-in-poland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-issues-its-first-ruling-on-interim-measures-regarding-the-rule-of-law-in-poland/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The October 19th decision by the Vice-President of the Court of Justice concerning Poland&amp;rsquo;s Judiciary Reform Act is groundbreaking. This decision, which orders Poland to halt the implementation of the Act and prevents the removal of judges due to the new retirement age, represents uncharted territory. It places the Court of Justice in the unprecedented position of compelling a sovereign member state to decide between adhering to European integration principles or embracing illiberalism.</description></item><item><title>Going from bad to worse? Examining the rule of law initiatives of the Commission and the Council</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</guid><description>Dimitry Kochenov* and Laurent Pech**
*Professor of EU Constitutional Law at the University of Groningen and Visiting Professor of Private Law at the Universita degli studi di Torino
**Jean Monnet Professor of EU Public Law, Head of the Law and Politics Department at Middlesex University London
The principle of the rule of law is a cornerstone of the European Union, as stated in Article 2 of the Treaty on European Union.</description></item><item><title>Is Malta on the verge of a Van Gend moment for EU rule of law through its courts' judicial independence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-malta-on-the-verge-of-a-van-gend-moment-for-eu-rule-of-law-through-its-courts-judicial-independence/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 16:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-malta-on-the-verge-of-a-van-gend-moment-for-eu-rule-of-law-through-its-courts-judicial-independence/</guid><description>Justin Borg-Barthet, Senior Lecturer in EU Law at the University of Aberdeen, writes:
Despite being an EU member for fifteen years, Maltese courts have been hesitant to refer legal interpretation questions to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). This could change with a case that has significant implications for the direct effect of EU member states&amp;rsquo; rule of law and human rights obligations. This legal challenge raises new and critical questions about democratizing EU constitutional law, similar to how the internal market law was democratized through the Van Gend case.</description></item><item><title>Is Poland violating the principle of effective judicial protection? Recent developments in the CJEU suggest so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</guid><description>Femke Gremmelprez, PhD Researcher and Academic Assistant, Department of European, Public and International Law, Research group Ghent European Law Institute
While the Court of Justice plays a significant role in enforcing EU law through infringement and preliminary ruling procedures (Articles 258 and 267 TFEU, respectively), it has largely been excluded from enforcing EU values, particularly the rule of law. The EU Treaties lack explicit provisions granting the Court of Justice the power to address rule of law breaches by Member States.</description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the downfall of Poland's controversial "judicial reforms"? Reflections on the recent ECJ decision in Commission v Poland regarding the Independence of the Supreme Court.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-downfall-of-poland-s-controversial-judicial-reforms-reflections-on-the-recent-ecj-decision-in-commission-v-poland-regarding-the-independence-of-the-supreme-court/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-downfall-of-poland-s-controversial-judicial-reforms-reflections-on-the-recent-ecj-decision-in-commission-v-poland-regarding-the-independence-of-the-supreme-court/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, a Professor of European Law at Middlesex University London, and Sébastien Platon, a Professor of Public Law at the University of Bordeaux, have written about a situation unfolding in a country within the EU where the government and parliament, both controlled by the same political party, have made changes to their judicial system.
These changes include lowering the retirement age for judges on the country&amp;rsquo;s highest court. This move has been presented by the government as a necessary reform to hold accountable judges who were supposedly involved in the country&amp;rsquo;s previous communist regime, even though that regime ended three decades ago.</description></item><item><title>The complete text of the Commission Opinion on the Rule of Law in Poland, dated 1 June 2016, is now accessible.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complete-text-of-the-commission-opinion-on-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-dated-1-june-2016-is-now-accessible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 03:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complete-text-of-the-commission-opinion-on-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-dated-1-june-2016-is-now-accessible/</guid><description>Professor Laurent Pech
Those interested in the rule of law might find the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s unpublished Opinion on the Rule of Law in Poland, adopted June 1, 2016, insightful (see the Annex for the full text).
This post aims to provide context for non-experts. It will briefly outline the instrument used by the Commission to formulate its Rule of Law Opinion and then summarize why the Commission felt compelled to address rule of law concerns in Poland.</description></item></channel></rss>