<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Arm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arm/</link><description>Recent content in Arm on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/arm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523) began, as always, with the arm lowering mechanism. The lubricants in these mechanisms often harden with age, preventing the tonearm from lowering correctly. The mechanism is shown here in its original condition:
Each moving part was removed
for cleaning and re-lubrication before reassembly. Next, I lubricated the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point. This required removing the sensor arm, as pictured below from the back:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Final Adjustments, Repair of a Damaged Pinth Corner and Test Drive with Bobby Hutcherson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration is nearing completion. Following the installation of new gold-plated RCA plugs, I made adjustments to the sub-chassis, platter height, and meticulously cleaned the aluminum surfaces. To prevent the needle from contacting the platter ribs if the record detection mechanism fails, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit.
Subsequently, I calibrated the tracking weight scale and enhanced the counterweight adjustment mechanism. The original flimsy circlip was replaced with a more durable M3 nut and washer setup, enhancing its resistance to transport-related stress.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Prematurely Activating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is progressing well. Rebuilding the deck led to a successful initial power-up where the carriage moved to the correct position, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower. A visual inspection showed a disconnected thin grey wire from the SK3054 NPN power transistor (0TR4).
Tracing the wiring and consulting the schematic revealed that the grey wire connected to the transistor&amp;rsquo;s emitter, responsible for bypassing a current-limiting resistor (7R1) during the arm&amp;rsquo;s initial descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Final Touches - AC Motor Calibration, Adjusting Platter and Sub-Chassis and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration is nearly complete. After deep cleaning the aluminum panels and platter, I adjusted the sub-chassis and platter height, tonearm lowering limit, and tracking weight.
There are videos on my YouTube channel demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, similar for the 4000 and 4002 models. Another video covers the crucial adjustment of lowering limits, essential because the 4002&amp;rsquo;s system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent damage from photosensor failure. Proper adjustment acts as a safeguard, potentially saving an expensive cartridge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments, a New Solenoid, and Test Drive with Christoph Spendel &amp; Wolfgang Schlüter Group on MPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</guid><description>The final steps of restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) involved replacing the sensor arm light bulb with an LED assembly and performing standard adjustments. These included calibrating the tracking feedback, platter height, level, sub-chassis height, and arm lowering limit, which prevents stylus damage.
To ensure accurate tracking weight calibration, the C-clip securing the counterweight adjustment screw was replaced with an M3 nut and washer for permanent fixation. This guarantees that the calibration remains consistent during shipping.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's "The Love Connection"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project is finished after some final tuning. I made adjustments to the platter height and sub-chassis alignment, documenting the process for my YouTube channel. While my videos feature a Beogram 4000, the method for adjusting the platter bearing and sub-chassis are quite similar for the 4002 model.
The arm lowering limit was the next step, a crucial adjustment to safeguard the cantilever if the record detection malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter Height, Tonearm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>After successfully positioning the top aluminum plates, I could adjust the sub-chassis and platter. This step is crucial as it sets the foundation for adjusting the arm lowering limits and, ultimately, the tracking force. This Beogram will be ready for an initial test run once this is completed. I&amp;rsquo;ve previously provided detailed explanations of the chassis and platter adjustment process on my blog and YouTube channel. Two videos demonstrate the platter bearing adjustment and the subchassis adjustment (using a Beogram 4000 as an example, although the procedure is almost identical for the 4002).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Final Adjustments, Some Odds and Ends and a Test Drive with Cal Tjader</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</guid><description>After switching the original black plinth with a teak one from a Beogram 4002, it was time for the final adjustments and a test run of the Beogram 4000 turntable. I started by setting the platter height, tilt, and alignment with the surrounding aluminum panels. Next, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowest point to make sure the needle wouldn&amp;rsquo;t touch the black ribs on the platter if the platter detection system malfunctioned.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Chico Hamilton on Auto-Repeat!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</guid><description>It was time for the final adjustments on the Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration project. Adjusting the platter and sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking force is always a satisfying part of the process. It means the turntable is ready for its initial post-restoration playback. Observing the intricate mechanics in motion, bringing out the best in vintage vinyl, is always captivating.
This Beogram presented a unique sub-chassis and platter adjustment challenge. The platter was positioned too close to the front right edge of the aluminum plate cutout.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 11:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism/</guid><description>My work began on the recently acquired Beogram 4002 (5513). The arm lowering mechanism, as is common, was the first issue to address. The usual hardened lubricant was present, resulting in sluggish movement. The setup can be seen here:
To address this, I removed the linkages and the damper to clean and lubricate them:
Here, the disassembled damper and linkages are visible:
A detailed video demonstration of this process is available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Adjusting Platter and Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 23:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</guid><description>The visual appeal of a Beogram 400x relies heavily on the platter&amp;rsquo;s alignment with its surrounding aluminum panels. A correctly aligned platter sits flush with these panels, allowing the black &amp;lsquo;ribs&amp;rsquo; to stand out against a flat aluminum surface. Achieving this alignment is intricate, requiring several parameters to be perfectly adjusted. I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that a sensor arm that isn&amp;rsquo;t entirely parallel to the floating chassis often complicates this process. Both the service manual and my videos detail an adjustment procedure assuming the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s parallelism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Mechanisms, and Installation of a New Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, often problematic due to hardened lubricants, required attention. While the lowering damper section was functional, the damper-to-arm linkage was stuck and only moved because its pin had loosened.
The restoration process involved carefully disassembling the arm lowering mechanism, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubrication. The seized damper-to-arm linkage was removed, requiring a workbench procedure to press out its stuck pin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My work began on the Beogram 4000 turntable that arrived from Germany. As is my practice, the tracking and arm lowering mechanisms were the first to be refurbished. The arm lowering mechanism, controlled by a solenoid and damper arrangement, is pictured here:
After removing components requiring cleaning and lubrication, the area looked like this:
Here are the disassembled parts:
With cleaning and lubrication complete, reassembly followed. Next, I addressed the seized damper-to-arm linkage, accessible only after detaching the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Upgrade of the Tracking System with a LED Based Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</guid><description>With the DC motor operating correctly, the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) continued with the arm lowering mechanism and tracking feedback system.
The arm lowering mechanism, consisting of a solenoid and damper, was disassembled, cleaned, and lubricated. This process involved removing the damper, linkages, retaining washer, and spring. Detailed videos illustrating the rebuilding process are available. After reassembly, the arms were meticulously aligned parallel to each other and the keypad edge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My first step when restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable is to focus on the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. The arm lowering mechanism often requires attention because hardened lubricants can hinder the solenoid and damper assemblies. To address this, I disassemble the mechanism.
Once the solenoid and linkages are removed, I take the parts to my workbench for cleaning and re-lubrication.
Next, I address the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm, as it can cause delays in arm lowering, particularly after storage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Sub-Chassis and the Platter, and RPM Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 04:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</guid><description>Today was dedicated to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis on a Beogram 4002 (5513) that I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I aimed to align the platter&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface with the surrounding panels, center the sub-chassis within the transport locks&amp;rsquo; limits, and ensure the arms were parallel to the aluminum surfaces. It&amp;rsquo;s intricate work involving aligning numerous components. After gaining experience with this process, I achieved a satisfactory result, aligning the Beogram to specifications.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddy Hubbard's 1975 Album "Polar AC"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable to its former glory is always fulfilling. This particular restoration involved several meticulous adjustments before I could relish Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s music.
The first crucial step was aligning the platter and arms flawlessly. Next, I had to align the platter with its surrounding aluminum panels while ensuring the chassis remained suspended, delicately balanced on its spring-loaded arms. This procedure requires precision as the tolerances for these adjustments are minimal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's Liquid Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</guid><description>Following the installation of the Beolover 4002 Commander remote control and internal RIAA pre-amplifier, it was time for final adjustments before testing the turntable. The first step was tracking feedback adjustment. A blue trimmer on the tracking sensor LED light source simplified the fine-tuning of the feedback after the coarse mechanical adjustment of the sensor housing.
Next, the subclasses and platter height were adjusted, followed by the arm lowering limit. The lowering limit ensures the needle can descend below the record surface without hitting the platter ribs if the record detection fails.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustments, Cleaning the Aluminum Surfaces and a First Spin with Freddie Hubbard!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</guid><description>Following the installation of a new gold-plated DIN 5 plug, the Beogram 4000 was ready for its initial test. The RPM was fine-tuned using a custom Beolover RPM device, aided by the recently installed precision multi-turn trimmers. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that allowing the unit to warm up for approximately 15 minutes before this adjustment is recommended, as the RPM can fluctuate slightly during this period. For fellow enthusiasts, the Beolover RPM device is available upon request via email or the contact form and includes a separate base for convenient setup and occasional RPM checks.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival on Beolover's Bench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</guid><description>During the holiday season, I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable for repair. My initial assessment showed that it was packaged very well, with some innovative methods used to protect it during shipping.
The dust cover was secured using soft foam blocks to hold the sub-platter and the RPM panel in place.
The MMC20E cartridge was also protected by foam and arrived in good condition.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the cartridge after unpacking:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 06:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</guid><description>My work began with the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, as is customary for me. My client had already addressed the cleaning and lubrication of the damper and solenoid linkages, so my task was to detach the linkage connecting the damper and tonearm. This required removing the sensor arm assembly, as shown here:
Extracting the sensor arm involved removing two screws at its base:
The linkage could then be detached:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Platter, Sub-Chassis, Arm Lowering Limit and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>To prepare the Beogram 4002 (5513) for testing, several mechanical adjustments were required. The platter needed to be perfectly aligned with the surrounding aluminum plates. This involved balancing the floating sub-chassis within its support brackets. After aligning the chassis and platter, the arm lowering limit was addressed. Finally, the tracking force was calibrated to match the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s weight dial.
Prior to adjusting the sub-chassis, damaged cabinet guidance washers, crucial for securing the top aluminum plates, were replaced with 3D-printed replicas.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A Second Beogram 4002 (5523) Arrived for some TLC - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) in need of restoration arrived with its MMC4000 cartridge still attached and transport locks disengaged, causing initial concern about potential damage. The foam meant to support the tonearm had deteriorated, leaving it to swing freely.
Fortunately, the cartridge appeared undamaged, likely due to the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s light weight and protective tape. Testing on a restored Beogram 4000 confirmed its functionality.
The hood was in good condition, showing only minor scratches and signs of polishing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and the Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I was working on had a completely frozen arm lowering mechanism. The old lubricant had become so hardened that I had to use a screwdriver to pry the linkages off their pivot pins. This is a common issue, easily resolved by cleaning and re-lubricating the mechanism. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the solenoid, damper, and linkages before disassembly:
This image shows the disassembled parts laid out on my workbench:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) began with the arm lowering and tracking systems, as these are essential for any further testing or repair work.
To start, I took out the damper and linkages to clean and lubricate them. Thankfully, all the components were in good condition, so lubrication and reassembly were straightforward. Next, I lubricated the pivot point connecting the damper to the arm linkage. This required removing the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Repair of a Dead H-Bridge and Some Other Updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-dead-h-bridge-and-some-other-updates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:52:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-dead-h-bridge-and-some-other-updates/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, previously restored in 2020, returned for repair. The issue was a familiar one: the carriage wouldn&amp;rsquo;t move towards the platter, suggesting a faulty power transistor in the carriage motor&amp;rsquo;s H-bridge.
This recurring problem has become a pattern, leading to a routine replacement of the H-bridge transistors during restorations. However, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t standard practice in 2020, necessitating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s return for transistor replacement.
Along with the H-bridge transistors, other known problematic components were also updated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Idris Muhammad (KU-17) After Platter and Tonearm Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day at the shop, where another Beogram 4002 (5513) is looking and sounding fantastic! The finishing touches involved adjusting the sub-chassis and platter to ensure they float freely and sit flush with the deck&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface. My YouTube channel features two videos demonstrating these adjustments for a Beogram 4000, which are very similar to the 4002 model.
Afterward, the tonearm lowering limit was adjusted, a crucial procedure given the 4002&amp;rsquo;s control system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent photosensor malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>Following the repair of the MMC cartridge mount on the Beogram 4000, attention shifted to the malfunctioning arm lowering and tracking mechanisms.
The arm lowering system, comprising a solenoid and damper, was examined. The damper and its associated linkages were removed for cleaning and lubrication.
Inspection revealed the absence of a vital rubber washer in the damper unit, substituted with a makeshift transparency foil piece. This modification hindered proper damper function.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A Stuck Tonearm and Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously repaired, returned with a tonearm tracking issue. The problem was a misaligned tracking sensor aperture obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. To fix this, I slightly repositioned the aperture after loosening its screw. I replaced the original screw with a more secure flat socket head screw to prevent future misalignment. I then recalibrated the tracking sensor feedback.
While the Beogram was with me, the customer decided to have the dust cover polished.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED and Improvement of the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>Replacing the sensor arm LED is typically the final step in converting a Beogram 4002 to use all LEDs. After restoring the DC motor, the next task was to install a recently designed flex-PCB-based LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb. The image below shows the sensor arm with the detector assembly removed:
Upon zooming in on the full-resolution image, a small black spot is visible on the glass bulb. This spot indicates significant tungsten evaporation from the filament, suggesting the bulb is nearing the end of its life and could soon fail, rendering the Beogram inoperable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter and Tonearm Weight and Limits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</guid><description>The final stage of restoring the Beogram 4002 (5503) involved balancing the sub-chassis, setting the correct platter height, and adjusting the tonearm. To ensure the best range of motion, the sub-chassis must be carefully positioned between the transport lock clamps. The platter height and vertical alignment need to be set so that the platter sits level with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s aluminum covers. This allows for the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit to be established and the tracking weight to be calibrated against the adjustment dial located on the arm weight housing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Floating Chassis, Arm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>The next steps were to make adjustments to the platter, sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking weight. Additional information on this process is available on my Beogram 4000 page, which includes posts and videos. Before starting, I needed to replace the cabinet guiding washers because they were either damaged or replaced with unsuitable substitutes.
[Image of a missing cabinet guidance washer]
A video demonstrating this process is available in my Beogram 4002 playlist on my YouTube channel.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Arm, Replacement of the Damper Gasket and Re-Glueing of a Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 required a few final adjustments before it could be returned to its owner following a wiring sleeve replacement on the carriage harness and a fix for an intermittent solenoid.
During its initial restoration in 2020, I was unfamiliar with some common problems that these turntables develop. One such issue involves the damper gasket, which tends to harden over time. This hardening can lead to uneven arm lowering due to inconsistent airflow around the gasket.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Linear Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</guid><description>My restoration project of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable started with the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. These mechanisms often require attention because of hardened lubricants and misadjusted tracking sensors.
After taking the mechanism apart for cleaning and lubrication, I addressed the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm, which commonly experiences stiffness due to hardened lubricants.
The sensor arm was then removed for disassembly to further work on the linkage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A Broken Off Solenoid Plunger and New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, recently serviced and returned to a customer, unexpectedly came back with a faulty tonearm. The culprit was a broken solenoid plunger, a part responsible for lowering the tonearm. This unusual breakage was likely due to material fatigue.
To fix the issue, the solenoid was replaced with one from a donor Beogram 4002. During the repair, it was discovered that the transport lock bushings had also deteriorated and needed replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Broken SO ('Shut Off') Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 05:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-so-shut-off-switch/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about a malfunctioning &amp;ldquo;Shut Off&amp;rdquo; (SO) switch, which was missing a crucial plastic part, causing issues with the deck&amp;rsquo;s shutdown process. To address this, a 3D printed replacement part was designed and created. The &amp;ldquo;End Switch&amp;rdquo; (ES), still equipped with its plastic component, is pictured alongside the SO switch, highlighting the missing element.
Creating a functional replacement part was challenging due to its small size and the limitations of the 3D printer.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with an SMD LED Light Source and Adjustment of the Feedback Sensisitivy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 turntable had a damaged part (the tracking sensor aperture) that was bent and obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. This issue prevented the tracking system from working correctly. The initial setup used an incandescent light bulb:
Upon removing the bulb housing, it was evident that the aperture was bent and rubbing against the optical sensor housing:
The aperture was carefully straightened, and the bulb assembly was replaced with a new SMD LED light source.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Lever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 11:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</guid><description>A customer asked for help with a broken part, a solenoid lever, from their Beogram 4002 Type 5503 turntable. The AC-powered versions of this model use a mechanical switch to control the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s current after the arm lowers. To accomplish this, the solenoid arm has a tab that depresses the switch once the arm is down. Some later AC versions use a plastic extension riveted to the lever to achieve this, a design change I observed to be problematic in my experience.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:19:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>The initial phase of the Beogram 4000 restoration involved the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking mechanisms. The solenoid and damper, essential for the arm&amp;rsquo;s smooth and controlled descent onto the record, were revealed.
Each part was carefully removed, cleaned, and lubricated.
Attention then turned to the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm. Located on the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s side, it required the arm&amp;rsquo;s removal to access and lubricate the linkage&amp;rsquo;s pivot point.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Chassis, Platter, Tonearm Limits and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. After adjusting the sub-chassis and platter, I set the tonearm limits and calibrated the tracking force. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to finalize the platter height before adjusting the arm, ensuring the correct arm-to-platter distance. My YouTube channel has videos demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, particularly for the Beogram 4000, but the 4002 process is similar.
Here’s the result:
The platter is now centered and level within the main aluminum plate.</description></item></channel></rss>