<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Connection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-connection/</link><description>Recent content in Network Connection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-connection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>