<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marina on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marina/</link><description>Recent content in Marina on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Nongsa Regatta took place in January 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</guid><description>Source: Nongsa Regatta Facebook page.
The first Nongsa Regatta will take place at Nongsa Point Marina &amp;amp; Resort in Batam, Indonesia, from January 27th to 31st, 2016. This period coincides with the strongest point of the northeast monsoon. The competition welcomes yachts, sporting boats, and racing multihulls. Additionally, there will be races for dinghies and traditional &amp;ldquo;kolek&amp;rdquo; boats.
Having hosted the Singapore Straits Regatta for almost two decades, the resort possesses extensive experience in regattas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Iftar gatherings at AquaMarine, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 03:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</guid><description>Originally from the Marina Mandarin Singapore website, this photo displays the Bakar Station&amp;rsquo;s offerings of chicken, oxtail, prawns, and sea bass cooked in banana leaves.
AquaMarine, a Halal-certified buffet restaurant, has recently renovated its Terrace@AquaMarine space. Now fully air-conditioned, it&amp;rsquo;s an ideal location for larger gatherings.
The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s current iftar menu, available until July 17th, features dishes like dates, slow-roasted baby lamb seasoned with Moroccan spices, bulgur wheat with raita, and a traditional Indonesian oxtail soup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Marina Mandarin Singapore welcomes the arrival of hairy crabs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</guid><description>Peach Blossoms, the renowned Cantonese restaurant located on the 5th level of Marina Mandarin Singapore, is now offering a seasonal delicacy flown in from Shanghai, China: hairy crabs.
Also at the Marina Mandarin, on the 4th level, the AquaMarine buffet restaurant is spotlighting seafood until October 29th.
Source: Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
AquaMarine features an array of Asian dishes, including Vietnamese Braised Fish in Clay Pot, Thai Curry Mud Crab, authentic Filipino Beef Adobo, fresh Cambodian Fish Curry, and many more...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>