<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Power Supply Checks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/power-supply-checks/</link><description>Recent content in Power Supply Checks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:33:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/power-supply-checks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Reassembly and Power Supply Checks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-reassembly-and-power-supply-checks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-reassembly-and-power-supply-checks/</guid><description>This Beomaster 1900 is almost ready for final testing after reassembly and initial power supply checks.
The power transistor heatsinks, crucial for cooling, have been reinstalled using Sil-Pad insulators for thermal protection. This process started with the power transistors in their original state before any capacitor replacements. After restoration and the addition of new thermal insulation, they were carefully mounted back onto the unit.
To prepare for the upcoming No-Load Current adjustments, test leads were soldered onto the board.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Performance Testing and a Volume Control LDR Problem</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-performance-testing-and-a-volume-control-ldr-problem/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 21:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-performance-testing-and-a-volume-control-ldr-problem/</guid><description>Today, I completed some service manual adjustments on the Beomaster 1900 and started evaluating its performance by measuring THD and Frequency Response.
The first adjustments involved setting the tuning voltage for FM 1 and FM 5 according to the Beomaster 1900 service manual. The procedure involves setting the FM 1 tuning potentiometer (4R3) to the 88MHz dial position and adjusting trimmer 4R2 to achieve a reading of 4.5 VDC at test point 4TP1 with FM 1 selected as the audio source.</description></item></channel></rss>