<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beogram 6000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beogram-6000/</link><description>Recent content in Beogram 6000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 21:33:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beogram-6000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000 (type 5215): replacing sensor arm photo cell with modern one</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</guid><description>I recently had two Beogram turntables (a BG4000 and a BG4002) in my workshop with malfunctioning photocells in the detector arm. Usually, these photocells have a long lifespan, but the light bulbs can experience broken wires. While a pre-existing LED replacement for these bulbs exists (see sensor arm light bulb replacement), in this instance, the photocells themselves had broken wires and even a fractured cell, rendering repair impossible. Finding replacements proved futile as well.</description></item><item><title>An Early Christmas! Beosystem 6000 is in the House!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-early-christmas-beosystem-6000-is-in-the-house-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 17:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-early-christmas-beosystem-6000-is-in-the-house-/</guid><description>Today, I took a 340-mile round trip to purchase a nearly perfect Beosystem 6000 from a fellow vintage audio enthusiast. It was a fantastic day! The Beogram 6000, complete with an MMC6000 cartridge, is in fantastic cosmetic shape. All the keypads look almost brand new, the veneer is in excellent condition, and it even includes replacement plexiglass components. It even came with all of the original owner&amp;rsquo;s manuals and service manuals, including the Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s German &amp;ldquo;Technische Produktbeschreibung&amp;rdquo; (product description)!</description></item></channel></rss>