<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Life on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/life/</link><description>Recent content in Life on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 17:53:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Today marks the grand opening of Singapore's most Instagram-worthy nightclub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</guid><description>MARQUEE Singapore, a massive new nightclub, is launching at Marina Bay Sands on April 12, 2019. The opening weekend will feature world-renowned DJs Tiësto and Afrojack, with a special appearance by American rapper A$AP Rocky.
The 8K screen serves as a backdrop for TAO&amp;rsquo;s
co-founders Tepperberg (left) and Strauss (right).
This marks the first expansion into Asia for MARQUEE, a brand with clubs in New York, Las Vegas, and Sydney. The Singapore location is also the 35th project for TAO Group, the nightlife and hospitality company partnering with Marina Bay Sands on this venture...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ProtectSecure Prime life plan is now available from AmMetLife Insurance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 08:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</guid><description>AmMetLife Insurance has introduced ProtectSecure Prime, a whole life insurance plan with guaranteed premiums starting as low as RM150 each month. The plan offers three premium payment term choices: 10 years, 20 years, or until age 60. After the chosen payment period, no further payments are needed to maintain the policy.
Source: AmMetLife website.
Furthermore, policyholders will receive an automatic 10% increase in their initial sum assured annually from the end of the first policy year until the end of the tenth year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing work and play on your smartphone: Four helpful tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. View the full infographic.
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming harder to separate our work and personal lives with smartphones being used for both. For instance, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Lumia 640 and 640 XL come with an Office 365 subscription.
Dr. Mark Batey, an Organizational Psychologist at Manchester Business School in the UK, collaborated with Microsoft to offer advice on finding a good balance:
1. Capture inspiration immediately.
He says, &amp;ldquo;Make use of note-taking apps on your phone to jot down brilliant ideas as they come, anytime and anywhere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The difficulty of innovating quickly enough to ensure a comfortable life until the age of 100</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 14:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</guid><description>An on-site poll at The Longevity Summit – Is Asia ready for 100? in Singapore revealed that the majority (60%) of the 200 Asian business leaders, government officials, and healthcare professionals present didn&amp;rsquo;t believe the current pace of innovation could address the challenges of increasing longevity. Attendees convened to explore how to better integrate Asia&amp;rsquo;s senior population into the workforce and promote healthier, longer lives.
A Call for Total Change Kanwaljit Soin, Founding President of Women’s Initiative for Ageing Successfully, emphasized the need to overhaul the current linear life model...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>