<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IPhone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iphone/</link><description>Recent content in IPhone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What To Do With Old Cell Phones and Electronics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</guid><description>So, you&amp;rsquo;ve finally upgraded to the latest smartphone but now you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with your old one. It&amp;rsquo;s useless without a service plan but you hesitate to get rid of it.
Years pass and you stumble upon it again, completely forgotten. It&amp;rsquo;s just an outdated piece of technology now, the battery long depleted. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe it was once worth hundreds of dollars, leaving you wondering if you could have sold it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Here’s Why Companies Actually Want BYOD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The concept of &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) can be a real headache for IT managers. While employees may enjoy the convenience, it poses a significant risk to a company&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data. When personal devices connect to the company network, carefully constructed security protocols are often bypassed. So, what can be done?
Many companies address this issue by drawing a hard line. Recognizing the challenges of managing diverse personal devices, they prohibit their use for business purposes altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smartphone Charger and Backup Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/</guid><description>We all know the struggle of low battery life. It always seems to happen at the worst possible time, leaving us stranded. If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of being tethered to a wall outlet, the ZAGGsparq 2.0 might be the solution.
This handy device is both a charger and a backup battery. You can charge your USB devices, which seems like almost everything these days, and it provides up to four times the charge of your device&amp;rsquo;s battery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting today, the Apple iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are now available in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 04:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus will be offered in China starting October 17th through various channels like Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, major carriers, and authorized retailers. These smartphones will also be available in 36 more countries and territories by the end of October, reaching a total of over 115 countries by the year&amp;rsquo;s end.
Source: Apple. The iPhone 6 and
the iPhone 6 Plus.
Both iPhone models support TD-LTE and FDD-LTE, allowing customers to use 4G/LTE networks from China Mobile, China Telecom, and China Unicom throughout mainland China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>iPhone Getting its Video in a Sling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</guid><description>The mobile video landscape is seeing growth in various forms, including carrier-specific services like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s VCAST and Sprint TV, and dedicated channels such as MediaFLO. Sling Media&amp;rsquo;s introduction of a SlingPlayer for iPhone has the potential to disrupt the market by giving control of content back to the user.
Sling Media is known for its Slingbox, a device that connects to your television source (satellite receiver, DVR, or cable box) and a broadband connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LifeProof has unveiled new cases designed specifically for the latest iPhones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 11:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/</guid><description>LifeProof has introduced the FLiP, their first iPhone case to include built-in storage.
“Our iPhones are essential for capturing photos and videos, providing long-lasting battery life, and keeping us connected,” stated Jim Parke, LifeProof&amp;rsquo;s CEO.
Source: LifeProof.
“Apple is known for its continuous innovation, and LifeProof aims to complement the phone&amp;rsquo;s sleek design with cases that maintain optimal performance.”
Engineered to withstand drops from 2 meters, the single-piece FLiP case incorporates a wallet-like panel on the back, providing storage for cards and cash...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Send Fax From Email On Your Computer or Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</guid><description>Do you recall fax machines with thermal paper rolls? Those messages had a distinct look and tended to fade. To preserve them, you&amp;rsquo;d copy them onto regular paper using a laser printer, then diligently wash the strange residue off your hands.
Fax technology has significantly evolved. Thermal paper is out, and even traditional fax machines are becoming rare. Cloud-based electronic transmission and storage are the modern alternatives.
Sending and receiving faxes via email is the contemporary approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel hosts launch event for iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:08:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Singtel began offering the iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus to customers this morning. Eager customers with confirmed appointments started lining up as early as 4:45 am, hoping to be among the first in Singapore to get their hands on the new devices.
Over 40,000 customers expressed interest in the new iPhones, and all 12,000 launch appointment slots were booked. The iPhone 6s Plus and the rose gold models were particularly popular, selling out in less than three minutes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-hosts-launch-event-for-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The iPhone SE is introduced by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 06:02:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Apple has launched the iPhone SE, boasting a 4-inch display and impressive processing power in a familiar compact design. This updated model features smooth, angled edges, a color-coordinated stainless steel Apple logo, and a choice of four metallic finishes, including rose gold.
“The iPhone SE is a fresh take on a beloved design — we took a popular, iconic look and completely redesigned its internals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel announces pricing for iPhone SE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Singtel has revealed its plans to offer Apple&amp;rsquo;s 4-inch iPhone SE starting March 31, 2016. Customers can pre-order the device now. A 16 GB model with the most affordable plan, costing S$27.90 per month for two years, is priced at S$350.
The telecom provider recently conducted a crowdsourced study, highlighting its superior 4G network speed and coverage in Singapore. The study, based on data from IDA&amp;rsquo;s MyConnection SG crowdsourced survey and 4G Mobile Service Coverage results, positioned Singtel as a frontrunner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub announces pricing for newest iPhone models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 14:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone 11 Pro and iPhone 11 Pro Max are available in midnight green, space grey, silver, and gold finishes.
StarHub has quickly released pricing for the newly announced iPhone 11, iPhone 11 Pro, and iPhone 11 Pro Max. The iPhone 11 Pro and iPhone 11 Pro Max represent a new generation of iPhones offering high-level performance.
According to Apple, the pro line boasts a new Super Retina XDR display, the brightest ever seen on an iPhone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-announces-pricing-for-newest-iphone-models/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting from 26 September, StarHub is excited to welcome buyers of the iPhone 6s and 6s Plus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 18:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</guid><description>Source: StarHub. Customers waiting in line inside the newly renovated StarHub Shop in VivoCity, one of 38 StarHub stores serving pre-order customers on September 25th.
On September 25th, pre-orders for Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus became available for pickup at 38 StarHub stores across Singapore. To ensure a smooth pickup process, customers who pre-ordered were given specific locations and time slots when they booked their appointments.
Starting September 26th, customers can visit any StarHub Shop or participating authorized retailers to purchase the phones directly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-26-september-starhub-is-excited-to-welcome-buyers-of-the-iphone-6s-and-6s-plus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Charge your iPhone while also using a 3.5mm jack simultaneously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:25:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/</guid><description>Belkin, a company known for its mobile accessories, has introduced a new adapter called the 3.5 mm Audio + Charge RockStar for iPhone models 8, 8 Plus, X, 7, and 7 Plus. This adapter allows users to charge their iPhones and listen to audio through 3.5 mm headphones simultaneously.
The adapter connects to the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s Lightning connector and supports data syncing, microphone use, and remote control functionality through the headphone jack...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ally In The Android vs iPhone Battle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 20:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s initial Android offering, the LG Ally for Verizon Wireless, is a remarkable device. It boasts a range of features and access to a vast library of apps on the Android Market.
If you prioritize texting and email, you&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the tactile feedback of real keys. The LG Ally features a 3.2-inch touchscreen and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with well-sized keys. With five customizable home screens, you can personalize it with numerous Android apps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazing Sonos S5 Wireless Whole House Music System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazing-sonos-s5-wireless-whole-house-music-system/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 17:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazing-sonos-s5-wireless-whole-house-music-system/</guid><description>Remember those old record players and stereos? They were once staples in our homes, but now there&amp;rsquo;s a new way to enjoy high-quality music. Introducing the Sonos S5 wireless music system!
Sure, stereos are fine if you&amp;rsquo;re content with limited options like FM radio or your old record collection. But technology has evolved, and the Sonos S5 is leading the way.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let the bookshelf speaker design fool you, these units are packed with five individual speakers and amplifiers for impressive audio performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazing-sonos-s5-wireless-whole-house-music-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazing-sonos-s5-wireless-whole-house-music-system/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>