<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asset on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asset/</link><description>Recent content in Asset on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally.</description></item><item><title>Tracking assets for project accounting.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-assets-for-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-assets-for-project-accounting/</guid><description>Many clients are using Microsoft Dynamics GP&amp;rsquo;s Project Accounting module in unconventional ways, often because it&amp;rsquo;s included in their software suite. One example is using it to track capital expenditures, effectively managing the various costs associated with a capital project, such as labor, materials, and overhead.
A common question is how to manage asset &amp;ldquo;recognition&amp;rdquo; when a project reaches a certain completion stage and construction in progress (CIP) becomes capitalized. We can address this by utilizing the Work in Progress (WIP) function within Project Accounting, employing a time and materials project to simulate the transfer of expenses from a CIP account to an asset account.</description></item></channel></rss>