<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VXSuite on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vxsuite/</link><description>Recent content in VXSuite on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vxsuite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>