<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EU Budget on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-budget/</link><description>Recent content in EU Budget on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-budget/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Benefits of a Hard Brexit? Transforming Britain's £24 billion worth of unicorns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The pro-Brexit group &amp;ldquo;Change Britain&amp;rdquo; recently released a statement claiming significant financial benefits for the UK following a &amp;ldquo;hard Brexit,&amp;rdquo; where the UK leaves both the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market and customs union. This claim was widely circulated in the media despite being fundamentally flawed.
While the report attempts to offer a thorough analysis, it highlights the poor quality of the overall Brexit debate. The report&amp;rsquo;s claim of a £24 billion benefit originates from three key areas: ending contributions to the EU budget, potential savings from reduced regulation, and the anticipated benefits of new trade agreements.</description></item><item><title>REPowerEU: Expanding Europe's financial capacity post-pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 18:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</guid><description>Rosalba Famà, PhD student in EU law, Bocconi University
Photo credit: ThibaultC, via wikicommons media
In response to the energy crisis stemming from the Russian invasion of Ukraine, the European Union is implementing REPowerEU. Presented in May 2022, the comprehensive REPowerEU strategy encompasses proposals to modify existing energy directives and an ambitious industrial policy program aimed at achieving energy independence. This analysis will focus on the latter, referred to as the REPowerEU plan.</description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights under ordinary EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Can the EU penalize its member states for consistently violating human rights and the rule of law? And if so, how?
This article, the second in a three-part series, explores this question. The first installment analyzed the official mechanism designed for this purpose: Article 7 TEU. As previously discussed, this process, which could result in the suspension of certain EU membership rights for a member state, is highly political, offers limited involvement from EU courts, and is challenging to implement.</description></item></channel></rss>