<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Uc on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uc/</link><description>Recent content in Uc on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tata Communications updates the jamvee unified communications platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications provider, recently launched the newest version of its cloud-based unified communications platform, jamvee.
Source: Jamvee website.
Leveraging Tata Communications&amp;rsquo; robust global network, jamvee consolidates various client software and devices into a single, secure, and versatile platform. This approach streamlines communication and collaboration within and across organizations, allowing employees, suppliers, and customers to connect seamlessly using any combination of audio, video, messaging, and content sharing tools, regardless of their device or browser...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Here’s Why Companies Actually Want BYOD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The concept of &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) can be a real headache for IT managers. While employees may enjoy the convenience, it poses a significant risk to a company&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data. When personal devices connect to the company network, carefully constructed security protocols are often bypassed. So, what can be done?
Many companies address this issue by drawing a hard line. Recognizing the challenges of managing diverse personal devices, they prohibit their use for business purposes altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Business Needs Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There was a time when the only way to communicate electronically was with that clunky black phone on your desk. While that phone might still be there, modern technology has made it lighter and brought a wealth of new communication methods. Email, text messages, mobile phone calls, and video chats are now commonplace across various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, smartphones, and even watches.
A significant challenge, particularly in business, is that these platforms and applications don&amp;rsquo;t always work well together...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra introduces the Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company known for creating intelligent audio devices, has introduced the Jabra Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset. This new headset is a unified communication (UC) upgrade from their original Jabra Stealth and is designed specifically for professionals who are often on the go.
Weighing in at a mere 0.24 ounces (approximately 6.8 grams), the Jabra Stealth UC is remarkably lightweight, making it both inconspicuous and incredibly easy to carry around...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra emphasizes the importance of educating and incentivizing employees to guarantee the success of UC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that makes audio solutions, believes the tech industry needs to rethink its definition of success for unified communications (UC) deployments.
Source: Jabra website.
Currently, only 10% of companies use UC. This is because employees don&amp;rsquo;t want to give up their current tools and ways of working. Companies are spending a lot of money on UC, but employees don&amp;rsquo;t see how it can help them be more productive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>