<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2013/33 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2013/33/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2013/33 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2013/33/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item><item><title>Is it permissible for Member States to confiscate the assets of asylum-seekers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk (Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen) and Steve Peers
Recently, several countries within and outside the EU have made headlines for seizing assets from asylum-seekers upon entry. This raises the question of whether this practice aligns with EU law. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine national practices, the development of relevant EU regulations, and finally, draw our conclusions.
Denmark
In November 2015, the Danish government put forward 34 measures aimed at deterring asylum seekers.</description></item></channel></rss>