<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beach on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beach/</link><description>Recent content in Beach on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort introduces its new private villas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort has introduced new villas that provide enhanced privacy and luxury for guests. These villas overlook the Gulf of Thailand and the resort&amp;rsquo;s lotus lagoon. Their spaciousness makes them perfect for hosting private events, parties, or intimate gatherings, with amenities like a private chef, outdoor barbecues, and more.
Situated in a secluded part of the resort, the four three-bedroom and one four-bedroom villas offer direct access to the Club InterContinental Lounge.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life.</description></item></channel></rss>