<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIP Telephones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-telephones/</link><description>Recent content in SIP Telephones on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-telephones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telephony In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>When we think about cloud networking, we often picture data networks moving information between locations. However, many businesses are also transitioning their phone systems to the cloud. This shift brings both benefits and hurdles.
The traditional phone network is essentially a large cloud network. This system is designed for reliability and high-quality service, handling countless users at once. Users connect to this cloud through a direct line to their nearest local central office, unconcerned with the complexities of the system.</description></item><item><title>E911 For Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>The transition from traditional phone lines to internet-based calling has brought about some unexpected issues, particularly with emergency services. We often take 911 for granted, assuming help will always be on the way. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case with internet-based phone systems.
Imagine a scenario where a fire breaks out in your office. You dial 911, report the emergency, and evacuate. However, the fire department ends up at your company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters instead of your current location.</description></item></channel></rss>