<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cable Business Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cable-business-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Cable Business Broadband on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cable-business-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies.</description></item><item><title>SD-WAN is Your Super LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-is-your-super-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The current trend of companies moving their technology and communications systems to cloud-based providers is significant. While this migration offers many benefits, it presents a challenge: establishing reliable connections over long distances, which is much more complex than using a simple ethernet cable.
The Expanding Digital Landscape
The internet has evolved from a platform for text and images to one that encompasses video, e-commerce, and now, remote applications, databases, and unified communications.</description></item></channel></rss>