<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backhaul Connectivity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backhaul-connectivity/</link><description>Recent content in Backhaul Connectivity on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backhaul-connectivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Broadband Options in Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses located in bustling city centers have a wide array of broadband Internet options, unlike their rural counterparts. While the lack of service providers in less populated areas might make it seem like broadband is a luxury they can&amp;rsquo;t afford, there are actually several options available, depending on the location.
Rural businesses might feel limited in their connectivity choices. Unlike their city counterparts, they don&amp;rsquo;t have numerous service providers vying for their business.</description></item><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>