<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2022 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2022/</link><description>Recent content in 2022 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:33:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Xiaomi's latest flagship smartphone is the MIX Fold 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:33:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</guid><description>Source: Xiaomi. The MIX Fold 2 is available in Black and Gold colourways.
Xiaomi recently debuted its most advanced foldable phone, the Xiaomi MIX Fold 2, in Mainland China. The company also introduced the Xiaomi Pad 5 Pro, Redmi K50 Ultra, and a variety of other ecosystem devices.
When unfolded, the Xiaomi MIX Fold 2 measures a mere 5.4mm1, providing a seamless viewing experience across its inner and outer screens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick reference guide for Chinese New Year in the Year of the Water Tiger</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:44:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</guid><description>In 2022, the ox replaces the rat as the third animal in the 12-year Chinese zodiac cycle, bringing hope for positive change. Chinese New Year commences on February 1st, ushering in a period of customary greetings and well wishes.
A wish for plentiful business opportunities.
生意兴隆.
Common greetings include &amp;ldquo;Happy New Year&amp;rdquo; (新年快乐, xin nian kuai le) and &amp;ldquo;Congratulations on receiving riches and prosperity&amp;rdquo; (恭喜发财, gong xi fa cai). Prosperity holds significant value in Chinese culture, particularly during Chinese New Year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is increasing interest in cold pressed juices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</guid><description>Source: Techsci Research.
A TechSci Research report projects the global cold-pressed juice market to experience a significant growth rate, exceeding 10% annually, between 2016 and 2022. This anticipated growth is attributed to several factors, including increased disposable incomes, heightened consumer awareness, effective marketing campaigns by industry leaders, widespread product availability, and a strong global distribution network.
Global GDP per capita, adjusted for purchasing power parity, rose from US$14,020.31 in 2012 to US$15,470...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There has been an increase in crypto giveaway scams</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</guid><description>Source: Group-IB. A screen capture from a fake YouTube video that appears to show Elon Musk.
Group-IB, a cybersecurity firm based in Singapore, has detected a significant surge in websites promoting cryptocurrency giveaway scams using fake YouTube live streams during the first half of 2022. These scams have become increasingly organized, evolving into a distinct market segment with various services supporting fraudulent activities.
The firm&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that while 63% of these new scam domains are registered with Russian registrars, they primarily target English and Spanish-speaking individuals interested in cryptocurrency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel's 2022 Chinese New Year film features the Angs and the Huangs facing off on Sentosa with the addition of 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 23:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chinese New Year festive film for 2022.
To celebrate the Year of the Tiger and the values of family and community central to the holiday, Singtel has released its annual Chinese New Year short film. The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger is the third installment in a series of films by Singtel featuring the amusing rivalry between two families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo unveils a retail sales guide for Chinese New Year in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:48:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</guid><description>Criteo, a commerce media company, has unveiled insights from the 2022 Chinese New Year (CNY) to help retailers anticipate consumer demand and leverage similar trends in 2023.
Starting in January 2022, retail sales surpassed typical levels (based on the average between December 18th and 31st, 2021) until a week prior to CNY 2022 (February 1st), indicating a strong consumer appetite for purchasing. In Southeast Asia (SEA), retail sales hit a peak of 27% on January 25th, a week before CNY...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kinoya in Dubai has been awarded the One to Watch Award for 2022 by MENA's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Kinoya restaurant has been awarded the One To Watch Award 2022 by Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. This recognition is given to up-and-coming restaurants in the region that have the potential to earn a spot on the 50 Best list in future years.
Kinoya&amp;rsquo;s founder, Neha Mishra, also known as the Ramen Queen, opened the restaurant after the success of her home-based supper club, A Story of Food...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Submissions are now open for the 2022 Sony World Photography Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submissions-are-now-open-for-the-2022-sony-world-photography-awards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 01:08:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submissions-are-now-open-for-the-2022-sony-world-photography-awards/</guid><description>The Sony World Photography Awards is currently accepting entries for its 15th edition. Participation is free.
Source: Sony World Photography Awards. Copyright: © Majid Hojjati, Iran, Winner, Professional, Landscape, 2021 Sony World Photography Awards. Series name: Silent Neighborhoods.
Series description: Our experiences shape who we are. What we encounter today transforms us for tomorrow. Life persists in a constant struggle for survival, with nature as the backdrop. The forces of nature remain constant - ocean waves, storms, the earth itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submissions-are-now-open-for-the-2022-sony-world-photography-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submissions-are-now-open-for-the-2022-sony-world-photography-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers now prioritize sustainable travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 20:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</guid><description>Trip.com Group, a leading travel service company, recently published its first-ever Sustainable Travel Consumer Report to coincide with World Tourism Day. The report highlights the growing popularity of sustainable travel and its significant effects on the travel industry and the world at large.
Sustainable travel is increasingly becoming a top priority for travelers worldwide, with over 68% in Singapore and 90% in Thailand recognizing its importance.
Source: Trip.com. Despite regional variations, there is a clear upward trend of individuals adopting sustainable travel habits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By 2022, consumers are projected to spend over $155 billion on apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 18:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</guid><description>Source: App Annie. App Annie predicts app trends will change by 2022. Figures are in US dollars.
A new report by App Annie, a mobile app data and insights company, projects global consumer spending on apps to reach US$156.5 billion by 2022, a 92% increase from 2017.
The App Annie Forecast 2017-2022 highlights major trends expected to shape the app economy in the coming years. Global first-time app downloads are predicted to rise by 45% between 2017 and 2022, hitting 258...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SiteMinder: Travelers are projected to spend in 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</guid><description>A recent global survey of over 8,000 travelers reveals a growing desire for international travel, even with increasing living expenses.
Source: SiteMinder Changing Traveller Report 2022. Global accommodation momentum from 2020 to 2022.
The report identified five key travel trends:
Macro-travel: The desire to travel outweighs concerns about inflation.
Digital influence: Travelers are currently the most receptive to marketing efforts.
Bleisure: Business travelers seek modern hotel amenities.
Trust: Digital interactions are crucial for building trust with travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ipsos: More than half of Singaporeans are feeling positive about 2022, but have mixed emotions about 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</guid><description>A recent worldwide survey conducted by Ipsos explored global citizens&amp;rsquo; opinions on the past year and their outlook for the future. The survey revealed that 73% of respondents believe their country had a challenging year, marking a slight improvement compared to the previous year (2021).
The Ipsos Global Predictions for 2023 report, which included data from 36 countries, indicated that over half (56%) of respondents globally considered 2022 a difficult year personally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC and holoride introduce glasses that are ready for a ride</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-and-holoride-introduce-glasses-that-are-ready-for-a-ride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 07:07:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-and-holoride-introduce-glasses-that-are-ready-for-a-ride/</guid><description>HTC VIVE, a leading virtual reality platform, is teaming up with holoride, an innovative in-car entertainment company, to bring XR experiences to passengers. Launching in the latter half of 2022, holoride&amp;rsquo;s technology blends extended reality content with real-time car data, such as motion and location, to craft immersive adventures synchronized with the journey.
HTC&amp;rsquo;s VIVE Flow, a lightweight and portable VR headset, will be the first to integrate holoride&amp;rsquo;s technology for in-car use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-and-holoride-introduce-glasses-that-are-ready-for-a-ride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-and-holoride-introduce-glasses-that-are-ready-for-a-ride/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>