<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Multiple Business Locations on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multiple-business-locations/</link><description>Recent content in Multiple Business Locations on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multiple-business-locations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Managed MPLS Networking Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</guid><description>Imagine your company with offices across the country, each operating its own independent local network for computers, phones, and video calls. While efficient individually, they lack integration. To unify your company, connecting these separate networks is key. This will boost efficiency by centralizing functions, improving collaboration among employees nationwide, and enabling specialized support centers.
Integrating your phone system with your network can lead to substantial savings on long-distance calls. Instead of relying on traditional phone lines, internal communication happens within your network, cutting toll charges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A New Edge On Private IP Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</guid><description>With the increase in businesses operating from multiple locations, IP network solutions have become more affordable and accessible. New Edge Networks, a key player in this domain, specializes in private IP-based WANs, offering enhanced quality and performance for connecting multiple business sites by bypassing the public internet.
While the internet has revolutionized global communication, its ubiquity and open nature pose limitations for businesses. Network neutrality principles treat all data equally, regardless of its importance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>