<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flickr on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flickr/</link><description>Recent content in Flickr on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flickr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Flickr App for iPad has been optimized for iOS 8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a new Flickr app designed for iPads, allowing users seamless photo management across all devices. Yahoo claims the app is optimized for iOS 8, providing an enhanced experience for capturing, editing, and browsing images.
Source: Yahoo.
Current iPad users can update their existing Flickr app, while new users can download it from the App Store. The app supports multiple languages, including English, French, Indonesian, Korean, Chinese, and Vietnamese...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flickr Wall Art is now available worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</guid><description>Yahoo has expanded its Flickr wall art service to global markets, enabling businesses worldwide to adorn their walls with photographic artwork from Flickr artists.
Initially introduced in October, the Flickr Wall Art service allows the transformation of photographs from licensed artists within the Flickr Marketplace into high-quality wall prints available for purchase directly on Flickr.
The Flickr team has curated a collection of licensed photographs from popular categories such as abstract, landscapes, travel, and animals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new version of Flickr is now available for iOS 9</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 02:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s Flickr app for iOS 9 now includes features designed for the updated operating system.
Source: Yahoo.
The app utilizes 3D Touch on the latest iPhones. This allows users to preview content by pressing lightly on the screen. For example, in the Camera Roll, lightly pressing a photo shows a preview, while a harder press expands it to full screen.
Another 3D Touch feature, &amp;ldquo;Quick Actions,&amp;rdquo; lets users perform certain tasks directly from the app icon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In its latest update, Yahoo! introduces cutting-edge search technology to Flickr</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 10:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/</guid><description>Yahoo! has introduced several major updates to Flickr, potentially revitalizing the platform. These updates include an improved search engine and simplified access, organization, discovery, and sharing of images and videos across various devices. Over 112 million users, including businesses, will benefit from these enhancements, making it easier to manage their combined 11 billion photos on Flickr.
Tim Miller, Head of Engineering at Flickr, expressed their aspiration to create a space for lifelong memories and highlighted the new tools&amp;rsquo; role in maximizing the platform&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 GB storage capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-its-latest-update-yahoo-introduces-cutting-edge-search-technology-to-flickr/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>