<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Computing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-computing/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Computing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 17:15:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Aircards Work For Mobile Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 17:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</guid><description>Internet access via broadband has become a standard requirement for almost all businesses and home offices. Individuals can easily find and afford DSL and Cable Internet. Businesses, on the other hand, often opt for T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, and Ethernet connections. However, challenges arise when venturing beyond the confines of a traditional workspace. Without WiFi hotspots, staying connected becomes difficult. How can tasks such as delivering presentations, accessing inventory, or entering orders at a client&amp;rsquo;s office be accomplished if they necessitate a broadband connection?</description></item><item><title>iPad Jones. I’ve Got An iPad Jones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipad-jones-i-ve-got-an-ipad-jones/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipad-jones-i-ve-got-an-ipad-jones/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in e-book readers since the Amazon Kindle was released. The idea of carrying many books conveniently is appealing. Even better is the ability to enlarge the font size for reading without glasses. Plus, not needing shelf space for dusty books is a definite advantage. However, I haven&amp;rsquo;t purchased one because I don&amp;rsquo;t read books constantly anymore. The interactive nature of the internet holds my attention more effectively. An e-book reader combined with an internet-capable computer would be amazing!</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile 3G Aircard For PC and Mac</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</guid><description>Want to connect your laptop to T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s 3G network and get free access to their HotSpots? The T-Mobile webConnect USB Laptop Stick can make that happen.
This device is a wireless modem with a USB connector that plugs into your PC or Mac. PCs require Windows XP or Vista, while Macs need OS X 10.3.9 or higher.
This aircard provides internet access virtually anywhere in the U.S. with T-Mobile cellular coverage.</description></item><item><title>Will Cell Phones Replace Laptop Computers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</guid><description>Laptops have taken over as the primary mobile work tool, but their days may be numbered. They are bulky, heavy, and require constant charging. A simple legal pad is starting to look more appealing in comparison. The search is on for a mobile device that offers the right balance of power and portability. Could the answer be cell phones?
The idea of an all-in-one cell phone is appealing because most people carry one anyway.</description></item></channel></rss>