<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-networks/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VPLS Is The Ethernet Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re all familiar with cloud networks, but wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have a private cloud connecting all your business locations?
Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS) offers a solution. While not a fully private cloud, it comes close.
VPLS allows you to share a private multipoint network built on technology like Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS). MPLS networks can handle various traffic types, including Ethernet, making it ideal for diverse needs.</description></item><item><title>2x2 Ethernet Takes on T-1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</guid><description>For the past decade, small and medium businesses have relied on T1 lines as their primary commercial telecom solution. However, a new competitor called 2x2 Ethernet, recently introduced by major nationwide carrier MegaPath, is emerging to challenge the long-standing T1. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what 2x2 Ethernet offers.
It might seem surprising that T1 lines would face competition, considering their 50-year history and widespread adoption. As the first widely available broadband digital connection for businesses, T1 emerged from telephone company research.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>Ethernet WAN is the most significant advancement in business broadband since T1 service prices dropped. What exactly is Ethernet WAN, and why should you care?
Ethernet has become the dominant standard for Local Area Networks (LANs). You could say that Ethernet is everywhere. An RJ45 Ethernet jack is standard on every desktop and laptop computer. You might not get a CD-ROM drive, probably won&amp;rsquo;t get a floppy disc drive, and may never use the phone modem jack again.</description></item><item><title>Comprehensive Network Services From Telarus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</guid><description>Creating and managing a network can be a significant challenge for businesses of all sizes. Small businesses find it distracting, while larger companies view it as a costly endeavor that can either help or hurt their efficiency. Integrating local and wide area networks seamlessly is a particularly difficult problem.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: Telarus. Regardless of your size or technical expertise, Telarus provides a range of services to address your networking needs.</description></item><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging.</description></item><item><title>When Networks Get Too Big To Fail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-networks-get-too-big-to-fail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-networks-get-too-big-to-fail/</guid><description>Do you remember a time when computer networks were simply useful tools for businesses? Back then, we relied on standalone computers, fax machines, and overnight mail for document delivery. It seems like a bygone era, but you might find yourself longing for those simpler times when your network crashes and remains unusable for hours. Today, local area networks (LANs) are as indispensable as electricity, while wide area networks (WANs) are as crucial as roads and highways—we simply cannot function without them.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Welcome To The Big Bandwidth Era</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 17:07:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</guid><description>Remember the days of big band music? While many may not be familiar with that era, technology has dramatically changed since then. We&amp;rsquo;ve moved from radio and kilocycles to the digital age with bandwidth measured in Mbps and Gbps. This is the era of big bandwidth.
But what exactly qualifies as &amp;ldquo;big bandwidth&amp;rdquo;? NuVox, a leading telecommunications company, defines it as any bandwidth exceeding 10 Mbps. This speed is the target for home internet providers as video streaming gains popularity.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Shows How The Converged Business Network Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</guid><description>Larger organizations have been moving towards network convergence since IP became the standard network protocol. However, smaller companies, often lacking substantial IT departments, haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted this approach as readily. This is changing. Convergence is now a viable option for businesses of all sizes.
What&amp;rsquo;s driving this shift? The answer, as always, is cost savings. In today&amp;rsquo;s business climate, reducing expenses is crucial. The real game-changer is the availability of managed convergence services.</description></item><item><title>Aggressive Passive Optical Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 02:09:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</guid><description>Passive Optical Networking (PON) is becoming a budget-friendly way to bring fiber optic connections directly to homes and businesses. This technology is advancing so rapidly that new PON standards are being surpassed almost as quickly as they are established. For instance, Ericsson is currently showcasing 10 Gbps GPON. Will we soon see speeds of 100 Gbps or even terabits per second?
While it&amp;rsquo;s not happening overnight, bandwidth requirements are definitely increasing for both home and business wide area networks (WANs).</description></item><item><title>Telexplainer Expectations For 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</guid><description>As we begin a promising new year for business and technology, let&amp;rsquo;s explore some key trends for 2011 and how to leverage them.
Bandwidth demands will continue to escalate this year, as they do annually. The economic recovery will likely generate increased internet traffic as more individuals return to work. Expect bandwidth demand to surge proportionally with employment, if not more. During the recession, businesses learned to enhance individual productivity by investing in technology.</description></item><item><title>Why The WAN Lags The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</guid><description>Corporate networks are often set up to ensure smooth data flow within the organization (LAN), but the real bottleneck often lies in the connection to the outside world (WAN).
LANs typically use Ethernet standards with speeds of 10/100/1000 Mbps, while WAN connections like T1 or DS3 lines operate at much slower speeds (1.5 Mbps to 45 Mbps). This disparity in speed results in significant slowdowns when transferring files outside the organization.</description></item><item><title>Ciena Takes New Bandwidth Technologies On The Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</guid><description>Today, June 29th, those in Waltham, MA can experience cutting-edge carrier bandwidth technology firsthand. Visit the Ciena Innovation Lab to see live demonstrations of their latest optical, Ethernet, and software solutions. The lab will move to its next location in White Marsh, MD on July 15th.
What exactly is the Ciena Innovation Lab? It&amp;rsquo;s a mobile showcase housed in a semi-trailer, packed with the most recent advancements in telecom and networking.</description></item><item><title>Juniper Has Routers For The 100 Gbps WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</guid><description>Verizon and Juniper are partnering on a large-scale project to implement 100 Gbps fiber optic connections to meet the increasing demand for faster internet speeds.
While carriers have experimented with 100 Gbps transmission, which is significantly faster than the typical 10 Gbps long-haul networks, it seems that widespread adoption is on the horizon. Juniper has developed an interface capable of handling this bandwidth directly, eliminating the need for carriers to combine multiple links.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet MPLS Has Cost and Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-mpls-has-cost-and-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 17:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-mpls-has-cost-and-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet, also called Metro Ethernet, and MPLS networks are two popular technologies for voice, video, and data networking. These technologies can be used together to increase bandwidth while reducing costs.
Traditionally, there&amp;rsquo;s a significant difference in speed and compatibility between customer networks and telecom networks. These differences stem from their distinct developmental paths. While connecting these networks is now possible through clever interfacing, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal. We can now transmit data packets between LANs over telephone-based telecom networks, but a better solution exists.</description></item><item><title>Trade In Your T1 Line For 10 Mbps Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-in-your-t1-line-for-10-mbps-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-in-your-t1-line-for-10-mbps-ethernet/</guid><description>If your T1 line contract is expiring soon or has already ended and you&amp;rsquo;re on a month-to-month plan, don&amp;rsquo;t rush to renew. You might be able to obtain a 10 Mbps Ethernet connection for the same price.
It might seem implausible to get 10 Mbps for the price of 1.5 Mbps at the same location, given that business telecom pricing is based on bandwidth and distance. However, due to recent advancements in the telecommunications industry, many businesses can upgrade from their outdated T1 services to significantly faster options.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard about Metro Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s rise in popularity for business WAN connections, particularly in major cities with concentrated business areas. These areas have been the primary focus of competitive bandwidth providers offering lower per-Mbps pricing. However, you might assume that Ethernet WAN services are only accessible in downtown areas or large suburbs.
This is about to change. Hatteras Networks has introduced a line of repeater and line power modules that extend Mid-Band Ethernet service up to 25 miles over standard telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>Vocal IP Networx Offers Free SNMP Monitoring</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with the challenges of managing T1 lines and bandwidth, especially keeping track of service availability across different vendors and equipment. While large companies have dedicated IT teams, smaller businesses often handle this responsibility as issues arise.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be beneficial to have affordable network monitoring support? Vocal IP Networx, a leading IP telephony provider, offers a solution: free, continuous SNMP monitoring for all circuits and customer premises equipment (CPE) they provide.</description></item></channel></rss>