<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cargo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cargo/</link><description>Recent content in Cargo on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:43:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cargo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ACN and MENA Cargo will be providing enhanced services in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:43:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</guid><description>The Asia Cargo Network (ACN), a Southeast Asian air cargo charter provider, is expanding its reach globally through a new partnership with Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s MENA Aerospace. This agreement will see ACN stationing six cargo planes in Bahrain and the GCC to better serve the Middle East, North Africa (MENA) region and beyond.
These operations will fall under the MENA Cargo brand, a subsidiary of MAE specializing in freight cargo. The rollout will occur over the next year and a half, with the first of the six aircraft scheduled to arrive and begin operations within the next two months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>