<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Grand Millennium on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grand-millennium/</link><description>Recent content in Grand Millennium on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grand-millennium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Grand Millennium Dubai is providing daily iftar buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</guid><description>During Ramadan, the Grand Millennium Dubai, located near Sheikh Zayed Road, is hosting nightly iftar buffets at their Atrium restaurant. For AED 145 per person, guests can enjoy live cooking stations, along with Arabic and international dishes.
Source: Grand Millennium Dubai website. The Atrium restaurant.
The restaurant offers special group rates for iftar. The Silver package, priced at AED 165 per person, accommodates up to 50 guests. The Gold package, for a maximum of 100 people, costs AED 155 per person.</description></item></channel></rss>