<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Irregular Immigration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/irregular-immigration/</link><description>Recent content in Irregular Immigration on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/irregular-immigration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's Returns Directive beneficial or detrimental to the well-being of undocumented migrants?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at the EU Returns Directive: Five Years On Many EU citizens are worried about the impact of immigration, especially when it comes to unauthorized migrants without legal status. Others, however, prioritize humane treatment for these individuals. To manage this challenge, the EU created the &amp;ldquo;Returns Directive&amp;rdquo; in 2008, outlining procedures for returning unauthorized migrants, including detention rules and procedural rights.
Upon its introduction, the Directive faced criticism from NGOs and academics who felt it was overly harsh...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU employment law and irregular migrants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Determining the employment rights of undocumented migrants is complex. On one hand, granting them full access to employment law protections could incentivize unauthorized migration. On the other hand, applying standard employment laws to all workers, regardless of immigration status, could prevent the exploitation of undocumented migrants and deter employers from hiring them to save money.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this issue in the Tumer case, which focused on the application of the EU Directive on insolvent employers to undocumented migrants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Strategy on immigration policy in the EU by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</guid><description>This is an unofficial preview of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s communication on the EU migration agenda, scheduled for release on May 13th. Please be aware that the content may change before publication and may be incomplete.
I. Introduction
Migration has been a constant throughout human history, driven by a range of factors such as political oppression, war, poverty, opportunity, and family reunification. Each migrant&amp;rsquo;s story is unique, and their movement has diverse impacts on society, necessitating a variety of responses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating Discontent: Questions and Answers about the legal concerns of asylum-seekers crossing the Channel.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 23:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Supported by an ESRC Priority Brexit Grant on &amp;lsquo;Brexit and UK and EU Immigration Policy&amp;rsquo;.
Some politicians are trying to create unnecessary fear and outrage over a relatively small number of people crossing the English Channel. This situation does bring up important legal questions. While the legal aspects have been discussed elsewhere, such as in the Free Movement blog, this post aims to clarify some of these legal issues in a straightforward question-and-answer format...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Utilization of Prisons for Detaining Migrants in Europe and the EU Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, a researcher at the Global Detention Project and the Global Migration Centre, and a PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies in Geneva, examines a legal question: can immigration detainees be held in prisons alongside ordinary prisoners?
On July 17, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this question in its decisions regarding the combined cases of Bero and Bouzalmate and the separate case of Pham...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing Celaj and Vélez Loor: The implications of Latin American immigrants' detention in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</guid><description>Dr Andrea Romano, Research assistant, “Sapienza” University of Rome
Introduction
The recent Celaj judgment and its debatable connection to past rulings of the Court of Justice concerning the Returns Directive has been the subject of much discussion. This analysis will provide a concise comparison between this judgment and the Vélez Loor case, which was decided by the Inter-American Court of Human Rights (IACtHR) in 2010.
The Court of Justice of the European Union’s judgment in the Celaj case stemmed from various preliminary rulings brought forth by Italian judicial bodies regarding the Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU leaders are avoiding taking significant action to address the migrant crisis.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU leaders convened yesterday and agreed on a policy to handle the escalating migrant death toll in the Mediterranean Sea. This new policy expands on the recently implemented 10-point plan established by ministers. Notably, some significant last-minute revisions to the initial draft highlight the leaders&amp;rsquo; priorities.
Detailed comments
The leaders&amp;rsquo; statement appears to demonstrate more empathy than the prior 10-point plan. It acknowledges the immense loss of life as a tragedy and prioritizes the prevention of further deaths at sea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's strategy to eliminate human trafficking is all talk and no action.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</guid><description>Dr Matilde Ventrella, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Wolverhampton (UK)
1. Introduction
The European Commission recently released two important documents on October 17th: a progress report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat human trafficking and a report on how a specific directive (Directive 2004/81) is being used to protect victims. This analysis will delve into the key findings of both reports and offer concluding observations.
2. Progress Report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s Fight Against Human Trafficking..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comments on the outcomes of the most recent European Council meeting regarding EU migration policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU faces another crisis alongside &amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;: a surge in immigration. Initial EU responses culminated in an emergency summit in April. I previously discussed the outcomes of that summit. Subsequently, the Commission released its EU migration &amp;ldquo;Agenda&amp;rdquo; in mid-May, followed by detailed proposals. Last week, the European Council revisited immigration, reaching several conclusions. This post outlines those conclusions and offers my commentary. The third part of the conclusions, which vaguely promises increased cooperation with third countries, is omitted...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the voluntary departure of irregular migrants: Act before you are forced to leave.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued its first ruling on &amp;ldquo;voluntary departure&amp;rdquo; provisions within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, which governs the deportation of undocumented non-EU migrants. While technically still an obligation to leave under threat of force, &amp;ldquo;voluntary departure&amp;rdquo; offers a more humane alternative to forced removal.
Typically, migrants are given 7 to 30 days for voluntary departure, extendable in specific cases. However, this period can be denied or shortened to less than seven days if the migrant is deemed a flight risk, if their application for legal stay was rejected as unfounded or fraudulent, or if they pose a risk to public safety, security, or national interests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The decision in Celaj by the CJEU: Implications of criminal penalties, entry bans, and the Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</guid><description>By Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a decision on October 1, 2015, in the case of Skerdjan Celaj (C-290/14) that once again addressed the relationship between immigration and criminal law. Specifically, the court examined whether national criminal penalties for unlawful migration align with the EU Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Court of Justice has made a ruling on the Schengen Conundrum, which involves a non-EU citizen who has been ordered to leave one Member State but holds a valid residence permit in another Member State.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</guid><description>Professors Elspeth Guild, Queen Mary University of London and Kingsley Napley, and Steve Peers, University of Essex
This article examines a case presented to the Court of Justice concerning the situation of a non-EU citizen residing in one Member State while facing potential expulsion by another.
Background
This issue presents legal complexities due to the involvement of two separate EU law sources. Article 25 of the Schengen Convention, amended in 2010, dictates that a Member State considering issuing a residence permit must first check the Schengen Information System (SIS) for any entry bans (alerts) on the individual...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the judicial oversight of detention a misleading disruption?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III
Member of the Institut Universitaire de France
On June 5, 2014, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) issued a decision in the Mahdi case, providing further interpretation of the Return Directive. This directive, formally known as Directive 2008/115/EC, establishes common standards for EU Member States regarding the return of illegally staying third-country nationals. The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s judgment builds upon its prior rulings concerning this directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mr. Avramopolous travels to Brussels: reflections on the European Parliament hearing for the new Migration Commissioner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Throughout his extensive three-hour hearing at the European Parliament, Dimitris Avramopolous, the nominee for Commissioner for migration and home affairs, consistently emphasized his commitment to liberal values. He expressed strong support for upholding the Schengen system, adopting a liberal stance on asylum and legal migration, and protecting the freedom of movement for EU citizens. However, he fell short of providing specifics on the implementation of these principles and how the various facets of EU policy in this domain would harmonize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is establishing procedural requirements in EU law the key to better safeguarding fundamental rights in migration?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/</guid><description>Opinion of Advocate General de la Tour in Joined Cases C, B (C‑704/20) and X (C‑39/21)
Alicja Słowik, Research Assistant, Centre for European Legal Studies (CEJE), University of Geneva
Photo credit: Abouttt, via Wikimedia commons
Finding a balance between a country&amp;rsquo;s right to manage its own legal processes and the need to protect rights granted by EU law has always been challenging for the European Court of Justice (ECJ or the Court)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>