<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MMC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mmc/</link><description>Recent content in MMC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mmc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount.</description></item><item><title>Bang &amp; Olufsen MMC Cartridge Protector: Dimensionally True Reproduction with Stereolithography</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 05:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</guid><description>I recently decided to test out the clear resin (sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;maker juice&amp;rdquo;) on my Formlabs Form 1 printer. I chose to design a replica of a Multi Media Card (MMC) cartridge protector, as they always seem to go missing. While I own multiple MMC cartridges, I only had one remaining protector.
As you can see in the images, the finished product is pretty good! The term &amp;ldquo;transparent&amp;rdquo; might be subjective, as the 3D-printed clear material doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite match the real thing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:</description></item><item><title>Bang&amp;Olufsen MMC20EN Vintage Cartridge Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</guid><description>The MMC20EN cartridge that came with my recently restored Beogram 4004 parts was tested using my evolving cartridge testing methodology.
My approach involves evaluating the frequency range and trackability of a cartridge. For this, I utilize three test records: the Analogue Audio Ultimate Test LP for checking frequency response up to 20kHz, the Fisher Test &amp;amp; Performance Standard Quadradisc to observe 30kHz carrier frequency reproduction, and the Clearaudio Trackability Test Record to assess the cantilever suspension&amp;rsquo;s condition at different groove amplitudes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame.</description></item></channel></rss>