<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>High Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/high-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in High Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/high-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Offers Lower Cost Carrier Grade Fiber Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</guid><description>Large bandwidth consumers, including major corporations, healthcare systems, independent phone companies, video production companies, and internet service providers, now have an affordable alternative for obtaining the reliable bandwidth they require. This shift is thanks to Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet provides metropolitan and long-distance bandwidth services using Ethernet technology rather than conventional telephone company methods. This service is often called Metro Ethernet within a single metropolitan area. These services deliver professional-grade bandwidth solutions characterized by high reliability and dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Corporate Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</guid><description>For medium to large businesses, a 100 Mbps connection speed is becoming the new norm. While this might seem excessive and expensive, it&amp;rsquo;s actually neither. In essence, Fast Ethernet is taking over the role of DS3.
A decade ago, a 1.5 Mbps T1 line was considered high bandwidth. Today&amp;rsquo;s need for 100 Mbps reflects the significant evolution of application requirements. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from basic video conferencing to high-definition, two-way video and telepresence.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item></channel></rss>