<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Serviced on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/serviced/</link><description>Recent content in Serviced on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/serviced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DAMAC introduces Maison Cour Jardin in the heart of downtown Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</guid><description>At the end of December 2014, DAMAC Properties, a high-end real estate developer, launched its third luxury serviced apartment complex in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area. Located just a short distance from popular attractions like the Dubai Mall and Dubai Fountain, DAMAC Maison Cour Jardin joins the company&amp;rsquo;s growing portfolio, which includes DAMAC Maison Dubai Mall Street and DAMAC Maison Canal Views.
Source: DAMAC Properties.
“DAMAC Properties is expanding its hospitality offerings, both in terms of scale and quality, to cater to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s visitors,” stated Niall McLoughlin, Senior Vice President of DAMAC Properties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ERC has opened a co-working space in multiple cities across Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</guid><description>The University Mentorship program will connect lecturers with the BIG Work community to offer guidance. Users can utilize ERC&amp;rsquo;s expertise in various business areas and schedule consultations with program managers and resource advisors Guests at the BIG Hotel, catering to international and startup business travelers, will have early access to new hospitality-related products and services for research. Entrepreneur Resource Centre Holdings (ERC) has launched BIG Work, a new co-working space with locations in Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ascott Star Rewards is marking its second anniversary with special promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 20:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</guid><description>Ascott Star Rewards (ASR), the loyalty program of The Ascott Limited, is marking its second anniversary with a &amp;ldquo;Celebrate The Little Joys&amp;rdquo; campaign. This campaign offers double bonus points and complimentary tier upgrades to show appreciation and reward its members.
Since its 2019 launch, ASR has experienced over 400% membership growth. ASR members are responsible for roughly 90% of Ascott’s direct online bookings, and over 60% are repeat guests. Compared to non-members, ASR members spend 36% more with Ascott...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DAMAC Properties has revealed plans for three new serviced hotels in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 05:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</guid><description>High-end real estate company DAMAC Properties is expanding its presence in the hospitality sector with the addition of three new serviced hotels in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area.
Two of these hotels, Cour Jardin and Capital Bay, are scheduled to open within the next few months, while Canal Views is already operational and receiving guests. This initiative is part of DAMAC Properties&amp;rsquo; goal to become the leading provider of serviced hotel apartments in the Middle East by 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>