<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ukraine on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ukraine/</link><description>Recent content in Ukraine on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:46:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon examine important legal matters related to EU sanctions against non-EU countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:46:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*
I recently attended a hearing at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning a case brought by Russian energy company Rosneft against EU sanctions imposed after Russia&amp;rsquo;s intervention in Crimea. The case, heard by the High Court of Justice (England &amp;amp; Wales), asks the CJEU to clarify the legitimacy of several aspects of these EU sanctions.</description></item><item><title>People without nationality and refugees escaping Ukraine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-without-nationality-and-refugees-escaping-ukraine/</guid><description>Chris Nash, Director of the European Network on Statelessness*
*Reblogged from the Network website
As the number of people seeking refuge from the conflict in Ukraine approaches two million, our organization and our members working in the region are working to understand the specific needs of stateless individuals displaced by this crisis.
Based on previous experiences, including our research from the Stateless Journeys initiative, we know that stateless people fleeing from conflict encounter additional obstacles when crossing borders and seeking asylum.</description></item><item><title>Opinion of Advocate General Szpunar on the compatibility of the Energy Charter Treaty with the Treaties and the jurisdiction of the CJEU in Case C-741/19.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</guid><description>Hannes Lenk, an Assistant Professor in Law at Aarhus University, examines a September 24, 2019 request by the French Cour d’appel de Paris. The court asked the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) to interpret &amp;ldquo;investment&amp;rdquo; as used in Article 1.6 of the Energy Charter Treaty (ECT). The intersection of the ECT and EU law, especially following the Achmea judgment against investor-state dispute settlement (ISDS) provisions in bilateral investment treaties (BITs) between EU Member States, has drawn scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>How can legislation empower Europe? By phasing out fossil fuels and implementing the Sustainability Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 02:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</guid><description>Ewan McGaughey, Reader in Law, King’s College London
Photo credit: Geopolitical Intelligence Services, via Wikicommons
Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine has prompted initiatives like RePowerEU and similar UK programs, aiming to eliminate reliance on Russian fossil fuels. President Biden has even called for a complete end to fossil fuel use, arguing that dependence on any authoritarian regime for energy is no longer acceptable. This shift recognizes the need to transition to renewable energy sources rapidly, acknowledging everyone&amp;rsquo;s fundamental right to benefit from scientific advancements.</description></item><item><title>Is there another accountability gap with the European Peace Facility?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</guid><description>Ellen Cantraine, PhD researcher, Ghent European Law Institute
Photo credit: Dietmar Rabich / Wikimedia Commons / “Münster, Stadtweinhaus, Beflaggung Ukraine und EU &amp;ndash; 2022 &amp;ndash; 0219” / CC BY-SA 4.0 / see also
Introduction
Following the 2021 coup attempt in Mali, the EU&amp;rsquo;s mission in Mali (EUTM) continued operating despite concerning reports of serious misconduct by EU-trained soldiers. Funded by the European Peace Facility (EPF), EUTM&amp;rsquo;s case exposed significant flaws in the EU&amp;rsquo;s external funding mechanisms.</description></item><item><title>Navigating a legal minefield: the potential dangers of expanding the reach of the EU Temporary Protection Directive past March 2025.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 07:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</guid><description>Dr Meltem Ineli-Ciger, Associate Professor, Suleyman Demirel University Faculty of Law; Migration Policy Centre Associate, European University Institute
Photo credit: Falin, on Wikimedia Commons
A crucial question arises as the March 2025 deadline for the Council Directive 2001/55/EC (Temporary Protection Directive), applicable to those fleeing the Ukraine conflict, approaches. This issue revolves around the fate of these individuals once this directive expires. Numerous experts, including myself, have explored potential solutions.</description></item><item><title>EU foreign policy sanctions: utilizing EU criminal law powers to extend and enforce them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 02:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post draws upon research for the forthcoming 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law (OUP, 2023)
The EU Council recently decided to expand its criminal law authority to encompass breaches of EU foreign policy sanctions. Following this, the EU Commission presented a proposal for a Directive that aims to utilize this expanded authority to harmonize the criminal laws of Member States on this subject.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Union a cause worth sacrificing for? Contemplating the future of Ukraine and the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</guid><description>There were many reasons to criticize the Yanukovych government in Ukraine, but the protests that led to its downfall were sparked by Yanukovych&amp;rsquo;s refusal to sign an agreement with the European Union. This strong desire for EU membership among some Ukrainians raises important questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s future.
The first steps after the planned elections would be straightforward. A pro-European government would likely ratify the association agreement, which connects Ukraine to EU law more closely than previous agreements.</description></item><item><title>Questions and Answers on Temporary Protection for Ukrainians in the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-and-answers-on-temporary-protection-for-ukrainians-in-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-and-answers-on-temporary-protection-for-ukrainians-in-the-european-union/</guid><description>Temporary Protection for People Fleeing Ukraine: What You Need to Know By Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*updated March 2 2022 to include the Commission proposal for use of the temporary protection Directive, and guidance for applying EU external borders law. Updated March 3 to refer to the Council agreeing on the decision. Updated March 4 to discuss the text of the decision. Updated March 28 to refer to guidance on and discussion of implementation.</description></item><item><title>Harmonisation of criminal law and foreign policy sanctions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post builds on and updates research for the 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law(OUP, 2023)
In late 2023, EU Member States and the European Parliament reached an agreement on a Directive designed to standardize criminal law related to violations of EU foreign policy sanctions. (Update: The Directive was formally adopted in April 2024 and subsequently published in the EU Official Journal).</description></item><item><title>What impact will the Dutch referendum on the EU/Ukraine association agreement have?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Brkan and Alexander Hoogenboom
On April 6, 2016, Dutch voters rejected the EU-Ukraine association agreement. The vote, with 61.1 percent voting against the agreement, was not unexpected based on recent polling. While voter turnout barely passed the 30 percent minimum, the outcome itself delivers a resounding &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;
The EU has established numerous association agreements with countries like Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, Israel, Egypt, Chile, Kosovo, and others. So why was a referendum held specifically for Ukraine?</description></item></channel></rss>