<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sports on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sports/</link><description>Recent content in Sports on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:46:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Actxa Spur makes training in your heart rate zone easier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</guid><description>Actxa has launched the Spur, a wearable fitness tracker that continuously monitors heart rate and provides zone indication. The Spur aims to make heart rate zone training accessible to everyone, not just athletes, by offering a user-friendly alternative to chest straps.
For years, fitness enthusiasts and athletes have used heart rate as a measure of workout intensity. A higher heart rate generally indicates a more intense workout.
The Spur uses a wrist-based sensor to measure resting heart rate and track different heart rate zones: Warm Up, Fat Burning, Cardio, Intense, and Maximum.</description></item><item><title>The 5th annual PCCW Global Charity Run will be held in Singapore this June</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</guid><description>Source: PCCW Global Charity Run web page. A picture from the same event in 2017.
The 5th yearly PCCW Global Charity Run will happen this June, and both PCCW employees and the general public can participate.
This run is organized by PCCW Global, a telecommunications company operating in Asia, Africa, Latin America, and the Middle East.
All funds raised from this year&amp;rsquo;s run will be donated to Make-A-Wish Singapore, an organization that grants wishes for children facing life-threatening illnesses.</description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself for the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</guid><description>Get ready for football fever this July as Arsenal, Atlético de Madrid, and Paris Saint-Germain head to Singapore for the 2018 International Champions Cup. This renowned annual tournament showcases top European football clubs competing across North America, Europe, and Asia.
Source: Sports Hub website. Three football clubs will be playing against each other at the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore on July 26, 28 and 30.
Beyond the three matches at the National Stadium on July 26th, 28th, and 30th, fans can immerse themselves in the excitement at the House of Football pop-up in Clarke Quay, Singapore’s vibrant nightlife and dining hub.</description></item><item><title>New retail and dining tenants have been announced at City Square Mall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</guid><description>City Developments (CDL) is updating the dining and retail options at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s City Square Mall.
The Decathlon store at City Square Mall, taken on 21 May.
French sporting goods retailer, Decathlon, launched its first Singaporean store on May 21, 2016. The company, known for its wide selection and reasonable prices, aims to make sports accessible.
“Our 21,500 sq ft store carries over 85,000 innovative, high-quality products across 50 sports. It will help Decathlon achieve its mission of making sports accessible to every Singaporean,” remarked Bastien Grandgeorge, CEO of Decathlon Singapore.</description></item><item><title>The YEEZY BOOST 350 will be released on August 22nd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</guid><description>On August 22, 2015, Kanye West and adidas Originals will launch a new all-black version of the YEEZY BOOST 350 sneaker in select stores worldwide. This release follows the successful June launch of the white YEEZY BOOST 350.
This is the third shoe model designed collaboratively by West and adidas. The low-top YEEZY BOOST 350 in black features a one-color upper made from adidas Primeknit, a material engineered to feel like a second skin.</description></item><item><title>Hisense introduces new televisions in Malaysia in anticipation of the World Cup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hisense-introduces-new-televisions-in-malaysia-in-anticipation-of-the-world-cup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 21:47:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hisense-introduces-new-televisions-in-malaysia-in-anticipation-of-the-world-cup/</guid><description>Hisense, a global technology company and official sponsor of the 2018 FIFA World Cup, recently introduced new high-definition televisions to the Malaysian market.
Andy Huang, Managing Director of Hisense Malaysia, highlighted the positive reception of their previous television models and their commitment to delivering an exceptional viewing experience. With the anticipation of the 2018 FIFA World Cup approaching, Hisense aims to enhance the football viewing experience for fans with their latest offerings: the U9A, U7A, and Laser TV.</description></item><item><title>The Bare Your Sole 2016 barefoot walkathon is scheduled to take place in Singapore this September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 14:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</guid><description>Source: Habitat for Humanity Singapore.
&amp;ldquo;Bare Your Sole,&amp;rdquo; the annual barefoot walkathon organized by Habitat for Humanity Singapore, returns to raise funds and awareness for those in need within Singapore. Now in its tenth year, the event will be held at OCBC Square on September 10th at 7:30 am.
The 2.5km and 5km charity walkathon will benefit Project HomeWorks, a local initiative dedicated to improving the living situations of the elderly, ill, and disabled individuals facing challenging conditions across Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing a football package that includes both Copa America and UEFA Euro 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Singtel will broadcast the Copa America Centenario USA 2016. This competition is the oldest international tournament for nations in the Americas and features top players like Alexis Sanchez, Lionel Messi, and Luis Suárez. This year, for the first time, the tournament will be hosted outside of South America.
Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director, Home, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, stated that combining Copa America 2016 and UEFA Euro 2016 broadcasts allows Singtel to provide fans with two of the most exciting football events globally.</description></item></channel></rss>