<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IDA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ida/</link><description>Recent content in IDA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:42:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ida/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel provides an explanation of mobile performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</guid><description>Singtel contributed to the Infocomm Development Authority&amp;rsquo;s (IDA) MyConnection SG study, highlighting connectivity, speed, and coverage as crucial aspects of user experience.
Singtel emphasized that, based on study feedback, users prioritize network coverage, call stability, customer service, and reliable data connections over pure speed. Consistent speed across a broad coverage area is key for a positive user experience. This feedback helps Singtel pinpoint areas for service enhancement.
Connectivity, as defined by Singtel, is the server connection response time, measured in milliseconds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IDA in Singapore has compiled a report on home computer usage in Singapore for the year 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</guid><description>A 2014 survey by the Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) of Singapore revealed a surge in smartphone, computer, and internet use among Singaporean seniors. The study, titled Annual Survey on Infocomm Usage in Households, found that 74% of Singaporean residents used a computer in the three months leading up to the survey. Senior citizens aged 50 and above showed the most significant increase in computer usage.
Between 2012 and 2014, computer use among seniors aged 50 to 59 grew by 14 percentage points, while those over 60 showed an 11 percentage-point increase...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Saturday at Suntec will demonstrate the future direction of consumer technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</guid><description>Source: Smart Nation website.
Tech Saturday is a public carnival presented by the Infocomm Development Authority of Singapore to demonstrate the power of technology. In addition to tech exhibitions, visitors can participate in interactive &amp;ldquo;Worksheds.&amp;rdquo;
Located throughout the carnival, these booths provide hands-on technology workshops. With options ranging from circuits to 3D printing, all workshops are free. While pre-registration is closed, same-day registration is available at counters near the Worksheds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>iWeb To Help Queenie The Elephant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iweb-to-help-queenie-the-elephant/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iweb-to-help-queenie-the-elephant/</guid><description>My wife and I are advocating for better living conditions for circus and zoo elephants. We believe animal sanctuaries like PAWS and The Elephant Sanctuary in Tennessee offer a more humane environment. Our focus is on Queenie, an elephant previously used for rides and performances at the Shrine Circus. Since losing her exhibitor&amp;rsquo;s license, she has been confined in Texas, often tethered to a tree.
We are urging the USDA to relocate Queenie to the spacious PAWS sanctuary in California...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iweb-to-help-queenie-the-elephant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iweb-to-help-queenie-the-elephant/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>