<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Subscription on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/subscription/</link><description>Recent content in Subscription on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/subscription/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel provides leasing options for high-end smartphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first mobile phone leasing program to make high-end devices more accessible.
Subscribers with SIM Only plans can choose to pay a low monthly fee to use premium Apple and Samsung handsets instead of buying them outright. They can lease the newest Apple iPhone and Samsung Galaxy models for two years and have the option to upgrade in the twelfth month for a S$200 fee.
With prices starting at S$35 per month for a Samsung Galaxy S9 (64 GB), customers can save up to S$578 off the regular retail price if they lease the phone for a year or S$358 if they keep it for two years.</description></item><item><title>Bookmate has teamed up with StarHub for its initial launch in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Bookmate. Pictured at the December 17 launch of Bookmate in Singapore are (from left): Simon Dunlop, Bookmate Founder, Andrew Baev, Bookmate Managing Director, and Michael Sim, StarHub Lead Futurist, i3 (Innovation, Investment, Incubation).
Bookmate, a social platform for reading e-books, has launched in Singapore, its initial entry point into the Southeast Asian market. The service offers subscribers unlimited reading for a fixed monthly price, drawing from a library of over half a million e-books provided by 600 publishers.</description></item><item><title>Google Drive prices have been significantly reduced by Google</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 23:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</guid><description>A blog post published on March 13 revealed that Google significantly reduced prices for cloud storage. The monthly fees have been adjusted to US$1.99 for 100GB (previously US$4.99), US$9.99 for 1TB (previously US$49.99), and US$99.99 for 10TB, with the option to purchase additional terabytes as required.
A 15 GB plan remains free of charge. This storage space can be utilized across Drive, Gmail, and Google+ Photos.
Source: Google
Existing paying users will be automatically transitioned to the corresponding updated plan without incurring additional costs.</description></item><item><title>The video-on-demand service HOOQ has been launched in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 06:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: HOOQ. Bithos.
HOOQ, a leading premium video-on-demand service targeting the Asian market, has officially launched in Singapore. This expansion follows successful launches in the Philippines, Thailand, India, and Indonesia, bringing their reach to a potential audience exceeding 1.6 billion people.
Established in Singapore in 2015, HOOQ is a joint venture between Singtel, Sony Pictures Television, and Warner Brothers. This partnership represents a significant collaboration between major media companies to revolutionize entertainment consumption in Asia.</description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination.</description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry.</description></item><item><title>Subscribe to Grabz for exclusive insider privileges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</guid><description>Source: Grabz website.
Grabz is a subscription service that provides its members with exclusive benefits and special offers. Using location-based alerts and a wide range of affiliated businesses, the app connects its subscribers with exclusive deals and privileges in their city.
For a monthly fee of S$15.98, premium members enjoy invitations to events and promotions such as discounted business class airfare and exclusive access to limited-edition luxury watches.
Premium members also get access to the Grabz Concierge, a personalized booking service that assists members with securing reservations at clubs and getting on guest lists for exclusive parties in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>