<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cost on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cost/</link><description>Recent content in Cost on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new budget-friendly Lumia is about to be released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The Lumia 430.
Microsoft has released the Lumia 430 Dual SIM, its most budget-friendly Lumia smartphone that can be upgraded to Windows 10*. Priced at approximately S$119, the Lumia 430 joins Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s affordable smartphone lineup alongside the Lumia 435, which features Lumia Camera.
Equipped with Windows Phone 8.1, a Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a 1.2GHz dual-core CPU, and pre-installed Microsoft Office, Skype, and OneDrive, the Lumia 430 Dual SIM enables users to be productive at work, enjoy entertainment, and stay connected while on the move...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Times Are Tough, Cell Phones Are Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 16:24:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/</guid><description>With the current economic climate, most people are looking for ways to save money. Instead of spending lavishly, it&amp;rsquo;s wiser to be cautious and prepare for potential tough times ahead. One way to save money is by finding deals on essential items like cell phone services and devices.
Many people purchase their cell phones from carrier stores or large retailers, but these places often charge a premium for the phones themselves...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian cities have been rearranged in Mercer's Cost of Living Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</guid><description>Five Asian cities—Hong Kong (ranked 2nd), Tokyo (3rd), Singapore (5th), Seoul (6th), and Shanghai (8th)—were named among the top 10 most expensive cities for expatriates in this year&amp;rsquo;s ranking.
Currency fluctuations played a significant role in shaping the rankings of most Asian cities.
While all mainland Chinese cities surveyed experienced a drop in ranking, Tianjin (12th) stood out as an exception, climbing 18 positions.
Mumbai, India made a remarkable jump of 25 places this year, attributed to robust economic growth, inflation, and a stable currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing financial consequences of cybercrime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</guid><description>Source: HP infographic.
HP recently released the findings of their sixth annual study, conducted in partnership with the Ponemon Institute, exploring the financial effects of cyberattacks on both public and private sectors.
The study shows a substantial rise in the total cost of cybercrime, indicating that smaller companies bear a proportionally larger cost than larger ones.
The 2015 Cost of Cyber Crime Study, carried out by the Ponemon Institute and supported by HP Enterprise Security, calculates the yearly cost of cybercrime for businesses across seven countries: the US, UK, Japan, Germany, Australia, Brazil, and Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>