<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Minimum Unit Pricing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/minimum-unit-pricing/</link><description>Recent content in Minimum Unit Pricing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/minimum-unit-pricing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The alignment of Ireland's Public Health (Alcohol) Bill with EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Ollie Bartlett, Maynooth University
After nearly three years of discussion, the Irish Public Health (Alcohol) Bill has been passed by the Irish Parliament. The Bill aims to address Ireland&amp;rsquo;s significant alcohol-related harm through five key measures: minimum alcohol pricing; stricter labeling; advertising restrictions; separating alcohol from other retail products; and limitations on alcohol sales and supply.
While lauded as &amp;ldquo;groundbreaking&amp;rdquo; by Health Minister Simon Harris, some argue that elements of the Bill, particularly those related to the free trade of alcohol within the European Union, might not be legal.</description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34.</description></item><item><title>Balancing Health and Trade: The Scotch Whisky Association ruling on finding the right equilibrium.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School The Court of Justice has issued its judgment regarding the legality of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s minimum alcohol pricing (MUP) measure in Case C-333/14. Both the Scottish Government and the Scotch Whisky Association (SWA), which initiated the legal challenge, have expressed satisfaction with the ruling, although the SWA might be more content as the case now returns to Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Inner House of the Court of Session, which had referred it to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General considers the intersection of public health, trade, and competition in setting minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School Background to the Opinion Advocate General (AG) Bot provided his opinion on September 3rd, 2015, regarding Case C-333/14, which involved the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to establish a minimum price per unit (£0.50) on alcohol sales. This Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) faced legal challenges from the Scotch Whisky Association, leading to the case reaching the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The CJEU was asked to determine whether the MUP aligned with the single Common Market Organisation (CMO) and the free movement principles of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item></channel></rss>