<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Packet Switching on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/packet-switching/</link><description>Recent content in Packet Switching on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/packet-switching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sipping on the Trunk Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</guid><description>The history of telephone trunks goes back to the early days of telephones. Trunks are lines that carry multiple phone conversations, initially connecting switchboards and switching offices. They&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from wire bundles to analog and now digital circuits, with T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and SONET being common digital trunking services. However, SIP trunking is emerging as a popular alternative.
Telephone trunking saves money by combining multiple phone lines into a single high-bandwidth connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodbye Frame Relay, Hello MPLS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</guid><description>Managing communication across multiple business locations can be challenging. While private lines offer a solution, their cost increases with the number of locations. Frame Relay, a private network solution, gained popularity for its reliability, security, and affordability. However, MPLS networks have emerged as a newer technology offering higher bandwidth and lower costs.
Frame Relay bridges the gap between public switched telephone networks and dedicated private lines. It replaces physical wires with virtual circuits, eliminating the need for dedicated circuits that incur costs regardless of usage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigaMAN and Gigabit Ethernet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</guid><description>Organizations in need of truly fast wide area network connections should consider gigabit Ethernet services like GigaMAN. These high-bandwidth circuits are now more affordable than ever.
Ethernet WAN services are a newer option for businesses and organizations, offering end-to-end Ethernet protocol signal maintenance. This eliminates the need for protocol conversion between a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN and traditional TDM telco circuits.
Ethernet speeds range from 10 Mbps (standard) to 100 Mbps (Fast Ethernet) and 1000 Mbps (Gigabit Ethernet)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>