<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guiding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guiding/</link><description>Recent content in Guiding on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guiding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Transport Lock Bushings and cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>Many Beogram 4002 (5513) turntables, including the one I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring, require replacement of the transport lock bushings and cabinet guidance washers. These components are crucial for proper platter and arm alignment. Without them, alignment is unreliable and won&amp;rsquo;t hold during transport.
This image shows the front transport lock missing its bushing:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the disassembled mechanism with the lower part of the new bushings installed:
The top part of the bushing is added next:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings and Missing Cabinet Guiding Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration involved addressing the common issue of fragile orange transport lock bushings and missing cabinet guiding washers. Many Beograms used plastic washers, which are prone to cracking and falling apart. This was evident in the restoration project, as some washers were missing entirely.
To rectify this, five new 3D-printed washers were installed. For aesthetic purposes, using a black washer for the front-center position is recommended to avoid visibility through the gap between the aluminum panel and the plinth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Glueing a Delaminated Platter Back Together and Installation of New Cabined Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on was unfortunately damaged during shipping due to inadequate packaging by the seller. Because the platter wasn&amp;rsquo;t secured, it moved around and ultimately split into two pieces. The images show the separated top and bottom sections of the platter.
Examining the platter&amp;rsquo;s interior reveals interesting details about its construction. The heavier bottom section of each platter was individually balanced, much like car tires. This involved drilling away small amounts of material from the heavier side, as evidenced by the red pen marks near the drill holes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Tracking Force and Replacing the Strange Original Front Center Cabinet Guiding Washer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s playing beautifully. As I write this, I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying &amp;ldquo;Song for My Father&amp;rdquo; by Horace Silver on a reissue, as original pressings are unfortunately outside my budget these days.
One of the final tasks was refining the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s mechanics. I calibrated the tonearm weight and limits and replaced the guiding washer, which ensures the plinth moves smoothly. The original washer, pictured below, has a design flaw that was later corrected in the Beogram 400x series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>