<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NSW on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nsw/</link><description>Recent content in NSW on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nsw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Sydney ICC Hotel will now be referred to as the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Artist&amp;rsquo;s rendition of the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
Accor, the leading hotel group in Australia, will manage the new International Convention Centre (ICC) Hotel in Sydney under its luxury Sofitel brand. The hotel will be called Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
This Sofitel hotel is part of the New South Wales government&amp;rsquo;s A$2.5 billion project to transform Darling Harbour, creating a new hub for conventions, exhibitions, and entertainment in Sydney.</description></item><item><title>Come to Vivid Sydney and immerse yourself in the biggest festival of light, music, and ideas in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</guid><description>Source: Vivid Sydney/Destination NSW.
Vivid Sydney, a global festival celebrating light, music, and ideas, will illuminate Sydney until June 8th. Last year, the festival drew in 1.43 million attendees.
Stuart Ayres, the NSW Minister for Trade, Tourism and Major Events, highlighted the festival&amp;rsquo;s ability to transform Sydney for 18 days and nights with creativity and vibrant light displays. He emphasized it as a must-see event for showcasing the city&amp;rsquo;s pride.</description></item></channel></rss>