<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GigE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gige/</link><description>Recent content in GigE on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gige/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow.</description></item><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light.</description></item><item><title>High Fiber Diet for Business Not Expensive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</guid><description>With business picking up, many companies are hitting a wall – their internet connections can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the increased data flow. The solution? A high-fiber diet for their network.
Fiber optic cables are incredibly efficient. A single strand can handle massive amounts of voice, data, and video simultaneously, far exceeding the needs of most businesses. This capacity can be further multiplied by splitting the light into different wavelengths, each carrying gigabits per second.</description></item><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>Lock In Telecom Cost Savings For Next Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</guid><description>As we wrap up the year and analyze our performance, it&amp;rsquo;s common to wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re overspending on business operations, especially networking and telecom. A thorough market analysis often reveals opportunities to secure better rates for the same services. By doing this now, you can lock in savings for the entire next year.
Why are such savings possible? Primarily, increased competition and technological advancements. Previously, businesses were limited to local telephone companies for their communication needs.</description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs.</description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>Ethernet WAN is the most significant advancement in business broadband since T1 service prices dropped. What exactly is Ethernet WAN, and why should you care?
Ethernet has become the dominant standard for Local Area Networks (LANs). You could say that Ethernet is everywhere. An RJ45 Ethernet jack is standard on every desktop and laptop computer. You might not get a CD-ROM drive, probably won&amp;rsquo;t get a floppy disc drive, and may never use the phone modem jack again.</description></item><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>E-Rate Discounted Broadband Internet for Schools and Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</guid><description>Educational institutions and libraries are demanding high-speed internet, which has become essential for business, personal growth, and various types of learning. While most public resources have some internet access, there is increasing pressure to enhance speed for more users and advanced applications. The main obstacle is the cost.
Discounted Service is Available A government program offers discounts of 20% to 90% on broadband internet upgrades for most K-12 schools and libraries.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Fiber Needed By Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</guid><description>While many believe fiber optic bandwidth is the way of the future, it&amp;rsquo;s already a smart choice for businesses today.
Traditionally, businesses have depended on copper-based telecom services. The copper wiring integrated during a building&amp;rsquo;s construction becomes the backbone for multi-line phone systems, ISDN digital trunking for PBX systems, and T1 lines connecting offices and providing broadband internet. This infrastructure has been the standard for many small and medium-sized businesses for decades.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Buildings Offer High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Do you want to upgrade your internet speed from slow copper or fixed wireless connections to the rapid speeds offered by fiber optic cables? Are you trying to avoid the high cost of installing new fiber optic cables? If so, you should consider moving into a fiber building.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; a fiber building isn&amp;rsquo;t constructed from exotic materials like carbon fiber. The term &amp;ldquo;fiber&amp;rdquo; refers to the type of telecommunication services already available within the building.</description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth is Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Business bandwidth solutions are significantly more expensive than residential options like DSL or Cable. While this is partly due to their guaranteed reliability and dedicated lines, another factor is the complex infrastructure involved. Providing business-grade services often requires collaboration between a long-haul carrier and the local phone company for the final connection.
Despite recent price drops in dedicated T1 connections, high-bandwidth services remain costly, potentially hindering smaller companies needing to transmit large amounts of data.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</guid><description>Businesses can now benefit from a new, cost-effective broadband connection service: Ethernet Internet. To learn more about this exciting development, watch my concise YouTube presentation here: Ethernet Internet business presentation.
As the presentation highlights, Ethernet Internet offers a rare combination of affordability and superior performance. This cutting-edge technology is rapidly evolving and expanding beyond metropolitan areas. Soon, it will be accessible across the country, delivered wirelessly in rural regions and through copper or fiber optic connections in urban centers, with speeds reaching up to 10 Mbps or higher.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades.</description></item><item><title>Diverse Connections For Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</guid><description>The reliability of data connections is crucial for data centers and colocation facilities to ensure service availability. Having multiple separate network connections is not enough; you need multiple diverse data connections from different providers that take different routes to your facility.
Simply having multiple connections from a single provider offers limited protection because a catastrophic failure could take down the entire connection. This risk is amplified in your own facility, where a single connection runs for miles and is vulnerable to disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand.</description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles.</description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet as a DS3 Upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line provides have historically opted for DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. This high-speed digital connection typically runs on a SONET fiber optic circuit, with the final connection to the customer&amp;rsquo;s location installed and maintained by the local phone company. DS3 is fast, very reliable, and more affordable than ever before. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new contender – Fast Ethernet.
Fast Ethernet is a standard Ethernet LAN speed that delivers 100 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps).</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Covad and ADTRAN Make Everything Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</guid><description>The arrival of Carrier Ethernet is generating considerable excitement around IP core networks and Ethernet access solutions. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean traditional TDM services are obsolete. DS1 and DS3 circuits can be adapted for Ethernet transport with the right equipment, as demonstrated by Carrier Covad and equipment manufacturer ADTRAN.
Covad is expanding its Ethernet service area using ADTRAN&amp;rsquo;s central office and network termination equipment. With a nationwide core network, Covad serves 44 states and 235 major markets, specializing in business DSL, data T1, fixed wireless, bonded T1, and integrated voice and data solutions.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Plus Copper Equals High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 03:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Our appetite for bandwidth is insatiable, growing daily. Businesses and consumers alike are hampered by insufficient bandwidth, preventing them from fully utilizing the latest technologies. Content providers and productivity vendors face similar hurdles, unable to deliver their full potential due to inadequate transport and last-mile bandwidth.
This scenario mirrors the early days of personal computers. For decades, limitations in processor speed, RAM, and hard disk capacity were constant challenges. While advancements in these areas have significantly minimized these bottlenecks, they haven&amp;rsquo;t entirely vanished.</description></item><item><title>Insatiable Demand For Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>10 Gbps used to be a bandwidth amount so large that only major telecommunications companies needed it. That&amp;rsquo;s no longer true, as businesses are now using that much WAN bandwidth and wanting even more.
Beyond internet providers, who could need 10 Gbps? According to Carrier Ethernet News, the finance, streaming entertainment, and medical industries are leading the demand for high bandwidth. Some are even hoping for 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps!</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>As companies increasingly adopt cloud services and engage in data-heavy activities like video streaming and big data analysis, the demand for greater WAN bandwidth is on the rise. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming commonplace to see requests for 1,000 Mbps connections, often fulfilled by a 1 Gbps Ethernet or GigE point-to-point connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the details and available choices for Gigabit Ethernet service.
Ethernet, the standard protocol for LANs, commonly operates at speeds of 10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1,000 Mbps, or 10 Gbps.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future.</description></item><item><title>GigE For Business Not So Far-Fetched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</guid><description>The increasing demands of online technologies, particularly those using graphics and video, are putting pressure on Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. While ordering a T1 line was once a big decision, businesses may soon need to consider Gigabit Ethernet connections.
While Gigabit Ethernet is often associated with large-scale networks, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly relevant for businesses. With corporate LANs already transitioning to faster speeds, the WAN connection often becomes a bottleneck.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need Bandwidth on Demand?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When subscribing to bandwidth, you&amp;rsquo;re usually expected to understand your network&amp;rsquo;s needs and pick the optimal service. But what if your needs are unclear or fluctuate? What about transitioning from in-house IT to cloud-based services? What are the consequences of an incorrect choice?
Traditional Bandwidth Services Fall Short
Conventional line contracts offer fixed bandwidth for a predetermined period, like a DS3 connection providing 45 Mbps constantly. While this guarantees consistent speed, you pay even when it&amp;rsquo;s idle.</description></item><item><title>100, 1000, 10000 Mbps Internet Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As technology progresses, businesses require significantly faster internet speeds. Our Wide Area Networks (WANs) are now crucial for operations. Today, internet connections of 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps, and even 10,000 Mbps are standard and essential. Fortunately, pricing has decreased as speeds have increased, making these bandwidth levels attainable.
100 Mbps Fast Ethernet
100 Mbps is the current standard bandwidth, replacing the older 45 Mbps DS3 bandwidth. DS3, an upgrade from slower T1 lines, is part of the TDM telecom standard.</description></item><item><title>How Growing Companies Buy Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-growing-companies-buy-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-growing-companies-buy-bandwidth/</guid><description>As businesses recover and grow, they&amp;rsquo;ll need more resources. But with economic uncertainty, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to expand cautiously. Is that even possible with bandwidth?
Yes, it is. Traditional telecom contracts lock you into a service level for 1 to 3 years. For example, a T1 line provides a fixed 1.5 Mbps bandwidth for a monthly fee. Doubling bandwidth means another T1 line. These lines can be &amp;lsquo;bonded&amp;rsquo; for combined bandwidth, either by the provider or using devices like Mushroom Networks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Truffle.</description></item><item><title>T1's for Business Parks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</guid><description>Most businesses require reliable communication services, but options can be limited outside of major city centers. While downtown areas boast a variety of high-speed internet providers, businesses in industrial parks often face fewer choices.
Similar to essential utilities, reliable internet access is crucial for modern businesses. However, many older industrial parks were developed before the internet&amp;rsquo;s prominence, lacking the infrastructure for high-speed connections.
Despite this, businesses in these areas still have reliable options.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic ISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</guid><description>Internet service used to rely on dial-up connections, but it has advanced significantly since then. Today, medium-sized businesses are now transitioning to fiber optic internet service providers, a technology already embraced by larger corporations.
Residential fiber optic internet, like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS, offers high speeds, with Google soon to introduce even faster Gigabit service. Business broadband connections, however, have already surpassed Gigabit speeds, with 10 Gbps becoming increasingly common. The technology is well-established, leaving businesses to determine their bandwidth needs and locations.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Connection Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</guid><description>Businesses require internet access for both customer communication and internal operations. Unlike residential internet, business connections demand higher reliability because downtime directly translates to financial losses, especially for online businesses. Cost-effectiveness is also crucial.
Ethernet Internet is a relatively new technology that offers advantages in both cost and reliability. Additionally, it may provide bandwidth options previously unavailable in your area. A quick search with this Ethernet Internet Finder can reveal your options.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet and Colocation For Texas Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</guid><description>Texas is known for its expansive size, thriving businesses, massive data generation, and a critical need for extensive bandwidth. Alpheus, a Texas-based telecommunications company, is acutely aware of these needs and caters its services to businesses across various sectors including finance, energy, government, healthcare, IT, legal, and media.
Headquartered in Houston, Alpheus boasts a robust fiber optic network that interconnects major Texan cities like Dallas, Fort Worth, Waco, Bryan, Austin, San Antonio, Laredo, McAllen, Harlingen, Corpus Christi, Victoria, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Fiber Replaces Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 02:23:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T1 lines have been a popular connectivity solution for businesses for many years due to their reliability and flexibility in private lines, dedicated internet access, and telephone trunking. However, with the increasing demands of cloud applications and HD video, the fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps has become a significant limitation.
Solution #1: Bonded T1 Lines
One way to increase bandwidth is to combine multiple T1 lines. This can be achieved using a WAN aggregation device or by ordering bonded T1 lines from a provider.</description></item><item><title>What Can GigE Bandwidth Do For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly common in local area networks, with network cards and backbones now supporting these higher speeds. Companies that rely heavily on digital processes and high bandwidth data transfers are likely already using Gigabit Ethernet. However, they need a way to extend these high-speed transfers beyond their local networks.
Companies with large numbers of employees, extensive customer bases, or applications that generate significant amounts of data can benefit from Gigabit Ethernet WAN connections.</description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Internet Access Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 02:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes now have near-universal access to broadband internet. However, are you utilizing the optimal internet connection for your needs? It might be time to consider Ethernet.
Metro Ethernet Networks are rapidly expanding and provide significant benefits to businesses. Cost savings are a key advantage, potentially cutting your internet bandwidth expenses by half or more compared to your current solution. This significant cost reduction comes without compromising reliability or dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting in Clouds and Colos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</guid><description>There are many hosting choices available. Shared hosting is popular among individuals and small businesses due to its affordability and acceptable performance. However, as your needs grow, you face a decision: self-hosting or a managed solution.
While setting up a website previously required technical expertise in server management, Linux and Windows hosting have become increasingly user-friendly and widely accessible. Even large enterprises accustomed to managing their servers in-house are reconsidering colocation and cloud solutions, driven by cost and resource optimization.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Speeds Without DS3 Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</guid><description>Businesses needing substantial bandwidth for tasks like online commerce, video streaming, medical data transfer, or dedicated internet access have historically relied on DS3 connections. These provided speeds exceeding T1 lines. However, a new option delivers comparable speeds without the high price tag: Metro Ethernet and Carrier Ethernet.
These terms represent regional and long-distance high-bandwidth transport services using the Ethernet protocol. An Ethernet WAN connection connects your LAN to another business location, a network of multiple locations, or a dedicated high-speed internet connection.</description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive.</description></item><item><title>FastE Is The New DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than their T1 lines can provide have usually upgraded to DS3. However, a faster and more affordable option, Fast Ethernet (FastE), is now available.
While you might not know Fast Ethernet as a Metro or Carrier bandwidth service, the term is likely familiar. Fast Ethernet refers to 100 Mbps Ethernet, one of the standard LAN speeds alongside 10 Mbps and 1,000 Mbps Ethernet (Gigabit Ethernet or GigE).</description></item><item><title>Finding Fiber Lit Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 18:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</guid><description>To secure high bandwidth at affordable rates, you need to be in a &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; building. This term refers to buildings equipped with active fiber optic bandwidth services, utilizing laser light to transmit data through fiber optic strands.
If your building is &amp;ldquo;lit,&amp;rdquo; obtaining fiber optic bandwidth is typically straightforward, though construction costs might apply if cabling to your space is absent. However, a bigger challenge arises if your building lacks fiber optic connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price.</description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet is Cheaper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</guid><description>You probably know that T1 and DS3 lines have become much cheaper in recent years. But for those who need bandwidth of 10 Mbps or more, there&amp;rsquo;s an even better deal: Ethernet.
While you might know Ethernet as a local area network protocol, it&amp;rsquo;s now a wide area network protocol too. This means your carrier can provide an Ethernet connection that plugs directly into your existing network router or switch. You might see it called Ethernet WAN, Metro Ethernet, Carrier Ethernet, or Ethernet Transport.</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Maps At Your Fingertips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</guid><description>You might want to upgrade to a faster internet service, but the cost of installing fiber optic cables might seem scary. How can you figure out if upgrading from copper to fiber is affordable?
The easiest way is to compare quotes from different providers in your area. A telecom broker, like Telarus, Inc., can gather these quotes for you quickly and easily. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a report with pricing from all major providers in your area.</description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Service Access For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</guid><description>Having internet access is essential for businesses today, whether they operate primarily online or from a physical location. It&amp;rsquo;s how businesses connect with customers, suppliers, remote employees, and even their own offices. But is the internet service used by businesses the same as what individuals use at home?
There are actually different options for internet service, each with unique features: dedicated or shared bandwidth, symmetrical or asymmetrical speeds, wired or wireless connection, copper or fiber optic cables, and varying levels of bandwidth and cost.</description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Leads in High Bandwidth Ethernet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 22:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a significant change in high-bandwidth services, moving away from older SONET/SDH technology and towards Ethernet IP technology. This shift, driven by the long-term transition from analog to digital communications and the widespread use of Ethernet, could indicate a turning point for Ethernet in fiber optic communication, as argued by AboveNet.
AboveNet, a provider of high-bandwidth services in 15 major U.S. markets and the UK, specializes in fiber optic MAN and WAN connectivity, offering speeds from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps at lower prices than traditional telecom providers.</description></item><item><title>Why Look For Fiber Lit Buildings?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-look-for-fiber-lit-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 19:06:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-look-for-fiber-lit-buildings/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fiber lit building&amp;rdquo; refers to a building already equipped with fiber optic service. This is a significant advantage because it provides access to high-bandwidth internet without expensive installation costs.
To find these buildings, you can use the Ethernet Buildings Lit Building Locator. This online tool acts as a map to locate buildings with existing high-bandwidth infrastructure.
Fiber optic connections offer almost limitless bandwidth potential. While renting an office space won&amp;rsquo;t likely provide terabits per second, fiber connections can readily handle Gigabit Ethernet, 10 GigE, and even multiplexed connections for significantly higher capacity.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Competitive Fiber Optic Service Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</guid><description>Does your company use a lot of bandwidth? We&amp;rsquo;re talking 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps or more of reliable, commercial-grade bandwidth. If so, bonded T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper won&amp;rsquo;t cut it. You need fiber optic service. But is competitive fiber optic bandwidth an option in your area? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out&amp;hellip;
The reality is that buildings equipped for fiber optic service are appearing faster than ever. Why? Because today&amp;rsquo;s data-heavy applications need increasingly faster network speeds.</description></item></channel></rss>