<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dubai on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dubai/</link><description>Recent content in Dubai on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dubai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The success of Dubai as a business hub will depend on talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-success-of-dubai-as-a-business-hub-will-depend-on-talent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-success-of-dubai-as-a-business-hub-will-depend-on-talent/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Crown Prince and Chairman of The Executive Council, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, emphasized the importance of skill development, talent discovery, and attracting skilled professionals to establish Dubai as a future-forward city during his visit to LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s regional headquarters.
He attributed Dubai&amp;rsquo;s success in drawing entrepreneurs and multinational corporations to its conducive investment climate, fostering a hub of exceptional talent. This aligns with the vision of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister and Ruler of Dubai, to shape Dubai into a knowledge-based, innovation-driven economy.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber has announced the launch of the Dubai Smartpreneur Competition for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, working with the Smart Dubai Office, launched the second annual Dubai Smartpreneur Competition. This aligns with the vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, to make Dubai a leading smart city.
Source: Dubai Chamber. The event featured a panel discussion about the UAE government&amp;rsquo;s progress on smart city and innovation initiatives, and what will drive future sustainable growth.</description></item><item><title>DED allows for the licensing of eight additional business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</guid><description>Source: DED. Bushahab.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Economic Development (DED) has expanded its list of permissible business activities, increasing the total to 2,133. This decision stems from regular feedback gathered from various industry sectors regarding local market needs and the balance of supply and demand. The goal is to simplify business operations and offer essential resources for growth.
The new additions encompass several specialized activities. These include assembling industrial robots, providing tax consultancy services, printing secure documents, manufacturing scanners, collecting and transporting hazardous waste, offering health consultancy, brokering financing deals, and developing and managing applications for social media.</description></item><item><title>Dubai-Opoly aims to showcase Dubai as a premier business destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-opoly-aims-to-showcase-dubai-as-a-premier-business-destination/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-opoly-aims-to-showcase-dubai-as-a-premier-business-destination/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Dubai Chamber creates Dubai-Opoly game to promote
Dubai.
The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced Dubai-Opoly, a board game designed to highlight Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing as a global business and trade hub.
Inspired by the classic game Monopoly, Dubai-Opoly will soon be available in stores across the UAE and GCC region. The game will showcase some of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most iconic landmarks and attractions. This initiative aligns with the Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s efforts to strengthen the emirate&amp;rsquo;s image as a thriving commercial center and top tourist destination.</description></item><item><title>Consumer Card achieves outstanding success, according to DIB's report</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</guid><description>Source: DIB website. Banner for the Consumer Card page.
The Consumer Card, a collaboration between the Department of Economic Development (DED) in Dubai and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the largest Islamic bank in the UAE, has surpassed expectations in a very competitive market by the close of 2016. This success highlights how much customers value the card&amp;rsquo;s transparency and customer-centric approach.
Customers appreciate the card&amp;rsquo;s straightforward rewards system, which focuses on everyday transactions rather than requiring increased spending.</description></item><item><title>Dubai World Central is pleased to welcome partnerships between the UAE and Japan through the Japan Trade Centre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</guid><description>Source: Dubai World Central. Khalid Abdulla, Vice President, Licensing, Registration &amp;amp; Permits Approval, Dubai World Central, Usama Saleh, Vice President, Land Planning and Development, Dubai World Central, with Shogo Ishida, Director, JTC DWC LLC, during the inauguration of the Japan Trade Centre at Dubai World Central in January 2015.
The Japan Trade Centre (JTC), a private business-to-business platform promoting Japanese small and medium enterprises (SMEs) internationally, is now operational at Dubai World Central (DWC)&amp;rsquo;s Business Park.</description></item><item><title>The perspectives of Gen Z differ from those of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</guid><description>A panel discussion at the Global Islamic Economy Summit focused on the characteristics of Generation Z, the generation following Millennials. Growing up with the internet and mobile phones, Gen Z is not only tech-savvy but also possesses a distinct perspective.
Sunil John, CEO of ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller, pointed out that governments are increasingly paying attention to this generation, questioning if current education and employment systems meet their needs. Citing the ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey 2016, John highlighted that 58% of young Arabs desire higher education, and 36% aim to start businesses, a departure from the traditional reliance on government jobs.</description></item><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC).</description></item><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha provides Iftar and suhoor meals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</guid><description>Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha is offering special meals for iftar and suhoor throughout Ramadan.
Source: Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha website. The Gem Garden.
George Sarkis, Director of Food and Beverage at the hotel, highlights the extensive iftar buffet, which combines Oriental and Continental cuisines with traditional Ramadan drinks.
Both iftar and suhoor are served at The Gem Garden, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s all-day dining venue. The iftar buffet, available from sunset to 10 pm, costs AED120* per person and includes live cooking stations.</description></item><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home.</description></item><item><title>Take a virtual tour of Emaar hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Using panoramic photography and videography, each virtual tour showcases the hotel&amp;rsquo;s features in detail.
Emaar Hospitality Group, the hospitality and leisure branch of Emaar Properties, has launched 360-degree virtual tours of its hotels in Dubai, UAE. These tours, created with high-definition photos and videos, allow potential guests to experience each hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique offerings, explore its various aspects, and make well-informed booking decisions.
The virtual tours encompass properties under the luxury Address Hotels + Resorts brand, the upscale lifestyle Vida Hotels and Resorts brand, and the new contemporary mid-scale Rove Hotels brand.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA announces transport service timings for Eid al Fitr holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) has released the operating schedules for its services during the Eid al-Fitr holidays. The schedule covers various services, including customer service centers, parking, public buses, Dubai Metro and Tram, marine transit, driving institutes, and vehicle testing and registration centers.
Source: RTA. Al Marri.
Moaza Al Marri, RTA&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communication, stated that Customer Service Centers will be closed for the Eid al-Fitr holiday from Sunday, July 3rd, 2016, and will reopen on Sunday, July 10th, 2016.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has welcomed three new celebrity chefs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. From left: Costa, Joinie-Maurin, Kurdahl, Semblat and Silva.
The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has added three new chefs to its roster of acclaimed restaurants, aiming to elevate the dining experience for their guests.
Jose Silva, CEO of Jumeirah Group, stated that the addition of these culinary experts to their flagship Dubai hotel signifies the beginning of a more diverse and innovative culinary program. He emphasized their dedication to guest experiences as a crucial aspect of luxury hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Air Arabia has opened a new sales office in Dubai and has also introduced city check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</guid><description>Air Arabia, a leading low-cost carrier in the Middle East and North Africa, has expanded its presence in Dubai, UAE, by opening a new sales office and city terminal check-in facility.
Adel Al Ali, Group CEO of Air Arabia, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to enhancing customer experience and convenience across its network. He emphasized the significance of the new sales office in strengthening their services in Dubai and the UAE.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Jumeirah City Break</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah website.
City Breaks at Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Jumeirah Creekside Hotel, and Jumeirah Living World Trade Centre Residences come with perks like free entry to Wild Wadi Waterpark and Zero Gravity Private Beach.
Jumeirah Emirates Towers boasts shopping at the Boulevard, various dining and nightlife options, and a convenient location just five minutes from Dubai Mall, accessible via the hotel&amp;rsquo;s complimentary shuttle service.
Reserve a room for three or more nights at participating Jumeirah hotels in Dubai with the Jumeirah City Break promotion and enjoy a 20% discount on the best available rates, along with:</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new flights to Istanbul's Sabiha Gokcen Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</guid><description>Emirates now offers 18 flights to Istanbul every week, including a new daily service to Sabiha Gökçen Airport in addition to its existing flights to Istanbul Atatürk Airport. This makes Istanbul the third city after London and Tokyo to be served by Emirates from two airports. The new daily flight is operated with an Airbus A330-200, offering 12 First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 183 Economy Class seats, and also provides up to 12 tonnes of cargo capacity each way.</description></item><item><title>The DIB Mobile app has been enhanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</guid><description>Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has launched an upgraded version of its mobile banking app for iOS and Android devices. This enhanced app offers access to over 60 services, including features designed to help users manage their personal finances effectively.
With smartphone usage on the rise and Nielsen reporting that 78% of the UAE population owns at least one such device, DIB&amp;rsquo;s mobile app caters to this growing trend.</description></item><item><title>Winners of the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Awards are influential figures in promoting knowledge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 01:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. A representative from the MiSK Foundation receives the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award.
The Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award recipients, celebrated on November 21st, share a common goal: shaping the future. This award acknowledges those who significantly contribute to the creation and dissemination of knowledge globally.
Among the winners, Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s MiSK Foundation focuses on developing educational institutions and bolstering scientific research.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has identified Tokyo, Singapore, and Dubai as some of the top choices in its Cities Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</guid><description>Singapore at night.
The travel website TripAdvisor recently published its second annual Cities Survey, which collected data from over 54,000 user reviews. The survey evaluated cities worldwide based on traveler feedback.
Tokyo received the highest ranking for providing the best overall travel experience. It also earned top scores for its helpful residents, taxi services, public transportation, and clean streets. Tokyo ranked among the top ten cities in 13 out of 16 survey categories.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Golf introduces special promotions for Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Golf website.
During Ramadan, Dubai Golf has several special iftar and suhoor packages perfect for corporate events.
QD&amp;rsquo;s
QD&amp;rsquo;s has a special Ramadan tent where they serve both iftar and suhoor. The daily iftar buffet features a variety of traditional hot and cold Arabic mezze, soups, Middle Eastern and international main dishes, and desserts. This comes with your choice of juice and traditional Arabic sweets and dates.</description></item><item><title>Art covering Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 08:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</guid><description>Brand Dubai, the creative branch of the Government of Dubai Media Office (GDMO), and the Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) have joined forces to enhance the city&amp;rsquo;s aesthetics. This three-year partnership will involve a series of city beautification projects.
Their first initiative, the Dubai Metro Murals Project, will feature artwork on the pillars of the Dubai Metro line along Sheikh Zayed Road. Renowned artists Daniel Cortez from Peru and Evoca1 (Elio Mercado) from the Dominican Republic will create murals between the Dubai International Financial Centre and Emirates Towers stations.</description></item><item><title>In 2018, Dubai drew in more than 1,000 residents with a net worth of over a million dollars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</guid><description>Hamdan bin Mohammed: &amp;ldquo;The UAE&amp;rsquo;s forward-looking leadership has made it a top global destination for living and business.&amp;rdquo;
Over 1,000 millionaires relocated to Dubai in 2018.
Crown Prince of Dubai, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, credits the UAE&amp;rsquo;s robust investment and economic landscape to its leadership&amp;rsquo;s visionary approach. He highlights their commitment to the well-being of residents, visitors, and investors, along with fostering innovation, as key factors in establishing the UAE as a premier lifestyle and business hub.</description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www.</description></item><item><title>Emirates now offers a total of seven daily flights between Dubai and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Emirates will introduce a seventh daily flight between Dubai and Bangkok to accommodate rising passenger numbers. This will make Bangkok a top destination for Emirates, equal to Kuwait and Doha.
This new Boeing 777-300ER service will bring the total weekly flights to 49, increasing weekly seat capacity by 2,520 and cargo capacity by 134 tonnes each way. This addition complements the existing four daily A380 and two daily 777 flights, boosting travel and trade between Thailand and Emirates&amp;rsquo; global network.</description></item><item><title>Compass Offices has launched a new business center at Oberoi Centre in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</guid><description>Compass Offices, a leading provider of serviced offices in the Asia Pacific region, is expanding its presence to the United Arab Emirates with the inauguration of its first business center in Dubai in July 2014. This strategic move comes on the heels of the company&amp;rsquo;s recent expansion into Australia and Kazakhstan, as well as the establishment of new business centers in Hong Kong.
Alexander Passler, Vice President of Business Development at Compass Offices, highlighted Dubai&amp;rsquo;s growing appeal for businesses, stating, &amp;ldquo;Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation for economic stability and its thriving financial hub status are attracting a growing number of companies.</description></item><item><title>Dubai ranks in the middle of the global innovation push, according to the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 03:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has published the findings from the inaugural Dubai Innovation Index. Introduced last year, this index is part of the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s plan to encourage innovation and global best practices in the private sector. The index identified medical care, media, marketing, IT, and retail industrial sectors as the most innovative, while professional services, agriculture, fisheries, construction, and energy were identified as the least innovative in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>The recipients of the MRM Business Award and MRM Business Innovation Award have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. HH Sheikh Ahmed Al Maktoum acknowledged the recipients of the 10th Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (MRM) Business Award and the 2nd MRM Business Innovation Award in Dubai, UAE.
Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, President of Dubai Civil Aviation Authority, as well as Chairman &amp;amp; Chief Executive of the Emirates Airline &amp;amp; Group, presided over the ceremony, which was held under the patronage of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Vice-President and Prime Minister of the UAE and Ruler of Dubai, and organized by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions.</description></item><item><title>The Wyndham brand has entered the UAE market with its presence in Dubai Marina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</guid><description>Source: The First Group. The new Wyndham
Dubai Marina.
Wyndham Dubai Marina, the first hotel solely developed by leading Dubai-based property developer, The First Group, has officially opened. This launch signifies the Wyndham brand&amp;rsquo;s entrance into the UAE market.
This four-star deluxe Wyndham Dubai Marina, managed by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, the largest hotel management company globally, represents a significant achievement for The First Group. The developer has established a strong reputation for creating high-quality serviced apartments and &amp;ldquo;aparthotels&amp;rdquo; in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Grand Millennium Dubai is providing daily iftar buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</guid><description>During Ramadan, the Grand Millennium Dubai, located near Sheikh Zayed Road, is hosting nightly iftar buffets at their Atrium restaurant. For AED 145 per person, guests can enjoy live cooking stations, along with Arabic and international dishes.
Source: Grand Millennium Dubai website. The Atrium restaurant.
The restaurant offers special group rates for iftar. The Silver package, priced at AED 165 per person, accommodates up to 50 guests. The Gold package, for a maximum of 100 people, costs AED 155 per person.</description></item><item><title>DAMAC introduces Maison Cour Jardin in the heart of downtown Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</guid><description>At the end of December 2014, DAMAC Properties, a high-end real estate developer, launched its third luxury serviced apartment complex in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area. Located just a short distance from popular attractions like the Dubai Mall and Dubai Fountain, DAMAC Maison Cour Jardin joins the company&amp;rsquo;s growing portfolio, which includes DAMAC Maison Dubai Mall Street and DAMAC Maison Canal Views.
Source: DAMAC Properties.
“DAMAC Properties is expanding its hospitality offerings, both in terms of scale and quality, to cater to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s visitors,” stated Niall McLoughlin, Senior Vice President of DAMAC Properties.</description></item><item><title>The Ibn Battuta Gate Office building is experiencing increased demand as Expo 2020 Dubai approaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</guid><description>Source: Seven Tides website.
As Expo 2020 Dubai approaches, Ibn Battuta Gate Offices, a property developed by Seven Tides, is leveraging its prime location in New Dubai. Situated near the Mövenpick Hotel, Ibn Battuta Mall, and a metro station, the office building is attracting significant attention.
The appeal of this location is further enhanced by the planned expansion of Ibn Battuta Mall. The AED160 million project will add 28,000 square meters, including a 350-room hotel, 150 shops, 50 restaurants, and a cinema with 21 screens.</description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers.</description></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Information System for sharing insights on businesses in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced the Business Intelligence Information System (BIIS), a new digital platform designed to revolutionize how business information is accessed and utilized.
This initiative aligns with the UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, HH Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum&amp;rsquo;s vision of transforming Dubai into a smart city. BIIS provides a centralized hub for users to obtain crucial information about local and international businesses, empowering companies to identify potential partners and make well-informed decisions.</description></item><item><title>Makani numbers in Dubai assist taxi drivers in locating their customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</guid><description>Source: RTA. Dubai taxis are now connected to the city through the Makani system.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) Public Transport Agency has successfully connected 4,500 taxis operated by franchise companies to the Dubai Municipality&amp;rsquo;s Makani System. This system utilizes unique coordinates, known as Makani numbers, for precise building location.
Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems at RTA&amp;rsquo;s Public Transport Agency, highlighted the significant role of the Makani System.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval.</description></item><item><title>You can have a Claire Luxton experience in Dubai this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. Visitors can enjoy a unique experience showcasing the work of artist Claire Luxton at select hotels, such as the InterContinental Dubai Festival City.
InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, part of IHG Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts Luxury and Lifestyle Collection, has partnered with British artist Claire Luxton to launch a series of immersive guest experiences. Available at various hotels, including the InterContinental Dubai Festival City, until mid-July, these experiences celebrate global travel and exploration through the artistic vision of Claire Luxton.</description></item><item><title>Atlantis Dubai offers a diverse selection of options for iftar dining</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</guid><description>This Ramadan, Atlantis is offering three unique dining experiences for iftar and suhoor: Asateer, Nobu, and Kaleidoscope, each providing a taste of Arabian culture.
Asateer, meaning &amp;ldquo;legends&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, provides a traditional tent setting overlooking the Arabian Sea, accommodating up to 900 guests. A customary iftar buffet is available at sunset for AED195, featuring Ramadan juices and followed by an à la carte suhoor menu starting at 9:30 pm.
During iftar, guests can enjoy classic dishes like foul moudammas and balila, complemented by a variety of Ramadan beverages such as jallab, laban, kamr al deen, and karkadeh.</description></item><item><title>Cirque de Cuisine: The Festive Edition returns to Atlantis, The Palm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</guid><description>Source: Atlantis, The Palm. Cirque de Cuisine.
The Cirque de Cuisine event will launch Dubai&amp;rsquo;s holiday season with a Winter Wonderland theme. Held on December 6th at The Avenues in Atlantis, The Palm, this all-you-can-eat-and-drink event offers early bird tickets starting at AED495 for four hours of holiday festivities.
Cirque de Cuisine gives diners the opportunity to sample signature dishes, live cooking stations, buffets, drinks, and live entertainment at a variety of restaurants.</description></item><item><title>Bayara excels in creating engaging digital activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</guid><description>Bayara, a Middle Eastern brand famous for dried fruits, nuts, and spices, hosted a unique iftar (Ramadan fast-breaking meal) at The Oberoi in Dubai. The buffet featured recipes submitted by their social media followers.
Source: Bayara. Jean-Marc Lourau, CEO of Bayara, congratulated the winners whose dishes were featured at the buffet and also shared the progress that Bayara has made over the last 25 years that they have been in the market.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai government is collaborating with Microsoft to develop a new font named "Dubai."</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-government-is-collaborating-with-microsoft-to-develop-a-new-font-named-dubai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-government-is-collaborating-with-microsoft-to-develop-a-new-font-named-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Government Media Office.
The Dubai Crown Prince and Chairman of the Dubai Executive Council, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid, has instructed the General Secretariat of the Dubai Executive Council to create a new font called &amp;ldquo;Dubai.&amp;rdquo; The initial phase will concentrate on developing unique Arabic and English fonts with advanced typographic capabilities.
Sheikh Hamdan emphasized that this initiative will reinforce Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing in information technology, aligning with the government&amp;rsquo;s strategy for leadership and innovation.</description></item><item><title>A white paper by the Dubai Chamber examines the funding landscape for startups in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Cover for the white paper.
A recent report highlights the need for a simplified guide to help UAE startups navigate the funding landscape and connect with eager investors. The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, in partnership with Roland Berger, published this white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Helping Startups Access Funding,&amp;rdquo; during the March edition of Dubai Startup Hub&amp;rsquo;s Entrepreneurship Advocacy Series. Dubai Startup Hub, the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s entrepreneurial arm, offers guidance and clarity to new businesses through various programs and workshops.</description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Meliá Hotels opened at least 11 new locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</guid><description>Meliá Hotels International is adding at least 11 new hotels to its portfolio in 2015, including the Sol House Kuta Bali in Indonesia.
Source: Meliá Hotels website.
The recently opened 317-room Meliá Doha, which began welcoming guests in January, is the first Spanish hotel in Qatar. Located within Bin Samikh Tower, a prominent skyscraper in Doha&amp;rsquo;s West Bay district, the hotel enjoys a prime position on the Qatari coast.
The urban German brand, Innside by Meliá, is expanding its Middle Eastern presence with the upcoming Innside Dubai, a 125-room hotel.</description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world.</description></item><item><title>Emirates NBD observes improvement in Dubai's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</guid><description>Source: Emirates NBD. Emirates NBD Dubai Economy Tracker Index: Sector
summary. Seasonally adjusted, 50 = no-change.
Data from April shows a continuing upswing in private sector output. Compared to March, all three major sub-sectors reported greater new business growth. Employment figures are increasing again, but at a slower rate than the survey average. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s private sector companies reported continued recovery and growth momentum since the survey&amp;rsquo;s record low in February.</description></item><item><title>Booking.com has recognized Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments as a top performer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 06:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</guid><description>Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments, managed by Flora Hospitality Dubai, has received recognition for its exceptional performance based on guest feedback on Booking.com.
Source: Booking.com website. Flora Creek Delluxe Hotel Apartments receives an 8.6 rating from guest reviews.
This award acknowledges the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to outstanding hospitality. The overall scores reflect a blend of factors such as cleanliness, comfort, location, amenities, staff service, value, and the quality of complimentary Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established a new office in Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 10:37:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</guid><description>To capitalize on promising markets and solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s position as a global business hub, the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established its seventh international office in Shanghai, China.
His Excellency Hisham Al Shirawi, Second Vice-Chairman of Dubai Chamber, emphasized China&amp;rsquo;s significance as Dubai&amp;rsquo;s top trading partner and highlighted the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s decade-long dedication to fostering strong trade relations. The Shanghai office, Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s first in China, reflects this commitment and aligns with the Dubai Plan 2021&amp;rsquo;s goal of bolstering Dubai&amp;rsquo;s status as a leading business and investment destination.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA has entered into a partnership with Careem for ride-hailing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</guid><description>Source: RTA. HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of RTA and Mudassir Sheikha, Founder and Managing Director of Careem, signed the agreement on behalf of the two respective entities. RTA executives attending the signing included Mohammed Obaid Al Mulla, Member of Board of Executive Directors, Abdullah Yousef Al Ali, CEO of Public Transport Agency, and Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems. Bassel Al Nahlaoui, VP of Business Development &amp;amp; Government Relations attended on behalf of Careem.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's tourism numbers have increased thanks to MICE travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</guid><description>During the first six months of 2014, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s hotels received a record-breaking 5.8 million guests, as reported by Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
DTCM attributes this surge in tourism to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s prominent position as a regional center for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events (MICE). A prime example was the incentive trip in April that brought in over 14,500 delegates from China alone. Significant business events hosted in the first half of 2014 included Gulfood, the Arabian Travel Market, and Intersec, a major trade show for safety, security, and fire protection in the region.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person.</description></item><item><title>The highlight of the Downtown Dubai New Year's Eve Gala is the Burj Khalifa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</guid><description>To celebrate the arrival of 2015, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Khalifa will showcase a dazzling LED display across its 828-meter height, synchronized with a spectacular fireworks show, according to a report from the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
Emaar Properties, the developer behind Downtown Dubai, is orchestrating a six-part extravaganza for their New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Gala. The event will feature a captivating blend of fireworks, laser displays, and a light show. A highlight of the celebration will be a special tribute to Dubai, its leaders, and the UAE&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments over the past 43 years, projected onto the specially designed LED screen.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Food Festival guarantees a February full of foodie fun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-food-festival-guarantees-a-february-full-of-foodie-fun/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-food-festival-guarantees-a-february-full-of-foodie-fun/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Food Festival website.
The second Dubai Food Festival (DFF) will showcase celebrity chefs and new events in addition to popular experiences from the previous year, according to the Dubai Festivals and Retails Establishment (DFRE), a branch of Dubai Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
New additions include Dubai Food &amp;amp; Film, the first foodie film event in the area, and Fatafeat Kitchen, a new program for 2015 and a first in the Middle East, featuring nine consecutive celebrity chef cooking events.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life.</description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes.</description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is set to introduce a third daily service to Brisbane</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates will begin offering a third daily flight to Brisbane, Australia starting December 1, 2017, adding to their current two daily flights.
This direct flight will utilize a Boeing 777-200LR, which boasts eight First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 216 Economy Class seats. This will increase the route&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3,724 seats weekly, both to and from Brisbane and Emirates&amp;rsquo; Dubai hub.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian.</description></item><item><title>Dubai welcomes the opening of a new Chinese Business Hub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 23:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</guid><description>Source: CBH. Pictured at the Business Centre opening ceremony are (from left to right) Justin Wilshaw, SVP Commercial, Dubai South; Shoaib Alrahimi, VP, Business Park, Dubai South; Mohsen Ahmad, VP, Logistics District, Dubai South; alongside other senior officials and association representatives. The UAE&amp;rsquo;s first dedicated business center specifically designed for new and expanding Chinese startups and SMEs, known as the Chinese Business Hub (CBH), has officially opened its main office in Dubai South Business Park.</description></item><item><title>Dubai CommerCity aims to establish Dubai as a leading e-commerce destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</guid><description>Dubai CommerCity, a new AED2.7 billion, 2.1-million sq ft e-commerce free zone, has been jointly launched by Dubai Airport Freezone Authority (DAFZA) and wasl Asset Management Group. As the first of its kind in the MENA region, this project aims to solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing as a major e-commerce hub, boost economic diversification, and advance smart transformation strategies.
This initiative seeks to capitalize on the burgeoning GCC e-commerce market, predicted to reach US$20 billion by 2020.</description></item><item><title>Dubai is optimistic about its FDI prospects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</guid><description>His Highness Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai and Chairman of The Executive Council, stated that the increase in foreign direct investment (FDI) inflows demonstrates growing investor confidence in Dubai, UAE.
His Highness reported that FDI into Dubai reached US$4.84 billion, a 26% increase compared to the first half of last year, during the first half of 2018. The number of FDI projects also rose significantly to 248, a 40% increase over the same period last year.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is adding another daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates has launched an additional daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka. Starting August 1, 2016, the airline will offer five daily flights between the two cities, except on Wednesdays, when four flights will be available. This new flight will provide an extra 2,520 seats and boost cargo capacity by 161 tonnes weekly in both directions, increasing the total weekly services on this route to 34.</description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers.</description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE.</description></item><item><title>DAMAC Properties has revealed plans for three new serviced hotels in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 05:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</guid><description>High-end real estate company DAMAC Properties is expanding its presence in the hospitality sector with the addition of three new serviced hotels in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area.
Two of these hotels, Cour Jardin and Capital Bay, are scheduled to open within the next few months, while Canal Views is already operational and receiving guests. This initiative is part of DAMAC Properties&amp;rsquo; goal to become the leading provider of serviced hotel apartments in the Middle East by 2018.</description></item><item><title>The winners of the SME Exporter of the Month award were honored by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently acknowledged member companies for their exceptional export achievements during the first nine months of 2016.
Nine trading companies received recognition at the &amp;ldquo;SME Exporter of the Month&amp;rdquo; ceremony: Universal International, Moon Flor General Trading, Signature Snacks, Al Khoud Trading, Raheeq Alasal Trading, Rais Hassan Saadi Logistics, Orient Links Co, Mohamed Abdulrahman Al Bahar, and Rayhan Al Sharq General Trading.
These companies were celebrated for excelling in categories such as highest export value, most export markets served, highest number of certificates of origin issued, and highest export value achieved by a start-up within a specific month.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry saw an increase in registered activity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-saw-an-increase-in-registered-activity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-saw-an-increase-in-registered-activity/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.
Member exports and re-exports reached a value of AED273 billion The Dubai Chamber was involved in 78 events spanning 50 cities The Chamber welcomed 681 delegations representing 81 countries The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry in the UAE experienced a 9% growth in its member network during 2016, adding 16,800 companies. This brought the organization&amp;rsquo;s total membership to 201,000 by the year&amp;rsquo;s end, solidifying its standing as a leading global chamber of commerce in terms of membership.</description></item></channel></rss>