<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Class on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/class/</link><description>Recent content in Class on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/class/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Activpass provides discounted rates for wellness activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</guid><description>Source: Activpass. Activpass is a mobile-based marketplace for booking lifestyle activities.
The team behind Activpass, a platform designed for businesses and professionals in fitness, wellness, and beauty, believes in living life to the fullest. Their mobile platform gives users access to over 1,000 services like yoga, training sessions, golf, massages, and beauty treatments, all without requiring a long-term commitment.
Users can easily book and pay for services on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New website offers discounted gym classes in Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</guid><description>Source:
FILLMYCLASS.
Similar to discounts for last-minute travel bookings, you can find more affordable gym classes at the last minute too.
A new website called FILLMYCLASS has launched in Melbourne, Australia. This website connects fitness enthusiasts with open spots in fitness classes at gyms and studios nearby.
FILLMYCLASS founder Daniel Waide states, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all about flexibility. The aim is to encourage more people to be active. Offering the ability to select classes that fit their schedule at any gym or studio increases the likelihood of people becoming and staying active...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In Support of Classifications (Inventory)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 16:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</guid><description>During a recent phone support session, I encountered a case that highlighted the often-overlooked advantages of using classes in Dynamics GP. While classes are generally known for providing default values, enabling changes to cascade down to records, and facilitating the grouping of records for tasks like reporting, their practical benefits go beyond these commonly recognized uses.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate this with an example from inventory management. When a new item is created manually (Cards&amp;raquo;Inventory&amp;raquo;Item), the option to maintain history is not enabled by default...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>