<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Academic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/academic/</link><description>Recent content in Academic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 17:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/academic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SMU and Alibaba Cloud introduce groundbreaking upskilling program beyond China for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>Singapore Management University (SMU) and Alibaba Cloud have teamed up to introduce a series of courses designed to enhance the skills of over 1,000 working professionals in Singapore.
This joint initiative, known as the SMU-Alibaba Series, marks Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s first professional continuing education program outside of China. Set to commence in March 2019, the program will be delivered through SMU Academy, the university&amp;rsquo;s professional training division.
With a specific focus on empowering small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), the Series aims to equip businesses with the necessary competencies to navigate the challenges posed by rapid technological advancements and evolving consumer behavior.</description></item><item><title>Learn about data science quickly with CEG Digital's online course</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</guid><description>CEG Digital, the flexible learning branch of global education provider Cambridge Education Group (CEG), has teamed up with the Web Science Institute at the University of Southampton (WSI), a top-100 university, to offer short online courses.
Dr. Elena Simperl, WSI Associate Professor and Scientific Director of the European Data Science Academy, emphasized the importance of data science skills, stating, &amp;ldquo;Data science is crucial for our economy. Our new series of short professional courses complement our postgraduate degrees and target decision-makers, business analysts, IT developers, and others interested in cutting-edge data science technologies and applications in fields like digital marketing, finance, and healthcare.</description></item><item><title>IBM has raised concerns about the skills gap in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</guid><description>Source: IBM. Cover for the Upskilling India report.
IBM has released a study conducted by the IBM Institute for Business Value (IBV), in partnership with the Economist Intelligence Unit. This study assesses India&amp;rsquo;s increasing skills gap and offers suggestions to address the issue.
The study surveyed Indian executives, and most believe that the Indian workforce&amp;rsquo;s skills are on par with or better than those of other nations. However, only 40% reported that new employees possess the necessary skills.</description></item></channel></rss>