<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Latency on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/latency/</link><description>Recent content in Latency on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/latency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow.</description></item><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>High Reliability VoIP Phone Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</guid><description>The days of traditional phone lines, even ISDN PRI, are fading. Cloud-based systems and computer networks offer more adaptable, feature-rich, and cost-effective voice communication solutions. To tap into these advantages, adopting packet-based phone service, also known as VoIP, is key.
People&amp;rsquo;s feelings about VoIP as a replacement for traditional phone service are mixed, ranging from enthusiastic support to staunch opposition. This spectrum of opinions stems from individual experiences with the technology and when they first used it.</description></item><item><title>Telx Cloud Exchange Reduces Service Lag Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</guid><description>Cloud services promise cost savings by replacing your data center with rented infrastructure, platforms, and software. While this sounds good in theory, some users experience performance issues.
Cloud computing boasts virtually unlimited resources, instantly available when needed. So why do some cloud-based operations become slower than their local counterparts?
It boils down to connectivity. Although electrical signals travel at the speed of light, distance still matters. Light speed is significantly reduced in terrestrial circuits compared to a vacuum, and signals face further delays due to network equipment.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware.</description></item><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections.</description></item><item><title>Why T1 Is Available Where Other Line Services Aren’t</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:47:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</guid><description>Businesses located outside of city centers may struggle to obtain the same quality of network services as their downtown counterparts. While it may seem like options are limited, a reliable and affordable digital telecom service called T1 is often accessible in these areas.
Contrary to outdated beliefs, T1 lines are no longer prohibitively expensive or geographically restricted. They are widely available for businesses, though they may not be suitable for residential use.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Service Providers Colocate With Customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</guid><description>A new trend is emerging, and it&amp;rsquo;s not just about companies moving their data to the cloud. Now, cloud service providers are moving into the same facilities as their customers.
Why is this happening? Companies are realizing that running applications on distant servers can&amp;rsquo;t match the speed of having them on-site. While this can be addressed by investing in high-bandwidth, low-latency connections, it&amp;rsquo;s often more cost-effective to simply be in the same location as your provider.</description></item><item><title>Wireless SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Traditionally, business phone lines and dedicated internet relied on physical wires. However, wireless SIP trunking is emerging as a new option.
](http://www.affordablevpn.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
Airband Communications, a frontrunner in this technology, offers business-class voice services packaged with wireless internet access. This is comparable to a SIP trunk or an integrated voice and data service in the wired world, but Airband&amp;rsquo;s offering presents unique benefits.
Similar to other integrated services, a single connection provides both phone and internet access, only in this case, it&amp;rsquo;s wireless.</description></item><item><title>HughesNet Special Deals on Satellite Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</guid><description>Living remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to be disconnected. Just like you get your TV via satellite, you can get internet access the same way. You&amp;rsquo;ll need a specialized dish that transmits and receives data, connect it to your power source and computer, and you&amp;rsquo;re online!
HughesNet is one provider catering to both homes and businesses. Plans start at $59.99 per month, with download speeds up to 700 Kbps and upload speeds up to 128 Kbps, similar to many DSL or cellular broadband services.</description></item><item><title>Telx Minimizes Latency WIth Colocation Near Carriers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</guid><description>For applications sensitive to delays, proximity to service providers is crucial. Regardless of your equipment&amp;rsquo;s speed, signal propagation sets the minimum latency. This speed is about a millisecond per 186 miles in a vacuum and increases with copper or fiber cables, further compounded by routers and switches. Being directly connected to your provider minimizes this distance. Telx offers a solution.
Telx specializes in colocation, connecting customers and providers physically. With 15 strategically located centers in 9 states, they offer proximity to media hubs, cable landings, fiber paths, and exchanges.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic.</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Symmetric Internet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you unhappy with how the internet performs for your business? Do you think it&amp;rsquo;s more for entertainment and casual use than for getting work done quickly and efficiently? You need the internet to function, though. Your customers and suppliers, along with important information, are online. Even your software and communication tools might be cloud-based. What you likely need is a business-grade broadband connection with better performance.</description></item><item><title>Advantage of Dedicated Cloud Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</guid><description>Companies of all sizes are increasingly adopting cloud services due to their cost-effectiveness. However, the assumption that a basic internet connection is sufficient for accessing these services is proving to be inaccurate in many situations.
While the internet&amp;rsquo;s widespread availability and affordability make it appealing for WAN services, its security concerns led to the development of VPNs. These secure tunnels encrypt data, allowing remote workers and branch offices to connect securely to corporate networks and transfer sensitive information.</description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements.</description></item><item><title>Scalable Cloud Servers Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 20:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</guid><description>Considering a move to cloud servers but feeling apprehensive about the cost and complexity? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses desire the flexibility and cost-effectiveness of cloud computing without needing excessive processing power.
Scalable cloud servers are a great option for businesses of all sizes, offering pay-as-you-go pricing and easy scalability. Before committing to a major provider, explore options specifically designed for small to medium-sized businesses. These services often provide per-second billing, eliminating wasted expenses, along with free setup and no contractual obligations.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own World Wide Web</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet has its downsides despite the benefits of global and instant information access. Sharing large files between offices, conducting high-quality teleconferences, and experiencing seamless application interactions can be challenging. Network crashes, congestion from high-bandwidth activities, and constant security threats further diminish the internet&amp;rsquo;s appeal. So, is there a better alternative?
The Connectivity Conundrum
Imagine having an exclusive internet solely for your business, customers, and suppliers. Bandwidth wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue, and the network would operate seamlessly.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind.</description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>What Is VoIP For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of talk about the benefits of switching from traditional phone services to VoIP, and for good reason. Businesses can gain a lot from enterprise VoIP solutions. However, there are potential downsides to watch out for to ensure a smooth transition. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what VoIP is and how it compares to your current phone service.
One thing that often causes confusion about VoIP is the name itself.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party.</description></item><item><title>A New Edge On Private IP Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</guid><description>With the increase in businesses operating from multiple locations, IP network solutions have become more affordable and accessible. New Edge Networks, a key player in this domain, specializes in private IP-based WANs, offering enhanced quality and performance for connecting multiple business sites by bypassing the public internet.
While the internet has revolutionized global communication, its ubiquity and open nature pose limitations for businesses. Network neutrality principles treat all data equally, regardless of its importance.</description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades.</description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards.</description></item></channel></rss>