<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>China on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/china/</link><description>Recent content in China on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The more specific the mobile advertisement, the higher its earnings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</guid><description>Smaato, a mobile advertising company, has observed that the most successful advertising categories in China during the first quarter of the year were shopping, e-commerce, communication, and technology. These categories achieved high eCPMs (effective cost per mille), reaching up to US$0.30.
When analyzing mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad expenditures in China during the same period, entertainment (30%) and games (22%) were the top two categories.
Ajitpal Pannu, Smaato&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, noted that both monetization and brand spending increased when essential parameters were shared globally with advertising partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines introduces direct flight between Shenzhen and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Pictured at the Auckland welcoming ceremony are the Consulate General of China in Auckland, Acting Consul General Luo Binhui, Auckland Airport CEO Adrian Littlewood, Hainan Airlines President Sun Jianfeng, and Hainan Airlines&amp;rsquo; VIP customers.
On December 30, 2016, Hainan Airlines launched its inaugural non-stop flight between Shenzhen, China, and Auckland, New Zealand. The new route connects the two cities with an 11-hour flight.
Hainan Airlines will service the Shenzhen-Auckland route with wide-body Airbus A330s, known for their spacious cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fitch Learning has teamed up with Golden Education to provide a certificate in quantitative finance in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:47:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</guid><description>Fitch Learning has partnered with Golden Education, a financial education company in China, to provide the Certificate in Quantitative Finance (CQF) program to professionals throughout the country. The CQF is gaining recognition in China, as demonstrated by a 55% increase in enrollment by Chinese participants from 2018 to 2019.
The CQF program includes six modules, two elective advanced modules, three exams, and a final project. Quantitative finance utilizes mathematical modeling to examine financial markets and securities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fitch-learning-has-teamed-up-with-golden-education-to-provide-a-certificate-in-quantitative-finance-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zhaopin reveals changes in the entry-level job market in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</guid><description>Zhaopin, a Chinese career platform that connects users with job opportunities, conducted a 2017 career survey of college graduates in China, revealing notable trends. The survey indicated that graduates faced a more challenging job market and lower average salaries, presenting a difficult situation for the 7.95 million graduates entering the workforce.
2017 Labor Market for College Graduates Difficult and very challenging: 40.8% Difficult, but acceptable: 47.0% The market was OK: 9...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Uber Malaysia users now have the option to request a driver who speaks Mandarin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia.
Uber Malaysia is introducing UberMANDARIN, a new service in Johor Bahru, Kota Kinabalu, and Penang that connects riders with Mandarin-speaking UberX drivers.
According to Warren Tseng, GM of Uber Malaysia and Singapore, the Ministry of Tourism and Culture projects a significant increase in Chinese tourists, from 3 million this year to potentially 8 million by 2020. UberMANDARIN aims to support the government&amp;rsquo;s tourism initiatives by offering Mandarin-speaking visitors a more comfortable and convenient experience, aligning with Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s renowned hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wanda Vista brand expands globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</guid><description>Qian Jin, the head of the upscale hotel group Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has revealed the global growth plan for their Wanda Vista brand.
Wanda Vista represents the top tier of luxury within Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, designed specifically for guests who appreciate art and culture. Situated in major international cities and drawing inspiration from Eastern aesthetics, the brand focuses on providing personalized service catered to each guest&amp;rsquo;s individual requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting today, the Apple iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are now available in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 04:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus will be offered in China starting October 17th through various channels like Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, major carriers, and authorized retailers. These smartphones will also be available in 36 more countries and territories by the end of October, reaching a total of over 115 countries by the year&amp;rsquo;s end.
Source: Apple. The iPhone 6 and
the iPhone 6 Plus.
Both iPhone models support TD-LTE and FDD-LTE, allowing customers to use 4G/LTE networks from China Mobile, China Telecom, and China Unicom throughout mainland China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Jiangsu strengthen economic ties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-jiangsu-strengthen-economic-ties/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 23:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-jiangsu-strengthen-economic-ties/</guid><description>The Singapore-Jiangsu Cooperation Council (SJCC) aims to boost opportunities for companies from both regions in areas like collaboration in third-party markets, trade and logistics, and financial services. This contributes to the existing Singapore-Jiangsu economic partnership and advances the Belt and Road Initiative (BRI). Thirteen memoranda of understanding (MoUs) reflect these goals.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Heng Swee Keat, who is also SJCC Co-Chairman, emphasized the strong, enduring relationship between Singapore and Jiangsu...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-jiangsu-strengthen-economic-ties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-jiangsu-strengthen-economic-ties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The President of China promises to create a thriving society</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-president-of-china-promises-to-create-a-thriving-society/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-president-of-china-promises-to-create-a-thriving-society/</guid><description>In his New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve address in Beijing, Chinese President Xi Jinping welcomed 2020 by promising to meet the centenary goal of achieving moderate prosperity for everyone, as reported by China Daily.
Xi urged the nation to &amp;ldquo;seize the day and live it to the full.&amp;rdquo;
He highlighted several achievements:
China&amp;rsquo;s 2019 gross domestic product (GDP) is projected to be nearly US$14.37 trillion, with per-capita GDP expected to reach US$10,000. China has established diplomatic ties with 180 countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-president-of-china-promises-to-create-a-thriving-society/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-president-of-china-promises-to-create-a-thriving-society/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now offers Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner on flights from Abu Dhabi to Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has upgraded its Abu Dhabi to Shanghai route, now offering flights on the Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner. This change increases capacity by 14%, offering 28 business class and 271 economy seats.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Peter Baumgartner, highlighted the significance of the Chinese market, particularly the rising demand from business and leisure travelers. The decision to utilize the Dreamliner reflects Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s status as a major global hub and its importance in Etihad&amp;rsquo;s network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China's unicorn company has revealed the top 10 rankings in the Google Play store for its Wi-Fi crowdsourcing app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</guid><description>Source: Play Store.
The free app WiFi Master Key, which helps users find and connect to crowdsourced Wi-Fi hotspots, is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia. It helps people access the internet in a region where connectivity is rapidly expanding.
The app lets users share Wi-Fi hotspot information with the community. While this information allows others to connect for free, the app prioritizes privacy and security by encrypting and storing shared Wi-Fi passwords in its cloud database instead of revealing them directly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Food tours are available in Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo through Eating Adventures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</guid><description>Source: Eating Adventures website.
Eating Adventures has expanded its food tour services to Hong Kong. The company, already established as the leading provider of food tours in Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo, China, aims to provide travelers with an authentic cultural and culinary experience by guiding them through local neighborhoods.
Wai Zhou, owner of Eating Adventures Food Tours, highlights that while Hong Kong has existing food tour operators, most are not run by locals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is the inaugural Hyatt hotel in the Jiangsu province</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</guid><description>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou has officially opened in Suzhou, a city renowned for its historic canals, stone bridges, and UNESCO-recognized classical gardens.
Source: Hyatt. The hotel boasts a 29-floor atrium, the tallest in Suzhou.
&amp;ldquo;The launch of Hyatt Regency Suzhou is a significant move for Hyatt as we expand our brand presence in China,&amp;rdquo; stated Christopher Koehler, Vice President of Operations for Hyatt in China. &amp;ldquo;We aim to create valuable connections among global business and leisure travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jin Jiang International Hotels and Hanwha Hotels &amp; Resorts have officially merged their loyalty programs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</guid><description>Jin Jiang International Hotels from China and Hanwha Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts from Korea have joined their loyalty programs.
Starting September 1st, members of Jin Jiang&amp;rsquo;s J-Club and Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s THE PLUS will share membership benefits. This includes perks like discounts on rooms, food, and beverages, as well as late check-outs and room upgrades at both hotel groups. J-Club&amp;rsquo;s over 14 million members will also have access to Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s resorts and golf courses across Korea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online retailing is becoming increasingly popular for smartphones in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</guid><description>Want to expand your customer base? Consider partnering with an e-mall, especially in China. A recent IDC Mobile Phone Tracker report indicates a rise in the share of e-tailers, like JD, Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Tmall, and Suning Yigou, in China&amp;rsquo;s smartphone market, from 14% in Q2 2014 to 21% in Q2 2015. This translates to a 58% year-on-year surge in the number of smartphones sold via these online platforms.
Tay Xiaohan, a Senior Market Analyst at IDC Asia/Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Client Devices team, highlights that as operators scale back smartphone subsidies, vendors find more opportunities in the open market, with e-tailers emerging as a crucial channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guangzhou businesses enter into Letters of Intent with Singapore organizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</guid><description>Source: Guangzhou Municipal Government. Cai.
The city of Guangzhou held a promotional event in Singapore to explore collaboration and innovation between the two business hubs. Two agreements were reached: one between the Sino-Singapore International Joint Research Institute and Chinese Academy of Sciences Holdings Company, and another between Guangzhou Gas Group, Guangzhou Port Group, and the industrial group Royal Golden Eagle.
Guangzhou&amp;rsquo;s Vice Mayor, Cai Chaolin, who also leads the Nansha District&amp;rsquo;s Communist Party and Development Zone, highlighted the shared attributes between Guangzhou and Singapore, such as their size, cultural similarities, and languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its 200th property in Greater China, located in Chengdu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Fairmont Chengdu lobby.
The Fairmont Chengdu marks the 200th property for AccorHotels in Greater China and is the first Fairmont Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts establishment in Western China. This opening is a key part of AccorHotels’ expansion within the luxury market.
Situated on Tianfu Middle Avenue in Chengdu&amp;rsquo;s high-tech zone, the hotel provides 336 guest rooms and suites, each offering impressive views of the city skyline. Shuangliu International Airport is easily accessible at just a 25-minute drive away, and the nearby metro station provides convenient access to Tianfu Square, the forthcoming Tianfu International Airport, and the South CBD zone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces WeChat SIM card for tourists from China visiting Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced two new prepaid SIM cards, named &amp;ldquo;StarHub WeChat Go SIM&amp;rdquo;, specifically designed for Chinese tourists visiting Singapore. This launch is a collaboration between StarHub and WeChat.
The StarHub WeChat Go SIM aims to meet the connectivity needs of the increasing number of Chinese tourists. Data from the Singapore Tourism Board shows a 36% rise in tourists from China in 2016 compared to the previous year. A 2017 Hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aeromexico introduces an additional flight connecting Shanghai and Mexico City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Aeromexico will expand its service between Shanghai and Mexico City to include a third weekly flight on Sundays. This increase will bring the total number of seats available on the route to over 1,500 each week. The flights, operated by Boeing 777 aircraft, accommodate 277 passengers with 49 business class seats and 228 economy seats.
Each Aeromexico flight features personal entertainment systems, increased passenger space, and lie-flat seats in Clase Premier, its business class section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business confidence in China continues to be weak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</guid><description>While overall business confidence in China showed a slight improvement, activity declined in December as large companies continued to face weak demand and an uncertain business climate. According to MNI Indicators, a provider of economic data and analysis, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t anticipate significant improvement in early 2016. This is reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator, which remains close to the previous month&amp;rsquo;s low point.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator, a measure of current business sentiment, rose 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet has teamed up with Apex Air to provide private jet travel services in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</guid><description>VistaJet, a provider of luxury long-range private jet travel, announced that Apex Air, a business jet operator authorized by the Civil Aviation Administration of China (CAAC), will oversee and operate a fleet of aircraft based in China for VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s Flight Solution Program.
VistaJet is prepared to offer point-to-point service within China as early as the third quarter of 2015 with its first Chinese-registered aircraft, a Bombardier1 Challenger 8501. Chinese customers will also have access to VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s fleet of over 50 large-cabin, long-range Bombardier Challenger and Global aircraft for international flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beijing is the first place outside of the Americas to experience Starbucks Nitro Cold Brew</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</guid><description>The China World Trade Centre Starbucks in Beijing is the first location outside of the US and Canada to offer Nitro Cold Brew on tap in addition to their regular Cold Brew. Starbucks plans to introduce this in more locations over the coming months. This follows a very successful launch of Starbucks Cold Brew across China.
&amp;ldquo;We are dedicated to achieving perfection in our coffee expertise, and Nitro Cold Brew shows our significant investment in coffee innovation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the second quarter of 2014, China's RTB ad spending increased by 616% compared to the previous quarter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</guid><description>Smaato, a company specializing in mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad exchange (SMX) and supply side platform (SSP), has reported significant growth in mobile RTB in its Q2 2014 Global Mobile RTB Insights Report.
Source: The Smaato RTB Insights Report for Q2 2014. RTB spending in the APAC region for the top five countries.
Smaato&amp;rsquo;s findings show a 69% increase in RTB spending in the second quarter of 2014 compared to the first quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen collaborate for a flash sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 01:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</guid><description>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen have teamed up to offer the Grand Spring Voyage flash sale, featuring accommodation packages ranging from two to five nights in both cities. This convenient travel opportunity is made possible by the newly extended MTR East Rail line, which directly connects the two hotels. The journey between the nearest stations, Exhibition Centre Station in Hong Kong and Lo Wu Station in Shenzhen, is a quick 40 minutes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the VIP treatment at Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</guid><description>Source: Hard Rock Hotels. Interior, Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen.
The Hard Rock Hotel brand has debuted its first establishment in China with the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen. This new property combines pop culture with high-end hospitality to create a luxurious experience for travelers seeking a unique experience.
Opening its doors in the summer of 2017, the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen is located within Mission Hills Centreville. Situated near a golf course, the hotel also provides convenient access to a variety of leisure, wellness, and entertainment options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ignoring preferred payment methods could result in travel companies losing customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</guid><description>Around 85% of Chinese consumers take at least one leisure trip per year.
Credit cards (36%) and debit cards (29%) are the top payment choices for travel worldwide. PayPal is also popular (17%) across various countries and age groups.
Electronic payments are prevalent in China, with 78% favoring Alipay.
Seven out of ten Chinese travelers report experiencing fraud.
A recent global survey* of 7,400 consumers by YouGov and ACI Worldwide, a provider of electronic payment solutions, found that over a third (36%) of respondents from Britain, America, China, France, and Germany are dissatisfied with limited online payment choices for booking vacations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new route connecting Dubai with Yinchuan and Zhengzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</guid><description>Emirates airline is increasing its commitment to China by starting a new service from Dubai to Yinchuan and Zhengzhou, two rapidly developing cities in Midwest China. This addition brings Emirates&amp;rsquo; total destinations in mainland China to five, including existing service to Beijing, Shanghai, and Guangzhou.
Source; Emirates. Emirates&amp;rsquo; Chairman and Chief Executive, HH Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, along with other company executives and a delegation of UAE business leaders, were on the inaugural flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zhaopin in China introduces chat feature to Highpin recruitment platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</guid><description>Source: Highpin.cn website.
Zhaopin, a Chinese career platform, has introduced Highpin Chat, a desktop-based instant messaging feature for its executive recruitment site, Highpin.cn.
This new chat feature aims to streamline the hiring process on Highpin.cn. Recruiters and employers can now directly connect with candidates, enabling better candidate evaluation and efficient job matching. Similarly, job seekers can use the chat to ask recruiters and employers about specific roles and follow their application status in real time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Berkeley Earth raises concerns about air pollution in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</guid><description>Source: Berkeley Earth website.
A recent study published in PLOS ONE by Berkeley Earth reveals that air pollution causes approximately 4,000 deaths per day in China, representing 17% of the country&amp;rsquo;s total deaths. This non-profit organization, established to investigate concerns raised by global warming skeptics, determined that the air quality for 38% of China&amp;rsquo;s population would be deemed &amp;ldquo;unhealthy&amp;rdquo; by United States standards.
Berkeley Earth&amp;rsquo;s analysis of hourly measurements from 1,500 ground stations over a four-month period indicated coal as the most likely source of PM2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/berkeley-earth-raises-concerns-about-air-pollution-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wanda Realm Taian is now officially open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</guid><description>Source: Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
The Wanda Realm Taian.
The Wanda Realm Taian (泰安万达嘉华酒店) marks its grand opening, becoming the 77th establishment under the Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts umbrella. This addition represents the 30th Wanda Realm hotel in China and the 41st property fully owned and operated by Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
This hotel is the fourth launched by Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts under their Wanda Realm brand in Shandong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is committed to connecting with Chinese tourists through investment efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotel Resorts Spas&amp;rsquo; Chinese website.
To expand its online footprint, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has launched a website in Chinese. The new website offers the same content and features as the brand&amp;rsquo;s English website. This move is anticipated to attract more customers from China, a key growth market for Six Senses.
In addition to the website, Six Senses is connecting with Chinese customers through brand engagement on social media platforms like WeChat, Youku, and Sina Weibo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Shunde Marriott Hotel has officially opened its doors in Foshan, China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its presence in China with the opening of the 258-room Shunde Marriott Hotel. Located in Shunde, a district of Foshan in Guangdong Province, the hotel is owned by Shunde Midea Group and managed by Marriott under a long-term agreement. This latest addition brings the Marriott Hotels brand&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in Greater China to 19 properties.
Source: Marriott. The Shunde Marriott offers guests views of either Shunfeng Mountain Park or the city skyline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It is now easier for visitors to Mainland China to make payments using Weixin Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-now-easier-for-visitors-to-mainland-china-to-make-payments-using-weixin-pay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 13:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-now-easier-for-visitors-to-mainland-china-to-make-payments-using-weixin-pay/</guid><description>Tencent has simplified and strengthened the registration and payment processes for international visitors using WeChat and Weixin Pay. Overseas users can now register using non-Chinese mobile numbers and link international payment cards for transactions. This provides access to millions of merchants across China, with enhanced transaction limits for verified users.
The updated system allows for convenient payments up to a certain limit. Higher limits are available after a quick identity verification process, with passport verification taking seconds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-now-easier-for-visitors-to-mainland-china-to-make-payments-using-weixin-pay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-now-easier-for-visitors-to-mainland-china-to-make-payments-using-weixin-pay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wanda Reign Wuhan has now opened its doors to guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts debuted its luxury brand, Wanda Reign, with the opening of Wanda Reign Wuhan on March 29th. The brand emphasizes personalized service, exemplified by its &amp;ldquo;Imperial Welcome&amp;rdquo; which includes a Bentley service, and its &amp;ldquo;Reign Butler,&amp;rdquo; offering tailored assistance like schedule management and shopping guidance.
Source: Wanda Reign website
Situated near shopping and attractions in Wuhan&amp;rsquo;s East Lake Scenic Area, the hotel is conveniently located 30 minutes from Wuhan Tianhe airport and 15 minutes from the Wuhan high-speed railway station...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Tencent collaborate to simplify gifting and payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Wong.
Starbucks Coffee Company and Tencent Holdings, a Chinese provider of online services, are collaborating. In early 2017, they plan to launch a new social gifting feature within WeChat, a popular mobile communications service in China. Additionally, Starbucks customers at nearly 2,500 stores across mainland China can now use WeChat Pay for their purchases.
This partnership makes Starbucks the first retailer in China to provide an integrated, locally relevant social gifting and digital payment experience within WeChat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the behavior of luxury travelers from China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</guid><description>A recent study on Chinese luxury travelers, conducted by Marriott International and the Hurun Research Institute, reveals evolving travel preferences among young, affluent Chinese travelers aged 18 to 36. These travelers seek personalized experiences, value-added services throughout their journey, and seamless integration of technology.
The study indicates a preference for digital platforms, with WeChat emerging as the primary source for travel information, followed by official accounts, recommendations from friends, and travel professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The doors of Wanda Realm Fuyang are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts has expanded its portfolio with the opening of Wanda Realm Fuyang in the bustling business district of Fuyang, Anhui province, China. This addition marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 78th hotel, the 42nd under its ownership and management, and the 30th property under the Wanda Realm brand.
André Liu, General Manager of Wanda Realm Fuyang, highlighted the strategic importance of the location, stating, &amp;ldquo;Fuyang city is a rapidly developing hub with the largest population and fourth-largest size in Anhui province...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Term deposits from ICBC are available through Alipay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</guid><description>ICBC, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest bank by assets, now offers three-year term deposit services through Alipay, a popular digital lifestyle platform.
This collaboration between Alipay and ICBC began in 2005 with online payment services. In January 2020, ICBC introduced a one-year term deposit service on Alipay, allowing customers to make deposits directly through the platform. This service has seen a sevenfold increase in size since May.
The new three-year term deposit option, called Anxin Cun (Secure Deposits), offers a 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud will assist companies in accelerating their entry into the Chinese market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud recently introduced its China Gateway Program alongside eight local partners: the Info-communications Media Development Authority (IMDA), Enterprise Singapore, DBS SME Banking, Singapore Chinese Chamber of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (SCCCI), SMU Academy, SGTech, Action Community for Entrepreneurship (ACE), and TechNode.
Alibaba Cloud, the data intelligence branch of the Alibaba Group, recently hosted its second Alibaba Cloud APAC Summit in Singapore, showcasing its dedication to serving Asia.
During the summit, the company announced the China Gateway Program in collaboration with IMDA, Enterprise Singapore, DBS SME Banking, SCCCI, SMU Academy, SGTech, ACE, and TechNode...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China and Kunming Airlines have initiated a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Source: Air China. The image shows representatives from Air China and Kunming Airlines at a signing ceremony for a codeshare agreement on September 3.
Air China and Kunming Airlines launched a codeshare partnership on September 15, 2014.
This agreement allows the airlines to link their respective networks through the city of Kunming. Air China will place its &amp;ldquo;CA&amp;rdquo; code on 26 Kunming Airlines routes, encompassing nearly 500 weekly flights. This expands Air China&amp;rsquo;s reach to various cities within Yunnan province and its neighboring areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton introduces a new MICE venue in Hainan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and its DoubleTree by Hilton brand have opened a new resort in China called the DoubleTree Resort by Hilton Hainan - Qixianling Hot Spring. Situated within the Qixianling Hot Spring National Rainforest Park, the 254-room hotel is conveniently located 50 km from Lingshui Railway Station and 90 km from Sanya Phoenix International Airport.
John Greenleaf, Global Head of DoubleTree by Hilton, emphasized the brand&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding guest expectations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to BrandZ, Tencent is currently the most valuable brand in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</guid><description>Tencent, a Chinese company, has become the most valuable brand in Asia and the fastest growing brand globally, achieving a brand value of US$54 billion in the 2014 BrandZ Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands ranking. This success propelled Tencent to the 14th spot globally, surpassing China Mobile.
Source: Millward Brown website.
Deepender Rana, Managing Director of Millward Brown Greater China, emphasized the significance of a market-driven Chinese brand like Tencent taking the lead over state-owned enterprises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Drone Experience Program by JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp; Resorts is launching in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. View from a DJI drone.
JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and drone manufacturer DJI have partnered to introduce the brand&amp;rsquo;s first Drone Experience Program.
This program will allow guests to try out DJI&amp;rsquo;s drone technology and experience JW Marriott properties from a fresh perspective. They can also capture and share these unique moments with loved ones.
Launching on November 12, 2016, at JW Marriott Zhejiang Anji, the program will feature on-site sessions hosted by DJI experts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UnionPay cardholders in Singapore can now enjoy exclusive visa privileges for travel to China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</guid><description>UnionPay International (UPI), a branch of China UnionPay, partnered with Chinese Visa Application Service Centre to offer special VIP treatment to UnionPay cardholders in Singapore applying for a Chinese visa. This express service features a dedicated VIP counter and a faster queue for UnionPay cardholders (card numbers starting with 62).
UnionPay is currently the only international card brand offering expedited Chinese visa applications at Chinese embassies, consulates, and participating visa processing centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Handbags will be the focus in India and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</guid><description>A new report from Technavio predicts the handbag market in Brazil, Russia, India, and China will experience significant growth between 2014 and 2019. This growth is projected to be over 7.41% in revenue and 7.02% in volume.
Technavio attributes this anticipated growth to the increasing association of handbags with social status among consumers. The introduction of stylish and functional designs, along with attractive colors, finishes, and textures, are making handbags more desirable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports a decrease in luxury demand in China and an increase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, predicts the global luxury goods industry will experience a 19% growth, reaching $405 billion by 2019.
Fflur Roberts, the Head of Luxury Goods Research at Euromonitor, pointed out China&amp;rsquo;s significant luxury market growth of $9.6 billion over the past five years. She noted that this growth, while impressive, slowed at the end of 2013, prompting luxury brands to reassess their strategies in China and other emerging markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jumei expands its online beauty offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</guid><description>Source: Jumei website.
Jumei International Holding, a Chinese online retailer specializing in beauty products, has formed several strategic alliances with international brands. The company revealed that Max Factor and OPI Products have joined its Authentic Beauty Product Alliance (ABPA) and that it has established a partnership with American fashion designer Jill Stuart.
Through its website and mobile app, the company provides a variety of products, including branded beauty items, fashionable apparel, and other lifestyle goods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can now get .cn domain names from GoDaddy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 09:53:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a company that provides technology specifically to small businesses, now offers a total of 421 domain name extensions. This increase is due to the addition of the &amp;ldquo;.cn&amp;rdquo; domain, China&amp;rsquo;s country code. This expansion targets the growing number of Chinese residents seeking to establish an online presence.
China boasts over 1.6 billion internet users, with over 600 million residing within the country itself. While China has registered over 16 million &amp;ldquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK Automotive industry continues to export to China as its third-largest destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</guid><description>The Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders (SMMT) recently released data revealing that Britain is exporting more cars than ever. The number of British-built cars shipped globally increased by 10.3%, reaching a new record of 1,354,216 units. This marks the second year in a row that this record has been broken.
China, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest car market, maintained its position as the UK&amp;rsquo;s third largest trading partner, after the EU and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The acceptance of UnionPay is expanding globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 19:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</guid><description>UnionPay has successfully expanded its network, brand, and products globally, advancing the international use of Chinese financial technology standards. UnionPay International is now present in over 50 markets involved in the Belt and Road Initiative.
Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International, emphasized their strategy of adapting to each local market, fostering personnel exchange between China and other regions, and supporting the globalization of Chinese financial standards.
In Kazakhstan, over 1.3 million UnionPay cards have been issued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LBS and Fudan have collaborated to introduce a new Global Masters in Management program with a double business degree</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</guid><description>London Business School (LBS) and Fudan University&amp;rsquo;s School of Management (FDSM) have partnered to create a dual-degree Global Masters in Management (MiM) program.
Sir Andrew Likierman, Dean of London Business School, emphasized the increasing need for skilled professionals who can navigate the business landscape in both Eastern and Western contexts. He highlighted that this collaboration reflects their dedication to close partnerships with Chinese corporations. The program aims to equip graduates with a global perspective through direct engagement with both China and the West...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tmall Global report showcases the preferences of Chinese consumers in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</guid><description>A recent report on import consumption in China, the Annual Report on Tmall Global Data 2016, was released by Tmall Global, an online platform allowing businesses outside China to connect with Chinese consumers, and CBNData. The report reveals the strength of e-commerce in China, showing a growing customer base, expanding product interest, and notable trends influenced by significant events.
The report highlights several key findings. First, cross-border e-commerce is entering a new phase, supported by favorable policies from both the Chinese government and global trade organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established a new office in Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 10:37:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</guid><description>To capitalize on promising markets and solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s position as a global business hub, the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established its seventh international office in Shanghai, China.
His Excellency Hisham Al Shirawi, Second Vice-Chairman of Dubai Chamber, emphasized China&amp;rsquo;s significance as Dubai&amp;rsquo;s top trading partner and highlighted the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s decade-long dedication to fostering strong trade relations. The Shanghai office, Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s first in China, reflects this commitment and aligns with the Dubai Plan 2021&amp;rsquo;s goal of bolstering Dubai&amp;rsquo;s status as a leading business and investment destination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>16% of the top 100 MBAs from the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Business schools in Asia may be overlooking the potential of online MBAs. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s first ever Online MBA Rankings for 2014, which came out in March, contained no Asian business schools in its list of the top 15 programs.
However, the region performs better in the traditional MBA format. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s Global MBA Rankings for 2014, published in January 2014, features a number of Asian schools within its top 50...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural Bitcoin conference in China will take place in May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</guid><description>Bitfund.pe, a private equity firm focused on Bitcoin, and UBM China have jointly revealed plans for the first international Bitcoin conference in China. This event, the Global Bitcoin Summit 2014 (GBS), is scheduled for May 10-11 in Beijing.
Source: GBS
The summit will be structured around eight key themes, featuring conversations on Bitcoin trends both within China and globally. Additionally, there will be exploration of how to leverage Bitcoin for new business creation and expansion of existing ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Used cooking oil fuels 1,000 km flight in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</guid><description>A Hainan Airlines flight recently completed a journey of over 1,000 km from Shanghai to Beijing using a blend of conventional jet fuel and biofuel made from recycled cooking oil. The Boeing 737-800 aircraft, carrying over 100 passengers, was powered by a 50/50 mix of biofuel, produced by Sinopec using waste oil from Chinese restaurants, and standard petroleum fuel.
Sustainable biofuel is gaining traction in the aviation industry for its potential to significantly reduce carbon emissions (by 50-80%) compared to traditional fuels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is now offering flights from China to France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</guid><description>Hainan Airlines has introduced a fifth European route to its network, joining existing services to Moscow, Saint Petersburg, Brussels, and Berlin. The inaugural flight, HU7907, departed Hangzhou International Airport on September 3rd, with a stopover at Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport before continuing to Paris&amp;rsquo; Roissy-Charles de Gaulle Airport.
Source: Hainan Airlines. The ribbon-cutting ceremony for the first flight on September 3.
This new service aims to enhance political, economic, and cultural ties between China and France, especially as 2014 marks the 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between the two nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Weixin have collaborated to introduce a new social gifting feature</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-weixin-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-social-gifting-feature/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-weixin-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-social-gifting-feature/</guid><description>Source Starbucks. Starbucks and Weixin launch a new social
gifting feature.
Starbucks and Tencent have launched &amp;ldquo;Say it with Stars,&amp;rdquo; a new gifting feature on the Chinese social media platform Weixin. This follows their strategic partnership announced in December 2016.
This service allows users to send gifts instantly, such as Starbucks beverages or digital gift cards. Belinda Wong, CEO of Starbucks China, stated their goal is to deepen connections between people by allowing them to express feelings like love and gratitude through the act of giving Starbucks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-weixin-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-social-gifting-feature/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-weixin-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-social-gifting-feature/</a></p></description></item><item><title>71 SG introduces international market access programs for startups based in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/71-sg-introduces-international-market-access-programs-for-startups-based-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/71-sg-introduces-international-market-access-programs-for-startups-based-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore-based startup, 71 SG, has introduced programs designed to assist other local startups in expanding into the Chinese market. These programs are supported by International Enterprise (IE) Singapore. One such program, the Start-up Development &amp;amp; Learning Programme (SDL), aims to facilitate a smooth market entry for startups by connecting them with potential customers, partners, and investors.
The SDL offers Singaporean startups a five-day tech and business workshop that provides access to overseas markets, market intelligence, networking opportunities, and funding prospects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/71-sg-introduces-international-market-access-programs-for-startups-based-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/71-sg-introduces-international-market-access-programs-for-startups-based-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud introduces the Create@Alibaba Cloud startup program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing branch of Alibaba Group, has launched its first international startup program, Create@Alibaba Cloud. The program was announced in Singapore, home to Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s international headquarters, which will also serve as the regional hub for the initiative.
Singapore was selected as the regional hub due to its strong ties and access to other ASEAN markets, such as Thailand, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The company explained that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s robust connectivity and reputation as Asia&amp;rsquo;s most entrepreneurial economy enable participating startups to easily connect within Singapore and expand into neighboring markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sofitel Kunming provides convenient access to the city center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 07:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</guid><description>Sofitel, the luxury hotel brand under AccorHotels, has launched its newest property, Sofitel Kunming. Located in the city center, it&amp;rsquo;s the only international luxury hotel in Kunming.
Situated in Kunming&amp;rsquo;s central business district, the 400-room hotel spans the 27th to 52nd floors. It showcases a blend of French elegance and art de vivre with touches of Yunnan&amp;rsquo;s vibrant ethnic cultures and customs.
&amp;ldquo;The debut of Sofitel Kunming signifies a period of rapid growth for AccorHotels in China, as we continue to solidify our dedication to delivering world-renowned, refined French hospitality to discerning Chinese travelers,&amp;rdquo; shared Paul Richardson, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines increases frequency on Hong Kong-Haikou route with two additional flights per week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</guid><description>Starting December 25th, Hong Kong Airlines will offer two more weekly flights on its route between Hong Kong and Haikou, increasing the total frequency to nine flights per week. The new flights to Haikou will operate on Fridays and Sundays.
Flight no.*
Route
Departure/Arrival time*
Frequency
HX157
Hong Kong to Haikou
19:25/20:50
Every Friday
18:15/19:45
Every Sunday
HX158
Haikou to Hong Kong
21:55/23:15
Every Friday
21:15/22:35
Every Sunday
*Flight number and schedule may change without prior notice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the successful first year of Hyatt Regency Suzhou with our Anniversary Meeting Package</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Suzhou.
The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is commemorating its first anniversary with various special offers as a thank you to its loyal and valued guests for their support throughout the year.
Having opened its doors on August 24, 2014, in the Suzhou Industrial Park (SIP), the conveniently located Hyatt Regency Suzhou boasts 355 rooms and suites. Amenities include a Regency Club, five dining options, and over 15,000 square feet of space for events...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Childcare centers are emerging in Chinese workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</guid><description>Government policy changes are fueling the growth of the preschool or childcare market in China. Technavio forecasts a CAGR exceeding 6% for this market between 2016 and 2020. This growth is largely attributed to recent policy adjustments, notably the 2015 amendment to the one-child policy, now permitting couples to have two children. This shift aims to balance population development and, coupled with rising disposable incomes among middle-class families, is driving increased preschool enrollment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li blends traditional shikumen architecture with modern French elegance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</guid><description>Source: Capella Shanghai website. Villa entrance.
Located in Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French Concession, the Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li, offers a journey back to the city&amp;rsquo;s early 20th-century charm. Situated within the Jian Ye Li estate, the property is a rare surviving example of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;shikumen&amp;rdquo; townhouses, characterized by their three-story brick construction and stone accents.
The goal was to develop an ultra-luxury experience while meticulously preserving the site&amp;rsquo;s historical character. Jaya Interior Design and BLINK Design Group drew inspiration from Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s past, seamlessly integrating traditional Chinese elements with French elegance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines introduces new flights to Okinawa, Hangzhou, and Ho Chi Minh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</guid><description>On March 19th, Hong Kong Airlines launched new flights for its Hong Kong-Okinawa and Hong Kong-Hangzhou routes to meet the increasing demand from business and leisure travelers. The airline celebrated the occasion with events at Hong Kong International Airport and both destination airports.
Alex Wu, Hong Kong Airlines General Manager of the Hong Kong Sales Office, welcomed passengers on the inaugural Okinawa flight HX678 with model airplanes. At the gate, passengers received certificates acknowledging their support for the new route...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Shanghai is set to make its debut in late 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</guid><description>Source: HKRI. The Sukhothai Shanghai.
HKR International will soon expand its Sukhothai Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts portfolio with a second hotel – The Sukhothai Shanghai. This new addition, situated in the Nanjing Road West central business district, is set to launch in late 2017.
Designed by Neri &amp;amp; Hu, The Sukhothai Shanghai is a contemporary luxury boutique hotel. It offers 168 guest rooms and 33 suites, ranging from 44 to 172 square meters in size...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Suzhou is gaining more recognition in the MICE industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</guid><description>The Suzhou Culture and Expo Centre Company (SCECC), which manages the Suzhou Culture and Arts Centre and the Suzhou International Expo Centre, claims that Suzhou is arguably the top Meetings, Incentives, Conferences and Exhibitions (MICE) destination in China.
SCECC highlights Suzhou&amp;rsquo;s success in hosting significant events, such as the 53rd World Table Tennis Championships earlier this year and Armani&amp;rsquo;s selection of the city&amp;rsquo;s Humble Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Garden as the venue for the global debut of its Pivoine Suzhou perfume...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Standard Chartered Bank is launching credit cards in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/standard-chartered-bank-is-launching-credit-cards-in-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/standard-chartered-bank-is-launching-credit-cards-in-china/</guid><description>Standard Chartered Bank has launched its credit card services in China, focusing on the mid-range and high-end consumer market. These new credit cards blend international and local features.
The bank aims to give customers special shopping and dining offers at over 1,000 locations by merging resources and platforms across mainland China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan. Recognizing the growth of online shopping and shifting consumer habits, Standard Chartered provides cardholders with the convenience of online payments and cashback rewards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/standard-chartered-bank-is-launching-credit-cards-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/standard-chartered-bank-is-launching-credit-cards-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai welcomes the opening of a new Chinese Business Hub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 23:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</guid><description>Source: CBH. Pictured at the Business Centre opening ceremony are (from left to right) Justin Wilshaw, SVP Commercial, Dubai South; Shoaib Alrahimi, VP, Business Park, Dubai South; Mohsen Ahmad, VP, Logistics District, Dubai South; alongside other senior officials and association representatives. The UAE&amp;rsquo;s first dedicated business center specifically designed for new and expanding Chinese startups and SMEs, known as the Chinese Business Hub (CBH), has officially opened its main office in Dubai South Business Park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Foul Odor of Decaying Prepaid Calling Cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are a popular choice for international calls due to their incredibly low advertised rates. The cards often boast incredibly low per-minute rates, but these rates don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story. Like perishable food, prepaid calling cards have a limited lifespan once you start using them.
Hidden in the fine print on the back of these cards are details about connection fees, minimum call durations, and weekly service fees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indulge in Glamour at the Bund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</guid><description>The renowned &amp;lsquo;M&amp;rsquo; Restaurant Group, led by Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s celebrated entrepreneur Michelle Garnaut, has unveiled Glam, a chic new dining lounge and bar in Shanghai. Situated at 5 on the Bund, the location previously housed the iconic M on the Bund restaurant.
Michelle Garnaut, known for establishing new dining benchmarks in Asia, began her restaurant empire with M at the Fringe in Hong Kong in 1989. She later spearheaded Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s return to sophistication with M on the Bund in 1999 and elevated the city&amp;rsquo;s nightlife with The Glamour Bar in 2006...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor examines consumer opportunities for individuals aged 60 and above</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 12:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Market research firm Euromonitor International has published a new report on the growing market of older consumers. Though businesses have often overlooked this demographic— individuals aged 60 and above— due to perceptions of low spending, limited income, and resistance to marketing, this group is expanding rapidly.
In 2014, the global population aged 60 and over reached 912 million, accounting for 12.6% of the total. By 2030, this segment is projected to increase to 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Commemorative stamp marks 34 years of diplomatic relations between the UAE and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commemorative-stamp-marks-34-years-of-diplomatic-relations-between-the-uae-and-china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 21:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commemorative-stamp-marks-34-years-of-diplomatic-relations-between-the-uae-and-china/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Post Group. Commemorative stamps for 34 years of diplomatic relations between the UAE and China.
In honor of Chinese President Xi Jinping&amp;rsquo;s visit to the UAE, Emirates Post Group (EPG), working with the UAE Ministry of Foreign Affairs and International Cooperation, has introduced commemorative stamps. These stamps celebrate 34 years of diplomatic ties between the two nations.
The stamps showcase three distinct designs: one featuring a portrait of UAE President HH Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan, another with a portrait of the Chinese President, and the third displaying both countries&amp;rsquo; flags...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commemorative-stamp-marks-34-years-of-diplomatic-relations-between-the-uae-and-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commemorative-stamp-marks-34-years-of-diplomatic-relations-between-the-uae-and-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A white paper providing solutions for talent management in the Chinese hospitality industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</guid><description>Florida International University&amp;rsquo;s Chaplin School of Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Management (CSHTM) and its Institute for Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Education &amp;amp; Research (IHTER) have published a new resource for HR professionals and hospitality businesses, particularly those working with Chinese markets. The white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Managing Growing Pains of China’s Relentless Hotel Development Pipeline,&amp;rdquo; examines the significant lack of qualified talent within China&amp;rsquo;s rapidly expanding hotel industry. The paper offers practical solutions such as professional development programs, conflict resolution strategies, and clearly defined career paths to attract and retain skilled employees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Businesses operating in the South China Sea region should be cautious of the Spring Dragon APT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</guid><description>Kaspersky Lab is issuing a warning about a threat actor targeting nations surrounding the South China Sea. The cybersecurity company has observed a rise in attacks since 2017 from an advanced persistent threat (APT) known as Spring Dragon (or LotusBlossom) using new and enhanced tactics.
Noushin Shabab, Senior Security Researcher at Kaspersky Lab&amp;rsquo;s Global Research &amp;amp; Analysis Team (GReAT), emphasizes the importance of vigilance, stating, &amp;ldquo;We believe Spring Dragon will continue to reappear in the Asian region, making it crucial to be familiar with its methods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China Telecom is conducting a trial of a connected car concept in partnership with Gemalto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</guid><description>Gemalto, a digital security company, and China Telecom, a major Chinese mobile operator, are collaborating on a connected car project. They are using Gemalto&amp;rsquo;s LinqUs On-Demand Connectivity (ODC) subscription management solution.
The companies recently demonstrated at Mobile World Congress Shanghai how remote provisioning can securely connect mobile devices. They plan to apply this ODC solution to vehicles. This would allow China Telecom&amp;rsquo;s automotive clients to provide their customers with instant in-car connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Wuhan and Changsha were recognized as the top sustainable cities in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</guid><description>The 2015 China Sustainable Cities Report: Measuring Ecological and Human Development reveals that 35 Chinese cities have shown progress in their sustainability performance since 2014, as indicated by their scores on the Urban Ecological Input Index (EUII). This report, which assesses the progress of Chinese cities towards sustainable development, was presented in Beijing at the 2015 International Forum on Sustainable Cities in China.
A collaboration between the United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Xinhua Oriental Outlook Weekly, and a team of experts from Tongji University, this report marks the first of its kind in China since the UN&amp;rsquo;s 193 member states adopted the 17 Sustainable Development Goals in September 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is offering a promotion during Golden Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</guid><description>The Sanya EDITION hotel is offering a special promotion for travelers visiting China during Golden Week, which falls on October 1st to 7th.
To celebrate, the hotel is hosting guest chef Matthew David Ona from Roof 325 Restaurant and Bar in Shanghai. Chef Ona, known for his culinary expertise at one of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s top dining destinations, will be at The Jade Egret restaurant from October 1st to 3rd. He has designed special steak and seafood tasting menus for the occasion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amara Signature Shanghai has been softly launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 02:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</guid><description>![Source: Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. The Amara Signature Shanghai.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgAfBJYJW9dykG8i4PiZBEX_SuEbBpNrdOHxK7OgjVsJ6TA5Nt3-In_JgJHn8Ca19sRF5j5K5W-upNOpJ4qsG-tQA9WfYeGX2oQViKTULwU3f0PwufZs6HVNmCPk3UB45hfYmL_9NVDfxE/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;The Amara Signature Shanghai is the first Amara Signature in China.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. The Amara Signature Shanghai.
The Amara Signature Shanghai, a new luxury hotel under Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has recently held its soft opening.
This 30-story, five-star hotel showcases a sleek, all-glass exterior and sits at the crossroads of Changshou Road and Jiaozhou Road in Shanghai, China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in October, Air China will offer nonstop flights from Beijing to Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</guid><description>Air China will commence nonstop flights between Beijing and Mumbai starting October 25, 2015. This decision comes as a response to the growing travel demand between these two BRICS nations, driven by strengthening political and economic ties.
Source: Air China.
The route will operate four times a week, with flights on Tuesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays, and Sundays. The seven-hour journey departs Beijing at 7:40 PM local time and arrives in Mumbai at 1 AM the following day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Presidential Villa is now available at Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:01:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort.
The Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort is located near Dujiangyan, a UNESCO World Heritage &amp;amp; Natural Cultural site known as the home of giant pandas.
Inspired by the region&amp;rsquo;s history as the birthplace of Taoism, Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain introduces a new Presidential Villa. This villa embodies Taoist principles of living in harmony with nature, offering a space for reconnection and self-discovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CIER Employment Index indicates a decrease in employment rates in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</guid><description>The Chinese job platform Zhaopin and the China Institute for Employment Research (CIER) at Renmin University have published their CIER Employment Index Report for July to September 2015.
The report&amp;rsquo;s index, which measures the ease of finding a job, rose consistently from 2011 to 2014. However, mirroring the economic slowdown, the job market has weakened, leading to a decline in the CIER Index for the past two quarters. The index dropped from its peak of 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>