<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PLDT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pldt/</link><description>Recent content in PLDT on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pldt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The MyNumber service from Hashtag assists businesses in reducing their hotline expenses in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>PLDT, through its corporate business group PLDT ALPHA Enterprise, has launched the PLDT #MyNumber service. This service streamlines a business&amp;rsquo;s hotline system into a memorable four to eight-digit contact number that starts with the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; symbol (for example, #8888). This single number can be reached by consumers nationwide using PLDT landlines, Smart, Talk N’ Text, and Sun mobile phones.
This service is designed for businesses that currently advertise different hotline numbers for different regions.</description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination.</description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right).</description></item></channel></rss>