<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Logistics on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/logistics/</link><description>Recent content in Logistics on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/logistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canon has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Canon Singapore has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution providing businesses with real-time delivery tracking and automated scheduling. Designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) that rely on scheduling, delivery, and documentation for their core operations, FleetnexG offers a way to optimize resources and boost efficiency.
Vincent Low, Director &amp;amp; General Manager of Business Imaging Solutions at Canon Singapore, highlights the need for SMEs to go beyond timely order fulfillment. He emphasizes that optimizing resources for greater efficiency and productivity is crucial for success in today&amp;rsquo;s business landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LBC 360 provides comprehensive business services in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 20:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: LBC YouTube channel.
In November 2014, LBC Express, the top cargo and logistics company in the Philippines, introduced a unique, fully integrated payment and logistics solution for the country. This platform, called LBC 360, aims to assist Filipino businesses of all types and sizes in overcoming supply chain obstacles.
“LBC 360 is intentionally crafted to be advantageous for all business models, from physical stores to online marketplaces,” explained Miguel Camahort, LBC President and Chief Operating Officer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aramex logistics support is available to Shopmatic merchants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 23:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</guid><description>Shopmatic, a Singapore-based e-commerce software as a service (SaaS) provider, has partnered with Aramex, a global logistics and transportation company. This partnership aims to provide online merchants with efficient and secure delivery options.
Shopmatic offers a comprehensive, commission-free e-commerce platform for businesses to establish and manage their online presence. By integrating with Aramex&amp;rsquo;s services, Shopmatic strengthens its position as a one-stop solution for anyone looking to sell online.
Anurag Avula, CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Shopmatic Group, highlights the significant growth potential of online shopping in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zap Delivery in Singapore guarantees fast and reliable couriered deliveries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</guid><description>Source: Zap Delivery.
Zap Delivery, an on-demand courier service, promises quick, safe, and dependable deliveries of packages and documents within Singapore in two hours or less using their new mobile app. This app utilizes advanced authentication and real-time tracking to provide peace of mind for those awaiting deliveries.
“We’ve experienced our fair share of delivery issues, so we created a user-friendly app that fosters trust,&amp;quot; explained Michael Tan, Zap Delivery Co-founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL introduces new freight service from Taiwan to Austria for shipments smaller than a full container</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding has introduced a new weekly Less-than-Container-Load (LCL) service originating in Taiwan and arriving in Vienna, Austria, by way of Koper, Slovenia. This service, departing every Monday from Keelung or Kaohsiung, allows Taiwanese exporters to ship cargo with a 35-day transit time to Vienna.
Kelvin Leung, CEO, Asia Pacific at DHL Global Forwarding, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to understanding industry trends and supporting exporters. He highlighted the increasing demand for Asian products in Eastern Europe and positioned the new service as a way to strengthen trade partnerships and improve the speed and efficiency of services for Taiwanese businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cainiao will collaborate with Ethiopian Airlines to provide cold chain air freight services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 09:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</guid><description>Source: Alibaba Group. Cainiao will distribute temperature-sensitive medications, including COVID-19 vaccines, globally, excluding Africa, via Dubai in partnership with Ethiopian Airlines.
Cainiao Smart Logistics Network, the logistics branch of Alibaba Group Holdings, has partnered with Ethiopian Airlines. Their collaboration will establish a specialized cold chain air freight system to transport temperature-controlled medical supplies. These shipments will originate from Shenzhen Airport, recognized as China&amp;rsquo;s first medical cross-border cold chain facility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACN and MENA Cargo will be providing enhanced services in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:43:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</guid><description>The Asia Cargo Network (ACN), a Southeast Asian air cargo charter provider, is expanding its reach globally through a new partnership with Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s MENA Aerospace. This agreement will see ACN stationing six cargo planes in Bahrain and the GCC to better serve the Middle East, North Africa (MENA) region and beyond.
These operations will fall under the MENA Cargo brand, a subsidiary of MAE specializing in freight cargo. The rollout will occur over the next year and a half, with the first of the six aircraft scheduled to arrive and begin operations within the next two months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FedEx packages can now be picked up by customers themselves at any time of day in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 08:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: FedEx. FedEx has launched a new self-collection service in Singapore, allowing customers to pick up their packages at designated locations. These include bluPort and Parcel Santa lockers, and Park N Parcel retail outlets across the island.
FedEx Express, a subsidiary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest express transportation company, now offers 24/7 package collection in Singapore.
Customers can retrieve their parcels from all participating bluPort and Parcel Santa lockers, as well as Park N Parcel retail collection points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, the Brunei freight and logistics market had a value of US$157.25 million</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</guid><description>A new report by Mordor Intelligence, titled &amp;ldquo;Brunei Freight &amp;amp; Logistics Market Study - Market Trends, Analysis &amp;amp; Forecasts to 2023,&amp;rdquo; has been added to ResearchAndMarkets.com&amp;rsquo;s collection.
The Brunei freight and logistics market, valued at US$157.25 million in 2017, sees its biggest opportunity in the multi-trillion dollar halal industry. Mordor Intelligence highlights Brunei&amp;rsquo;s positive image within the Islamic world, where it is regarded as a hub of Islamic culture.
Brunei&amp;rsquo;s strategic location for China, along with its alignment with the Belt and Road project, presents significant opportunities for its halal certification industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singpost will collaborate with Shippit on final delivery services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</guid><description>Shippit has partnered with Singapore Post (SingPost) to offer their delivery services and special negotiated rates on its platform. This collaboration allows small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to deliver parcels throughout Singapore.
This partnership provides SMEs on Shippit&amp;rsquo;s platform with more e-commerce fulfillment options. They can now offer customers island-wide parcel collection through SingPost&amp;rsquo;s POPStation network. Additionally, Shippit will provide access to SingPost&amp;rsquo;s Speedpost Express Service and discounted, pre-negotiated rates for next-day and economy deliveries—services previously exclusive to larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SingEx has introduced Last Mile Fulfilment Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 06:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</guid><description>Last Mile Fulfilment Asia (LMFAsia), a debut trade show and conference centered around last-mile fulfillment in logistics and e-commerce, will premiere in Singapore next year.
This is the first event of its kind to hone in on last-mile fulfillment challenges and prospects in Asia. SingEx anticipates the event will attract around 1,500 attendees, representatives, and exhibitors from the Asian region in its first year. LMFAsia aims to unite four crucial sectors – e-commerce, retail, logistics, and parcel delivery – under one roof to maximize business opportunities for e-commerce in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SCALA, the Singapore Workforce Development Agency, is offering a logistics reskilling program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 14:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</guid><description>The Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA) and Supply Chain and Logistics Academy (SCALA) joined forces to launch the Logistics Professional Conversion Programme (PCP). The initiative aims to help professionals, managers, executives, and technicians (PMETs) gain the necessary skills to enter the logistics industry.
This program seeks to create opportunities for newcomers and seasoned professionals in logistics, allowing them to expand their skillsets and advance their careers. Over the next two years, the PCP will offer 150 positions for PMETs, specifically as Logistics Officers and Logistics Executives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scala-the-singapore-workforce-development-agency-is-offering-a-logistics-reskilling-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia and Pos Malaysia are working together for order fulfillment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</guid><description>Shopee Malaysia has partnered with Pos Malaysia, the national courier service, to offer free shipping to all sellers on its platform.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace with a strong regional presence of over 12 million users, operates as a free online customer-to-customer (C2C) platform. Launched in December 2015, Shopee aims to empower both individual and business entrepreneurs to conduct secure buying and selling transactions on their mobile devices. In Malaysia alone, Shopee&amp;rsquo;s app has been downloaded over a million times within a six-month timeframe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aramex is constructing private parcel lockers to meet the demands of the expanding e-commerce industry in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:04:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Aramex, a leading provider of global logistics and transportation solutions, has partnered with InPost, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest parcel locker network. This collaboration aims to provide consumers in the Middle East with convenient access to private, automated parcel lockers for all their e-commerce needs by the end of 2014.
Aramex attributes the significant growth of the e-commerce sector in the region to several factors. These include a growing affluent urban population, increased interest in and demand for online products and services, and a rise in new online retailers entering the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai CommerCity aims to establish Dubai as a leading e-commerce destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</guid><description>Dubai CommerCity, a new AED2.7 billion, 2.1-million sq ft e-commerce free zone, has been jointly launched by Dubai Airport Freezone Authority (DAFZA) and wasl Asset Management Group. As the first of its kind in the MENA region, this project aims to solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing as a major e-commerce hub, boost economic diversification, and advance smart transformation strategies.
This initiative seeks to capitalize on the burgeoning GCC e-commerce market, predicted to reach US$20 billion by 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL eCommerce has launched a new Fulfillment Center in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</guid><description>DHL eCommerce, a branch of the logistics giant Deutsche Post DHL Group, has opened a Fulfillment Center in Sydney, Australia. The new center will help the company meet the demands of Australia&amp;rsquo;s rapidly growing number of online shoppers buying goods from overseas.
Damien Sheehan, Managing Director for DHL eCommerce in Australia, highlighted the significance of Australian online shoppers, stating, “Australian shoppers are some of the most frequent buyers from international sellers online, and their influence will only grow as cross-border e-commerce continues to expand at an average rate of 29% annually through 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InPost has officially started its operations in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: InPost.
InPost, a global leader in automated parcel locker networks, has expanded its services to Malaysia. The launch was accompanied by a roadshow, themed &amp;ldquo;Malaysia E-commerce Day (MED) 2015,&amp;rdquo; aimed at raising awareness about the latest advancements in e-commerce, e-payments, and logistics.
According to InPost Malaysia Managing Director Rosland Mohd Jannes, the initiative seeks to connect with businesses and individuals, boosting consumer confidence in online shopping and alleviating delivery-related anxieties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopmatic has partnered with Easyship to make it easier for merchants to deliver their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</guid><description>Source: Shopmatic. Shopmatic co-founders from left: Kris Chen,
Anurag Avula, and Yen Ti Lim. Shopmatic, the Singapore-based e-commerce company, has teamed up with Easyship, a comprehensive shipping platform for global e-commerce. This partnership will enable Shopmatic merchants to streamline product delivery and expand their businesses internationally.
Easyship offers integrated shipping services from over 100 providers, including DHL, FedEx, and UPS. It allows for immediate order shipping with discounts of up to 70%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>