<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electronic Payments on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronic-payments/</link><description>Recent content in Electronic Payments on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:36:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronic-payments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small Business Merchant Accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:36:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</guid><description>Could you be missing out on sales because you don&amp;rsquo;t accept credit cards? While setting up credit and debit card processing might seem expensive and complex, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be. With the right processing partner, it can be a smooth and straightforward process.
Don&amp;rsquo;t mistake this for implying that credit card processing is simple. Behind the scenes, it involves a network of banks, credit card companies, merchant service providers, computer systems, and specialized equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need A Managed Security Services Provider?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 05:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</guid><description>Cybercrime has evolved from mere mischief into a substantial threat focused on financial gain. If your network holds valuable data, cybercriminals will see it as a target, making network security essential.
Protecting your digital assets isn&amp;rsquo;t optional; the choice lies in managing it yourself or outsourcing it to managed security services, also known as Security as a Service (SaaS).
MegaPath, a prominent carrier, provides comprehensive managed security services, including firewalls, intrusion prevention, malware and virus protection, web filtering, anti-spam measures, application control, data leak prevention, log management, vulnerability assessments, security information management, and file integrity monitoring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>