<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Casio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/casio/</link><description>Recent content in Casio on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:08:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/casio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CASIO introduces the G-SHOCK x ITZY SS2024 collection in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-the-g-shock-x-itzy-ss2024-collection-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-the-g-shock-x-itzy-ss2024-collection-in-singapore/</guid><description>CASIO is promoting their new G-SHOCK shock-resistant watches for spring 2024 with the help of K-pop group ITZY, who have been G-SHOCK brand ambassadors since February 2023.
ITZY is shown wearing the new GMA-P2100SG-1A, GMA-P2100SG-4A, GMA-S120VA-7A, and GMA-S140VA-7A watches in a promotional image. Ryujin and Chaeryeong showcase the GMA-P2100SG-1A and GMA-P2100SG-4A, which are inspired by sunset hues on a beach. These watches are based on the GMA-P2100, a smaller version of the well-liked GMA-S2100 analog-digital combination watch.</description></item><item><title>Verizon Goes After Blue Collar Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</guid><description>When picturing someone in a hard hat using a cell phone, most people think of a Nextel phone, known for their walkie-talkie feature and durability. However, Verizon is now entering this market, aiming to capture the construction and outdoor enthusiast demographics.
Verizon has the advantage of being a larger company with a wider customer base and a broader phone selection. They have leveled the playing field by adding push-to-talk (PTT) functionality and introducing tougher phones.</description></item></channel></rss>