<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Commission on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commission/</link><description>Recent content in Commission on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The discussion on drones in the UK and its impact on the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 05:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</guid><description>By Chris Jones
A new report, Back from the battlefield: domestic drones in the UK, investigates the use of drones by public and private entities in the UK. It focuses on law enforcement and border control agencies, examining the laws, regulations, and public and private funding surrounding drone technology development. The report analyzes the current situation and potential future applications, advocating for public discussion and decision-making before widespread drone use, particularly for surveillance, becomes commonplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it appropriate for the outcome of the European Parliament elections to dictate the selection of the next President of the European Commission, or are there valid concerns about this democratic process?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s doubtful the European Court of Justice will decide the next European Commission President. Election laws typically set the stage but don&amp;rsquo;t directly determine the winner, although there are notable exceptions like the 2000 US election.
The 2014 Commission President election is unique because the rules changed, and their interpretation is debated. Previously, the European Council appointed the President after European Parliament approval. The Treaty of Lisbon introduced new rules, applied for the first time, stating the Parliament &amp;ldquo;elects&amp;rdquo; the President based on the Council&amp;rsquo;s nomination, &amp;ldquo;taking account&amp;rdquo; of Parliament election results...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU establishes significant limitations on the Commission's power to initiate actions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</guid><description>Steve Peers
It is a fundamental principle of EU law, as taught to every student of the subject, that the Commission has a near-monopoly on proposing new EU legislation - it is the &amp;lsquo;motor&amp;rsquo; of EU integration. This near-monopoly is often called the Commission&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;right of initiative&amp;rsquo;. But does this right also imply a right to withdraw proposals? And if it does, are there any limitations to this power? These questions were addressed by the CJEU in a significant ruling...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cracks in the unity of EU representation are evident in the Global Compact for Migration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</guid><description>Pauline Melin, PhD, Lecturer in European Law (Maastricht University) and Researcher at the Institute for European Law (KULeuven)
The UN Global Compact for Safe, Orderly and Regular Migration is scheduled for approval at a conference in Marrakesh, aiming for adoption as a UN General Assembly Resolution in New York on December 19th, 2018. However, the political climate surrounding the Compact&amp;rsquo;s adoption has become contentious. Since Austria, an active participant in the negotiations, withdrew its support in late October 2018, multiple EU Member States have followed suit, publicly questioning or withdrawing their support every week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dalli Saga: A Story of Accountability and Defenestration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City University
The forced resignation of the Santer Commission in 1999 due to accusations of fraud, maladministration, and mismanagement remains a relevant topic even after nearly two decades. The European Commission has faced ongoing criticism for its administrative shortcomings and the structural flaws within the Union&amp;rsquo;s accountability system. Numerous reports have portrayed the Commission as an institution grappling with systemic and political irregularities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU visa policy driving growth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s visa policy has traditionally focused on managing illegal immigration and security threats while considering foreign policy goals. However, in recent years, promoting economic growth, particularly in the tourism sector, has become increasingly important. This shift, initiated by a 2012 Commission communication, is evident in recent updates to the EU&amp;rsquo;s visa &amp;lsquo;whitelist&amp;rsquo;. The criteria for visa liberalization now include trade and investment, leading to the inclusion of Peru and Colombia after they signed a trade agreement with the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The labeling of the European Union in the International Maritime Organization is more of a focus than the EU's actual competence.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</guid><description>Cathleen Berg, doctoral student, University of Bayreuth
Advocate General (‘AG’) Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s November 25, 2021, opinion regarding a legal challenge from the European Commission against the European Council (Case C-161/20) highlights the contrasting interests between the European Union (‘EU’) and its Member States. This disagreement centers around how they exercise their authority within the International Maritime Organization (‘IMO’), an organization where the EU currently holds neither membership nor observer status. If the Court of Justice sides with AG Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s analysis, this case could significantly impact how the EU interest is represented within IMO committees, potentially shifting power from the Commission to the Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on immigration for students and researchers a minor advancement or a significant stride?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU has been working for many years to attract highly skilled individuals from non-EU countries. However, the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s reports indicate that the existing legislation, specifically the 2005 Researchers&amp;rsquo; Directive and the 2004 Students&amp;rsquo; Directive, have not significantly increased the number of students and researchers coming to the EU.
As a result, in 2013, the Commission recommended a complete overhaul of these laws. The European Parliament (EP) and the Council recently reached an agreement on the content of this proposal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Going from bad to worse? Examining the rule of law initiatives of the Commission and the Council</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</guid><description>Dimitry Kochenov* and Laurent Pech**
*Professor of EU Constitutional Law at the University of Groningen and Visiting Professor of Private Law at the Universita degli studi di Torino
**Jean Monnet Professor of EU Public Law, Head of the Law and Politics Department at Middlesex University London
The principle of the rule of law is a cornerstone of the European Union, as stated in Article 2 of the Treaty on European Union...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-from-bad-to-worse-examining-the-rule-of-law-initiatives-of-the-commission-and-the-council/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving institutional equilibrium and the process of negotiating global treaties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</guid><description>Andrés Delgado Casteleiro, Lecturer at Durham Law School
Introduction
In a ruling on Case C-425/13, Commission v Council, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with clarifying the Council&amp;rsquo;s authority in providing directions to the Commission during international negotiations. This case, decided on Thursday, specifically concerned the linking of Australia&amp;rsquo;s emissions trading system with the EU&amp;rsquo;s and involved examining the balance of power between the Council and the Commission during such negotiations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Feedback on the Commission's latest guidance for Family Reunions for Third-Country Nationals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Family life is essential for everyone living in the EU, regardless of their citizenship. For non-EU citizens (third-country nationals), family reunification is governed by the EU Directive on family reunion, adopted in 2003. Recently, the European Commission released new guidance on this Directive, offering potential for its better implementation and understanding. Although the guidance addresses several issues effectively, there are points that require further improvement or clarification...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's strategy to eliminate human trafficking is all talk and no action.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</guid><description>Dr Matilde Ventrella, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Wolverhampton (UK)
1. Introduction
The European Commission recently released two important documents on October 17th: a progress report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat human trafficking and a report on how a specific directive (Directive 2004/81) is being used to protect victims. This analysis will delve into the key findings of both reports and offer concluding observations.
2. Progress Report on the EU&amp;rsquo;s Fight Against Human Trafficking..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-strategy-to-eliminate-human-trafficking-is-all-talk-and-no-action/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new e-Privacy Regulation a threat to human rights? Exploring the implications of Tele2 and Watson.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-e-privacy-regulation-a-threat-to-human-rights-exploring-the-implications-of-tele2-and-watson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-e-privacy-regulation-a-threat-to-human-rights-exploring-the-implications-of-tele2-and-watson/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
Introduction
This post follows up on a previous one from last Christmas, which discussed data retention in the context of the proposed Regulation on Privacy and Electronic Communications (e-Privacy Regs). The European Commission released the official version of the e-Privacy Regs on January 10, 2017. Like the leaked version, the official proposal does not have specific provisions for data retention (para 1.3). The proposal allows Member States to maintain or create their own data retention laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-e-privacy-regulation-a-threat-to-human-rights-exploring-the-implications-of-tele2-and-watson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-e-privacy-regulation-a-threat-to-human-rights-exploring-the-implications-of-tele2-and-watson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it fair for EU citizens who relocate to still have the right to vote in their home country?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 02:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently issued a communication and recommendation addressing the loss of voting rights for EU citizens who relocate to other Member States. The Commission acknowledges that national identity grants Member States the right to determine voter eligibility. However, they urge Member States to consider if their policies on disenfranchisement hinder political participation. The Commission argues that many citizens maintain an interest in their home country&amp;rsquo;s politics, staying informed about political developments is easier than ever, and there&amp;rsquo;s a growing trend towards allowing expatriates to vote...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-fair-for-eu-citizens-who-relocate-to-still-have-the-right-to-vote-in-their-home-country/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Insights from interim proceedings: Amazon v DSA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</guid><description>Laureline Lemoine, Senior Associate, AWO Agency
Photo credit: KarleHorn, via Wikimedia Commons
A recent legal challenge to the Digital Services Act (DSA) provides insight into how Amazon is approaching its obligations under the new law. The case, initiated by Amazon after being designated a Very Large Online Platform (VLOP), centers around two main arguments.
First, Amazon contests the DSA requirement for an opt-out for recommender systems based on user profiling (Article 38), claiming it would negatively impact its business and users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should safeguarding the rule of law in the EU be the responsibility of the Commission?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-safeguarding-the-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-be-the-responsibility-of-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:22:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-safeguarding-the-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-be-the-responsibility-of-the-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Concerns about upholding the rule of law within the European Union have arisen lately, particularly regarding government actions in Hungary and Romania. Currently, the EU can address breaches of EU law and penalize severe, ongoing violations of EU values, including rule of law. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no mechanism to handle potential EU value breaches not directly tied to EU law or not reaching the threshold of a serious persistent breach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-safeguarding-the-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-be-the-responsibility-of-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-safeguarding-the-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-be-the-responsibility-of-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is a Title Sufficient to Override Constitutional Rules and Fundamental Rule-of-Law Principles? A Paper on Enforcement Priorities for Article 102 TFEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</guid><description>Konstantinos Sidiropoulos
DPhil Candidate at University of Oxford – Prof Steve Weatherill
Foundation for Education and European culture scholar
Introduction
The best way to regulate abuse of dominance in the EU has been a subject of much discussion. In the early 2000s, aiming to address criticisms of its approach to unilateral conduct control, the European Commission started reviewing the relevant law, including how it was being applied (see the EAGCP Report and the Discussion Paper)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What are the reasons behind the ineffectiveness of the Blue Card Directive for highly-skilled workers, and what solutions can be implemented to improve its functionality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 2009, the EU introduced the ‘Blue Card’ Directive to attract highly qualified individuals from non-EU countries. As part of a broader strategy for legal immigration, this Directive is crucial. However, a recent Commission assessment suggests that the Directive has not effectively reached its goals. This raises the question of necessary revisions for improvement.
Implementing the Directive
While all EU Member States obligated to implement the Directive have done so, the actual impact has been underwhelming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Handbook on Marriages of Convenience by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
In September 2014, the Commission introduced a Handbook designed to guide Member States in addressing marriages of convenience between EU citizens and non-EU nationals. The goal is to combat these marriages without unduly restricting the free movement rights of EU citizens. The Commission emphasizes that the guidelines, developed in collaboration with Member States, are not legally binding and don&amp;rsquo;t supersede existing EU law or its future interpretations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Could a third phase of the Common European Asylum System bring wisdom and goodness to those who are considered vile?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 05:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
The EU is looking to overhaul its Common European Asylum Policy, and the Commission has laid out its suggestions in a new discussion paper. These proposals, which are expected to lead to further legislation, aim to address the flaws in the current system. This blog post will break down these proposals and analyze their potential impact.
The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum policy has been developed in phases, with the initial legislation implemented between 2003 and 2005 and the second phase between 2011 and 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a difference this time? The Commission's work programme for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently released its yearly plan, outlining a different approach than previous years. Beyond the typical policy revisions, this Commission aims to introduce fewer new EU initiatives and withdraw more pending proposals.
Is this approach truly different from past Commissions? Comparing this year&amp;rsquo;s plan to those of previous Commissions offers insights.
In 2005, the incoming Barroso Commission put forward 32 pages of proposals, without mentioning any withdrawals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Europe v Facebook the start of the end for NSA surveillance of EU citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>The &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; Case: Challenging US Data Surveillance in Europe Since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about the NSA&amp;rsquo;s extensive spying activities, concerns have grown about the effectiveness of US data protection, particularly for EU citizens who benefit from stronger protections under the Data Protection Directive. One concern is the NSA&amp;rsquo;s ability to access communications processed by US-based social media companies like Facebook.
The Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s recent decision to refer questions in the &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; case to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) could potentially lead to the end of NSA access to EU citizens&amp;rsquo; data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Striving for fairness and adequacy: The proposal for minimum wages in the European Union.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 14:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Antwerp
Almost a year after promising an initiative on minimum wages, the European Commission presented its controversial proposal for a directive on this issue on October 28, 2020. This proposal has been met with criticism, particularly regarding the Commission&amp;rsquo;s authority on this matter, potential impacts on the autonomy of social partners and collective bargaining, and concerns about how this might affect the competitive advantage of member states with currently lower wages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU once again reinforces the EU's external role with In Vino Veritas ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While only a handful of EU countries excel in wine production, it&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed throughout the Union. This simple truth underpins the recent Germany v Council ruling, where the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) bolstered the EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign relations authority, aligning with several previous decisions.
Background
This case centers on instances where Member States act as &amp;rsquo;trustees&amp;rsquo; of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external competence. This situation arises when the EU, despite having authority over a subject, cannot join a treaty or international organization dealing with it (a frequent occurrence)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guide for Law Students: Understanding EU Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge*
EU law is a captivating field of study that offers something for everyone, particularly those interested in politics, visionary thinking, and pragmatic solutions. Even if these aren&amp;rsquo;t your primary interests, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to study EU law due to its mandatory nature. However, it&amp;rsquo;s unlike any other legal system you may have encountered, defying categorization and fitting into no single box.
Before diving in, it&amp;rsquo;s helpful to reflect on your existing political perspectives on the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Commission's draft EU-US Privacy Shield adequacy decision a new shield for transatlantic privacy or just more of the same?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</guid><description>Dr. Maria Tzanou (Lecturer in Law, Keele University)
In October 2015, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruled in the Schrems case that the US Safe Harbor framework did not adequately protect personal data transfers from the EU. The court found that US mass electronic surveillance practices violated fundamental EU privacy rights.
To address this, the European Commission and the US agreed on a new framework called the EU-US Privacy Shield...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Number of Human Trafficking Victims in the EU: A Statistical Puzzle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</guid><description>Dr. Vladislava Stoyanova
Postdoctoral Fellow, Faculty of Law, Lund University; Author of Human Trafficking and Slavery Reconsidered. Conceptual Limits and States’ Positive Obligations in Europe (Cambridge University Press, 2017)
In May 2016, the European Commission presented its initial findings on the progress made in combating human trafficking. This report, mandated by the 2011 EU Trafficking Directive, examines advancements in prosecuting traffickers, safeguarding victims, and preventative measures. It highlights trafficking patterns, incorporating statistical data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regarding knowledge as power: the transparency of procedures for making EU laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</guid><description>Päivi Leino (University of Helsinki)
A key promise made during the adoption of the Lisbon Treaty was increased transparency in EU law-making. However, this has not yet been realized. Access to documents related to EU legislative processes, especially &amp;ldquo;trilogues&amp;rdquo; (informal meetings between the European Parliament, the Council, and the Commission), has become a significant concern. This issue is highlighted in the new Interinstitutional Agreement (IIA) on Better Regulation, the European Ombudsman&amp;rsquo;s public consultation on trilogue transparency, and a legal appeal by a former LIBE Committee Secretariat head against the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s refusal to grant full access to legislative documents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are agency workers adequately protected under EU legislation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 06:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Workers with non-traditional employment arrangements, such as those lacking full-time permanent contracts, frequently face precarious positions in the labor market, making them susceptible to exploitation. Additionally, the utilization of such employment models may negatively impact other workers. Conversely, there are instances where such employment benefits both workers and employers, acting as a significant source of job creation. In balancing these concerns, the EU has implemented measures regulating three specific non-traditional employment categories: agency workers, part-time workers, and fixed-term workers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 3: Is there a lack of democracy in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, Middlesex University
Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The European Union is frequently criticized for being undemocratic or suffering from a &amp;ldquo;democratic deficit.&amp;rdquo; One common assertion is that all EU decisions are made by the unelected bureaucrats of the European Commission. This post will demonstrate why this criticism is fundamentally flawed. It stems from a misunderstanding of both the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s actual powers within the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes and how the European Commission is appointed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mr. Avramopolous travels to Brussels: reflections on the European Parliament hearing for the new Migration Commissioner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Throughout his extensive three-hour hearing at the European Parliament, Dimitris Avramopolous, the nominee for Commissioner for migration and home affairs, consistently emphasized his commitment to liberal values. He expressed strong support for upholding the Schengen system, adopting a liberal stance on asylum and legal migration, and protecting the freedom of movement for EU citizens. However, he fell short of providing specifics on the implementation of these principles and how the various facets of EU policy in this domain would harmonize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Overview of the European Democracy Action Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 04:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
The European Democracy Action Plan (EDAP) is one piece of a larger effort to regulate the online world. Unveiled as a key initiative by Commission President von der Leyen, it joins upcoming legislation like the Digital Services Act (DSA) and Digital Markets Act (DMA). These measures signal a change in how the EU approaches internet regulation and raise questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority in this space...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowdonomic is now a registered e-facility for equity crowdfunding in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 14:03:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Crowdonomic. Crowdonomic was one of just a few operators approved as a Registered Electronic Facility (Equity Crowdfunding Platform) by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Securities Commission. From left: Nicola Castelnuovo, Co-founder and Chief Commercial Officer of Crowdonomic; Datuk Ranjit Ajit Singh, Chairman, Securities Commission Malaysia and Leo Shimada, Co-Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Crowdonomic.
Crowdonomic, a leading crowdfunding platform in Southeast Asia, was designated as a registered electronic facility by the Securities Commission Malaysia (SC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Inquiries for potential Commissioners of Home Affairs and Justice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 01:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Emilio de Capitani, and Henri Labayle present a series of questions for Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to pose to the candidates for Commissioners of Immigration and Home Affairs and Justice. These questions aim to understand the candidates&amp;rsquo; plans and secure commitments on crucial matters.
Immigration and Asylum
Given the Commission&amp;rsquo;s stance on framing migration policy with the non-binding Global Approach to Migration and Mobility Partnerships, would the candidate propose a legally binding basis for agreements with relevant nations, based on Articles 77, 78, and 79 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Dublin Regulation coming to an end? Where should unaccompanied children seek asylum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Recent events have sparked debate concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin III Regulation, which dictates where asylum seekers must apply for asylum within the EU. A British court ruled that the UK is responsible for the asylum claims of unaccompanied children in France, particularly those in Calais, if they have family in the UK. Additionally, a press release suggested the Commission may soon propose significant changes to the Dublin rules...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>