<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephones/</link><description>Recent content in Telephones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Your Broadband Isn’t Stable Enough For VoIP Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You might get laughed at for sticking with your old-school analog phone lines. &amp;ldquo;Still using a rotary phone?&amp;rdquo; they&amp;rsquo;ll joke. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: those old-fashioned phone lines were built for clear sound and unwavering reliability. Sure, they might deteriorate over time, leading to static and eventually dropped calls. A quick fix from the phone company, though, and you&amp;rsquo;re back in business for years to come.
The modern approach is using the internet for phone calls, combining your phone and internet services onto one broadband connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Painless Way to Find Network Technicians</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</guid><description>Your company might be large and technologically advanced, utilizing an internal data network and a PBX phone system, or even a converged enterprise VoIP system. However, you may lack the resources for a dedicated IT department, let alone a telecom team. Hiring necessary services on an as-needed basis is a reality for your business. But is there a simple solution for finding contractors to handle this work?
Now there is. The solution is called the VAR Network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ignore That PBX Behind the Curtain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:31:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</guid><description>Operating a small business doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to sound like it, especially with tools like virtual PBX systems. These systems can give your two-person office the professional edge of a Fortune 500 corporation.
Traditional PBX systems, standard in large companies, offer features such as individual extensions, direct dialing, call transferring, and outside line access. However, they come with a hefty price tag. iTeleCenter, a virtual PBX solution, offers an affordable alternative that transforms your existing phones into a robust communication system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>