<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trade in Goods on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trade-in-goods/</link><description>Recent content in Trade in Goods on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trade-in-goods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration.</description></item><item><title>Negotiating the future relationship between the UK and EU: the EU's mandate for negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Thanks to Georgina Wright, of the Institute for Government, for a &amp;rsquo;track changes&amp;rsquo; version of the negotiation mandate. The usual disclaimer applies.
This week, the UK-EU future relationship negotiation process progressed. The EU Council approved the negotiation mandate, differing from the initial proposal. This post provides an updated analysis, comparing the final mandate to the political declaration, highlighting differences between the EU and UK&amp;rsquo;s positions that are expected to make negotiations difficult.</description></item></channel></rss>