<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Device on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/device/</link><description>Recent content in Device on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/device/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking.</description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones.</description></item><item><title>Wacom introduces the Wacom MobileStudio Pro, designed for demanding creative tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wacom-introduces-the-wacom-mobilestudio-pro-designed-for-demanding-creative-tasks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wacom-introduces-the-wacom-mobilestudio-pro-designed-for-demanding-creative-tasks/</guid><description>Wacom is launching the Wacom MobileStudio Pro, a new line of mobile computers designed for professional creatives who work on the go. These lightweight computers feature Wacom&amp;rsquo;s latest pen technology, including the new Wacom Pro Pen 2. With four times the accuracy and pressure sensitivity of its predecessor, the Wacom Pro Pen 2 makes the MobileStudio Pro a powerful tool for 2D, 3D, and CAD artists and designers.
The MobileStudio Pro family includes both 13.</description></item><item><title>Intel Security has released a list of the holiday gifts that are most vulnerable to hacking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</guid><description>· A survey indicates that 80% of shoppers are anticipated to make purchases online this year.
· While 85% of consumers begin utilizing connected devices within a day of obtaining them, a mere 45% report taking the appropriate security precautions.
· Despite acknowledging the significance of device security, nearly half of consumers (46%) are unsure if they are implementing adequate protective measures.
Intel Security has released its second yearly McAfee Most Hackable Holiday Gifts list, aiming to spotlight potential security vulnerabilities linked to popular gift items this holiday season.</description></item><item><title>Enhance car safety with 360-degree hands-free device viewing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</guid><description>Sprint-Cass, the sole distributor of Taiwanese brand Digidock in Singapore, is introducing a new line of Digidock mobile device holders for vehicles at IT Show 2015, happening from March 19th to 22nd at the Suntec Convention Centre. These holders are designed for cars, motorcycles, and bicycles.
Every Digidock holder features a 360-degree swivel joint, allowing users to securely position their smartphones or tablets at any desired angle. Engineered for simple attachment and removal, the holders come with interchangeable cradles and universal mounts.</description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading.</description></item><item><title>Smartfren Android users will receive a smart start screen from Celltick</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
The MySmartfren app.
Celltick, a company that provides mobile marketing solutions, has teamed up with Indonesian telecommunications company Smartfren Telekom (Smartfren) to introduce a smart home screen for Android users.
Smartfren aims to give its 12 million subscribers quick access to their most-used apps and features, along with special deals. This will be achieved through a personalized version of Celltick&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Start&amp;rdquo; app, pre-installed on Smartfren Android devices.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here.</description></item><item><title>HP introduces the thinnest laptop in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</guid><description>Every Spectre accessory has been designed to provide a luxurious experience.
The CNC machined aluminum body is as sleek as an AAA battery at a mere 10.4mm. Enjoy exceptional performance with Intel Core i5 and i7 processors. Immerse yourself in the vibrant visuals of a full HD 13.3&amp;quot; edge-to-edge display complemented by Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen sound. HP claims to have developed the slimmest laptop globally, meticulously refining every detail to provide an unmatched user experience and peak performance.</description></item><item><title>HP updates Pavilion features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pavilion PCs, including convertibles and notebooks, designed to be stylish and powerful. The company aims to provide customers with a range of options to suit their needs and budgets.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that HP understands customers&amp;rsquo; diverse needs, with some prioritizing portability and others seeking performance. The redesigned Pavilion PCs cater to both, offering affordability and style.</description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5.</description></item><item><title>Cisco has launched new personal hardware to improve collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</guid><description>At Cisco Live! 2014 in the US, Cisco unveiled new personal collaboration tools. The company recognizes that teamwork often spans continents, demanding tools that enable seamless and immediate collaboration, regardless of location.
Source: Cisco. The Cisco DX80 in action.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution comes in the form of the DX70 and DX80 desktop collaboration devices. These Android-based devices act as hubs for collaboration tools and applications. Featuring large touch screens, the DX70 and DX80 combine Cisco&amp;rsquo;s expertise in HD video, high-quality audio, and web conferencing with integrated business applications and web browsing.</description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure.</description></item><item><title>IDC reveals the preferences of APAC consumers when it comes to mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 05:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</guid><description>The International Data Corporation (IDC) has released an infographic that reveals how consumers in the Asia Pacific region make decisions about mobile devices. Key findings from the Essential Guide to Device Decisions of a Connected Consumer in Asia Pacific report include:
Source: IDC infographic. What consumers like about bigger phone screens.
77% of surveyed consumers reported having a larger smartphone now than their previous device, while only 8% opted for a smaller one.</description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time).</description></item><item><title>Acer introduces new convertible notebooks, the Aspire R 13 and R 14</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</guid><description>Acer has introduced two new convertible notebook lines, the Aspire R 13 and Aspire R 14 Series, both capable of transitioning between various notebook and tablet modes. These notebooks are designed for users seeking the functionality of a traditional notebook with added flexibility.
Source: Acer. The R 13 in one mode.
Acer&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Jason Chen, stated that their objective is to exceed expectations with their products at every price point. He believes these Aspire convertibles are ideal for users who require both portability and productivity.</description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping.</description></item><item><title>Sophos has simplified the process of securing corporate information on mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Source: Sophos website.
Sophos recently launched Sophos Mobile Control 5 (SMC 5), a software solution designed to differentiate personal and company data on devices to enhance corporate data security.
Managing devices like laptops, tablets, and smartphones often involves individual configuration, updates, and management. SMC 5 simplifies this process for IT administrators by allowing them to establish user-specific rules once to protect company data stored on the device or in personal cloud storage.</description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Science Park 1 will be testing a program for sharing personal mobility devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</guid><description>Ascendas-Singbridge Group, a leading provider of sustainable urban and business space solutions in Asia, has partnered with Neuron Mobility, a smart transportation solutions provider, to pilot a personal mobility device (PMD) sharing program at Singapore Science Park 1. This six-month trial reflects the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing accessibility and convenience for tenants, employees, and visitors within the park.
Starting June 14, 2017, fifty GPS-equipped e-scooters and twenty bicycles will be available for rent at six designated parking zones throughout Singapore Science Park 1.</description></item><item><title>HP introduces two phablets in the Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 05:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new mobile devices to their collection: the 6-inch HP Slate6 VoiceTab and the 7-inch HP Slate7 VoiceTab. These &amp;ldquo;voice tablets&amp;rdquo; will be released in India this February*.
These devices combine the functions of a phone and a tablet into one portable design. “The voice tablet market is growing because consumers want to combine their phones and tablets into one device,” said Ron Coughlin, Senior VP of HP&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Personal Systems Group.</description></item></channel></rss>