<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mall on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mall/</link><description>Recent content in Mall on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Join us at Smile Singapore in Clarke Quay Central and share your beautiful smile with us!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</guid><description>The installation of the Smile project at Clarke Quay Central is currently underway.
Clarke Quay Central mall is promoting a happier Singapore with its Smile Singapore campaign. Launched as part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Jubilee celebrations, this project gives companies a platform to share their happy moments in the nation.
Caine Teo, head of Ape Works, the Creative Partner of the Smile Singapore Campaign, believes happiness is infectious. By showcasing pictures of smiling faces, they hope to remind Singaporeans of the many reasons to smile in their country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ICSC's Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards honor D-Cube City, Jem, and Siam Center with gold awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</guid><description>The International Council of Shopping Centers (ICSC) Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards recently celebrated excellence in the region&amp;rsquo;s shopping center industry. Awards recognized outstanding achievements in marketing, retail property design and development, and retail store design.
The Design &amp;amp; Development category acknowledges retail properties for their overall design quality and development creativity, whether through renovation or expansion of an existing property or the innovative design of a new retail project. This category includes both new developments and renovations &amp;amp; expansions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New retail and dining tenants have been announced at City Square Mall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</guid><description>City Developments (CDL) is updating the dining and retail options at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s City Square Mall.
The Decathlon store at City Square Mall, taken on 21 May.
French sporting goods retailer, Decathlon, launched its first Singaporean store on May 21, 2016. The company, known for its wide selection and reasonable prices, aims to make sports accessible.
“Our 21,500 sq ft store carries over 85,000 innovative, high-quality products across 50 sports. It will help Decathlon achieve its mission of making sports accessible to every Singaporean,” remarked Bastien Grandgeorge, CEO of Decathlon Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>