<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gigabit Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Gigabit Ethernet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Makes the Upgrades Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has always been a popular choice for businesses, particularly those requiring high-speed connections. The good news is that fiber optic service is becoming increasingly accessible to businesses. IT managers and executives now face a decision: stick with their existing copper wireline services or upgrade to fiber optics. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the factors that make fiber optics the preferred choice.
Fiber Optics: The Way of the Future..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Colo Bandwidth Pricing Is Lowest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</guid><description>Intrigued by the idea of significantly cheaper bandwidth? Take a look at the pricing for colocation bandwidth and see for yourself.
It&amp;rsquo;s tempting, right? The cost per Mbps at a colocation center is often much lower than standard bandwidth costs for your servers, even with a discounted rate from a telecom broker. While this might seem unfair, it&amp;rsquo;s simply a matter of economics.
Colocation facilities can offer these reduced costs for a couple of reasons...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thirty Carriers, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</guid><description>Are you overwhelmed and frustrated with your current telecommunications services? Do you feel stuck with your local phone or internet provider and dread seeing your monthly bill?
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to endure this! You deserve a wide range of choices for your voice and data communication needs. Imagine having access to 30 different business-grade carriers, offering everything from basic phone lines to high-speed internet options like wireless and satellite.
Whether you need ISDN PRI lines for your office phone system, MPLS networks to connect multiple locations, or Gigabit Ethernet for high-bandwidth applications like video conferencing, you have options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Welcome To The Big Bandwidth Era</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 17:07:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</guid><description>Remember the days of big band music? While many may not be familiar with that era, technology has dramatically changed since then. We&amp;rsquo;ve moved from radio and kilocycles to the digital age with bandwidth measured in Mbps and Gbps. This is the era of big bandwidth.
But what exactly qualifies as &amp;ldquo;big bandwidth&amp;rdquo;? NuVox, a leading telecommunications company, defines it as any bandwidth exceeding 10 Mbps. This speed is the target for home internet providers as video streaming gains popularity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 GigE in the Long Run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/</guid><description>As internet and private network users demand increasingly higher bandwidth, long-haul fiber optic networks, including those used by regional and national carriers, are being upgraded to accommodate this growth. The current standard is 40 Gbps, but companies like XO Communications and Infinera are pushing boundaries by showcasing 100 Gigabit Ethernet on XO&amp;rsquo;s long-haul DWDM network.
This partnership addresses two key requirements: a high-capacity long-haul network and equipment capable of utilizing that capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gig E WAN Comes To The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</guid><description>It may seem surprising, but businesses can now access 10 Gigabit Ethernet connections for their wide area networks. What&amp;rsquo;s even more surprising is how many businesses can actually utilize this bandwidth.
Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular among large corporations and tech companies that need to manage and deliver massive amounts of data quickly. What kinds of companies are we talking about?
For those involved in video production or editing, Gigabit per second connections are essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (EoDWDM)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</guid><description>Large organizations with high bandwidth needs, such as financial institutions and research labs, often require more capacity than standard telecom services offer. Building a custom fiber network by installing owned or leased dark fiber is one solution. Another is leasing wavelengths on existing fiber infrastructure.
Your Own Fiber Installing fiber optic cable on your own property provides control over both the physical space and network assets. However, construction costs increase significantly beyond your premises, especially when obtaining right-of-way permissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Curb and Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Copper is quickly disappearing from telecommunications networks, being replaced by fiber optic cabling. While this new cabling might be installed in the same spaces as the old copper, the outdated copper lines are often left behind.
You might be thinking, &amp;ldquo;But I still use copper connections!&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s true that many devices use copper wiring. So where exactly is all this fiber?
Mostly Fiber Outside, Mostly Copper Inside..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why You Want A GigE Port</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</guid><description>Is it difficult to predict your future bandwidth requirements? You might be aware of your current traffic levels, but what about tomorrow, next week, or during peak seasons like holidays? How can you plan for the unknown?
Inaccurate bandwidth estimations can lead to overspending on unused capacity or, even worse, business losses due to insufficient bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to optimize your bandwidth allocation.
Traditional telecom services often come with lengthy installation and upgrade processes, making them inflexible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth For Remote Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</guid><description>Businesses need to have a solid plan to safeguard their important data. While basic backups on disks or tapes can help with minor issues like a crashed computer, they are inadequate for major events like natural disasters. Offsite backup is crucial in these situations.
The key is choosing a location geographically distant from your primary site to avoid shared risks. Backing up data across regional offices, separated by significant distances, enhances data protection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Iomega Zips Into Network Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</guid><description>Do you recall the Zip drive? When floppy disks were the standard for backups, Zip drives offered a remarkable hundredfold increase in capacity using removable cartridges. While hard drives now boast hundreds of gigabytes and beyond, leaving floppies and even Zip disks in the past, Iomega, the company behind the Zip drive, has continued to innovate. Their product line has expanded beyond desktops and into the server room.
Iomega, now a part of EMC, a Fortune 500 company specializing in enterprise storage solutions, still caters to individuals and small offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Communications Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 06:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a common understanding that our capacity for using twisted pair copper for bandwidth is reaching its limit. We&amp;rsquo;re even facing a serious shortage of wireless bandwidth. The Federal Communications Commission is searching for underused frequencies to allocate for wireless broadband. However, the idea that technology might stall due to depleted spectral resources is misguided if we consider an innovative solution.
Radio frequencies are a finite resource. Lower frequencies are less useful due to their limited capacity for carrying information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There Will Be Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</guid><description>The 19th and 20th centuries were defined by the gold rush and oil boom, respectively. Similarly, the 21st century is witnessing a fiber optic revolution. Fiber optic communication has become essential for modern businesses. This era presents lucrative opportunities for entrepreneurs to capitalize on the insatiable demand for high-bandwidth communication. A new technology has emerged, promising to reshape the competitive landscape.
Consider a scenario where two telecommunications providers are discussing the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigE For Business Not So Far-Fetched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</guid><description>The increasing demands of online technologies, particularly those using graphics and video, are putting pressure on Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. While ordering a T1 line was once a big decision, businesses may soon need to consider Gigabit Ethernet connections.
While Gigabit Ethernet is often associated with large-scale networks, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly relevant for businesses. With corporate LANs already transitioning to faster speeds, the WAN connection often becomes a bottleneck...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need Bandwidth on Demand?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When subscribing to bandwidth, you&amp;rsquo;re usually expected to understand your network&amp;rsquo;s needs and pick the optimal service. But what if your needs are unclear or fluctuate? What about transitioning from in-house IT to cloud-based services? What are the consequences of an incorrect choice?
Traditional Bandwidth Services Fall Short
Conventional line contracts offer fixed bandwidth for a predetermined period, like a DS3 connection providing 45 Mbps constantly. While this guarantees consistent speed, you pay even when it&amp;rsquo;s idle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100, 1000, 10000 Mbps Internet Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As technology progresses, businesses require significantly faster internet speeds. Our Wide Area Networks (WANs) are now crucial for operations. Today, internet connections of 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps, and even 10,000 Mbps are standard and essential. Fortunately, pricing has decreased as speeds have increased, making these bandwidth levels attainable.
100 Mbps Fast Ethernet
100 Mbps is the current standard bandwidth, replacing the older 45 Mbps DS3 bandwidth. DS3, an upgrade from slower T1 lines, is part of the TDM telecom standard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why GHz is So Last Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 09:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</guid><description>GigaHertz, representing a billion cycles per second, has become the standard, making MegaHertz seem outdated. However, as technology advances, even GigaHertz might be surpassed by TeraHertz speeds, potentially rendering current benchmarks obsolete.
In the early days of personal computers, 640 KB of RAM seemed excessive. However, as software evolved, demanding more resources with graphics, images, and the rise of the internet, hardware struggled to keep up. It took decades for platforms to mature and offer sufficient RAM, hard drive space, and processor speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigaMAN and Gigabit Ethernet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</guid><description>Organizations in need of truly fast wide area network connections should consider gigabit Ethernet services like GigaMAN. These high-bandwidth circuits are now more affordable than ever.
Ethernet WAN services are a newer option for businesses and organizations, offering end-to-end Ethernet protocol signal maintenance. This eliminates the need for protocol conversion between a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN and traditional TDM telco circuits.
Ethernet speeds range from 10 Mbps (standard) to 100 Mbps (Fast Ethernet) and 1000 Mbps (Gigabit Ethernet)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Video-Film Production Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 18:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</guid><description>The shift to digital video and film production has made it possible to work with collaborators across the globe. While physical delivery of tapes and disks is an option, tight production timelines often necessitate electronic file transfer. This, however, raises questions about how to carry out the process and the associated costs.
Bandwidth is the defining feature of digital transfer services, representing the transmission speed in bits per second. It&amp;rsquo;s typically measured in Mbps or Gbps, and generally speaking, a higher bandwidth comes with a higher price tag...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Can GigE Bandwidth Do For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly common in local area networks, with network cards and backbones now supporting these higher speeds. Companies that rely heavily on digital processes and high bandwidth data transfers are likely already using Gigabit Ethernet. However, they need a way to extend these high-speed transfers beyond their local networks.
Companies with large numbers of employees, extensive customer bases, or applications that generate significant amounts of data can benefit from Gigabit Ethernet WAN connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Fiber Lit Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 18:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</guid><description>To secure high bandwidth at affordable rates, you need to be in a &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; building. This term refers to buildings equipped with active fiber optic bandwidth services, utilizing laser light to transmit data through fiber optic strands.
If your building is &amp;ldquo;lit,&amp;rdquo; obtaining fiber optic bandwidth is typically straightforward, though construction costs might apply if cabling to your space is absent. However, a bigger challenge arises if your building lacks fiber optic connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Network For Orange County</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a rising demand for high-bandwidth, low-latency internet connectivity from businesses, particularly in sectors like finance, automation, cloud computing, and medical imaging. This surge is driving the expansion of fiber optic networks, with a prime example being the ongoing development in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
AboveNet, a prominent fiber optic network provider in the US and Europe, is constructing a major &amp;ldquo;feeder ring&amp;rdquo; in Orange County, California. This ring will connect various business locations, including office buildings, data centers, and carrier hotels, to an existing fiber optic backbone already serving the Irvine and Costa Mesa business districts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Connectivity Options For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</guid><description>Most medium to large businesses, and even some smaller ones with high bandwidth needs, can now afford fiber optic bandwidth. This is due to lower prices and a wider range of options, which is great news for those who need a lot of bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of these options that you may not be aware of.
Fiber optic bandwidth services generally fall into two categories: traditional time division multiplexed technology, originating from telephone company research, and newer IP-centric networks offered by both competitive service providers and traditional telecom carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Leads in High Bandwidth Ethernet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 22:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a significant change in high-bandwidth services, moving away from older SONET/SDH technology and towards Ethernet IP technology. This shift, driven by the long-term transition from analog to digital communications and the widespread use of Ethernet, could indicate a turning point for Ethernet in fiber optic communication, as argued by AboveNet.
AboveNet, a provider of high-bandwidth services in 15 major U.S. markets and the UK, specializes in fiber optic MAN and WAN connectivity, offering speeds from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps at lower prices than traditional telecom providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Same Budget, More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Is Slow Network Speed Affecting Your Business?
Are you experiencing frustrating network issues like slow downloads, choppy calls, interrupted streaming, and sluggish website loading?
Do You Need More Bandwidth?
There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance your internet connection needs more bandwidth. While your internal network might be fast enough, your external connection (WAN) might not be able to handle your current needs.
Signs You Need More Bandwidth
If your internet service hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years but your business relies more on multimedia and online tools, you probably need more bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Lit Towers Improving Rural Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 16:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</guid><description>Living outside the city limits often means limited internet options. While options like 3G and satellite exist, they come with slow speeds and download caps. Businesses might have access to slightly better choices like T1 lines, but high-speed options are generally nonexistent.
Rural areas face a digital disadvantage compared to cities where gigabit and even 10 gigabit ethernet connections are readily available. Fixed wireless and cable options also offer much faster speeds in these areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Competitive Fiber Optic Service Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</guid><description>Does your company use a lot of bandwidth? We&amp;rsquo;re talking 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps or more of reliable, commercial-grade bandwidth. If so, bonded T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper won&amp;rsquo;t cut it. You need fiber optic service. But is competitive fiber optic bandwidth an option in your area? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out&amp;hellip;
The reality is that buildings equipped for fiber optic service are appearing faster than ever. Why? Because today&amp;rsquo;s data-heavy applications need increasingly faster network speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Topology Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</guid><description>Businesses have various choices for connecting their branch offices, franchisees, suppliers, customers, and remote employees. The ideal network structure depends on the specific goals, whether it&amp;rsquo;s basic off-site backups or creating a virtual company spanning multiple states. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some prevalent WAN topologies used today.
The most widespread WAN is the Internet, connecting almost everyone everywhere. It&amp;rsquo;s a massive mesh network with affordable connections available through various methods like wireline, wireless, and fiber optic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>