<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>German Constitution on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/german-constitution/</link><description>Recent content in German Constitution on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/german-constitution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Battle of the Legal Giants: Can the Euro endure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The German Federal Constitutional Court (BVerfG) has finally submitted a legal question to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on a critically important issue: the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) policy. This policy is widely credited with saving the EU&amp;rsquo;s single currency. If either court finds the policy unlawful, the euro&amp;rsquo;s continued existence could be in jeopardy.
In simple terms, the OMT is a 2012 commitment by the ECB to buy government bonds from struggling eurozone countries on secondary markets (from banks and financial institutions)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New developments in EU case law regarding extradition to non-EU countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A recent European Court of Justice (ECJ) decision in the Pisciotti case concerning the extradition of citizens from one EU Member State to a non-EU country (in this instance, the USA) provides further legal precedent in this domain and carries potential implications for Brexit. This ruling expands on the September 2016 Petruhhin judgment, which dealt with extraditing citizens from one EU Member State to Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Arrest Warrant and the German Constitutional Court: A new development in the legal conversation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The German Constitutional Court (GCC) has issued another impactful ruling, this time concerning fundamental rights. In an order published yesterday, the GCC exercised its authority to review the implementation of a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) from Italy to Germany. The subject, a US citizen convicted in Italy in absentia, argued that his conviction lacked due process and that Italian law provided no recourse for appeal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mario's feet were pulled out from under him by the BVerfG and the ECB's OMT programme.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</guid><description>By Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster
The German Constitutional Court (BVerfG) is set to make a significant decision on the European Union&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union on June 21st. The court will rule on the Gauweiler case, which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. This program, designed to stabilize struggling Eurozone economies, was challenged by plaintiffs questioning its legal foundation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>