<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4G on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g/</link><description>Recent content in 4G on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is The End Of Cellular Phone Near?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</guid><description>Cell phones are essential to modern life, but a recent development calls into question the future of cellular service. The release of the Apple iPad and its allowance of VoIP applications over 3G cellular networks, along with AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network adjustments for this capability, signal a potential shift in the telecommunications landscape.
Why is this significant? Cellular networks have historically blocked VoIP due to its potential to congest networks and cannibalize voice call revenue.</description></item><item><title>How Maestro Smart Antenna Improves Fixed Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</guid><description>Accel Technologies, a branch of Accel Networks, is launching a groundbreaking product for fixed wireless connections: the Maestro smart antenna system. Maestro aims to make 3G and 4G fixed wireless broadband a more attractive alternative to pricier business connectivity options like T1, MPLS, VSAT, Frame Relay, and point-to-point microwave services.
What makes Maestro so special? Like other smart devices, Maestro utilizes active technology to enhance performance. In this situation, it improves the performance of a typically passive component: the RF antenna.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit WiFi For Video Streaming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</guid><description>WiFi has become the standard wireless connection due to its widespread availability, outpacing technologies like Bluetooth and WiMax. While cellular data is useful in the absence of WiFi, its limited bandwidth and potential for overage charges make it a secondary choice. In fact, data shows that most tablet users don&amp;rsquo;t even utilize their device&amp;rsquo;s cellular capabilities. WiFi&amp;rsquo;s strength is evident in its ability to not only replace cellular broadband but also wired connections.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Access Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</guid><description>Consumers access the internet in various ways, and businesses have similar options, along with some exclusive ones. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the choices available for companies at their business locations.
Popular consumer broadband choices include DSL and cable for stationary setups, and 3G for mobile use. 4G wireless is emerging, with providers like CLEAR offering it for both fixed and mobile applications. In remote areas, satellite broadband delivers connectivity where wires can&amp;rsquo;t reach.</description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service.</description></item><item><title>Speedier Network For The iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</guid><description>While the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s popularity is a boon for AT&amp;amp;T, which holds the exclusive contract, the device&amp;rsquo;s data demands present a significant hurdle.
Historically, cellular towers primarily handled voice calls, with data as a secondary function. Early data speeds were adequate for text-based services, but the advent of camera phones, web browsers, and video streaming dramatically increased bandwidth requirements. Today&amp;rsquo;s users demand home and work-level speeds, typically between 3 to 10 Mbps, far exceeding the capabilities of older networks.</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds.</description></item><item><title>Tripping the LTE Fantastic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</guid><description>Although fiber optic and mobile WiMAX are getting a lot of attention, LTE could become the next major broadband technology. Could gigabit wireless communication be on the horizon?
People struggling with slow 1G connections or the first iPhone might find the idea of 1,000 Mbps speeds on their mobile devices unrealistic. It seems like there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough bandwidth from cell towers. However, emerging technologies may increase wireless bandwidth significantly.</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>Digi introduces 4G LTE service in Johor Bahru, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Pictured at the launch of Digi&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE service in Johor Bahru are (from left): Tuan Haji Rizal B. Abd Malek, Regional Head of the Malaysian Communications and Multimedia Commission (SKMM) Southern Region; Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer; YB Datuk Ir Haji Hasni B Haji Mohammad, Chairman of the Johor Executive Council for Public Works, Rural and Regional Development; Digi’s Chief Network Officer Kesavan Sivabalan; and Ng Chak Khin, Digi’s Head of Southern Region.</description></item><item><title>Indosat Ooredoo introduces nationwide 4G-LTE service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo.
Indosat Ooredoo has introduced its high-speed 4G-LTE service across Indonesia. The company stated that the improved connectivity and call clarity offered by its new 4Gplus data network come at the same cost as its existing 3G services.
In the last two years, Indosat Ooredoo has doubled its network speeds, achieving the fastest 3G internet speeds available. Independent tests show its 4Gplus service can reach download speeds of up to 185Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G2 With Google is 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</guid><description>T-Mobile is raising the bar for smartphones with its new G2, a Google phone that seamlessly integrates with Google Voice. This allows for voicemails to be converted to text and read like emails or texts.
Powered by Android 2.2, the G2 boasts a 3.7-inch full touch screen with seven customizable home panels. Users can personalize their experience with thousands of apps and widgets from the Android Market.
One of the G2&amp;rsquo;s standout features is its Adobe Flash Player, unlike a well-known competitor.</description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 510 provides budget-friendly LTE capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 22:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</guid><description>HTC&amp;rsquo;s most budget-friendly LTE smartphone is hitting the shelves just days after the company launched the Desire 210 in Singapore. Starting September 6, 2014, you can find the HTC Desire 510 at mobile carriers and major retailers across Singapore. This device boasts a quad-core LTE processor, a 4.7” display, and runs on Android 4.4.
Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;While the industry has been buzzing about the impact of 4G, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook that only a handful of high-end devices truly utilize this technology,&amp;rdquo; says HTC CEO, Peter Chou.</description></item><item><title>The Samsung Epic 4G offers Epic Performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 17:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</guid><description>Imagine a smartphone so powerful it surpasses a netbook. Picture yourself declining WiFi because your cellular connection is faster. That&amp;rsquo;s the kind of speed the Samsung Epic 4G offers with its impressive 10+ Mbps download speeds, thanks to the Sprint WiMAX 4G network. You can even share your connection as a mobile hotspot for your other devices.
Beyond speed, the Epic boasts a stunning Super AMOLED touchscreen display with near-HD quality and unmatched contrast.</description></item><item><title>XOHM, XOHM's Got The Range</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</guid><description>Sprint&amp;rsquo;s XOHM (pronounced &amp;ldquo;zome,&amp;rdquo; like &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;) wireless broadband service has launched in Baltimore, marking the start of the highly anticipated rollout of WiMAX as the next generation of high-speed internet. If Sprint successfully implements its 4G vision, WiFi hotspots could become obsolete. DSL? Cable? Why bother with wires when you can have the freedom of wireless connectivity?
This vision relies on a new wireless technology standardized for global use in both fixed and mobile applications.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2.</description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet Broadband For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>When considering broadband, we usually think of DSL, cable internet, or cellular wireless. However, these options are typically consumer-grade and might not be suitable for business needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why these services might be frustrating for businesses and examine a promising alternative.
Cellular wireless, including 3G and 4G, relies on cell towers with limited bandwidth shared among many users. Smartphones consume significant bandwidth, and a high concentration of devices can overload the network.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices.</description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Cell phones today are capable of much more than just voice calls. The mobile networks have evolved to carry both voice and data, offering wireless broadband internet access that rivals DSL and cable connections.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t explored mobile internet recently, you might be surprised by its speed and availability. Currently, two competing systems are widely available, with two even faster networks in their early stages.
AT&amp;amp;T promotes its HSDPA and EDGE networks, notably featuring the Apple iPhone.</description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues.</description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>