<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Financing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financing/</link><description>Recent content in Financing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:59:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UOB discovers misunderstandings about financing options for small and medium businesses in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: UOB infographic. Statistics gathered from the Financing for Startups and Small Businesses Survey.
A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB) revealed that a significant number of startups and small businesses in Singapore lack a comprehensive understanding of the alternative funding options available to them for early expansion. These businesses are also uncertain about how to effectively utilize options such as venture capital, venture debt, and debt and equity crowdfunding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Terhal by Bank Muscat provides financing for travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</guid><description>To celebrate the summer holidays (from Q2 to Q3) and the upcoming Eid al Fitr, Bank Muscat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Terhal,&amp;rdquo; a new set of travel services combined with banking features. This initiative reflects the bank&amp;rsquo;s motto, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s do more,&amp;rdquo; and aims to offer a unique banking experience for customers who enjoy traveling.
Terhal provides customers with access to financing up to RO10,000 at a 3.5% interest rate, repayable over a year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces the Bunyani financing campaign for completion works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new campaign called &amp;ldquo;Bunyani&amp;hellip; from skeleton structure to delivery&amp;rdquo; to provide financing options for owners of residential, investment, and industrial land plots. This campaign aims to help customers complete various construction phases, including finishing works, maintenance, and restoration.
Ahmad Al-Khaled, Deputy General Manager Commercial Services at KFH, stated that the campaign offers clients simplified financing solutions. These include financing of up to KD70,000, a repayment period of 15 years, a grace period of 12 months for the first installment, and a competitive profit rate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-the-bunyani-financing-campaign-for-completion-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has relaxed its requirements for car loans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 08:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) announced adjustments to loan regulations for motor vehicles. The maximum loan-to-value (LTV) ratios and allowable loan durations will be relaxed, but some limitations will remain indefinitely.
These changes come after three years of sustained moderation in Certificate of Entitlement (COE) premiums and related inflationary pressures.
Financial institutions&amp;rsquo; motor vehicle loan restrictions were implemented in 2013 to control car and COE demand and reduce inflationary pressures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean financial technology company is striving to provide improved lending terms for business-to-business transactions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</guid><description>A Singapore-based fintech startup, Cash-IN-Asia, has introduced a new business-to-business (B2B) lending platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s fully digital approach lets business owners secure financing directly from their mobile devices.
Cash-IN-Asia aims to support micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in Singapore. The company offers products designed to meet current needs and help these businesses thrive even after the current economic challenges.
Their ISO27001-certified platform leverages artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics to deliver a comprehensive solution for MSMEs seeking transparent and flexible financing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>