<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Currency on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-currency/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Currency on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-currency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LEOCoin launches LEOxCHANGE in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: LEOxCHANGE. Andersson speaks at the launch of LEOxCHANGE in Hong Kong, emphasizing the high security of LEOCoin and its ability to protect consumer privacy.
A new digital currency has entered the market. Launched in London on March 25, 2015, LEOCoin is reportedly recognized by other digital currency exchanges and boasts the support of approximately 100,000 entrepreneurs.
The company behind LEOCoin, UK-based LEO (Learning Enterprises Organisation), provides entrepreneurship and leadership training via online tutoring, e-learning platforms, and in-person seminars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leocoin-launches-leoxchange-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Challenges of Implementing the Digital Euro by the Central Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:21:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</guid><description>Dr. (Annelieke) Anne Marieke Mooij, Tilburg University
The European Central Bank (ECB) is preparing to introduce a digital euro, a central bank digital currency (CBDC). The ECB has explored several design options, ranging from restricted access for financial institutions to broad accessibility for all consumers via national central banks. While a final design hasn&amp;rsquo;t been chosen, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s statements suggest a preference for broader accessibility. This blog post will examine the primary legal hurdles associated with each design option...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>