<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SONET/SDH on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sonet/sdh/</link><description>Recent content in SONET/SDH on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sonet/sdh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item></channel></rss>