<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wavelength Division Multiplexing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wavelength-division-multiplexing/</link><description>Recent content in Wavelength Division Multiplexing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wavelength-division-multiplexing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Many Wavelengths to Serve You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</guid><description>When your network reaches its maximum capacity, you typically need to upgrade to a faster network with faster components. Upgrading your entire network infrastructure can be extremely expensive. However, with fiber optic networks, you can significantly increase bandwidth within the same cables using a technique called Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM).
WDM allows multiple light beams to transmit data simultaneously over a single fiber optic cable. Each beam operates on a different wavelength, increasing capacity proportionally to the number of beams.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Networks Need Denser Wavelength Multiplexing To Meet Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</guid><description>Despite the economic downturn, fiber optic network providers are experiencing a surge in demand. However, instead of widespread digging, they are leveraging technology to boost capacity on existing infrastructure.
XO Communications, a leading fiber optic network provider, recently revealed plans to double its capacity per fiber strand using Infinera&amp;rsquo;s optical line equipment. The Infinera Line System 2 increases the channel count for C-band fiber optic systems from 80 to 160, resulting in an extra 1.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward.</description></item></channel></rss>