<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/service/</link><description>Recent content in Service on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA announces transport service timings for Eid al Fitr holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) has released the operating schedules for its services during the Eid al-Fitr holidays. The schedule covers various services, including customer service centers, parking, public buses, Dubai Metro and Tram, marine transit, driving institutes, and vehicle testing and registration centers.
Source: RTA. Al Marri.
Moaza Al Marri, RTA&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communication, stated that Customer Service Centers will be closed for the Eid al-Fitr holiday from Sunday, July 3rd, 2016, and will reopen on Sunday, July 10th, 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces music services that do not use data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</guid><description>Singtel debuted its Singtel Music service, a first-of-its-kind offering in Singapore. For a fixed monthly price, subscribers gain access to music from Spotify, KKBOX, AMPed, and MeRadio without incurring data charges.
Representatives from Singtel Music at the launch event.
Singtel Music provides premium accounts from Spotify, KKBOX, or AMPed, enabling users to stream an extensive library of songs without data usage concerns. Additionally, they can enjoy 13 MeRadio stations without impacting their data allowance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collective Works and CapitaLand are teaming up to launch a new coworking space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</guid><description>Artist&amp;rsquo;s impression of the new coworking space at Capital Tower, Singapore.
A new high-end coworking space will be launched on the 12th floor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Capital Tower. This joint venture between two companies will occupy 22,000 square feet and support 250 businesses. The space is adaptable and caters to a variety of businesses, from new startups to large corporations. Technological features include secure server hosting, video conferencing, internet phone services, and fiber optic broadband internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Limited edition experiences are a popular trend in the food service industry in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</guid><description>In 2015, Australian diners increasingly embraced their inner foodies, craving novel culinary experiences. Food service operators responded with innovation, experimenting with formats, menus, and dining concepts, according to a Euromonitor blog post.
One example highlighted by the research firm is Hotel Marriott in Melbourne&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Table for 12&amp;rdquo; concept, launched in October 2015. This exclusive dining experience offered a four-course degustation menu for a limited group of twelve guests, available only one night a week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-disciplinary conversations are reshaping the service economy at KODW 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Pictured at the KODW 2021 opening ceremony are (from left) Lofai Lo (Director and GM, ViuTV); Dr Lay Lian Ong (Principal, Hong Kong Design Institute &amp;amp; Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education); Victor Tsang (Head of Create Hong Kong); Professor Eric Yim (Chairman of Hong Kong Design Centre); guest of honor The Honourable Edward Yau (Secretary for Commerce and Economic Development); Victor Lo (Chairman, KODW Steering Committee of Hong Kong Design Centre); Professor Kun-Pyo Lee (Dean of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Design), and Dr Edmund Lee (Executive Director of Hong Kong Design Centre)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ERC has opened a co-working space in multiple cities across Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</guid><description>The University Mentorship program will connect lecturers with the BIG Work community to offer guidance. Users can utilize ERC&amp;rsquo;s expertise in various business areas and schedule consultations with program managers and resource advisors Guests at the BIG Hotel, catering to international and startup business travelers, will have early access to new hospitality-related products and services for research. Entrepreneur Resource Centre Holdings (ERC) has launched BIG Work, a new co-working space with locations in Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Foodpanda has introduced a high-end delivery service in the Central Business District of Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</guid><description>Source: foodpanda website.
In celebration of its third anniversary in Singapore, foodpanda Singapore has introduced a premium delivery service. This service includes approximately 50 restaurants and covers the central business district. It aims to serve busy professionals who want diverse food choices delivered directly to their workplaces.
Launched a month after securing US$110 million in funding, this new service reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing user experience and customer service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2024, 80% of service professionals in Singapore anticipate that customer service will play a larger role in generating revenue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</guid><description>A recent Salesforce report highlights the growing expectation for customer service to become a significant revenue driver in 2024. The report suggests that AI-powered personalized customer experiences empower service teams to capitalize on upselling, cross-selling, and customer retention to boost revenue.
This new &amp;ldquo;State of Service&amp;rdquo; report is based on insights from over 5,500 service professionals globally, including 100 from Singapore. It examines current trends, challenges, and strategies shaping the customer service landscape, emphasizing how service teams utilize AI and data to enhance revenue, efficiency, and customer satisfaction amidst rising customer expectations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has launched a new mobile broadband service called DataPass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</guid><description>HP has introduced new technology designed for business travelers in the Asia Pacific region called HP DataPass.
&amp;ldquo;In today&amp;rsquo;s constantly connected, fast-moving, and virtual business world, new opportunities are emerging for businesses and individuals,&amp;rdquo; said Nick Lazaridis, Senior VP, Printing and Personal Systems, and Managing Director of HP Asia Pacific and Japan. &amp;ldquo;At HP, our focus is on developing innovations that provide the best possible customer experience while creating opportunities for our customers to transition to the New Style of IT...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is dedicated to improving its services and is now providing Better Thursdays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 03:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. The new logo at Singtel headquarters in Singapore.
Singtel recently introduced a refreshed brand identity, the first update in 16 years, with the tagline &amp;ldquo;Let’s make everyday better&amp;rdquo;. This signifies a new chapter in Singtel’s evolution beyond traditional telecommunications, expanding into multimedia and ICT services.
Chua Sock Koong, Singtel Group CEO, stated: “Singtel is a familiar name for many generations in Singapore. We are seen as a dependable and trusted brand at the forefront of technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-dedicated-to-improving-its-services-and-is-now-providing-better-thursdays/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Giftano improves the experience of giving gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</guid><description>Giftano, a Singapore-based online gifting platform, has expanded its offerings to include a complete online gifting solution. In addition to their existing digital gift card selection, Giftano now features &amp;ldquo;Giftano Gifts,&amp;rdquo; a curated marketplace for physical presents.
Giftano aims to provide a seamless and personalized online gifting experience, especially with the holiday season approaching. The company has improved its platform by adding a user-friendly search engine and features that allow for custom gift cards and various delivery choices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Helion offers enterprise-level cloud services tailored for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Helion Managed Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Lean, a service designed to support cloud-based applications for medium and large businesses. This service is suitable for purposes like application development and testing, as well as collaborative work environments.
This managed infrastructure solution allows smaller companies to adopt cloud technology swiftly and scale their usage as needed, all at a lower price point than previous HP Helion managed services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>