<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wi-Fi on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wi-fi/</link><description>Recent content in Wi-Fi on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wi-fi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration.</description></item><item><title>Access free Wi-Fi at more than 200,000 hotspots throughout Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 21:28:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</guid><description>Source: Wire and Wireless Company. The logo displays the Wi-Fi symbol superimposed on an image of Mt Fuji.
Wire and Wireless Company, a Japanese telecommunications provider, is celebrating the second anniversary of its free TRAVEL JAPAN Wi-Fi app. The latest update includes enhanced features and a wider range of free Wi-Fi access points.
The app provides travelers with details about nearby stores, restaurants, and attractions, along with numerous discount coupons.</description></item><item><title>Kodak Alaris unveils new wireless scanners with network connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</guid><description>Kodak Alaris&amp;rsquo; latest desktop scanners, the Kodak ScanMate i1150WN and Kodak i1190WN, offer wireless and network connectivity and are compatible with mobile apps. These features support bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policies and workplace mobility.
Source: Kodak Alaris. The Kodak ScanMate i1150WN.
The i1150WN and i1190WN scanners can connect through an office network or Wi-Fi, making them adaptable to various office settings. Standard drivers (TWAIN, ISIS) allow integration with new and existing business applications, streamlining the capture process and simplifying software installation.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling in McFadden: Public Wi-Fi and Responsibility for Unauthorized Downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case, McFadden, examined whether businesses offering free wi-fi are responsible for customers&amp;rsquo; illegal downloads. This case centered around Article 12 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s eCommerce Directive, which protects &amp;ldquo;mere conduits&amp;rdquo; of information from liability. While generally aligning with existing laws, the ruling raised potentially significant points regarding injunction costs and internet access provision requirements.</description></item><item><title>Increase the coverage area of Linksys routers by adding new high-gain antennas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-the-coverage-area-of-linksys-routers-by-adding-new-high-gain-antennas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-the-coverage-area-of-linksys-routers-by-adding-new-high-gain-antennas/</guid><description>This is the WRT router four-pack.
Linksys, a leading provider of home and business networking solutions and the first company to sell 100 million routers worldwide, has introduced the first dual-band, omni-directional high-gain antennas designed specifically for consumers.
These new high-gain antennas from Linksys are sold in two- and four-packs. They enhance Wi-Fi performance by boosting signal strength and throughput, particularly at the edge of a Wi-Fi network.
These antennas are compatible with any wireless router equipped with an RP-SMA connection.</description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre now offers complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Guests at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) can enjoy free Wi-Fi access through the &amp;lsquo;ADNEC Free Wi-Fi&amp;rsquo; network.
Humaid Matar Al Dhaheri, Acting Group CEO of Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company, stated that providing complimentary Wi-Fi highlights ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s focus on using technology to improve visitor experiences. This service eliminates the need for visitors to seek out basic internet access, aligning with ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing its technological infrastructure and enhancing service offerings to meet the changing needs of its stakeholders.</description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading.</description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after.</description></item><item><title>The first router is introduced by Synology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</guid><description>Source: Synology. The Synology Router RT1900ac.
Synology has introduced its first router, the Synology Router RT1900ac. This router allows users to connect an external storage device, effectively creating a personal cloud storage solution.
The router boasts combined transfer speeds of up to 1,900 Mbps and utilizes beamforming technology to optimize Wi-Fi signals for individual devices. A mobile app provides users with control over the router&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description></item><item><title>Guests staying at the Hyatt hotel can enjoy complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels Corporation is demonstrating its commitment to enhancing the guest experience by providing free Wi-Fi at all of its hotels globally starting in February 2015. This initiative aims to provide guests with convenient connectivity regardless of how they booked their stay or their loyalty program status.
Guests will have access to complimentary Wi-Fi on an unlimited number of devices, including laptops and mobile phones, in both guest rooms and common areas of Hyatt-branded hotels.</description></item><item><title>Emirates offers passengers complimentary or heavily discounted in-flight Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates provides complimentary* Wi-Fi on a significant portion of its fleet, currently 106 aircraft, and is continuously expanding this service. Passengers on ultra long-haul flights (flights exceeding 14 hours) frequently utilize this service, with over 30% connecting to Wi-Fi.
All 59 Airbus A380s and 47 Boeing 777s in Emirates&amp;rsquo; fleet offer Wi-Fi connectivity. A majority of these aircraft provide the first 10MB of data free of charge, allowing passengers to update social media or use messaging apps.</description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing.</description></item><item><title>Avast Wi-Fi Finder helps you find trustworthy Wi-Fi connections globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</guid><description>Avast has released Avast Wi-Fi Finder, an Android app that helps users locate trustworthy, fast, and secure Wi-Fi connections no matter where they are. The app uses a map interface to display recommended and crowdsourced hotspots.
&amp;ldquo;Many of us, whether traveling or working remotely, have struggled to find dependable and secure Wi-Fi,&amp;rdquo; said Gagan Singh, President of mobile at Avast. &amp;ldquo;With Avast Wi-Fi Finder, consumers can now easily locate a safe and fast Wi-Fi connection at the gym, hotel, airport, bus station, library, or café.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy the first 15 minutes of free Wi-Fi on Qatar Airways, courtesy of Ooredoo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo. The MoU was signed by (from left) Waleed Al Sayed, CEO, Ooredoo Qatar and Qatar Airways Group Chief Executive, His Excellency Akbar Al Baker.
Ooredoo and Qatar Airways have established a partnership where Ooredoo will sponsor Qatar Airways&amp;rsquo; in-flight Wi-Fi for the next three years. This agreement will make Ooredoo the sole sponsor for Wi-Fi on all Qatar Airways flights equipped with the service.
This sponsorship allows passengers to use their personal electronic devices to connect to the internet, check emails, and send SMS/MMS messages once the service is active during their flight.</description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides triple the mobile data for a low price, along with Wi-Fi calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</guid><description>Singtel launched a new mobile data add-on called DataX3 at their iPhone 7 event held at Marina Bay Sands Convention Centre. For S$9.90 per month, DataX3 allows customers to triple their mobile data limit. This add-on is available to Singtel Combo Plan customers (Combo 2 and above). It follows the successful launch of the DataX2 add-on earlier this year.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, highlighted the importance of affordable mobile data for communication, shopping, banking, and entertainment in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>