<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Robert Walters on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/robert-walters/</link><description>Recent content in Robert Walters on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/robert-walters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions.</description></item><item><title>The demand for jobs in Singapore is being driven by digitization, according to Robert Walters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</guid><description>Source: Robert Walters. Click on the
image to view a larger version.
According to the international recruitment firm Robert Walters, the increasing presence of digital technology was the main driver of recruitment in Singapore during the second quarter of 2015. These insights were published in the company’s Asia Job Index for Q2 2015.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, acknowledged the anticipated decrease in job advertisements during this quarter.</description></item><item><title>Asian companies place a high value on feedback received during exit interviews</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</guid><description>A recent report from Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, reveals that most companies believe in the value of honest feedback during exit interviews, whether formal or informal. In fact, seven out of ten Asian companies conduct these interviews.
Titled &amp;ldquo;Acquiring Insights From The Exit Process To Build A Better Workplace,&amp;rdquo; the report highlights how improvements made based on exit interview feedback can help organizations attract and retain top-tier talent.</description></item></channel></rss>