<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Amazon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/amazon/</link><description>Recent content in Amazon on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/amazon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amazon has introduced exclusive holiday offers for Prime Now members</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</guid><description>This holiday season, Amazon Prime members in Singapore can enjoy thousands of deals on local and international products through the Prime Now app. These deals cover a wide range of categories, from toys and electronics to beauty products and holiday essentials.
Since its launch, Prime Now has expanded its offerings to include new brands like Yakult, Dell, Tefal, Sambucol, Bausch &amp;amp; Lomb, and Pinkfong. New categories such as fresh flowers, organic fruits (including durians), and international foods have also been added.</description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11.</description></item><item><title>Today marks the return of Amazon's Prime Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-return-of-amazon-s-prime-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-return-of-amazon-s-prime-day/</guid><description>Amazon.sg is holding its first-ever Prime Day event in Singapore on October 26 and 27, 2020, shortly after the company&amp;rsquo;s first anniversary in the country on October 8, 2020.
This event is predicted to drive substantial sales for both Amazon and its retail competitors, marking an unofficial start to the holiday shopping period.
The changes in shopping habits this year, with many consumers reducing physical store visits, are anticipated to result in a boost in online revenue.</description></item><item><title>Seller University has been launched by Amazon in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 05:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</guid><description>Amazon has introduced Seller University, an online platform designed to assist small and medium businesses (SMBs) in Singapore, at its inaugural Amazon Singapore Online Seller Summit 2020. Seller University offers interactive e-learning materials, practical exercises, and customized support to equip sellers on Amazon.sg with the skills to thrive.
Bernard Tay, Country Leader of Amazon.sg Seller Services and Head of Amazon Global Selling Southeast Asia, Australia and New Zealand, emphasized Amazon&amp;rsquo;s commitment to empowering local businesses through initiatives like Seller University.</description></item><item><title>Insights from interim proceedings: Amazon v DSA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insights-from-interim-proceedings-amazon-v-dsa/</guid><description>Laureline Lemoine, Senior Associate, AWO Agency
Photo credit: KarleHorn, via Wikimedia Commons
A recent legal challenge to the Digital Services Act (DSA) provides insight into how Amazon is approaching its obligations under the new law. The case, initiated by Amazon after being designated a Very Large Online Platform (VLOP), centers around two main arguments.
First, Amazon contests the DSA requirement for an opt-out for recommender systems based on user profiling (Article 38), claiming it would negatively impact its business and users.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Prime is currently being offered at a discounted rate in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-prime-is-currently-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-prime-is-currently-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate-in-singapore/</guid><description>Amazon Prime, offering perks like expedited shipping, streaming entertainment, and gaming, has launched in Singapore. This marks the 16th country to gain access to the program, following the recent discontinuation of free shipping for Singaporean shoppers on the US Amazon site.
Singaporean Prime members will now have access to free two-hour delivery on local orders over S$40 from a selection of tens of thousands of products through the Prime Now app.</description></item><item><title>Amazon is sharing the best-selling Christmas items from Prime Now Singapore orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</guid><description>Amazon has revealed the top-selling items purchased by Prime Now users in Singapore during a record-breaking holiday season worldwide. Customers took advantage of Prime Now&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ultra-Fast Delivery&amp;rdquo; option throughout the holiday period, with tens of thousands of products delivered, even in the final hours. The last Prime Now order was delivered at 10:23 p.m. on December 24th.
&amp;ldquo;The volume of shoppers in Singapore using Prime Now leading up to Christmas was remarkable, as was the number who signed up for a free Prime trial or initiated a paid membership,&amp;rdquo; shared Kourosh Kaghazian, Country Manager for Amazon Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Prepare for Chinese New Year with Amazon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</guid><description>Preparing your office for Chinese New Year might be easier with a little help from Amazon.sg&amp;rsquo;s dedicated Chinese New Year store.
Finding the right gifts for clients is made simpler with choices like an abalone gift set, priced at S$310.80 for two 454g cans, or bird&amp;rsquo;s nest, available for S$39.90 for six jars. To help everyone in the office get into the spirit, festive treats are a must-have:
Source: Amazon. Snacks for the office for Chinese New Year.</description></item><item><title>Taking a Read on the Amazon Kindle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taking-a-read-on-the-amazon-kindle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 17:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taking-a-read-on-the-amazon-kindle/</guid><description>Despite predictions that computers would lead to the disappearance of paper, the opposite has occurred. The demand for paper has increased significantly due to printers, and traditional media like newspapers and books remain popular. This raises the question: why is paper so persistent in the digital age?
Several factors contribute to this. E-books lack the tactile experience of physical books and the convenience of annotating paper copies. Additionally, reading on backlit screens can cause eye strain, unlike paper.</description></item></channel></rss>