<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Germany on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/germany/</link><description>Recent content in Germany on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/germany/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The inaugural commercial flight of the Etihad Boeing 787 Dreamliner is headed to Germany</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways, the flag carrier of the UAE, launched its inaugural Boeing 787 Dreamliner commercial flight. The first flight, a Boeing 787-9, flew from Abu Dhabi to Düsseldorf, Germany. Departing at 2:15 a.m. as flight EY23, the seven-hour, 25-minute journey landed at 6:40 a.m. The return leg from Düsseldorf departs at 10:20 a.m., arriving in Abu Dhabi at 7:50 p.m.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and CEO, stated that the Boeing 787 is a significant achievement for the airline, calling it the most technologically sophisticated aircraft in its class...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Utilization of Prisons for Detaining Migrants in Europe and the EU Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, a researcher at the Global Detention Project and the Global Migration Centre, and a PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies in Geneva, examines a legal question: can immigration detainees be held in prisons alongside ordinary prisoners?
On July 17, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this question in its decisions regarding the combined cases of Bero and Bouzalmate and the separate case of Pham...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions of the Attorney General on recent CJEU cases regarding national data retention laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
Advocate General Campos Sanchez-Bordana has presented his opinions on three cases concerning data retention: SpaceNet and Telekom Deutschland, GD v Commissioner of the Garda Síochána, and VD and SR. These opinions are the latest development in a series of legal challenges related to data retention that began with an Irish challenge to the Data Retention Directive.
The Data Retention Directive, which allowed for the retention of communications data under certain exceptions to privacy principles, was invalidated in the Digital Rights Ireland case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it permissible for Member States to confiscate the assets of asylum-seekers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk (Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen) and Steve Peers
Recently, several countries within and outside the EU have made headlines for seizing assets from asylum-seekers upon entry. This raises the question of whether this practice aligns with EU law. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine national practices, the development of relevant EU regulations, and finally, draw our conclusions.
Denmark
In November 2015, the Danish government put forward 34 measures aimed at deterring asylum seekers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Arrest Warrants and the autonomy of public prosecutors as ruled by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Julia Burchett, PhD candidate at the Université libre de Bruxelles and the University of Grenoble
Introduction
Widely recognized as a cornerstone of EU criminal law, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as one of the most, if not the most, utilized tools for judicial cooperation in criminal matters among EU member states. This streamlined cross-border surrender procedure, designed for prosecution or execution of custodial sentences and detention orders, has replaced traditional systems relying on political involvement from individual member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Getting Network Connections Into Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</guid><description>Although many businesses only require domestic WAN connections, a growing number are seeking global connectivity, particularly with European markets for financial trading, sales, and support. This raises the question of how US-based companies can establish cost-effective connections with Europe.
Fortunately, several carriers offer transatlantic connectivity to major European cities. Some US carriers have partnerships for traffic handover to European data centers, as illustrated by AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement with ancotel GmbH in Frankfurt, Germany...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Story of the Administrative Agreement on Asylum-Seekers between Greece and Germany: Is it a case of "paraDublin activity"?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</guid><description>Stathis Poularakis, Legal advisor - Advocacy Officer Médecins du Monde – Greece*
* Reposted from the EDAL blog. A previous version of this article was published in Greek on the immigration.gr blog. The opinions in this article belong to the author and don&amp;rsquo;t represent the official stance of Médecins du Monde – Greece. Thank you to Evangelia Tzironi, PhD Candidate at the Law School of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens, for proofreading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mario's feet were pulled out from under him by the BVerfG and the ECB's OMT programme.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</guid><description>By Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster
The German Constitutional Court (BVerfG) is set to make a significant decision on the European Union&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union on June 21st. The court will rule on the Gauweiler case, which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. This program, designed to stabilize struggling Eurozone economies, was challenged by plaintiffs questioning its legal foundation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>