<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Loan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/loan/</link><description>Recent content in Loan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/loan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training.</description></item><item><title>Singapore businesses can access cybersecurity and financing services from Acronis and Minterest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyberprotection company, has partnered with Minterest, a Singaporean online financial services provider, to offer financing to Singaporean businesses. This collaboration, called Acronis #CyberFit Financing, Powered by Minterest, aims to help businesses in Singapore stay resilient and #CyberFit during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Acronis and Minterest want to empower businesses by providing easily accessible, customized financing solutions. This will help businesses navigate challenging times while also strengthening their cybersecurity defenses.</description></item><item><title>A white paper by the Dubai Chamber examines the funding landscape for startups in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Cover for the white paper.
A recent report highlights the need for a simplified guide to help UAE startups navigate the funding landscape and connect with eager investors. The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, in partnership with Roland Berger, published this white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Helping Startups Access Funding,&amp;rdquo; during the March edition of Dubai Startup Hub&amp;rsquo;s Entrepreneurship Advocacy Series. Dubai Startup Hub, the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s entrepreneurial arm, offers guidance and clarity to new businesses through various programs and workshops.</description></item><item><title>AsiaKredit has introduced a consumer lending platform in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>AsiaKredit&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make financial services more accessible in the Philippines. They aim to achieve this by making credit easier to obtain and improving the approval rates for individuals with limited or no credit history.
Source: pera247 website. Screenshot of the pera247 app.
Pera247 is a completely digital platform offering short-term loans, up to 90 days, through a mobile wallet. These loans are typically small, unsecured, and target consumers with limited financial history.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has relaxed its requirements for car loans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 08:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) announced adjustments to loan regulations for motor vehicles. The maximum loan-to-value (LTV) ratios and allowable loan durations will be relaxed, but some limitations will remain indefinitely.
These changes come after three years of sustained moderation in Certificate of Entitlement (COE) premiums and related inflationary pressures.
Financial institutions&amp;rsquo; motor vehicle loan restrictions were implemented in 2013 to control car and COE demand and reduce inflationary pressures.</description></item><item><title>A Singaporean financial technology company is striving to provide improved lending terms for business-to-business transactions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</guid><description>A Singapore-based fintech startup, Cash-IN-Asia, has introduced a new business-to-business (B2B) lending platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s fully digital approach lets business owners secure financing directly from their mobile devices.
Cash-IN-Asia aims to support micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in Singapore. The company offers products designed to meet current needs and help these businesses thrive even after the current economic challenges.
Their ISO27001-certified platform leverages artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics to deliver a comprehensive solution for MSMEs seeking transparent and flexible financing.</description></item></channel></rss>