<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backhaul on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backhaul/</link><description>Recent content in Backhaul on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:29:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backhaul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WiMAX 2 Will Challenge Fiber For Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</guid><description>The idea that copper and wireless technologies are outdated in terms of bandwidth is circulating. While copper has found new life as a last-mile solution for Metro Ethernet services, and wireless stands out for its unmatched mobility, a new wireless technology is emerging that might surpass even fiber optic speeds.
It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to think that wireless could outpace fiber in terms of bandwidth.
While not all fiber optic services offer top speeds of 10 GigE, with many customers receiving 50 to 100 Mbps, especially in the case of Fiber To The Home (FTTH), the prospect of achieving 100 to 300 Mbps wirelessly anywhere in a city is enticing.</description></item><item><title>Ciena Takes New Bandwidth Technologies On The Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciena-takes-new-bandwidth-technologies-on-the-road/</guid><description>Today, June 29th, those in Waltham, MA can experience cutting-edge carrier bandwidth technology firsthand. Visit the Ciena Innovation Lab to see live demonstrations of their latest optical, Ethernet, and software solutions. The lab will move to its next location in White Marsh, MD on July 15th.
What exactly is the Ciena Innovation Lab? It&amp;rsquo;s a mobile showcase housed in a semi-trailer, packed with the most recent advancements in telecom and networking.</description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual.</description></item></channel></rss>