<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2-in-1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2-in-1/</link><description>Recent content in 2-in-1 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2-in-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dell introduces new laptops and monitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</guid><description>Dell Singapore has launched new laptops and a monitor for consumers.
The XPS 12 is the first 2-in-1 laptop with a 4K Ultra HD display. The Inspiron 11 3000 series offers an affordable and portable laptop option available in three colors. Dell also released their first 4K consumer monitor, the Dell 28 Ultra HD 4K Monitor.
&amp;ldquo;Consumers have increasingly diverse needs. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a student or a professional, size, power, design, and price all matter.</description></item><item><title>The HP 2 in 1 printer is perfect for home offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new PC and printer designed for home offices.
The HP Pavilion x2, available in Singapore starting in October from S$499, offers a stylish and practical solution. This versatile device functions as a 10-inch Windows tablet and easily transforms into a fully functional laptop. It features a detachable magnetic keyboard cover that doubles as both a screen protector and a multi-position stand. Equipped with an Intel Atom processor, the Pavilion x2 boasts front-facing speakers with DTS sound and a battery life of up to 11.</description></item><item><title>Acer introduces new convertible notebooks, the Aspire R 13 and R 14</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</guid><description>Acer has introduced two new convertible notebook lines, the Aspire R 13 and Aspire R 14 Series, both capable of transitioning between various notebook and tablet modes. These notebooks are designed for users seeking the functionality of a traditional notebook with added flexibility.
Source: Acer. The R 13 in one mode.
Acer&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Jason Chen, stated that their objective is to exceed expectations with their products at every price point. He believes these Aspire convertibles are ideal for users who require both portability and productivity.</description></item><item><title>HP has released a variety of mobile solutions to enhance business productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</guid><description>HP has introduced a suite of commercial mobility solutions aimed at boosting workplace productivity. The offerings include eight new mobile devices and accessories designed to simplify business processes.
Anneliese Olson, HP Asia-Pacific and Japan VP and GM of Personal Computing, highlighted how these products address evolving workplace dynamics, workforce trends, and work styles, ultimately reshaping workflows.
HP has developed a comprehensive mobility solution catering to diverse businesses, including those in specialized sectors like education, field service, healthcare, public safety, and retail.</description></item><item><title>Acer unveils three convertible notebooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</guid><description>Acer has expanded its line of 2-in-1 notebooks with the new 11.6&amp;quot; Aspire Switch 11 series and a new Switch 10 featuring a 1080p Full HD 10.1&amp;quot; display. The Aspire Switch 2-in-1 series combines a Microsoft Windows notebook and tablet in one device.
Source: Acer. The Aspire Switch 10.
The Aspire Switch series is thin, lightweight, and durable, designed for work and travel. It supports four modes: touch, typing, viewing, and sharing.</description></item></channel></rss>