<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dynamics GP vs. NetSuite on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dynamics-gp-vs.-netsuite/</link><description>Recent content in Dynamics GP vs. NetSuite on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:45:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dynamics-gp-vs.-netsuite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comparison of NetSuite and Dynamics GP: A Series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparison-of-netsuite-and-dynamics-gp-a-series/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparison-of-netsuite-and-dynamics-gp-a-series/</guid><description>Over the past two weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve embarked on my first NetSuite project thanks to an opportunity from a friend at Prolecto Resources. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered numerous articles comparing NetSuite and Dynamics GP, they often seem biased. My goal is to provide a more impartial comparison based on my nine years of experience with Dynamics GP.
Rather than engaging in the typical debates surrounding on-premise versus SaaS or licensed versus subscription models, this series will focus on comparing specific features and approaches within both systems.</description></item><item><title>NetSuite and Dynamics GP: Comparing Real-Time Transaction Processing to Batch Posting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/netsuite-and-dynamics-gp-comparing-real-time-transaction-processing-to-batch-posting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 01:24:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/netsuite-and-dynamics-gp-comparing-real-time-transaction-processing-to-batch-posting/</guid><description>To provide context, you can refer to my introduction to this series, &amp;ldquo;NetSuite vs. Dynamics GP: A Series.&amp;rdquo;
A key distinction between NetSuite and Dynamics GP lies in their transaction handling. NetSuite allows direct saving of transactions for committing, while Dynamics GP uses batches. In Dynamics GP, you can group multiple transactions into a batch for saving, but they remain uncommitted and editable. This batch acts as a temporary container, enabling verification of transaction count and total value.</description></item><item><title>Comparison between NetSuite and Dynamics GP: General Ledger Impact versus Distributions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparison-between-netsuite-and-dynamics-gp-general-ledger-impact-versus-distributions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 14:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparison-between-netsuite-and-dynamics-gp-general-ledger-impact-versus-distributions/</guid><description>This article compares how NetSuite and Dynamics GP handle sales account customization. The author had to customize NetSuite to categorize sales into three general ledger accounts based on specific criteria. In Dynamics GP, this could be achieved by adjusting transaction distributions - child records that specify how transaction amounts are allocated to GL accounts. This allows for modification at both the document and line item levels.
NetSuite, however, doesn&amp;rsquo;t have visible or editable distributions during invoice entry.</description></item></channel></rss>