<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transparency on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transparency/</link><description>Recent content in Transparency on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transparency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Access to documents: The Council may choose not to enforce a significant CJEU ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU is frequently criticized for its lack of transparency, particularly concerning its legislative processes. Ideally, these processes should be as open as those in national legislatures, allowing public access to draft legislation.
However, despite a 2001 regulation on public access to documents, EU transparency in this area remains an issue. Within the Council, some Member States prefer to keep their positions confidential during negotiations. This secrecy undermines the idea that citizens, through their national parliaments, can hold their governments accountable for actions taken within the Council...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC places a strong emphasis on ensuring compliance and transparency in all business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 11:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</guid><description>Following the release of the Panama Papers, the Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC) has reaffirmed its commitment to facilitating cross-border trade and investment, especially within the ASEAN region. The organization emphasizes its dedication to maintaining strict transparency and regulatory standards for all business activities conducted within the centre.
In a statement, the organization highlighted its continuous efforts to strengthen its regulatory framework and supervisory system. These efforts aim to meet international standards and practices related to transparency and regulatory compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-places-a-strong-emphasis-on-ensuring-compliance-and-transparency-in-all-business-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In order to create more responsive rules, the EU-US transatlantic trade and partnership (TTIP) negotiations are crucial.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</guid><description>Dr. Elaine Fahey, Senior Lecturer, The City Law School, City University London
The script
The EU and US have concluded six rounds of discussions on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Agreement (TTIP). This agreement aims to reduce trade barriers and other obstacles, such as differing regulations and standards, across various industries. TTIP is promoted as potentially setting a global trade standard. Some argue it&amp;rsquo;s already irrelevant, but while this downplays its potential influence, skepticism is understandable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is privacy prioritized over transparency in CJEU cases?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</guid><description>Peter Oliver, Barrister, Monckton Chambers; Visiting Professor, Université Libre de Bruxelles
Having a name is essential, as not having one can lead to problems. This is why courts in Strasbourg and Luxembourg have acknowledged a person’s fundamental right to use their own name.
The Court of Justice has traditionally used initials to protect the identities of vulnerable individuals like asylum seekers and children involved in sensitive litigation. However, in a recent announcement, the Court stated its intention to partially overturn this long-standing practice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the European Parliament's Closed Reading Rooms: Shedding Light on Transparency in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Dr Vigjilenca Abazi
Assistant Professor of European Law
Maastricht University
Documents related to various topics, such as Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership (TTIP) negotiations, EU Food Safety Authority oversight, and tax justice, share a common factor: accessing them requires select Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to participate in closed reading rooms. This blog post will examine how this departure from transparent parliamentary oversight is becoming increasingly common and question its potential impact on public access to documents requests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A leaked document discloses that the EU is considering suspending the Schengen agreement for a period of two years.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</guid><description>Commentary by Steve Peers
This is Council document 14300/15, from December 1, 2015, called &amp;ldquo;Integrity of the Schengen area,&amp;rdquo; and sent to Coreper (representatives of EU member states) and the Council - likely the Justice and Home Affairs ministers meeting December 3rd and 4th. (An official version of the document is available here).
The first three sections are relatively standard (see here for discussion), but section 4 proposes initiating a process to formally permit the reinstatement of internal border controls within the Schengen zone for a duration of up to two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>