<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reality/</link><description>Recent content in Reality on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The HALCYON VR murder mystery from Syfy will soon be accessible on the Samsung Gear VR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</guid><description>Source: Syfy. HALCYON investigates a VR murder.
Syfy, known for its imaginative entertainment, will debut its unique hybrid virtual reality (VR) series, HALCYON, on September 22nd at 10 pm. The series is a creation of Secret Location, a multi-award-winning content studio specializing in cutting-edge platforms.
Set in 2040, HALCYON centers on Julie Dover, a detective in the Virtual Reality Crimes Unit. She tackles the first-ever murder within virtual reality, a seemingly impossible crime, and unravels the hidden conspiracy behind it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore has released the new Moverio Pro smart glasses with augmented reality capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</guid><description>Epson, a global provider of projection technology and visual communication tools, has introduced the Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset. This binocular headset offers an augmented reality experience for applications such as inspections, training, and remote field service support for intricate repairs and troubleshooting.
Source: Epson Singapore. The new
Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset.
Augmented reality smart glasses have the potential to boost worker efficiency across various sectors, including warehousing, logistics, field service, automotive, manufacturing, construction, and retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Stay away from Pokemon Go scams and malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</guid><description>Source: Niantic blog.
The augmented reality game Pokémon Go, highly popular since its July launch, has attracted scammers and cybercriminals. While the game hasn&amp;rsquo;t officially launched in all of Asia, Symantec warns of potential risks for players.
Symantec&amp;rsquo;s blog post details several Pokémon Go scams, from fake PokeCoins to privacy concerns.
Free PokeCoin scams
Pokémon Go offers in-app purchases using real money to buy PokeCoins, a virtual currency. Players use these coins to purchase items like incense to attract Pokémon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Windows device will soon enhance your creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The possibilities of Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, sketched on a Microsoft Surface by Michael Mindflyer.
Microsoft has launched the latest version of its operating system, the Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, offering it as a free upgrade to current Windows 10 users globally. This update, the fourth major one for Windows 10, prioritizes creativity. It aims to make mixed reality and 3D design accessible to Windows users, leading to improvements in gaming, audiovisual content, and mixed reality experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AppShack is a reality show that connects investors with startups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appshack-is-a-reality-show-that-connects-investors-with-startups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 03:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appshack-is-a-reality-show-that-connects-investors-with-startups/</guid><description>Source: AppShack. The official launch was officiated by Bhg. Dato’ Jailani Johari, Deputy Minister of Communications and Multimedia Malaysia.
AppShack, a Malaysian company that connects startups with organizations seeking mobile application innovation, has officially launched.
This platform supports startups in developing their ideas by providing mentorship, technical expertise, business structure assistance, legal advice, and financial funding opportunities. Successful applicants can connect with investors and partners, including consortiums, venture capitalists, and bankers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appshack-is-a-reality-show-that-connects-investors-with-startups/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appshack-is-a-reality-show-that-connects-investors-with-startups/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The latest digital tools that lead to business success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</guid><description>Ebenezer Heng, Principal Consultant at Top Advertising, emphasizes that businesses must understand and leverage the connection between online and offline marketing to thrive. Speaking at the Fuji Xerox DocuWorld Conference, he argued that traditional success factors like &amp;ldquo;gut feel&amp;rdquo; are no longer enough in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
He illustrated this with the example of choosing a business location. Simply observing foot traffic isn&amp;rsquo;t sufficient; online sentiment analysis, which gauges public opinion about a location, can reveal a different picture of popularity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces the latest Moverio smart glasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the third generation of its Moverio smart glasses, designed for augmented reality applications. The Moverio BT-300 utilizes Epson&amp;rsquo;s innovative silicon-based OLED display technology, providing a truly transparent mobile augmented reality (AR) experience for both businesses and consumers.
Epson highlights the Moverio BT-300 as the lightest binocular see-through smart glasses available, boasting a weight reduction of over 20% compared to its predecessor, the Moverio BT-200. These glasses are powered by a quad-core Intel Atom X5 processor and run on Android 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>