<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4imprint on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4imprint/</link><description>Recent content in 4imprint on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4imprint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lessons for small and medium-sized enterprises from successful viral campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</guid><description>4imprint, a company that sells promotional products, has created a new infographic called &amp;ldquo;Going Viral.&amp;rdquo; This infographic explains how small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) can learn from viral marketing campaigns.
One suggestion is to connect a campaign with something already trending, like a popular TV show or book. This can effectively help a marketing effort gain traction with a specific audience.
The infographic also encourages businesses to consider product trials and giveaways.</description></item><item><title>Blue paper designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in developing effective Pinterest strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blue-paper-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-developing-effective-pinterest-strategies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blue-paper-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-developing-effective-pinterest-strategies/</guid><description>4imprint, a company selling promotional products, has published a guide to help small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) utilize Pinterest for business growth. This guide showcases the success stories of established brands on Pinterest and explores its role in a comprehensive marketing strategy.
[Image]
Source: Pinterest.
The guide emphasizes the platform&amp;rsquo;s visual nature, making it especially well-suited for industries like food, interior design, and fashion. With a user base of 70 million, &amp;ldquo;Grow your Business with Pinterest&amp;rdquo; suggests significant potential for businesses.</description></item></channel></rss>