<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contemporary on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contemporary/</link><description>Recent content in Contemporary on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contemporary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center.</description></item><item><title>The KOGEI Future Forward exhibition at Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store showcases the work of 15 artists</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</guid><description>The Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a contemporary art exhibition, KOGEI Future Forward, from February 15 to 20, 2017. The exhibition showcases the work of 15 Japanese artists, highlighting kogei as a unique form of Japanese fine art.
Kogei, meaning &amp;ldquo;craft,&amp;rdquo; emerged during the Meiji Period (1868-1912) and has evolved over time to gain recognition as fine art. This exhibition offers a fresh perspective on kogei, curated by Yuji Akimoto, a renowned art professor and museum director.</description></item></channel></rss>