<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Level on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/level/</link><description>Recent content in Level on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/level/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Today is the day for the landrush of .global, .website, and .press domain names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</guid><description>Starting August 27th, Singapore time, several top-level domain names will be up for grabs in a &amp;ldquo;landrush&amp;rdquo; phase, according to online brand specialist IP Mirror.
The &amp;ldquo;sunrise&amp;rdquo; phase, reserved for trademark holders to register their brands, precedes this period. During the landrush phase, anyone can secure remaining domain names at a premium price.
IP Mirror highlights &amp;ldquo;.global&amp;rdquo; as a particularly appealing option, signifying a broad international reach. This domain&amp;rsquo;s landrush phase lasts from August 27th to September 4th.</description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the Desire 616 dual SIM smartphone for entry-level users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</guid><description>HTC, a company known for mobile innovation and design, has introduced the HTC Desire 616 dual sim phone. This new phone offers high-end features at an affordable price. Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;The HTC Desire 616 dual sim is a powerful phone with a great price tag,&amp;rdquo; says Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;This new phone in the popular HTC Desire line offers an eight-core processor, fast processing speeds, and top-tier features at an accessible price, giving users a best-in-class experience.</description></item></channel></rss>