<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Employee on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employee/</link><description>Recent content in Employee on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness.</description></item><item><title>Finding good people is still a challenge, according to ManpowerGroup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</guid><description>Source: ManpowerGroup infographic.
Around the world, the most difficult positions to fill are in skilled trades (particularly chefs, bakers, butchers, mechanics, and electricians), sales, engineering (mechanical, electrical, and civil), technician roles, and drivers (especially heavy vehicle operators), according to workforce experts ManpowerGroup.
The situation in Singapore is somewhat different. While engineers are among the top five hardest roles to fill, as elsewhere, the other four are accounting and finance professionals, sales representatives, secretaries (including receptionists and administrative assistants), and marketing, public relations, and communications specialists.</description></item><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily.</description></item><item><title>Workers value recognition more than money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</guid><description>Source: ACCA report. Tone at the top influences corporate behaviour the most, according to 61% of respondents.
A recent report by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) titled &amp;ldquo;Culture and channelling corporate behaviour: ACCA member survey&amp;rdquo; found that workplace recognition is the most significant motivator for employees across all ages, industries, and locations. Notably, this recognition even outweighs monetary rewards.
The survey, conducted with support from the Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC), gathered insights from nearly 2,000 ACCA finance professionals globally.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>Helping individuals with disabilities transition from training programs to meaningful employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Individuals with disabilities should be placed in jobs where they can acquire skills on the job, rather than receiving training without a clear path to employment. Christy Lynch, CEO of KARE Ireland, an organization supporting individuals with intellectual disabilities and their families, emphasized the importance of collaborating with both individuals with disabilities and employers to create truly empowering opportunities. He spoke at the &amp;ldquo;Towards an Inclusive Workforce 2015&amp;rdquo; event, co-organized by SPD and supported by SG Enable and the Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA).</description></item><item><title>CIMB introduces a program to enhance the skills of non-executive employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</guid><description>CIMB Group, the second-largest financial services provider in Malaysia, has initiated a program to enhance the skills, productivity, career advancement prospects, and earning potential of its non-executive employees. This program, known as the CIMB Accelerated Career Enhancement Programme (CIMB ACE), was officially launched by Dato’ Sri Richard Riot Anak Jaem, the Minister of Human Resources.
The CIMB ACE program aligns with PR1ME (Program Majudiri 1Malaysia), a national initiative launched by the Prime Minister of Malaysia in November 2013.</description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued.</description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:</description></item></channel></rss>