<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Commerce Directive on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-commerce-directive/</link><description>Recent content in E-Commerce Directive on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-commerce-directive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU ruling in McFadden: Public Wi-Fi and Responsibility for Unauthorized Downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case, McFadden, examined whether businesses offering free wi-fi are responsible for customers&amp;rsquo; illegal downloads. This case centered around Article 12 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s eCommerce Directive, which protects &amp;ldquo;mere conduits&amp;rdquo; of information from liability. While generally aligning with existing laws, the ruling raised potentially significant points regarding injunction costs and internet access provision requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU interprets the e-commerce Directive regarding Facebook's responsibility for defamatory posts.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, several legal decisions have addressed how individuals can control their information online. Two cases, GC et al and Google v CNIL, focused on how search engines should interpret their obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This post will focus on a third case, Glawischnig-Piesczek v Facebook, which examined how the e-Commerce Directive&amp;rsquo;s prohibition on general monitoring applies to &amp;ldquo;stay down&amp;rdquo; notices. The case raises a broader question about the consistency of different internet regulations, including those related to intellectual property, child exploitation, and terrorism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cracking down on online terrorism - a threat to freedom of speech? The EU Regulation on online terrorist content under scrutiny.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
On September 12th, 2018, the European Commission presented a proposal for a regulation aimed at combating terrorist content online. This regulation would mandate that EU Member States require internet platforms to proactively remove such content and ensure that authorities possess the capabilities to address this illegal material. This proposal builds upon existing voluntary partnerships like the EU Internet Forum and previous non-binding recommendations from the Commission on tackling illegal content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracking-down-on-online-terrorism-a-threat-to-freedom-of-speech-the-eu-regulation-on-online-terrorist-content-under-scrutiny/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A case involving Facebook, defamation, and free speech is currently pending in the CJEU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Preliminary Notes on the Pending Case Glawischnig-Piesczek v. Facebook Ireland Limited
Dr Paolo Cavaliere, University of Edinburgh Law School, paolo.cavaliere@ed.ac.uk
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon release a potentially groundbreaking decision regarding political speech and internet platform liability. The court will address two related but distinct issues: the extent of platforms&amp;rsquo; responsibility to remove illegal content, specifically if it applies to content similar to posts previously deemed unlawful, and whether such obligations apply beyond the court&amp;rsquo;s jurisdiction...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>