<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blockchain on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blockchain/</link><description>Recent content in Blockchain on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In 2017, a settlement network powered by blockchain announced that it would waive fees for transfers to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</guid><description>OKLink, a global settlement platform, has introduced the first entirely free remittance corridor. The company stated that transfers up to US$100,000 each month to Singapore will be free throughout 2017.
Previously, OKLink applied a 0.1% fee on cross-border payments to Singapore, while other companies might charge up to US$5 per transaction.
&amp;ldquo;As the world&amp;rsquo;s largest blockchain-powered global settlement network, we can process cross-border payments faster and more affordably as more partners join,&amp;rdquo; explained Jack Liu, Chief Strategy Officer at OKLink.</description></item><item><title>The financial consequences of the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-financial-consequences-of-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-financial-consequences-of-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s potential in fostering trust within networks is significant.
The World Bank Group has been actively supporting clients throughout the COVID-19 pandemic. William Zhang, a Lead Information Security Architect and Blockchain Specialist at the World Bank Group, highlighted the severe economic impact of COVID-19, including a US$4 trillion global GDP decline, significant job losses, and numerous business closures.
Zhang, speaking at a webinar titled &amp;ldquo;Leveraging Blockchain Innovations to Cope with the COVID-19 New Normal,&amp;rdquo; organized by the 10x1000 Tech for Inclusion Programme, noted that projections indicate a 9% increase in both poverty and extreme poverty.</description></item><item><title>Acronis has launched Blockchain-supported data protection through Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-launched-blockchain-supported-data-protection-through-acronis-true-image-2017-new-generation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-launched-blockchain-supported-data-protection-through-acronis-true-image-2017-new-generation/</guid><description>Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation offers four key advantages: comprehensive backup, Blockchain-based authentication to ensure data integrity, protection against ransomware, and secure e-signatures.
Acronis, a global provider of hybrid-cloud data protection and storage solutions, has introduced Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation. This release builds upon the existing backup features of Acronis True Image with three significant additions:
Acronis Active Protection safeguards user data against ransomware attacks in real time.</description></item><item><title>A new e-trading platform for physical commodities, based on blockchain technology, has been launched in Singapore on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-e-trading-platform-for-physical-commodities-based-on-blockchain-technology-has-been-launched-in-singapore-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-e-trading-platform-for-physical-commodities-based-on-blockchain-technology-has-been-launched-in-singapore-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Commodities Intelligence Centre (CIC) has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first physical commodity business-to-business (B2B) e-trading platform in collaboration with key partners: Zall Smartcomm, a prominent B2B player in China; Global eTrade Services (GeTS) Asia, a subsidiary of CrimsonLogic; and Singapore Exchange (SGX). Enterprise Singapore played a crucial role in bringing these partners together.
CIC offers a comprehensive global trading platform powered by Blockchain technology. This platform provides commodity traders worldwide with a range of services, including transaction matching, simplified customs clearance, supply chain financing, flexible payment options, and enhanced resource pooling for both buyers and sellers.</description></item><item><title>Learn the fundamentals of blockchain technology at Smartcademy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-the-fundamentals-of-blockchain-technology-at-smartcademy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-the-fundamentals-of-blockchain-technology-at-smartcademy/</guid><description>Source: Unsplash, via Smartcademy. This image illustrates Blockchain technology, with cryptocurrency being one example of its use.
[
Smartcademy, a Singaporean organization focused on technology education and career development, has launched a beginner-friendly introductory course on Blockchain. This one-month program covers basic concepts and terminology, explores how Blockchain is used in finance, and explains the workings of Bitcoin. The course aims to equip individuals with the knowledge to navigate the risks and rewards of digital financial systems.</description></item></channel></rss>