<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Online Business on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-business/</link><description>Recent content in Online Business on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telecom and Network Domain Names For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong domain name is crucial for any online business. The best names reflect your business, are easy to remember for offline use, and are pronounceable. Owning your own domain provides a much stronger online identity compared to generic alternatives. This ownership gives you full control over your website, email, and branding.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in business telecom for almost 15 years and acquired many domain names related to that industry.</description></item><item><title>Try Cloud Website Load Testing Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve established your online presence, but the question remains: how strong is it? Just like the story of the three little pigs, a website needs to be built with strong materials to withstand the elements. While a website might appear impressive when it&amp;rsquo;s not in use, the true test comes with a surge of visitors. Load testing is the only way to determine if your site can handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>1&amp;1 makes 1.99</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:20:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</guid><description>Choosing 1&amp;amp;1 for web hosting is like getting a steal of a deal. They&amp;rsquo;re a leading web hosting company, even internationally recognized, and their starting price is incredibly low at $1.99 per month for the first three months, then $3.99 monthly.
You might think this means low quality, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. This entry-level package is comparable to professional hosting services. Here&amp;rsquo;s what your $1.99 gets you: a free domain name (that you choose!</description></item></channel></rss>