<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Error on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/error/</link><description>Recent content in Error on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:37:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/error/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The SanScript Library could not be loaded, and Integration Manager is affected.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanscript-library-could-not-be-loaded-and-integration-manager-is-affected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanscript-library-could-not-be-loaded-and-integration-manager-is-affected/</guid><description>Towards the end of the previous month, a client reached out for help with their Dynamics GP year-end update. After resolving that, they described a separate Integration Manager problem that a previous consultant couldn&amp;rsquo;t fix, even after resorting to completely reinstalling the system. Intrigued, I decided to investigate further.
The client demonstrated that when running an integration on a specific machine, it would initially start but then fail with the error message &amp;ldquo;Unable to load SanScript Library.</description></item><item><title>The creation wizard for the forecaster database has failed. We apologize for the inconvenience.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creation-wizard-for-the-forecaster-database-has-failed-we-apologize-for-the-inconvenience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:28:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creation-wizard-for-the-forecaster-database-has-failed-we-apologize-for-the-inconvenience/</guid><description>Setting up a new database in Forecaster is usually simple. You just open the Forecaster Database Creation Wizard, connect to your SQL Server, input the database details, and you&amp;rsquo;re done. However, recently I encountered a problem where the wizard unexpectedly stopped working after I named the new database.
This happened on multiple computers, but interestingly, creating the database on a different SQL Server worked fine. After checking the Application Event Log, I found a vague .</description></item><item><title>Access Denied Party due to Unhandled Object Exception!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-denied-party-due-to-unhandled-object-exception/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 07:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-denied-party-due-to-unhandled-object-exception/</guid><description>Today, I came across a strange problem. A client could log into GP but got &amp;ldquo;Unhandled Object Exception&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Access Denied&amp;rdquo; errors when clicking on home pages or area pages. The &amp;ldquo;Unhandled Object Exceptions,&amp;rdquo; besides saying &amp;ldquo;Access Denied,&amp;rdquo; also mentioned &amp;ldquo;Error Calling Method Save,&amp;rdquo; pointing towards a permissions issue.
Some sources linked similar home page errors to missing files like &amp;ldquo;AreaPage.xsl,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;HomePage.css,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;HomePage.xsl,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;PreviewPane.xsl&amp;rdquo; in the Backgrounds folder. We checked, and the files were present.</description></item><item><title>The object name 'DYNAMICS..taErrorCode' is not valid.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-object-name-dynamics-taerrorcode-is-not-valid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-object-name-dynamics-taerrorcode-is-not-valid/</guid><description>Was it a full moon or were there sunspots causing strange occurrences?
Just tonight, while setting up a new eConnect integration on a client&amp;rsquo;s development server, I encountered a strange problem.
Upon running the integration, I was greeted with an SQL Exception error stating: &amp;ldquo;Invalid object name &amp;lsquo;DYNAMICS..taErrorCode&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;.
This was perplexing, as I have extensive experience with eConnect integrations and had never encountered this error before. My usual resources, Google and PartnerSource, provided no helpful solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>