<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ho Chi Minh on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ho-chi-minh/</link><description>Recent content in Ho Chi Minh on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ho-chi-minh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines introduces new flights to Okinawa, Hangzhou, and Ho Chi Minh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</guid><description>On March 19th, Hong Kong Airlines launched new flights for its Hong Kong-Okinawa and Hong Kong-Hangzhou routes to meet the increasing demand from business and leisure travelers. The airline celebrated the occasion with events at Hong Kong International Airport and both destination airports.
Alex Wu, Hong Kong Airlines General Manager of the Hong Kong Sales Office, welcomed passengers on the inaugural Okinawa flight HX678 with model airplanes. At the gate, passengers received certificates acknowledging their support for the new route.</description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities.</description></item></channel></rss>