<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gender on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gender/</link><description>Recent content in Gender on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gender/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Most Singaporean women believe they are compensated fairly and that their employers value their opinions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</guid><description>Milieu Insight, a Southeast Asian consumer research firm, recently surveyed women in Singapore, Indonesia, and the Philippines to gauge their perceptions of workplace support, opportunities, and rewards.
Concept art featuring a woman
generated by dream by WOMBO.
Some key takeaways include:
While 67% of Singaporean women feel adequately compensated for their work, only half believe they are appropriately rewarded for exceeding expectations.
Although 65% believe their employers welcome their input, only 50% feel that feedback is acted upon.</description></item><item><title>The more specific the mobile advertisement, the higher its earnings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</guid><description>Smaato, a mobile advertising company, has observed that the most successful advertising categories in China during the first quarter of the year were shopping, e-commerce, communication, and technology. These categories achieved high eCPMs (effective cost per mille), reaching up to US$0.30.
When analyzing mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad expenditures in China during the same period, entertainment (30%) and games (22%) were the top two categories.
Ajitpal Pannu, Smaato&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, noted that both monetization and brand spending increased when essential parameters were shared globally with advertising partners.</description></item><item><title>According to Accenture, gaining digital skills could help reduce the gender gap by up to 40 years faster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</guid><description>Source: Accenture. Closing the gender gap at work.
According to Accenture research, digital skills and technologies are empowering women in Singapore to secure and progress in their careers. However, a wage disparity persists, with men earning more. Ranked 5th out of 31 countries in Accenture&amp;rsquo;s research, Singaporean women demonstrate significant progress in digital fluency, reflecting their adoption and utilization of digital tools for knowledge acquisition, networking, and enhanced efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area.</description></item><item><title>Identifying gender through Facebook posts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</guid><description>A 2013 study featured in the research journal Plos One reveals that language use in social media can indicate a user&amp;rsquo;s gender and age. The study, &amp;ldquo;Personality, Gender, and Age in the Language of Social Media: The Open-Vocabulary Approach,&amp;rdquo; found that men and women choose distinct words and phrases online. Location and age also factor into language choices.
Singapore bank DBS&amp;rsquo; lucky red packets
The study&amp;rsquo;s authors, from the University of Pennsylvania and University of Cambridge, noted that women tend to express emotions using words like &amp;ldquo;love,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;wonderful,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;excited.</description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has received the Women Entrepreneur City Blueprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</guid><description>Source: Dell SlideShare. Cover slide for the deck introducing the Dell 2018 Women Entrepreneur Cities Study.
At the 9th annual Dell Women Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN) in Toronto, Canada, Dell introduced new analytical resources for local governments and policymakers. These tools are intended to support the success of female entrepreneurs.
Based on the findings of the 2017 Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, Dell, in partnership with research firm IHS Markit, conducted in-depth analyses.</description></item><item><title>Ipsos provides insights on fatigue regarding equal rights in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-provides-insights-on-fatigue-regarding-equal-rights-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-provides-insights-on-fatigue-regarding-equal-rights-in-singapore/</guid><description>A recent study by market research firm Ipsos reveals that 62% of Singaporeans believe that sufficient progress has been made in achieving equal rights for women in Singapore. This sentiment is more pronounced among men (68%) compared to women (55%).
This data is drawn from a larger global study conducted by Ipsos in partnership with the Global Institute for Women’s Leadership at King’s College London for International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day 2024. The survey encompassed approximately 24,000 individuals across 31 countries, with 500 respondents from Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Policies that bring about transformation could result in an increase in the number of women in leadership positions in the APAC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/policies-that-bring-about-transformation-could-result-in-an-increase-in-the-number-of-women-in-leadership-positions-in-the-apac-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/policies-that-bring-about-transformation-could-result-in-an-increase-in-the-number-of-women-in-leadership-positions-in-the-apac-region/</guid><description>This image, created by Blue Willow, depicts a generic office discussion. The artist was not given specific genders for those sitting or standing.
Recent LinkedIn data from Australia, India, and Singapore reveals a significant lack of female leadership in the Asia-Pacific region.
For example, women make up almost half of Australia&amp;rsquo;s workforce but only hold 35% of leadership roles. This figure has remained stagnant since 2020. India (23%) and Singapore (38%) show similar imbalances.</description></item><item><title>AC Ventures is investing in women-led businesses in Indonesia, with a total value of US$421 billion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</guid><description>Source: AC Ventures. Wong speaks at the Women’s CEO Forum.
Helen Wong, Managing Partner at AC Ventures, a venture capital firm focused on early-stage investments, urged for concrete actions to support women investors. She highlighted that investing in female founders in Indonesia presents a significant opportunity exceeding US$421 billion annually.
Wong made these remarks during her address at the Women’s CEO Forum held in Jakarta. This event was an officially recognized side event of the ASEAN Business &amp;amp; Investment Summit (ABIS) 2023.</description></item></channel></rss>