<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computers/</link><description>Recent content in Computers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dial-Up is Alive and Kicking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world of high-speed internet, it might seem strange to talk about dial-up. Many people consider it outdated technology.
However, dial-up internet access is still relevant. Millions of people still use and appreciate it for browsing the internet and checking emails. This &amp;ldquo;outdated&amp;rdquo; technology remains profitable.
One of the main advantages of dial-up is its affordability. Unlimited access is available for a low monthly cost, making it a budget-friendly option compared to DSL or cable internet.</description></item><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own Private Cloud Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</guid><description>Lots of small and midsize businesses are using cloud storage, particularly for disaster recovery. However, local storage is still necessary. While Storage Attached Networks (SANs) are a common solution, they&amp;rsquo;re expensive and complex. A simpler option exists.
Introducing Drobo, an advanced hard disk storage solution that&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to use. It works with standard 3.5&amp;quot; SATA drives of any capacity, resembling a straightforward multi-bay drive enclosure. Adding or removing drives, even swapping a 1 TB for a 2 TB, is always possible.</description></item><item><title>Do You Build Wide Area Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:05:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Imagine offering your clients network installations that stretch across the city or even the entire country! You might think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible, but it&amp;rsquo;s more achievable than you think.
You won&amp;rsquo;t need massive spools of wire or heavy equipment. Everything is taken care of, allowing you to focus on expanding your business and profits.
This is possible due to two key advancements: the rise of Metro and Carrier Ethernet services from competitive carriers and a business model that lets you integrate these Ethernet WAN services into your network designs.</description></item><item><title>Drobo Mr. Storage Roboto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</guid><description>Hard drive space disappears faster than you can imagine, especially with large digital media files like photos and videos. Even large hard drives fill up quickly.
While upgrading or adding hard drives seems like a solution, it creates new problems like managing backups and worrying about data loss from hard drive failures. These tasks can be time-consuming, especially for professionals working with large files. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like you need a personal assistant to manage it all.</description></item><item><title>When It Comes to Computer Networks, Trust No One and No Thing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security is a major concern for businesses today. One might even miss the days of isolated computers, unconnected to any network.
However, even those isolated computers weren&amp;rsquo;t entirely secure. Malware could still spread and confidential files could be copied through physical transfer of files using floppy disks. The challenge today is that modern networks, encompassing local networks, data centers, multiple cloud platforms, and the internet, make it incredibly difficult to track who is accessing the network and their intentions.</description></item><item><title>iPhone Getting its Video in a Sling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</guid><description>The mobile video landscape is seeing growth in various forms, including carrier-specific services like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s VCAST and Sprint TV, and dedicated channels such as MediaFLO. Sling Media&amp;rsquo;s introduction of a SlingPlayer for iPhone has the potential to disrupt the market by giving control of content back to the user.
Sling Media is known for its Slingbox, a device that connects to your television source (satellite receiver, DVR, or cable box) and a broadband connection.</description></item><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?</description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business.</description></item><item><title>We Welcome a New iMac to the Family</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-welcome-a-new-imac-to-the-family/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 10:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-welcome-a-new-imac-to-the-family/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday afternoon, and I&amp;rsquo;m eagerly waiting for a delivery that seems to be taking forever. Finally, after hours of waiting, the FedEx truck arrives, carrying the item I&amp;rsquo;ve been anticipating for a week: a brand new, customized 24-inch Apple iMac.
You might wonder why I&amp;rsquo;m so excited, considering it took me a year after deciding to buy a new computer to finally order it. After all, I was a dedicated Mac user for over a decade before switching to PCs ten years ago.</description></item><item><title>We're Looking For Successful IT Consultants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</guid><description>Are you an experienced IT professional looking to expand your consulting business? If you specialize in voice and data network design, implementation, and troubleshooting, and perhaps even hold certifications with equipment vendors, we have an opportunity for you.
We&amp;rsquo;re offering a chance to grow your business with minimal effort. Gain access to new clients in your area and expand your service offerings without any upfront costs or extensive training. This is a simple way to boost your existing business.</description></item><item><title>Manage Your Cables Before They Manage You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/manage-your-cables-before-they-manage-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/manage-your-cables-before-they-manage-you/</guid><description>Network cabling can quickly become chaotic and overwhelming, much like weeds taking over an empty lot. Unorganized wiring, often referred to as a &amp;ldquo;rat&amp;rsquo;s nest,&amp;rdquo; is a common problem that creates confusion and makes troubleshooting difficult.
The solution to this problem is simple: organization. While organizing existing cables can be tedious, it is essential and best done sooner rather than later. Designing a structured cabling system from the outset is the most effective approach.</description></item><item><title>Take Your Office PC With You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</guid><description>Mobile professionals often rely on their laptops but might find themselves needing files left on their office desktops. Traveling long distances back for these files isn&amp;rsquo;t always feasible.
Imagine accessing your office desktop from anywhere, anytime. This eliminates the worry of having the right files and removes the need for duplicates. Your laptop and a special application are all you need to make any computer your office computer.
GoToMyPC is a remote access software, or KVM application, that allows this.</description></item><item><title>Smart Grids Picking the Bones of BPL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</guid><description>Were you eagerly anticipating the day when your electrical outlets would provide both electricity and high-speed internet? That dream might not materialize. Broadband over Power Line (BPL), as a consumer internet option, appears to be fading. However, despite complaints from amateur radio operators about interference, BPL is not disappearing entirely. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s transforming into a utility-focused communication system, potentially offering a solution that benefits everyone.
The turning point for BPL may have been the recent news that Current Communications is ending its BPL service in Dallas, initially intended for 2 million homes.</description></item><item><title>Telecom Providers Build Their Own Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</guid><description>As cloud computing companies start to establish themselves, internet service providers and similar carriers are developing their own cloud services. This creates a challenge for IT professionals and business owners who need to choose the best option.
It’s important to recognize that cloud computing is still in its early stages. Like any new technology, it will take time for it to fully develop. As the technology progresses, we will see a lot of activity from many different companies.</description></item><item><title>What Becomes Of The Broken Hardware?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</guid><description>_While troubleshooting a LAN for faulty wiring, I&amp;rsquo;m haunted by thoughts of server failures. The concept of uptime seems like a cruel joke, and I&amp;rsquo;m desperate for a solution.
What happens to malfunctioning equipment that dies prematurely? I need to determine the root cause of this outage.
The list of underlying issues is extensive, and the network is collapsing. The pressure mounts daily, becoming unbearable.
I examine server logs, looking for answers while facing the frustrated stares of the staff who demand updates.</description></item><item><title>Fight For Your Right to Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fight-for-your-right-to-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fight-for-your-right-to-broadband/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with slow internet speeds that interrupt your work and entertainment? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Despite being a global leader, the United States lags behind in internet access, ranking 16th globally in broadband subscriptions per capita.
While South Korea boasts 24.9 subscriptions per 100 people, the US has only 11.4. Furthermore, South Korea enjoys speeds of 45.50 Mbps, while Japan leads with 61 Mbps. In contrast, the US averages a mere 1.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Frame Relay, Hello MPLS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</guid><description>Managing communication across multiple business locations can be challenging. While private lines offer a solution, their cost increases with the number of locations. Frame Relay, a private network solution, gained popularity for its reliability, security, and affordability. However, MPLS networks have emerged as a newer technology offering higher bandwidth and lower costs.
Frame Relay bridges the gap between public switched telephone networks and dedicated private lines. It replaces physical wires with virtual circuits, eliminating the need for dedicated circuits that incur costs regardless of usage.</description></item><item><title>The VoSKY is the Limit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</guid><description>Skype, known for free international calls, has become a major player with over 300 million users and a growing presence in the corporate world.
While some might think Skype is just for techies, it has evolved significantly since eBay acquired it in 2005. Beyond basic computer-to-computer calls, a range of hardware now complements Skype, resembling traditional phone setups.
VoSKY, a California-based company, exemplifies this trend, catering to both home users and large companies.</description></item><item><title>Iomega Zips Into Network Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</guid><description>Do you recall the Zip drive? When floppy disks were the standard for backups, Zip drives offered a remarkable hundredfold increase in capacity using removable cartridges. While hard drives now boast hundreds of gigabytes and beyond, leaving floppies and even Zip disks in the past, Iomega, the company behind the Zip drive, has continued to innovate. Their product line has expanded beyond desktops and into the server room.
Iomega, now a part of EMC, a Fortune 500 company specializing in enterprise storage solutions, still caters to individuals and small offices.</description></item><item><title>USB 3.0 Offers Gbps Data Transfers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usb-30-offers-gbps-data-transfers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:28:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usb-30-offers-gbps-data-transfers/</guid><description>The arrival of USB 2.0 as a replacement for 1.1 nearly achieved the universal connectivity goal of its name. With a tenfold speed increase, USB 3.0, or &amp;ldquo;SuperSpeed,&amp;rdquo; aims to further solidify USB&amp;rsquo;s dominance.
While the existing 480 Mbps speed of USB 2.0 serves many devices well, surpassing the original USB 1.0&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 to 12 Mbps, the need for faster data transfer, especially for video, is evident. This need prompted the shift from FireWire to mini-USB in most video cameras.</description></item><item><title>Free Color Printers, Really?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-color-printers-really/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 15:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-color-printers-really/</guid><description>The introduction of television after World War II brought small, black and white images into homes. While basic, it was considered an improvement over radio. However, the arrival of color television quickly overshadowed its predecessor. Suddenly, black and white images seemed inadequate, especially when compared to the vibrant colors offered by the newer technology.
Similarly, early desktop computers displayed images in monochrome, often limited to black and white or basic color combinations.</description></item><item><title>Where Have All The IPs Gone?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-have-all-the-ips-gone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-have-all-the-ips-gone/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Where have all the IPs gone? Gone to users every one.&amp;rdquo;
- apologies to Pete Seeger
Have you heard? The internet is full. It&amp;rsquo;s expected to reach its limit in the next few years. This means no new users, websites, or online services. It&amp;rsquo;s like a club that&amp;rsquo;s reached capacity; they&amp;rsquo;ll have to turn people away at the door. &amp;ldquo;Here, take a pager, and we&amp;rsquo;ll call you when it&amp;rsquo;s your turn.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington</description></item><item><title>Banish Vampires To Reduce Global Warming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 08:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</guid><description>Electronic devices, like hidden vampires, silently drain electricity even when seemingly off. This &amp;ldquo;vampire power&amp;rdquo; not only increases your electricity bill but also contributes to global warming.
These &amp;ldquo;vampires&amp;rdquo; hide within devices, indicated by glowing lights, active displays, running fans, or warm surfaces, even when the device is switched off. Remote-controlled devices are prime suspects, as they constantly use power to stay ready for remote signals. Similarly, wireless networks and devices are notorious power consumers.</description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections.</description></item><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions.</description></item><item><title>Why GHz is So Last Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 09:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</guid><description>GigaHertz, representing a billion cycles per second, has become the standard, making MegaHertz seem outdated. However, as technology advances, even GigaHertz might be surpassed by TeraHertz speeds, potentially rendering current benchmarks obsolete.
In the early days of personal computers, 640 KB of RAM seemed excessive. However, as software evolved, demanding more resources with graphics, images, and the rise of the internet, hardware struggled to keep up. It took decades for platforms to mature and offer sufficient RAM, hard drive space, and processor speeds.</description></item><item><title>Holy Guacamole, It's Green Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</guid><description>The internet&amp;rsquo;s days of excessive energy consumption might be ending. Websites and online businesses contribute to environmental issues, but we can&amp;rsquo;t just abandon the technology we rely on. We need a more sustainable solution: eco-friendly hosting.
The demand for electricity is increasing while clean energy sources are limited. Traditional power sources like coal are harmful, and even with reduced emissions, they still contribute to climate change. Renewable energy is becoming a viable solution.</description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1.</description></item><item><title>Is Municipal WiFi On The Way Out?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</guid><description>While WiFi hotspots are incredibly convenient for travelers in airports, hotels, and restaurants, city-wide WiFi hasn&amp;rsquo;t been as successful as initially hoped. The recent closure of Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s Metro WiFi in Philadelphia raises questions about the future of this technology, even though broadband internet is thriving.
Despite a significant increase in broadband adoption, with dial-up becoming nearly obsolete, city-wide WiFi providers are struggling. Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s experience in Philadelphia, where they only gained a fraction of their projected subscribers, highlights this challenge.</description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 22:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</guid><description>For a long time, the idea of &amp;ldquo;rural broadband&amp;rdquo; seemed contradictory. While cities enjoyed a variety of high-speed internet options, from DSL and cable to fiber optic connections, rural areas remained stuck with slow dial-up or satellite internet. Although high-speed business lines have become more affordable, fiber optic cables in rural areas were deemed too expensive. However, an organization in Vermont is challenging this assumption.
ValleyFiber, led by Dr. Timothy Nulty, is bringing fiber optic broadband to rural homes and businesses in Vermont&amp;rsquo;s Upper Valley.</description></item><item><title>How the ZAC Browser Helps Autistic Kids</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-zac-browser-helps-autistic-kids/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 03:54:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-zac-browser-helps-autistic-kids/</guid><description>Occasionally, you find a story that leaves you amazed. I recently encountered one such story, &amp;ldquo;Grandfather builds Web browser for autistic boy,&amp;rdquo; about a software developer who took action when his six-year-old grandson struggled to use the internet. This might not seem unusual at first, but the situation becomes clearer with more context.
Zackary, the six-year-old grandson, has autism, making communication and interaction difficult, and he rarely speaks. He finds joy in games, music, and puzzles, many available online.</description></item></channel></rss>