<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hailing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hailing/</link><description>Recent content in Hailing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:17:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hailing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Makani numbers in Dubai assist taxi drivers in locating their customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</guid><description>Source: RTA. Dubai taxis are now connected to the city through the Makani system.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) Public Transport Agency has successfully connected 4,500 taxis operated by franchise companies to the Dubai Municipality&amp;rsquo;s Makani System. This system utilizes unique coordinates, known as Makani numbers, for precise building location.
Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems at RTA&amp;rsquo;s Public Transport Agency, highlighted the significant role of the Makani System.</description></item><item><title>Uber has expanded its services to Seremban, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 08:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Uber. UberX is arriving in Seremban in December
Uber is expanding its services to Seremban, the eighth city in Malaysia to have Uber. Starting December 1, 2016, residents of Seremban can hail a ride via the UberX service. This launch comes after the successful introduction of UberX in Melaka on October 27, 2016.
Uber also presents earning opportunities for driver-partners using their own vehicles. Drivers have the flexibility to set their own schedules and determine their earnings.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can enjoy Careem services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 14:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</guid><description>Source: Careem website. Emirates Skywards partners with Careem to provide benefits for their members.
Emirates Skywards, the loyalty program for Emirates, has partnered with Careem. This makes Emirates Skywards the only frequent flyer program to provide both earning and redemption opportunities with the leading car booking app in the region.
Careem is a rapidly growing company, currently operating in nine countries. Members can earn and redeem Skywards Miles when using Careem services in the UAE, Qatar, KSA, Lebanon, Jordan, Egypt, Pakistan, Kuwait, and Morocco.</description></item></channel></rss>