<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 CAS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-cas/</link><description>Recent content in T1 CAS on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-cas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>