<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Damages on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/damages/</link><description>Recent content in Damages on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/damages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An important Irish ruling on compensation for violation of EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) affirmed the right of individuals to sue Member States for damages resulting from breaches of EU law over two decades ago in the Francovich case, most subsequent lawsuits have been initiated by businesses seeking compensation for financial losses. The CJEU has yet to address a case involving damages claims related to the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU clarifies CILFIT regarding the final courts' obligations to refer questions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-clarifies-cilfit-regarding-the-final-courts-obligations-to-refer-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-clarifies-cilfit-regarding-the-final-courts-obligations-to-refer-questions/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
In a previous post, I argued that the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) held national supreme courts to a higher standard than the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) regarding preliminary references to the CJEU. I suggested this was due to the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s ruling in the CILFIT case. However, the CJEU has recently proven me wrong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-clarifies-cilfit-regarding-the-final-courts-obligations-to-refer-questions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-clarifies-cilfit-regarding-the-final-courts-obligations-to-refer-questions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Europol's Joint and Several Liability Regime Transforming Responsibility for EU Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 03:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Dr Joyce de Coninck, University of Ghent
Photo credit: Oseveno Introduction The Europol Regulation introduces a shared responsibility framework for the EU concerning unlawful data processing that violates Articles 7 and 8 of the Charter of Fundamental Rights. This developing system of liability is at the center of the Marián Kočner v Europol case, highlighting the need for clarity regarding joint responsibility for human rights violations when EU agencies and Member States collaborate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice in Bank Refah Kargaran making a groundbreaking decision by allowing action for damages in relation to CFSP decisions regarding restrictive measures?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</guid><description>Professor Dr. Peter Van Elsuwege and Joyce De Coninck (PhD Researcher), Ghent European Law Institute
The recent Grand Chamber judgment in the case of Bank Refah Kargaran v Council, issued on October 6, 2020, sheds further light on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) jurisdiction concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). Drawing on previous judgments such as Elitaliana, H v. Council, Rosneft, and SatCen vs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Responsibility in Joint Returns after WS and Others v Frontex: Letting the Active By-Stander Off the Hook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</guid><description>A Missed Opportunity for Accountability: Examining the General Court&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in WS and others v Frontex This analysis delves into the General Court&amp;rsquo;s September 6, 2023, decision in the case of WS and others v Frontex, where a Syrian refugee family&amp;rsquo;s claim for damages against Frontex was dismissed. The family, seeking refuge in the EU during the Syrian war, was returned to Turkey under questionable circumstances involving a joint return operation between Greece and Frontex...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where are EU Consumers' Actions for Damages Headed?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/</guid><description>By Sonsoles Prieto, EU competition law practitioner, London*
EU Member States are nearing the deadline to implement the EU Damages Directive. This directive aims to empower consumers and small businesses to seek damages from parties who violate competition law.
Although the need for such a directive was questioned in the past, the current perspective has significantly shifted. Nevertheless, adapting to this new approach presents ongoing challenges.
Background
Adopted in December 2014, the Directive mandates that all EU and EEA member states ensure individuals and entities impacted by competition law violations can claim and receive full compensation for their losses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-eu-consumers-actions-for-damages-headed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>After the Steinhoff case, the ECB has an increased responsibility to uphold and advocate for the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Diane Fromage, Maastricht University*
* I am grateful to Menelaos Markakis for his insightful feedback.
On March 12, 2020, the Court of Justice dismissed an appeal concerning the Steinhoff case (T-107/17), previously decided by the General Court in May 2019. This case, though not widely discussed, holds significant weight as it clarifies and broadens the European Central Bank (ECB)&amp;rsquo;s obligation to &amp;lsquo;respect the rights [of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (ECFR)], [to] observe the principles and [to] promote the application thereof&amp;rsquo; as stated in Article 51 ECFR, specifically concerning its advisory role...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU General Court's ruling in the WS and Others v Frontex case: Failure to hold accountable human rights violations at EU external borders.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</guid><description>Francesca Romana Partipilo, PhD candidate in International Law at Sant&amp;rsquo;Anna School of Advanced Studies (Pisa)
Photo credit: Rock Cohen, via Wikimedia commons
(see also critique of the judgment, by Melanie Fink and Jorrit Rijpma)
On September 6th, the EU General Court dismissed a case brought by a Syrian family claiming material and emotional damages from Frontex. They alleged experiencing anguish, fear, and suffering due to Frontex&amp;rsquo;s actions during a return operation conducted jointly with Greece on October 20th, 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>