<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VoIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voip/</link><description>Recent content in VoIP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>Is The End Of Cellular Phone Near?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</guid><description>Cell phones are essential to modern life, but a recent development calls into question the future of cellular service. The release of the Apple iPad and its allowance of VoIP applications over 3G cellular networks, along with AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network adjustments for this capability, signal a potential shift in the telecommunications landscape.
Why is this significant? Cellular networks have historically blocked VoIP due to its potential to congest networks and cannibalize voice call revenue.</description></item><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Duet Combines Voice and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses need both phone and internet services. Their phone systems often start small and expand over time, adding lines as needed. Similarly, internet service might begin with dial-up, transition to DSL, and eventually upgrade to dedicated connections for better reliability.
This piecemeal approach often leads to businesses overspending on telecommunications. Optimizing these systems could potentially cut costs by up to 50%.
The key to saving money is bundling services.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses.</description></item><item><title>Why Business Needs Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-business-needs-unified-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There was a time when the only way to communicate electronically was with that clunky black phone on your desk. While that phone might still be there, modern technology has made it lighter and brought a wealth of new communication methods. Email, text messages, mobile phone calls, and video chats are now commonplace across various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, smartphones, and even watches.
A significant challenge, particularly in business, is that these platforms and applications don&amp;rsquo;t always work well together.</description></item><item><title>TalkSwitch Supports both VoIP and Legacy PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</guid><description>Choosing between a traditional phone system (analog or digital TDM PBX) and a newer VoIP system can be tough. TalkSwitch offers a solution by supporting both technologies.
For example, the TalkSwitch 244vs desktop PBX handles 2 incoming lines, 4 extensions for analog phones, and features like voicemail and music on hold. It also supports 10 remote extensions, allowing cell phones, home phones, and phones on other systems to connect by dialing a 3-digit extension.</description></item><item><title>SMB Phone System Needs Only Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</guid><description>The simplicity of traditional phone systems, where plugging in a phone provided immediate dial tone, is making a comeback with cloud-based communication systems.
This modern approach, known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, shifts the responsibility of complex switching equipment to a service provider. This means the provider manages updates, maintenance, and scalability, leaving you with only the phones to handle.
These aren&amp;rsquo;t your typical phones; they are IP phones designed for computer networks, using different electrical signals and connectors.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Office Hosted Telecommunications at Half Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-office-hosted-telecommunications-at-half-price/</guid><description>Upgrading your business phone system can be pricey, but hosted telecommunications, like Packet8&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Office, offers a more affordable solution. For a limited time, they&amp;rsquo;re offering a 50% discount, making it even more budget-friendly.
Instead of buying and managing your own phone system, hosted telecommunications lets a specialized company handle the equipment and services. You simply plug in your phones wherever you need them. Packet8&amp;rsquo;s Virtual Office utilizes an internet-based PBX system, eliminating the need for on-site equipment.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs ISDN PRI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses have moved past analog phone lines, embracing PBX systems and ISDN PRI for their communication needs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: SIP Trunking. This technology offers potential cost and performance benefits for companies looking to enhance their voice services. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SIP Trunks with ISDN PRI to understand the best choice for your organization.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that both technologies rely on digital telephony, eliminating analog transmission.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>Ethernet WAN is the most significant advancement in business broadband since T1 service prices dropped. What exactly is Ethernet WAN, and why should you care?
Ethernet has become the dominant standard for Local Area Networks (LANs). You could say that Ethernet is everywhere. An RJ45 Ethernet jack is standard on every desktop and laptop computer. You might not get a CD-ROM drive, probably won&amp;rsquo;t get a floppy disc drive, and may never use the phone modem jack again.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location.</description></item><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone IP Communications offers Polished VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses usually don&amp;rsquo;t spend much effort on their telecommunication systems, often starting with basic necessities like desk phones, internet service, and maybe a simple VoIP system. It&amp;rsquo;s manageable for the owner or an office manager. However, as these businesses grow, their communication needs change. Suddenly, managing communication among numerous employees and locations becomes challenging. Reaching colleagues becomes difficult, and clients experience poor connection quality, leading to apologies. This situation calls for a &amp;ldquo;forklift upgrade.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>Lonliness of the Long Distance Landline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</guid><description>Recent data shows people are rapidly ditching landlines. If Alexander Graham Bell were alive today, he&amp;rsquo;d have trouble reaching anyone on his original invention. Instead, he&amp;rsquo;d have much better luck using a cell phone, just like everyone else.
It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that most people own a cell phone, or even multiple old ones. People want to be constantly connected, even when they perhaps shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be. Observe drivers at a stoplight, and you&amp;rsquo;ll likely spot several talking on their phones.</description></item><item><title>Managed IP Networks Enable Voice and Data Convergence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 04:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</guid><description>Businesses have been looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing service, and combining their computer and telephone networks into a single, multi-functional LAN that can connect to the public Internet and phone network seems like a good way to do it. Ideally, this means one network, one connection per desk, and one support team. However, the reality isn&amp;rsquo;t always so simple.
The reason for this is that computers and telephones use networks in very different ways.</description></item><item><title>Voice over Internet Protocol Phone Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) suggests it will likely replace traditional phone services, including landlines and ISDN PRI. This shift is primarily driven by the transition from traditional telephone networks to computer-based networks, further complicated by the emergence of wireless voice and data services.
Telephone networks, largely analog during their long history, were initially designed solely for voice communication. While attempts were made to use them for data transfer with analog modems, the limited bandwidth of these networks proved insufficient for anything beyond low-speed data.</description></item><item><title>Super Cheap Business Phone Service for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the economy slowly recovers, controlling business expenses, including phone bills, remains crucial. Many businesses find themselves overspending on phone services.
Businesses often begin with a single traditional phone line. As they expand, they might add cordless phones sharing that line or install a second line. While sufficient for small offices, this setup lacks the features and cost savings of PBX or enterprise VoIP systems.
Fortunately, small businesses can utilize network voice solutions, also known as VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), to reduce phone costs significantly.</description></item><item><title>Free International Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</guid><description>During tough economic times, everyone appreciates a good deal, especially free offers. Phone Power is offering free international calls through 2008 to promote its competitive business and residential VoIP services. This is a great opportunity for anyone who makes a lot of international calls. Even after the promotion ends, Phone Power&amp;rsquo;s rates remain very affordable.
This holiday season, you can call landlines in the following countries for free: United Kingdom (44), Spain (34), Ireland (353), Israel (972), Germany (49), Singapore (65), France (33), Denmark (45), Greece (30), Italy (39), and China (86).</description></item><item><title>High Quality Call Termination With SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Prioritizing voice packets on a network ensures high-quality VoIP calls within an organization. However, connecting to the outside world poses a challenge due to the incompatibility between modern packet-switched networks and the traditional circuit-switched phone system. To bridge this gap, organizations can either manage the conversion internally or outsource it to a third-party provider through SIP trunking.
SIP trunking offers a potentially cost-effective solution by consolidating multiple phone lines into a single &amp;ldquo;trunk&amp;rdquo; line and utilizing the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for call switching.</description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers.</description></item><item><title>Browser Based Video Conferencing and Webinars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</guid><description>Once restricted to businesses, video conferencing is now accessible to anyone with an internet connection and a web browser. MegaMeeting offers a suite of products for PCs, Macs, and Linux computers that don&amp;rsquo;t require typical downloads or installations. As long as you can use a web browser, you can participate in video conferences and webinars.
MegaMeeting&amp;rsquo;s web-based system utilizes the Flash Player 9 plugin, commonly found in browsers like Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari.</description></item><item><title>Wireless SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Traditionally, business phone lines and dedicated internet relied on physical wires. However, wireless SIP trunking is emerging as a new option.
](http://www.affordablevpn.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
Airband Communications, a frontrunner in this technology, offers business-class voice services packaged with wireless internet access. This is comparable to a SIP trunk or an integrated voice and data service in the wired world, but Airband&amp;rsquo;s offering presents unique benefits.
Similar to other integrated services, a single connection provides both phone and internet access, only in this case, it&amp;rsquo;s wireless.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX For Features and Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</guid><description>Determining if it&amp;rsquo;s the right moment to transition your business phone system to a cloud-based solution is crucial, especially if your current system struggles with capacity, needs frequent fixes, or lacks vendor support. However, even if your current system functions adequately, you might be overlooking opportunities to enhance productivity and reduce communication expenses with modern hosted PBX solutions.
A prime illustration is AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s updated Cloud Hosted IP PBX, AirePBX version 2.</description></item><item><title>Know the Lingo to Save Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</guid><description>To succeed with technology, you need to understand the terminology. This is especially true for VoIP telephony, where &amp;ldquo;Lingo&amp;rdquo; can refer to both the industry jargon and a specific company.
Lingo, the company, offers broadband phone services for residential and business users. These services provide significant cost savings compared to traditional landlines, especially for international calls from the US.
Residential plans include options like Chatter Box, Global Gabber, and Lingo Link, each with unique features and pricing.</description></item><item><title>Finding Information on PBX Telephone Systems Pricing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 15:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</guid><description>Planning a new office building or hotel? Upgrading your old business phone system? Finding the right PBX system at the right price is essential for a smart decision.
Instead of searching endlessly, utilize an online clearinghouse like the VAR Network. This platform connects businesses with qualified PBX and network equipment vendors.
The VAR Network focuses on these two interconnected technologies. Most businesses rely on both for internal communication and internet access.</description></item><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential.</description></item><item><title>Phone Power... To The People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:43:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</guid><description>VoIP and broadband phone services for businesses and residential customers are steadily replacing the century-old traditional phone industry. The reason? Price!
Traditional phone service relies on tariffs that charge for every little thing. You pay for the line, local service, long distance, and extra features like Caller ID. They even charge a monthly fee for maintaining the wiring in your home! It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that phone bills can be shockingly high.</description></item><item><title>VoIP is For Smaller Companies Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-is-for-smaller-companies-too/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 10:22:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-is-for-smaller-companies-too/</guid><description>Many people think Enterprise VoIP solutions are too complex and costly for small businesses. While that&amp;rsquo;s often accurate, advanced IP PBX systems can sometimes boost productivity for smaller, sophisticated companies. However, for those seeking quality calls at reasonable prices, SMB (Small and Medium Business) VoIP solutions can be the perfect solution.
VoIP ranges from using your computer as a phone to systems that are virtually identical to standard network-switched technologies. Home-based businesses might prefer VoIP services that utilize their existing Cable or DSL broadband for internet access.</description></item><item><title>I Shall Call It Cellular Mini-Me</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</guid><description>The change from landlines to mobile phones is accelerating as 3G networks expand coverage to suburban and rural areas. Smartphones like the BlackBerry and iPhone are becoming ubiquitous, prompting questions about the necessity of laptops. Wireless technology offers liberation from desktops, allowing users to communicate, browse, and enjoy videos on the move. However, this freedom is often hindered indoors.
Indoor spaces present a significant obstacle to wireless transmission. Walls and other barriers weaken high-frequency radio signals, leading to dropped calls and poor connectivity.</description></item><item><title>PRI Lines For Domestic Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are turning to domestic call centers, whether they are in-house or independent contractors. All call centers rely on telephone service, and PRI lines are the preferred choice. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, belongs to the Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) standard. ISDN aimed to transition all telephone lines from analog to digital. The basic offering, BRI (Basic Rate Interface), provides two phone lines or one phone line with either a 64 Kbps or 128 Kbps data service.</description></item><item><title>What Is MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</guid><description>MPLS networks are frequently mentioned as a way to connect multiple business locations. But what exactly is MPLS, and why is it superior to other network architectures?
MPLS, or Multi-Protocol Label Switching, is a technology distinct from traditional circuit-switched or packet-switched networks. While it allows IP traffic transmission, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t rely on IP routing.
The advantage of MPLS networks lies in their ability to handle almost any protocol without requiring conversions to fit the network structure.</description></item><item><title>The Need for Low Latency Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</guid><description>When discussing network performance, bandwidth is often the primary focus. Higher bandwidth is equated with faster speeds, allowing for quicker file transfers and increased productivity. However, another crucial aspect of network performance, latency, has gained significant attention recently.
Latency refers to the time delay within a network, specifically the time it takes for data packets to travel between nodes. While it might seem related to bandwidth, latency is a distinct characteristic.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking and Internet On a T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</guid><description>Many smaller companies utilize T1 lines for dedicated internet access, opting for this solution after experiencing unreliable or unavailable consumer-grade broadband options. T1 lines offer these businesses dependable, robust bandwidth at increasingly affordable prices. However, many are unaware that they can bundle their broadband and telephone services onto a single T1 line.
Traditional T1 lines offer various service options. The original format, designed for the telephone industry, provides 24 channels of digitized telephone service over two pairs of twisted copper phone wires.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need A Special Phone For VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:19:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</guid><description>Many people ask if a special phone is required for VoIP service. The answer depends on the situation.
Regular phones can&amp;rsquo;t plug directly into internet equipment because they use incompatible connectors. To bridge this gap, you need a special phone or an adapter.
Many residential and small business VoIP services, like PhonePower, offer adapters. These adapters allow you to connect your existing phone to your internet modem or router. Inside the adapter, circuitry converts the analog signals of your phone into digital packets for the internet, and vice versa.</description></item><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service.</description></item><item><title>The VoSKY is the Limit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</guid><description>Skype, known for free international calls, has become a major player with over 300 million users and a growing presence in the corporate world.
While some might think Skype is just for techies, it has evolved significantly since eBay acquired it in 2005. Beyond basic computer-to-computer calls, a range of hardware now complements Skype, resembling traditional phone setups.
VoSKY, a California-based company, exemplifies this trend, catering to both home users and large companies.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Comes To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s professionals juggle multiple devices like smartphones, tablets, and laptops in addition to their office setups, which often include desktop computers, LAN connections, and speakerphones. This begs the question: how can we unify these devices for a seamless workflow?
This multifaceted connectivity issue has plagued corporate IT departments for years as communication devices multiply faster than solutions for integrating them. Often, the simplest answer is printing business cards with separate numbers for each device.</description></item><item><title>Phone Power’s $14.95 A Month VoIP Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 08:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</guid><description>Are you thinking about switching to VoIP phone service, but put off by the high prices? That doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense! VoIP is meant to be a cheaper alternative to traditional landlines. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s still hope. Phone Power offers a fully featured residential and home office VoIP service for only $14.95 per month.
That&amp;rsquo;s more like it! Why pay $25 or $35 per month for local and long-distance calling when you can get the same or better service for $14.</description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Better Than a T3 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 voice and data lines, once a reliable option for businesses, now offer insufficient speed (45 Mbps) for modern demands, which often exceed 100 Mbps. Businesses today require significantly faster connections, with some even seeking speeds beyond 10 Gbps. If you&amp;rsquo;re still using a T3 line, you might find better bandwidth options at a similar or lower cost.
What is a T3 Line?
Developed by Bell Labs, the T3 line was designed to carry numerous simultaneous phone conversations, a function it still serves in certain settings.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand.</description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings.</description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-phone-service/</guid><description>A recent study reveals that a majority of cellphone and landline users spend more than they should on their phone services, often significantly exceeding reasonable costs. This overpayment can be as high as $3 per minute for landlines and $3 overall for cell phones.
While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this doesn&amp;rsquo;t apply to you, it&amp;rsquo;s worth examining your phone usage closely. Have you analyzed your phone bills recently? The results might surprise you.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Telecommunications from Packet8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</guid><description>If your company is outgrowing its current phone system but a full-blown PBX system seems like overkill, there&amp;rsquo;s a middle ground: hosted telecommunications.
Instead of housing your own PBX equipment, hosted solutions put that functionality in the cloud, similar to website hosting. You get all the features of an in-house system without the bulky hardware. Your office phones connect to the provider&amp;rsquo;s equipment through your broadband connection.
Packet8 is a leading provider of hosted telecom for small to medium businesses.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>T1 Telephony Has Many Flavors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</guid><description>Initially designed for high-volume call transfer between telephone exchanges, T1 technology has evolved into a leading digital phone solution for businesses. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering T1, understanding the available options is crucial.
T1 is a digital standard supporting voice, data, video, or a combination thereof. Originally, it carried 24 separate calls on individual channels called DS0s, collectively forming a T1 line or DS1. Each DS0 transmits digitized voice, call control, and signaling information.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally.</description></item><item><title>Clearest International Calls on Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clearest-international-calls-on-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 20:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clearest-international-calls-on-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Are you looking for the clearest international calls from your mobile phone without the drawbacks of VoIP? There is a solution, especially for those in the U.S. and Canada, that offers both clear calls and low rates.
A specialized service integrates with your existing cell phone to provide economical international calls with superior voice quality.
Tel3Advantage&amp;rsquo;s international long distance service offers rates as low as 1 cent per minute. Their current promotion includes discounted rates for the first 30 days and free minutes upon registration.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages.</description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably.</description></item><item><title>Is MagicJack The Next Ma Bell?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-magicjack-the-next-ma-bell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-magicjack-the-next-ma-bell/</guid><description>The telephone industry is facing challenges as young people are increasingly abandoning traditional landlines, which were once considered essential by previous generations. The breakup of the Bell System into smaller regional companies suggests that the era of a single, all-encompassing telephone provider is over. However, the story doesn&amp;rsquo;t end there.
While it&amp;rsquo;s true that cell phones have replaced landlines for a significant portion of the population, particularly among younger demographics who have grown up with wireless technology, the evolution of the industry goes beyond this shift.</description></item><item><title>HFC Broadband For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>Many small businesses don&amp;rsquo;t fit into the &amp;ldquo;residential&amp;rdquo; user category but don&amp;rsquo;t require or can&amp;rsquo;t afford expensive traditional business telecom services like T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper. One solution is HFC, or Hybrid Fiber Coax, broadband services.
You might know this as &amp;ldquo;Cable broadband for business.&amp;rdquo; Many home-based businesses successfully use it to manage websites, access online information, and send and receive emails. However, ordering residential service for a business location usually results in rejection.</description></item><item><title>How HD Audio Will Transform VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</guid><description>People who recall the era of analog phones and physical switches often feel nostalgic about the superior audio quality of those systems. The conversations back then possessed a clarity and immediacy that has largely vanished in recent times, though this might be changing soon. A new movement is underway to enhance the fidelity of VoIP calls significantly, aiming to make current phones seem primitive in comparison.
This advancement is known as high-definition audio or HD Voice, a term used by Polycom, a manufacturer of IP phones equipped with this technology.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach.</description></item><item><title>Why Are VoIP and SIP Trunking So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</guid><description>When your outdated PBX system needs an upgrade, consider transitioning to an IP PBX and replacing traditional phone lines with a SIP Trunk. This shift to modern technologies is driven by their ability to deliver new features and cost savings without compromising call quality.
Upgrading doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require replacing existing phones. While VoIP SIP phones offer advantages like network connectivity and simplified management, older phones can connect to the IP PBX via interface cards with FSX ports.</description></item><item><title>Low Latency Connections Bridge The Atlantic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 05:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</guid><description>The immense volume of data flowing through global fiber optic networks highlights our interconnected world. While intercontinental cables have existed for years, low latency networks are becoming increasingly vital.
High-frequency trading, particularly the use of automated programs, drives the demand for low latency. These programs compete to execute trades milliseconds or even microseconds faster than competitors, a feat impossible for human traders. This speed makes the physical path between traders and exchanges critical, with the delay on this path known as latency.</description></item><item><title>When Your Broadband Isn’t Stable Enough For VoIP Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You might get laughed at for sticking with your old-school analog phone lines. &amp;ldquo;Still using a rotary phone?&amp;rdquo; they&amp;rsquo;ll joke. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: those old-fashioned phone lines were built for clear sound and unwavering reliability. Sure, they might deteriorate over time, leading to static and eventually dropped calls. A quick fix from the phone company, though, and you&amp;rsquo;re back in business for years to come.
The modern approach is using the internet for phone calls, combining your phone and internet services onto one broadband connection.</description></item><item><title>866 Toll Free Numbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 18:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</guid><description>Everyone knows about 800 numbers; they were the original toll-free option. But did you know there are others, like 866? Is it truly toll-free?
Yes, 866 is indeed toll-free. It functions identically to 800; the difference is simply in the prefix. Just like area codes (202 for Washington, DC, 302 for Delaware), these prefixes are assigned nationwide.
This highlights a key difference: toll prefixes are location-specific (area codes), while toll-free prefixes are not.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient.</description></item><item><title>Types of Business Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Over time, business phone lines have evolved from a single analog option to a variety of choices. While you can still get traditional analog lines, various digital options offer potential cost and performance benefits.
The standard business phone line remains largely unchanged from its origins over a century ago, using a single twisted pair of copper wires to carry signals. This analog line, also called POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is the basis for multi-line phones connecting to multiple POTS lines, commonly seen in small office phone systems with one to four lines.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Holiday Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</guid><description>The holiday season is approaching quickly, bringing with it a surge in shopping activity. Both physical stores and online retailers experience their highest sales volumes during this period. Businesses need to ensure their systems can handle this increased demand to avoid losing customers to competitors.
While increasing server capacity is important, businesses often overlook the importance of sufficient bandwidth. A congested Wide Area Network (WAN) connection can lead to delays and disconnections, impacting order processing and customer service.</description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past.</description></item><item><title>QT Talk is Both VoIP and Dial-Around</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</guid><description>Many people are interested in VoIP phone service because of its features and affordability, but they also want the freedom of mobile calling. QT Talk offers a solution that combines the advantages of VoIP with the flexibility of cellular service.
QT Talk provides a feature-rich VoIP service, including their popular North America Plus plan. For a low monthly fee, users enjoy unlimited calls to the U.S., Canada, and Puerto Rico, along with a reduced rate to select international destinations.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness.</description></item><item><title>Where Competition Is Cutting Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</guid><description>In this day and age, everyone is trying to save money. Your monthly telecom costs are a great place to start. Telecom expenses are often high and confusing, so it’s a good idea to take a close look at your bills and see if you can find ways to reduce costs or find a better deal. Keep in mind that pricing can vary significantly depending on your location.
We often assume that the cost of goods and services is relatively consistent regardless of location.</description></item><item><title>What is a Cloned Phone Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-cloned-phone-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 12:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-cloned-phone-line/</guid><description>Phone Power&amp;rsquo;s 12-month prepaid VoIP service, already a great value with almost unlimited U.S. and Canada calling and a free second year, also includes a unique &amp;ldquo;cloned 2nd line&amp;rdquo; feature. This raises the question: is this a true second phone line, and why is it called &amp;ldquo;cloned&amp;rdquo;?
Essentially, this feature provides the functionality of nearly two lines for the price of one. It utilizes the two RJ-11 jacks found on most telephone interface adapters, which connect your phone to your broadband modem or router.</description></item><item><title>A Visual Guide To Enterprise VoIP Justification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</guid><description>Thank you to MegaPath Broadband Service Providers for this interesting infographic.
Is your company missing out on the advantages of enterprise VoIP technology, which can potentially reduce costs and increase productivity? A variety of on-site and hosted options are available to accommodate businesses of all sizes. Explore business VoIP solutions and pricing from MegaPath and other providers.</description></item><item><title>The Analog Telephone Adaptor Enables VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</guid><description>Analog Telephone Adapters (ATAs) bridge the gap between traditional analog phones and Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) technology. They essentially trick both the phone and the internet connection into thinking they&amp;rsquo;re interacting with familiar systems.
On one side, the ATA connects to a regular phone using a standard RJ-11 jack, providing the necessary power and signals like dial tone and caller ID. It also translates the phone&amp;rsquo;s touch-tone signals into a digital format for VoIP communication using the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP).</description></item><item><title>Is HPBX Your Next PBX?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</guid><description>Businesses across the country are ditching their in-house phone systems and returning to outside phone service providers, mirroring a past era. However, modern telephony has evolved significantly. While maintaining in-house phone systems seemed cost-effective initially, companies are realizing that it comes with unexpected expenses and complexities.
Larger businesses often require numerous phone lines, leading to challenges in internal communication. Having individual lines for each phone necessitates long-distance charges for calls outside the company.</description></item></channel></rss>