<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Junk on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/junk/</link><description>Recent content in Junk on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 18:53:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/junk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Earth Day Means Money For Electronics Recycling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-day-means-money-for-electronics-recycling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 18:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-day-means-money-for-electronics-recycling/</guid><description>Today is Earth Day, a day to appreciate nature and consider our impact. We should treat our planet with respect or face the consequences. Speaking of which, why not make some money while being environmentally conscious?
It&amp;rsquo;s entirely possible to earn money by responsibly discarding old electronics. Even someone very frugal would see the value in making a little cash while helping the environment. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree? How about making some easy money through recycling?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-day-means-money-for-electronics-recycling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-day-means-money-for-electronics-recycling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Cash For Your Used or Broken iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</guid><description>Your old iPhone may be worse for wear, but don&amp;rsquo;t throw it away! It&amp;rsquo;s still valuable. Discarding it wastes money and harms the environment when you can easily sell it for cash.
Surprisingly, companies will buy your used iPhone regardless of its condition. Naturally, better condition means more money, but even damaged phones have value, ranging from a few dollars to over $100! A functional iPhone 4S can fetch over $100, far more than you&amp;rsquo;d get tossing it in the garbage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clod Computing Challenges The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing is gaining popularity as a cost-effective alternative to traditional data centers. However, a new competitor called &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; computing is emerging, boasting even lower costs.
](http://www.sysnito.com/?crid=11591&amp;linkID=145&amp;refid=Telexplainer-Clod)Clod computing minimizes infrastructure expenses by utilizing readily available, discarded computers. Chip-On-A-Shingle, a clod computing startup, defines a &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; as a network of interconnected old computers and devices that collectively provide impressive processing power.
This approach is viable due to the abundance of still functional computers being discarded simply because they are outdated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There’s $$$ In E-Waste</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 06:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</guid><description>Imagine tossing a $100 bill in the trash. That&amp;rsquo;s essentially what&amp;rsquo;s happening when we discard old electronics, or e-waste. While it might not be actual cash, these devices hold significant monetary and material value that often gets overlooked.
E-waste isn&amp;rsquo;t a new issue. It&amp;rsquo;s been accumulating since the days of bulky radios and TVs. However, the sheer volume of discarded electronics has skyrocketed due to rapid technological advancements and shorter product lifecycles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>