<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtual Private Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-private-line/</link><description>Recent content in Virtual Private Line on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-private-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV.</description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area.</description></item></channel></rss>