<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RIPA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ripa/</link><description>Recent content in RIPA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ripa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the UK's new data retention bill in violation of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Despite the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidating the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive in April, the UK government is pushing for continued data retention authority. This piece examines whether the proposed law aligns with EU law and if it violates the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.
The connection to EU law lies in Article 15(1) of the EU&amp;rsquo;s e-privacy Directive. This article allows Member States to restrict certain rights concerning communication confidentiality for safeguarding national security and other serious matters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>