<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Key Telephone System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/key-telephone-system/</link><description>Recent content in Key Telephone System on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/key-telephone-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system.</description></item></channel></rss>