<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Terabit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/terabit/</link><description>Recent content in Terabit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/terabit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is 1 Tbps The Next Optical Network Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</guid><description>While everyday users are getting used to 100 Mbps speeds, network providers are already looking ahead to Terabit per second speeds, debating whether 400 Gbps or 1 Tbps will be the next standard.
This push for higher speeds is a natural progression, similar to the advancement from Kbps to Mbps and Gbps. Just like previous upgrades, the proposed standards represent a tenfold increase.
This speed increase mirrors Moore&amp;rsquo;s Law, which predicted the doubling of transistors on integrated circuits yearly.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning.</description></item></channel></rss>