<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nicola Sturgeon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nicola-sturgeon/</link><description>Recent content in Nicola Sturgeon on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:49:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nicola-sturgeon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scotland and Brexit: Courageous Heart or Fearful Creature?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</guid><description>Steve Peers
During the Scottish National Party (SNP) conference, Scotland&amp;rsquo;s First Minister, Nicola Sturgeon, revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to present a draft bill for a second independence referendum. She also announced their intention to introduce an alternate plan ensuring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the EU single market, even if the rest of the UK chooses to leave. This proposal would involve granting the Scottish Parliament substantial new powers, encompassing all current EU-related powers held by Scotland and additional authority to negotiate international treaties and manage immigration.</description></item><item><title>Legal Issues Surrounding Scotland, the EU, and 'Indyref2'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 08:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Scottish First Minister Nicola Sturgeon recently revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s desire to pursue a second independence referendum. This announcement follows the UK government&amp;rsquo;s dismissal of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s proposed Brexit alternatives. The timing of this potential referendum, contingent on the UK&amp;rsquo;s final Brexit arrangements, brings Scotland&amp;rsquo;s EU membership into focus. While a second referendum would encompass issues beyond EU relations, this analysis will primarily address the legal complexities surrounding Scotland&amp;rsquo;s potential EU membership, particularly the misconception of budget deficits as a barrier to entry.</description></item><item><title>Opinions on Scotland's Position in Europe: Analysis of the Scottish Government's latest suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The Scottish government recently released its anticipated paper exploring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s position within Europe. While acknowledging the government&amp;rsquo;s support for both EU membership and Scottish independence, the paper concentrates on potential outcomes should Brexit occur while Scotland remains part of the UK. Accusations that the paper dismisses referendum results, regarding either Brexit or Scottish independence, or simply rehashes arguments for independence are unfounded.
The paper essentially presents two main options: a UK-wide approach to Brexit that considers the concerns of Scottish voters, or, if that fails, a separate approach specifically for Scotland.</description></item></channel></rss>