<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephone Trunks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-trunks/</link><description>Recent content in Telephone Trunks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-trunks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sipping on the Trunk Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</guid><description>The history of telephone trunks goes back to the early days of telephones. Trunks are lines that carry multiple phone conversations, initially connecting switchboards and switching offices. They&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from wire bundles to analog and now digital circuits, with T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and SONET being common digital trunking services. However, SIP trunking is emerging as a popular alternative.
Telephone trunking saves money by combining multiple phone lines into a single high-bandwidth connection.</description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers.</description></item></channel></rss>