<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Security on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-security/</link><description>Recent content in Network Security on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When It Comes to Computer Networks, Trust No One and No Thing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security is a major concern for businesses today. One might even miss the days of isolated computers, unconnected to any network.
However, even those isolated computers weren&amp;rsquo;t entirely secure. Malware could still spread and confidential files could be copied through physical transfer of files using floppy disks. The challenge today is that modern networks, encompassing local networks, data centers, multiple cloud platforms, and the internet, make it incredibly difficult to track who is accessing the network and their intentions.</description></item><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data.</description></item><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging.</description></item><item><title>EVPL Ethernet Virtual Private Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of private line services used by businesses. These lines provide exclusive use, like dedicated analog phone lines or T1 lines for voice and data. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a new option: the Virtual Private Line (VPL).
Telephone lines weren&amp;rsquo;t always private. Shared lines, known as party lines, connected multiple households. Picking up the phone meant potentially overhearing neighbors&amp;rsquo; conversations, a form of pre-Twitter entertainment.
This lack of privacy is gone from phone lines.</description></item><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of SSL VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</guid><description>Cybersecurity is a significant concern for all internet users. With frequent news of hacking, data breaches, identity theft, and malicious bots, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that people are anxious about the security of their sensitive information, especially with the move towards cloud-based storage. This has led to a surge in interest in virtual private networks (VPNs).
Why would one choose a virtual private network over a traditional one?
The answer lies in our need for widespread connectivity.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series.</description></item><item><title>Why Demand a SAS 70 Type II Data Center?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-demand-a-sas-70-type-ii-data-center/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-demand-a-sas-70-type-ii-data-center/</guid><description>When choosing a cloud or colocation provider, prioritize data privacy and security, especially in regulated sectors like healthcare and finance. A facility with SAS 70 Type II compliance can offer this assurance.
SAS 70, based on the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA) Statement on Auditing Standards No. 70, Service Organizations, involves a rigorous audit of a company&amp;rsquo;s data handling practices by an independent firm. This audit results in a comprehensive written report.</description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits.</description></item><item><title>Why Colocate To An Omaha Data Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</guid><description>While major corporations might associate colocation data centers with locations like 60 Hudson St in New York City or One Wilshire in Los Angeles, Omaha, Nebraska, presents a compelling alternative.
Beyond being home to Warren Buffett and Berkshire Hathaway, Omaha boasts a robust business environment, earning recognition from Forbes magazine as the nation&amp;rsquo;s top &amp;ldquo;Best-Bang-For-The-Buck City.&amp;rdquo; Crucially, Omaha houses the Scott Data Center complex.
The Scott Data Center offers over 110,000 square feet of data storage, boasting continuous operation since 2006.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item></channel></rss>