<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learning on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/learning/</link><description>Recent content in Learning on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:34:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Webinars diving deep into GP 2010</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on in-depth GP 2010 webinars for Microsoft Certified Trainers (MCTs) and Partners. These webinars offer step-by-step guidance on setting up and using the new features in GP 2010. As a bonus, all were created and presented by MCTs. Check them out – we hope they help you get your clients ready for GP 2010!
Business Intelligence &amp;amp; Reporting (This one is mine!)
This demonstration-based presentation covers the setup and use of new reporting and business intelligence enhancements in Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hasso Plattner Institute is offering a free six-week MOOC on the Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</guid><description>The Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) is offering a free, six-week online course in English about the fundamentals of the Internet. Starting on March 31st, HPI&amp;rsquo;s director, Professor Christoph Meinel, will teach participants about the technical basis of the Internet through a massive open online course (MOOC) titled &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Internetworking with TCP/IP.&amp;rdquo; The course is available to anyone and can be accessed through free registration.
Professor Meinel believes that anyone who uses the Internet for daily tasks like online shopping, reading news articles, or sending emails should understand the technologies that make these actions possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Soothes The Savage Beasts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/</guid><description>Instead of resorting to strict discipline, a school in Vail, Arizona, found a simple solution to improve student behavior on their buses: providing Wi-Fi access. Surprisingly, once installed, disruptive behavior vanished, and students became more engaged in their homework.
This success story highlights a key point: providing Internet access can effectively address disciplinary issues. While students may engage in various online activities, the core issue of maintaining order is resolved...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The skills you possess will be valuable in securing future employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Legrand illustrates how LinkedIn is innovating by connecting existing skills with the needs of emerging jobs.
Olivier Legrand, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at LinkedIn, suggests that many individuals already possess some qualifications for in-demand jobs without realizing it.
During his keynote, &amp;ldquo;Job titles are out, skill sets are in,&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Computer Society&amp;rsquo;s Tech3 Forum, Legrand stated that LinkedIn aims to connect its members not only with employers but also with suitable companies, relevant jobs, and essential skills for future career prospects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GLG increases its presence in Singapore with office expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</guid><description>GLG, a professional learning platform connecting professionals with experts for knowledge sharing, has expanded its presence in Singapore with a new and larger office. The company&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Alexander Saint-Amand, highlighted the rapid growth of GLG&amp;rsquo;s business in Singapore, emphasizing the region&amp;rsquo;s significance for the company&amp;rsquo;s mission to transform professional learning.
The new 6,000-square-foot office, located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, can accommodate 64 employees. GLG&amp;rsquo;s leadership, including Evan Auyang, Head of Asia-Pacific and Managing Director, and David Anderson, Head of GLG Southeast Asia, underscored Singapore&amp;rsquo;s strategic importance as a business hub and its concentration of leading professionals and companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACCA is sponsoring a MOOC on FutureLearn that grants learners an exemption from the F1 paper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) is breaking new ground as the first professional accountancy body to use massive open online courses (MOOCs) for professional recognition. They are partnering with FutureLearn, a UK-based social learning platform, to offer free online courses in accounting, finance, and business.
This partnership aims to reach a global audience, providing valuable supplementary knowledge for professionals and introducing career paths to those new to the field...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IT Training Videos Get You Up to Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-training-videos-get-you-up-to-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-training-videos-get-you-up-to-speed/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there: needing to use a new software tool, so we install it and start clicking around, hoping to figure it out. It works, but is it the most effective way to learn? Not really. We end up only scratching the surface of what the program can do, just learning enough to get by.
The truth is, we&amp;rsquo;re all short on time and patience. We need to learn quickly and easily...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-training-videos-get-you-up-to-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-training-videos-get-you-up-to-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it relevant? Who cares?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 23:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</guid><description>Recently, I discussed staying relevant in a constantly evolving field with a respected colleague. As someone with potentially decades in my career ahead, this is a topic I&amp;rsquo;ve been pondering, especially considering my specialization in Dynamics GP and how other technologies intersect with it. While I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with my current skill set, I wonder if I should branch out and explore standalone technologies.
My colleague reassured me that my experience, teaching abilities, and the continued relevance of Dynamics GP contribute to my value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The language learning app HelloTalk has reached 1 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</guid><description>Source: HelloTalk app page at the Play Store.
The mobile language learning app HelloTalk has reached over one million registered users globally, according to its developer, HelloTalk.
The HelloTalk app allows users to teach each other their native languages using their mobile devices. Users can communicate in real-time with native speakers through various features, helping them practice their target language.
Over one million HelloTalk users, representing over 200 countries, use the app to learn various languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>