<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Verizon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/verizon/</link><description>Recent content in Verizon on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/verizon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Cable vs FTTH Bandwidth Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</guid><description>The competition for superior internet speed is underway. Fiber to the Home (FTTH), is perceived as the frontrunner, while Cable Broadband is the contender. It&amp;rsquo;s still uncertain who will come out on top, but one thing is for sure: users with substantial bandwidth requirements will be the ultimate victors.
This clash is unfolding in Washington state, where Comcast, the Cable behemoth, is introducing a 50 Mbps internet service to rival Verizon, the telecommunications giant, and its 50 Mbps FiOS internet service.</description></item><item><title>Juniper Has Routers For The 100 Gbps WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</guid><description>Verizon and Juniper are partnering on a large-scale project to implement 100 Gbps fiber optic connections to meet the increasing demand for faster internet speeds.
While carriers have experimented with 100 Gbps transmission, which is significantly faster than the typical 10 Gbps long-haul networks, it seems that widespread adoption is on the horizon. Juniper has developed an interface capable of handling this bandwidth directly, eliminating the need for carriers to combine multiple links.</description></item><item><title>Cheap Used Cell Phones For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 12:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</guid><description>Need a new cell phone but dread dealing with carriers and contracts? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Carrier stores are notorious for expensive phones and restrictive contracts. They might offer a &amp;ldquo;cheap&amp;rdquo; phone, but it comes with strings attached – usually a pricey new contract and limited model options.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been with your carrier long enough for an upgrade or prefer not to sign a new contract, carriers will charge full retail price for a new phone.</description></item><item><title>Samsung Omnia Smartphone for Smart People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Omnia&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; in Latin, a fitting name for a high-tech wireless device designed for mobile professionals.
The Samsung Omnia is a cutting-edge smartphone using the Windows Mobile 6.1 Pro operating system. It boasts a complete HTML web browser, Opera Mobile, on a 3.2-inch LCD touchscreen enhanced with Samsung TouchWiz technology. This technology provides tactile feedback through slight vibrations, while an accelerometer automatically adjusts the display based on the phone&amp;rsquo;s orientation.</description></item><item><title>Verizon enhances e-business capabilities with increased support for private IP services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</guid><description>Verizon Communications is expanding its Private IP services network, offering businesses a secure way to deliver e-business applications and conduct business-to-business e-commerce. The expansion includes 10 additional countries across the Middle East, Africa, and Asia-Pacific regions.
Verizon business and wholesale customers in the Middle East and Asia Pacific now have expanded access to Private IP Multiprotocol Private Label Switching (MPLS) services in Bangladesh, Cambodia, Laos, Nepal, Iraq, Lebanon, and Yemen. Chennai, India, gains an additional location, offering customers enhanced network resiliency and reach through increased access to MPLS services.</description></item><item><title>Medical Records Head To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/medical-records-head-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 19:06:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/medical-records-head-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The medical field is transitioning to electronic records to control rising costs. Verizon is at the forefront of this shift with its cloud-based service, Verizon Health Information Exchange. This service provides a platform for storing patient records in a standardized format, enabling healthcare providers to share information seamlessly via web-based access.
Verizon&amp;rsquo;s entry into this domain could lead to the establishment of industry standards for electronic medical records, much like IBM did for personal computers.</description></item></channel></rss>