<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Storage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/storage/</link><description>Recent content in Storage on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/storage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the RAM Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 utilizes a 3V battery to power its 16-word memory chip, an MCM144102, which is described as a peripheral memory unit in the Motorola 6804 manual but lacks readily available detailed specifications. This chip is responsible for storing calibration data and potentially the system time, although further investigation is required. A visual representation of the circuit is included below.
A positive aspect of the design is the inclusion of diode D27, which safeguards the battery against reverse polarity connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BEAM offers self-storage services in Singapore through a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>BEAM, a new self-storage company, has launched in Singapore, offering a unique approach to traditional storage solutions. Their services are managed entirely through a mobile app.
Unlike conventional self-storage providers that lease fixed spaces, BEAM offers flexible per-item storage. This means users only pay for the space their belongings occupy, eliminating wasted costs. Additionally, while traditional facilities are often inconveniently located, BEAM provides free pick-up and delivery to their secure 6,000 sq ft facility, equipped with CCTV and access control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hitachi drives are endorsed with a vote of confidence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</guid><description>In a January 2014 blog post, cloud storage company Backblaze reported that Hitachi and Western Digital hard drives have been the most reliable in their data centers.
Backblaze engineer Brian Beach revealed that Seagate&amp;rsquo;s 1.5TB drives had an annual failure rate of about 14%, significantly higher than Hitachi&amp;rsquo;s 2TB drives at approximately 1% and Western Digital&amp;rsquo;s 1TB drives at 3%. For 3TB drives, Seagate again had the highest failure rate at around 9%, while Western Digital stood at about 3% and Hitachi at roughly 1%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2018 features AI technology that can detect ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</guid><description>Acronis Integrates AI into True Image 2018 for Enhanced Data Protection Image: Beloussov introducing Acronis ahead of the launch of Acronis True Image 2018.
Beloussov speaking at the Acronis True Image 2018 launch event.
Acronis, a global leader in hybrid cloud data protection, is incorporating artificial intelligence (AI) into its entire product line. Serguei Beloussov, co-founder and CEO of Acronis, emphasized their commitment to AI integration across all products. This announcement was made during the launch of their flagship product, Acronis True Image 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sony introduces hard disk drives with high speed and high capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</guid><description>Sony Introduces Speedy and Durable Portable Hard Drives Boasting data transfer speeds up to 138MBps for both reading and writing, Sony&amp;rsquo;s latest portable hard disk drives (HDDs) promise both performance and resilience. Built to withstand the bumps of everyday use, these drives are shock-resistant, splash-resistant (IPX4 rating), and dust-resistant (IP5X rating). They can even tolerate drops from up to 6.5 feet thanks to their robust rubber damper design.
Source: Sony. The new 2TB drive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HPE has reduced the entry threshold for its storage portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</guid><description>Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) recently improved its entry storage products to help budget-conscious customers leverage their data and speed up applications. These new HPE MSA Storage options deliver the most budget-friendly dual-controller hybrid flash array from a major vendor while the new HPE StoreEasy 1650 Expanded makes storing large amounts of information more economical.
Being able to quickly and effectively use information is crucial for success. &amp;ldquo;Agility and speed are critical for staying competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s economy, no matter the business size,&amp;rdquo; said Manish Goel, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Storage at HPE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drobo Mr. Storage Roboto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</guid><description>Hard drive space disappears faster than you can imagine, especially with large digital media files like photos and videos. Even large hard drives fill up quickly.
While upgrading or adding hard drives seems like a solution, it creates new problems like managing backups and worrying about data loss from hard drive failures. These tasks can be time-consuming, especially for professionals working with large files. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like you need a personal assistant to manage it all...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces new storage solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Mid-size businesses need to adapt quickly, but they often don&amp;rsquo;t have the budget for the advanced storage solutions used by larger companies. HP is addressing this issue by offering affordable ways to enhance application performance. This includes a budget-friendly solid-state drive (SSD) read-caching solution from a leading provider, featuring SSD choices for HP MSA Storage.1
For businesses considering hybrid flash storage, HP is introducing a new HP StoreVirtual Storage system. This system boasts 12 times the speed of a similarly priced spinning media array...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google Drive prices have been significantly reduced by Google</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 23:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</guid><description>A blog post published on March 13 revealed that Google significantly reduced prices for cloud storage. The monthly fees have been adjusted to US$1.99 for 100GB (previously US$4.99), US$9.99 for 1TB (previously US$49.99), and US$99.99 for 10TB, with the option to purchase additional terabytes as required.
A 15 GB plan remains free of charge. This storage space can be utilized across Drive, Gmail, and Google+ Photos.
Source: Google
Existing paying users will be automatically transitioned to the corresponding updated plan without incurring additional costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Box Zones provides customers with increased flexibility in choosing the locations for storing their data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</guid><description>The enterprise content management platform Box has introduced Box Zones, enabling companies to store their data regionally in Europe and Asia. Utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) and IBM Cloud, Box Zones will allow content to be stored in Germany, Ireland, Singapore, and Japan, based on customer requirements.
Box CEO and co-founder Aaron Levie highlighted that businesses are increasingly interconnected, collaborative, and global due to cloud technology. However, local regulations often compel companies to make technological compromises that hinder their growth and reduce employee productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi has teamed up with Telenor to provide its subscribers with a complimentary image storage service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</guid><description>Telenor, through Digi, has launched Capture, a free mobile app and cloud storage service for backing up images and videos.
Capture allows users to automatically save and back up photos and videos from their devices, safeguarding memories if their phone is lost or needs to be replaced. It also provides additional storage, especially useful for entry-level devices with limited capacity.
Non-Digi customers can download and utilize Capture with 2GB of free storage space...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intel has introduced solid state drives designed for use in business environments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 23:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</guid><description>Source: Intel website.
Intel has introduced the Intel SSD Pro 2500 Series, a new business-class addition to their Solid-State Drive (SSD) Professional family.
The Intel SSD Pro 2500 Series provides robust security features and capabilities designed for businesses of all sizes, giving them peace of mind. These drives offer hardware-based encryption, remote management capabilities, and a lower annual failure rate than traditional hard disk drives (HDDs), reducing the need for on-site IT support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell has launched backup appliances for midmarket businesses, along with complimentary Windows data recovery software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</guid><description>Dell has introduced new data protection solutions tailored for small and medium-sized businesses to enhance the protection of their crucial systems, applications, and data, both on-site and in cloud environments. These solutions include data deduplication appliance models and the new Dell Data Protection | Endpoint Recovery – Free Edition.
Back up more and store less The latest additions to the Dell DR series of deduplication appliances are the Dell DR4300e, DR4300, and DR6300...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Stream notebooks include a complimentary one-year subscription to Office 365 and OneDrive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new notebook PCs to its HP Stream line of lightweight, cloud-based Windows devices. HP emphasizes affordability, offering these thin and light notebooks at a lower price point than typically seen.
Source: HP. The HP Stream notebooks come in horizon blue and orchid magenta.
“Consumers today want mobile devices that reflect their style and empower them to work and play from anywhere,” says Serena Yong, General Manager for Printing &amp;amp; Personal Systems at HP Singapore and Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Capital Starved Companies Upgrade Technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</guid><description>Even with the economy recovering, securing funds for new technology can be challenging for businesses. Instead of traditional financing, consider &amp;ldquo;hosted solutions&amp;rdquo; or renting technology. This approach avoids large capital investments, allowing businesses to upgrade their systems affordably.
Website hosting is a prime example. Initially, hosting your website on your servers made sense. However, with increased competition, affordable hosting services have become widely available, making it more practical to outsource this function...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has improved MSA Storage for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP is introducing new features for its MSA Storage solutions to benefit startups, SMBs, and customers with small sites. These enhancements aim to increase competitiveness.
The improved MSA 2040 Storage offers significantly faster application performance, up to 45% faster, without extra costs through firmware updates. Additionally, new MSA 2040 bundles provide cost savings of up to 45% for hybrid flash deployments. Furthermore, the introduction of Serial Attached SCSI (SAS) connectivity to the MSA 1040 Storage positions it as the most budget-friendly shared storage option from a major vendor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Western Digital introduces a microSD card with a storage capacity of 400GB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/</guid><description>This is the 400GB SanDisk Ultra microSD card.
Western Digital Corporation has introduced a 400GB SanDisk Ultra microSDXC UHS-I card, boasting the largest capacity available for mobile devices.
This UHS Speed class 1 card enables smooth recording of full HD videos. Smartphones that are compatible need to support the SDXC standard.
Margaret Koh, Sales Director, Asia South at Western Digital Corporation, emphasizes, &amp;ldquo;We provide storage solutions for everyone with digital content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Selecting the appropriate tea for the workplace break room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 16:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find pre-mixed tea sachets or teabags in office pantries. While these are convenient and widely available, Teabox, an online retailer specializing in premium Indian teas, suggests there might be downsides to these options.
Source: Teabox website.
Teabox CEO, Kaushal Dugar, explains that tea dust, a byproduct of tea production, lacks the full flavor, taste, and aroma of whole tea leaves. This tea dust is often what ends up in teabags, resulting in a less flavorful and potentially less nutritious cup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>