<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ESET on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eset/</link><description>Recent content in ESET on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:08:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ESET introduces the latest version of its security suite for consumers, version 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-security-suite-for-consumers-version-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:08:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-security-suite-for-consumers-version-10/</guid><description>ESET has introduced version 10 of its home security software lineup. Their top product, ESET Smart Security Premium, uses ESET&amp;rsquo;s NOD32 technology, designed for a balance of effective threat detection, speed, and user-friendliness.
This latest version includes a new password manager for simplified secure logins and ESET Secure Data for robust and convenient file encryption. In addition to ESET Smart Security Premium, users can also choose ESET Internet Security. &amp;ldquo;As online threats become more varied, users need comprehensive internet security suites with customizable features,&amp;rdquo; explains Lukas Raska, ESET&amp;rsquo;s COO for Asia Pacific...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-security-suite-for-consumers-version-10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-security-suite-for-consumers-version-10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET introduces security solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a company that provides proactive digital protection, has launched two new security products: ESET Multi-Device Security Home Office and ESET Small Office Security. These products are designed for small office/home office (SOHO) users.
&amp;ldquo;Cybercriminals often target small and home offices because they assume these businesses lack strong security measures,&amp;rdquo; said Andrew Lee, CEO of ESET North America. &amp;ldquo;There are 28 million businesses in this sector, and they need security solutions tailored to their unique needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET advocates for the use of two-factor authentication to enhance security for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, cautions that small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) are frequently targeted by cybercriminals due to the vulnerability of their data. Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research&amp;rsquo;s study reveals that stolen personal data fuels a multi-billion dollar industry.
Lukas Raska, COO of ESET Asia, emphasizes the evolution of cybercrime from viruses to the current threat of identity theft, highlighting its potential to cripple businesses and compromise customer trust.
Parvinder Walia, Director at ESET APAC, explains that SMBs are attractive targets because they often lack the robust cybersecurity budgets and dedicated personnel of larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The launch of ESET Smart Security 9 and ESET NOD32 Antivirus 9 has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</guid><description>ESET, a global cybersecurity company, has launched ESET Smart Security 9 and ESET NOD32 Antivirus 9. These releases feature a redesigned user interface and enhanced security features.
Parvinder Walia, ESET&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific Sales and Marketing Director, highlighted the Asia-Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s rapid growth in internet and mobile usage, leading to increased adoption of online and mobile banking. He emphasized that the new banking and payment protection in ESET Smart Security 9 will allow customers to conduct secure financial transactions online...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>40% of Singaporeans have experienced a data breach within the last year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</guid><description>Parvinder Walia, during his presentation, revealed that 72% of consumers react negatively to news of a company suffering a cyberattack or data breach.
ESET, a cybersecurity software company, conducted a survey to examine consumer online behavior and perspectives on cybersecurity in light of recent data breaches.
The ESET 2018 APAC Consumer Behaviour Survey found that 42% of Singaporeans had experienced some form of data breach in the preceding year. These breaches included theft and misuse of personal information, bank account fraud, social media account compromise, and attacks from malware and viruses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Here are five tips for creating stronger passwords, according to ESET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-are-five-tips-for-creating-stronger-passwords-according-to-eset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 02:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-are-five-tips-for-creating-stronger-passwords-according-to-eset/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, used World Password Day on May 3rd as an opportunity to share advice on creating stronger passwords.
World Password Day is a global event designed to promote the importance of strong passwords and safe online practices. ESET&amp;rsquo;s Senior Research Fellow, Nick FitzGerald, pointed out that even with secure password storage, weak or predictable passwords still leave users vulnerable to hacking.
FitzGerald highlighted a recent case involving Singapore Airlines, where hackers may have exploited weak passwords to steal KrisFlyer frequent flyer miles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-are-five-tips-for-creating-stronger-passwords-according-to-eset/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-are-five-tips-for-creating-stronger-passwords-according-to-eset/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Don't fall for the scam of cheap Ray-Ban sunglasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</guid><description>Source: ESET.
ESET&amp;rsquo;s spam filters have identified a growing trend of fraudulent emails enticing recipients with deeply discounted luxury items, particularly Ray-Ban sunglasses. These counterfeit websites lack encryption and might be designed to capture victims&amp;rsquo; payment information. While ESET had issued prior warnings about this scam targeting Facebook users, the shift to email attacks broadens the potential victim pool significantly.
“Providing payment card information on these fake websites poses a substantial financial risk,&amp;quot; cautions Lukáš Štefanko, an ESET Malware Researcher...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>