<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BenQ on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/benq/</link><description>Recent content in BenQ on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/benq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BenQ introduces new digital signage, projectors, and interactive flat panels, creating a buzz</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</guid><description>BenQ, a leading provider of visual display technology, has introduced a range of new projectors, digital signage, and interactive flat panels, all emphasizing high quality and innovative design. The company highlighted its commitment to delivering excellent visual experiences across various sectors, including business, retail, and food &amp;amp; beverage.
Business The MX666+ projector.
The MX666+ is the first wireless business projector to feature Near Field Communication (NFC) technology and USB connectivity, making it ideal for bring-your-own-device environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BenQ interactive flat panel simplifies education and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</guid><description>BenQ, a well-known name in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, introduces the RP750K, a new interactive flat panel (IFP). This innovative IFP offers a comprehensive solution by combining a 4K Ultra HD whiteboard with annotation and collaboration tools.
The RP750K excels in dynamic classroom or corporate training settings. Its Germ-Resistant Screen, infused with a safe and robust nano-ionic silver coating, effectively eliminates most surface germs, reducing cross-infection risks. This antimicrobial protection persists even with regular cleaning and extended use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BenQ has recently introduced a new series of digital laser projectors that offer precise color accuracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 21:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</guid><description>The BenQ LU9715 digital laser projector.
BenQ, a leading brand in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, has introduced a new series of laser projectors designed for large venues in corporate, professional, and academic settings.
BenQ highlights that the 24/7 operational capabilities will be particularly valuable in large business settings, museums, exhibition spaces, and boardrooms. Daren Low, Senior Product Manager at BenQ Singapore, emphasized the advantage of minimal maintenance, especially since these projectors are often mounted in high, hard-to-reach locations where scaffolding would be necessary for each maintenance session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>