<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Internet Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dedicated-internet-access/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Internet Access on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dedicated-internet-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable.</description></item><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity for Telemedicine and Remote Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The rapid emergence of the Coronavirus pandemic is speeding up existing trends, particularly telemedicine and remote work. Both heavily rely on broadband internet bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available connection options.
Connecting the User
Most remote workers and telemedicine patients connect from home using devices like desktops, smartphones, laptops, or tablets. Home users often prefer cable broadband with speeds of 30 to 100 Mbps, while remote users rely on public WiFi or 4G/5G cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components.</description></item><item><title>Why Choose Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet has transitioned from a novelty to a necessity, as indispensable as electricity or heat. However, its unreliability can be a source of frustration, especially given its immense potential for businesses. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to enhance Internet stability and dependability.
Internet vs Internet
Internet experiences are not universal, despite discussions about net neutrality claiming otherwise. While some enjoy superior performance, others face limitations. How is this possible?</description></item><item><title>Is a Virtual Leased Line Right For Your Applications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines have been a popular choice for businesses since they were introduced by telephone companies decades ago. This article explores the concept of virtual leased lines and their potential benefits for businesses.
Before delving into virtual leased lines, let&amp;rsquo;s review traditional leased lines and their functionality.
Leased Lines vs Shared Bandwidth
A leased line is a dedicated telecommunications line rented for a specific duration, usually 1 to 3 years.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business moves online and companies shift their IT to the cloud, the demand for WAN bandwidth continues to rise. These days, even small businesses frequently require reliable dedicated internet and inter-office network bandwidth in the range of 100 Mbps to 1 Gbps. Larger companies, particularly those dealing with tech-heavy products, services, or medical imaging, can easily saturate Gigabit connections, making a transition to 10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN a worthwhile consideration.</description></item><item><title>DS1 Bandwidth vs Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</guid><description>DS1, commonly called T1, is a popular choice for business internet. This article will explain DS1 and compare it to another popular option: Ethernet over Copper.
While the terms are often used synonymously, DS1 and T1 are slightly different. They both come from a set of technical standards created by Bell Labs called the T-carrier system, which was originally a digital replacement for analog phone lines. Though designed for telephones, DS1 and T1 are now widely used for dedicated internet connections and private lines.</description></item><item><title>Managed IP Networks Enable Voice and Data Convergence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 04:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</guid><description>Businesses have been looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing service, and combining their computer and telephone networks into a single, multi-functional LAN that can connect to the public Internet and phone network seems like a good way to do it. Ideally, this means one network, one connection per desk, and one support team. However, the reality isn&amp;rsquo;t always so simple.
The reason for this is that computers and telephones use networks in very different ways.</description></item><item><title>How Many T1 Lines Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</guid><description>For small businesses dissatisfied with DSL or Cable broadband, a professional T1 line might seem like the ideal solution. The superior reliability and dedicated bandwidth make T1 lines the popular choice for business voice and data services. However, as your business expands, you might encounter the bandwidth limitations of your once-sufficient T1 line. What then?
Similarly, high-tech businesses, such as Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) or video production companies, might find the 1.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>Thirty Carriers, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</guid><description>Are you overwhelmed and frustrated with your current telecommunications services? Do you feel stuck with your local phone or internet provider and dread seeing your monthly bill?
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to endure this! You deserve a wide range of choices for your voice and data communication needs. Imagine having access to 30 different business-grade carriers, offering everything from basic phone lines to high-speed internet options like wireless and satellite.
Whether you need ISDN PRI lines for your office phone system, MPLS networks to connect multiple locations, or Gigabit Ethernet for high-bandwidth applications like video conferencing, you have options.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>XO Communications Ups the Ante on Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</guid><description>A major telecommunications provider is expanding its Metro Ethernet services, offering businesses more options for high-bandwidth connectivity. This provider leverages its vast fiber optic network, numerous points of presence, and advanced Ethernet over Copper technology to make Ethernet an even more attractive option for Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.
Why is Ethernet so important? It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a natural progression for network technology that businesses of all sizes already rely on. This means Metro Ethernet provides a nearly effortless solution for connecting various locations, effectively unifying them under a single network.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Zayo Lights Denver With Expanded Fiber Optic Network Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</guid><description>Zayo Group, a prominent fiber optic bandwidth infrastructure provider, is expanding its existing metro fiber network coverage in Denver and Colorado Springs. The expansion project will add 521 miles of fiber along the Colorado Front Range, encompassing cities like Boulder, Longmont, Loveland, Greeley, and Fort Collins. This increase brings Zayo&amp;rsquo;s total fiber optic network in the Denver area to 900 route miles, supporting industries such as research, technology, education, and energy.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Attributes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-attributes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 13:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-attributes/</guid><description>T1 lines have become the standard connectivity solution for small and medium-sized businesses. They support various uses like dedicated internet connections, private lines, network access, and business phone lines. What makes T1 lines so popular?
A T1 line uses one or two twisted pairs of copper telephone wiring installed between a business and the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. While the local telephone company owns this copper wiring, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t have to buy T1 service directly from them.</description></item><item><title>Find A T1 Line For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re unsatisfied with your current internet options like DSL or Cable due to fluctuating speeds, frequent outages, or location limitations, and find Satellite internet&amp;rsquo;s lag, bandwidth restrictions, and weather-related disruptions unacceptable, there&amp;rsquo;s a better solution: T1 lines.
T1 lines, the gold standard for business wireline services, provide a reliable solution with consistent upload and download speeds, high reliability, quick problem resolution, and widespread availability. They offer secure connections between business locations and digital phone line options for PBX systems, features absent in other digital services.</description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof.</description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1.</description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses.</description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost.</description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Internet Access Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 02:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes now have near-universal access to broadband internet. However, are you utilizing the optimal internet connection for your needs? It might be time to consider Ethernet.
Metro Ethernet Networks are rapidly expanding and provide significant benefits to businesses. Cost savings are a key advantage, potentially cutting your internet bandwidth expenses by half or more compared to your current solution. This significant cost reduction comes without compromising reliability or dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>T1 is Your Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While metropolitan areas have many choices for broadband internet, rural areas often only have access to limited options like mobile 4G or satellite internet. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option that is often overlooked but may be a perfect fit for rural businesses and remote work: T1 dedicated internet access.
T1 is Everywhere T1 lines are widely available, often wherever standard phone lines exist. This is because T1 utilizes the same copper wiring infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs.</description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network.</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1.</description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers.</description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible.</description></item><item><title>Telephone and Internet for Chain Stores</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</guid><description>Cost-conscious small businesses need reliable communication systems. They can&amp;rsquo;t risk losing customers due to failed credit card transactions or dropped calls. Businesses with multiple locations also need efficient ways to connect their operations. Integrated T1 offers a solution that addresses these needs while staying budget-friendly.
Integrated T1 merges voice and data services onto a single line, combining the reliability of T1 phone lines with the efficiency of T1 internet connections. This approach minimizes costs without sacrificing quality.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 04:11:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</guid><description>There are two main types of broadband internet: shared and dedicated. While you might be familiar with terms like wireless, landline, satellite, or fiber optic, these refer to delivery methods that impact price and availability. Your primary choice lies in deciding between shared and dedicated internet access.
What sets them apart? The names are quite descriptive. Shared internet access resembles a buffet where you might eye a large roast, hoping for a full plate.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</guid><description>Traditional business bandwidth solutions, typically offering low to moderate speeds, have long relied on T1 lines and their bonded counterparts. However, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) solutions are rapidly replacing these older technologies, delivering enhanced bandwidth at a lower cost.
We&amp;rsquo;re focusing on services ranging from 1 to 20 Mbps, encompassing both dedicated point-to-point private lines and dedicated internet connections. Ethernet standards also enable private LAN services, facilitating connections between multiple business locations.</description></item></channel></rss>