<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Health on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/health/</link><description>Recent content in Health on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad introduces new, healthier menu choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has partnered with the Department of Health – Abu Dhabi to introduce Weqaya, a selection of healthy food choices, on flights and in its Abu Dhabi lounges.
Weqaya, meaning &amp;ldquo;prevention&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, is a program created by the Department of Health - Abu Dhabi to encourage healthy and balanced eating habits for improved health and well-being.
Etihad now offers several Weqaya dishes on First and Business Class long-haul and ultra-long-haul flights departing from Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASICS introduces its lightest-ever cushioning shoe for runners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The DynaFlyte.
ASICS has released its lightest cushioned running shoe to date. The DynaFlyte combines lightness and cushioning with a full-length FlyteFoam midsole, utilizing the company&amp;rsquo;s patented midsole technology in its most basic form. According to ASICS, the shoe&amp;rsquo;s reduced weight minimizes energy loss during the stride, resulting in more efficient running and the potential for increased speed at any distance.
Balancing efficient cushioning with minimizing weight is a significant challenge in running shoe design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>60% of employed Singaporeans report feeling burned out</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic has led 49% of Singaporeans to reevaluate their priorities, with their careers no longer holding the same level of importance. A new study by Employment Hero highlights the significant role employers can play in employee well-being to attract and keep talent, particularly given that 62% of Singaporean employees report experiencing burnout and 57% feel they have an inadequate work-life balance.
Employment Hero, a company specializing in payroll, HR, and people management solutions, suggests that burnout stems from multiple factors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Activpass provides discounted rates for wellness activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</guid><description>Source: Activpass. Activpass is a mobile-based marketplace for booking lifestyle activities.
The team behind Activpass, a platform designed for businesses and professionals in fitness, wellness, and beauty, believes in living life to the fullest. Their mobile platform gives users access to over 1,000 services like yoga, training sessions, golf, massages, and beauty treatments, all without requiring a long-term commitment.
Users can easily book and pay for services on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The goal of the Digestive Health Malaysia Society is to increase awareness of the importance of maintaining a healthy gut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-digestive-health-malaysia-society-is-to-increase-awareness-of-the-importance-of-maintaining-a-healthy-gut/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-digestive-health-malaysia-society-is-to-increase-awareness-of-the-importance-of-maintaining-a-healthy-gut/</guid><description>The Malaysian Ministry of Health&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Health Facts report reveals that digestive diseases are the fifth leading cause of hospital deaths in Malaysia, prompting the establishment of the Digestive Health Malaysia Society.
Dato&amp;rsquo; Dr Muhammad Radzi, Chairman of the Digestive Health Malaysia Society, highlighted that while colon cancer is widely recognized, awareness of other digestive diseases like irritable bowel syndrome, diverticulitis, gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD), and Crohn&amp;rsquo;s disease remains low. These conditions are often chronic and challenging to diagnose and manage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-digestive-health-malaysia-society-is-to-increase-awareness-of-the-importance-of-maintaining-a-healthy-gut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-digestive-health-malaysia-society-is-to-increase-awareness-of-the-importance-of-maintaining-a-healthy-gut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five years later, Club HEAL still works to raise awareness about mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-later-club-heal-still-works-to-raise-awareness-about-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 01:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-later-club-heal-still-works-to-raise-awareness-about-mental-health/</guid><description>Club HEAL, a volunteer-based organization, recently celebrated its fifth anniversary with a gala dinner. Almost 600 guests and supporters attended.
Dr. Radiah Salim, the founder and president of Club HEAL, stated that the organization strives to address as many service gaps as possible.
She shared that approximately 2,000 individuals have benefited from Club HEAL&amp;rsquo;s assistance. Her hope is to see more Club HEAL locations while expanding their outreach to those facing addiction challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-later-club-heal-still-works-to-raise-awareness-about-mental-health/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-later-club-heal-still-works-to-raise-awareness-about-mental-health/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globetrekker Challenge creates a wellness portal for Garmin in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Globetrekker Challenge, a Singapore-based corporate wellness software company, will provide their corporate wellness platform to Garmin for distribution across Asia and the Pacific. This collaboration leverages each company&amp;rsquo;s strengths, allowing them to focus on their core offerings.
Globetrekker&amp;rsquo;s platform offers customizable wellness programs, real-time analytics reporting, and health risk profiling for employers. Through this partnership, Garmin&amp;rsquo;s clients can access these features and integrate them with Garmin&amp;rsquo;s wearable devices, creating a comprehensive employee health improvement solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collagen, probiotics, and plant-based protein were popular subjects at Vitafoods Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</guid><description>Vitafoods Asia, a nutraceutical event showcasing the newest ingredients, product advancements, and technology driving innovation in the industry, revealed emerging trends.
Chris Lee, MD, Global Health &amp;amp; Nutrition Network Europe, Informa Markets, stated, &amp;ldquo;Nutraceuticals are a booming industry in Asia, and Informa Markets aims to support its growth in the region by providing a knowledge base and platform.&amp;rdquo;
First-time attendee Rikhia Mazumdar, Global Senior Brand Manager for Reckitt Benckiser, expressed her intention to return the following year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consuming protein at breakfast may aid in weight loss</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-protein-at-breakfast-may-aid-in-weight-loss/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-protein-at-breakfast-may-aid-in-weight-loss/</guid><description>Source: CSIRO.
Protein in the morning
could help with weight
management.
Increasing protein intake, particularly during breakfast, might be crucial for healthy weight loss, as per a new report from CSIRO. The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Protein Balance: New concepts for protein in Weight Management,&amp;rdquo; supports the CSIRO Total Wellbeing Diet for weight management. It highlights recent scientific findings suggesting that consuming at least 25 grams of protein per main meal can help regulate hunger and boost muscle metabolism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-protein-at-breakfast-may-aid-in-weight-loss/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-protein-at-breakfast-may-aid-in-weight-loss/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New website offers discounted gym classes in Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</guid><description>Source:
FILLMYCLASS.
Similar to discounts for last-minute travel bookings, you can find more affordable gym classes at the last minute too.
A new website called FILLMYCLASS has launched in Melbourne, Australia. This website connects fitness enthusiasts with open spots in fitness classes at gyms and studios nearby.
FILLMYCLASS founder Daniel Waide states, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all about flexibility. The aim is to encourage more people to be active. Offering the ability to select classes that fit their schedule at any gym or studio increases the likelihood of people becoming and staying active...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increase your productivity by installing a treadmill at your desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</guid><description>A recent study featured in the journal Plos One found that using a treadmill desk could lead to higher productivity compared to a traditional desk setup.
[Image of a treadmill desk]
Source: Plos One
This study, titled &amp;ldquo;Treadmill Workstations: The Effects of Walking while Working on Physical Activity and Work Performance&amp;rdquo;, was conducted by researchers from the University of Minnesota-Twin Cities, University of Texas-Arlington, Mayo Clinic, and Arizona State University. Over 12 months, they observed the impact of treadmill desks on physical activity and work output at a financial services company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anantara's Al Baleed Resort Salalah introduces new wellness program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</guid><description>Source: Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara. The Balance Wellness by Anantara program includes custom-designed vegan cuisine.
The luxurious, private pool villa resort Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara has introduced a new wellness program with an a la carte approach.
Situated between a private beach and a freshwater lagoon in Salalah, Oman, Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara provides a serene setting for guests to focus on their wellness goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kinetika Xtreme is unveiling innovative workout technology designed to enhance fitness levels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</guid><description>Ghaneswaran Sukumaran holds a certification from Italy and is one of only two TechnoGym Master Trainers in Singapore. His wife, Santhi Haridass, is the other. As the owner of Kinetika Xtreme, a gym in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Turf City that specializes in movement-based functional training, Sukumaran expresses concern that many individuals join gyms without proper research and engage in exercises that may be detrimental in the long term.
&amp;ldquo;Many people equate weight loss with fat loss and believe that excessive jogging is the key to achieving a slim physique...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Herbalife has found that women in Singapore who work are less active than men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</guid><description>Herbalife, a worldwide nutrition company, has found some differences in the health outlooks and routines of working men and women in Singapore. Their Nutrition at Work survey showed that, compared to men, women in Singapore tend to stay at their desks longer, eat lunch at their desks more, and have more difficulty being active during a typical workday.
“Our aim as a global nutrition company is to provide members and customers with high-quality nutrition products that support healthy eating and active lifestyles,” said Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australians are worried about the amount of sugar in fizzy drinks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</guid><description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s carbonated soft drink (CSD) market is experiencing ongoing challenges due to consumer worries about sugar content, as reported by Mintel, a global market intelligence firm.
Mintel predicts that the total sales volume of CSDs in Australia will likely decrease by 2.3% in 2017, following a 4.7% drop from 2014 to 2016.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research suggests that growing awareness of sugar&amp;rsquo;s negative effects has prompted many Australians to reevaluate their sugar consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IHH Healthcare, NUS, Otis, and PSA set new standards for leadership and workplace mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</guid><description>WorkWell Leaders (WWL), a Singapore-based non-profit focused on workplace wellbeing and mental health, has revealed the winners of the WorkWell Leaders Awards 2024. These awards acknowledge exemplary practices in promoting positive change within workplaces. WWL emphasized that these awards are unique in their recognition of specific elements of workplace wellbeing that drive business results, as well as leadership behaviors that foster cultural transformation within organizations.
Anthea Ong, Founder and Chairperson of WorkWell Leaders, stressed the importance of addressing mental health proactively in the workplace, stating, &amp;ldquo;With 70% of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s population employed and spending a significant portion of their day at work, workplaces must serve as catalysts to support employees and their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Making small changes to your lifestyle can lead to a healthier you in the long run, according to Herbalife</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</guid><description>People in Asia are interested in expanding their fitness routines beyond traditional practices like yoga and tai chi. However, Samantha Clayton, Director of Worldwide Fitness Education at Herbalife, notes that they face unique challenges, such as extreme weather and demanding work schedules, and need to adapt their fitness routines accordingly.
She emphasizes the importance of integrating fitness into everyday life, especially when environmental factors like air quality, heat, and humidity can be obstacles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bose's sleepbuds are specifically created to improve our sleep quality by masking noise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</guid><description>Bose has introduced noise-masking sleepbuds — wireless earbuds designed to combat common sleep-disrupting noises with a blend of comfortable design and soothing sounds.
Source: Bose. Bose sleepbuds offer noise
masking, not noise cancellation.
These sleepbuds, the most compact product Bose has developed, come equipped with 10 preloaded &amp;ldquo;sleeptracks.&amp;rdquo; These tracks are designed to mimic the frequencies of common noises like snoring, neighbors, dogs, and traffic, effectively masking them with calming audio...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce the risk of cancer in your workplace with International SOS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/</guid><description>International SOS has used World Cancer Day to highlight the impact of cancer on the workplace and encourage companies to take action. They emphasize that many cancer cases are preventable and point out that workplaces can contribute to cancer risk factors like unhealthy habits and exposure to harmful substances.
The organization&amp;rsquo;s Medical Director, Dr. Kate O&amp;rsquo;Reilly, stressed the growing impact of cancer on the workforce, stating that it affects not just the individual but the entire organization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-the-risk-of-cancer-in-your-workplace-with-international-sos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The latest Apple watches have the capability to contact someone in case of a fall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</guid><description>Apple has released the Apple Watch Series 4, a redesigned smartwatch focused on connectivity, activity tracking, and health management.
Maintaining its classic look, the fourth iteration boasts a 30% larger screen and a smaller, slimmer casing. This model introduces advanced fitness and communication features with watchOS 5, a new accelerometer and gyroscope for fall detection, and an electrical heart rate sensor that enables electrocardiograms (ECGs) through the new ECG app...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is prepared to take action in response to Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Health (MOH) has implemented the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s (WHO) recommendations for Ebola virus disease (EVD) preparedness and is going even further. The ministry is prepared to adjust its measures as the situation changes.
One of the recommendations is to educate travelers about the potential dangers of EVD. The MOH is using various channels, such as its website and media releases, to inform the public and potential travelers about the disease...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fighting tuberculosis in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fighting-tuberculosis-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 20:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fighting-tuberculosis-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>International SOS, a company specializing in health and security risk services, emphasizes the importance of protecting employees against tuberculosis (TB), particularly in light of World Tuberculosis Day on March 24th.
The World Health Organization (WHO) reports a concerning trend: an estimated 10.6 million TB cases in 2022, up from 10.3 million in 2021. International SOS stresses that this rise highlights the urgent need for heightened awareness and proactive preventative measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fighting-tuberculosis-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fighting-tuberculosis-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fosun Trade Medical Devices introduces a dual-function blood glucose and uric acid tester called BUZUD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 14:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</guid><description>Source: BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices. This image showcases the Safe AQ UG Blood Glucose and Uric Acid Monitoring System from BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices. This system allows for convenient at-home testing of both uric acid and blood glucose levels.
BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices, a medical device company, has launched the Safe AQ UG Blood Glucose and Uric Acid Monitoring System. This innovative device allows users to measure both blood sugar and uric acid levels from the comfort of their homes with ease and a high degree of accuracy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent Euromonitor survey reveals sugar as a new culprit in the food industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has observed a growing global trend of consumers turning against sugar. This shift in attitude stems from heightened awareness of its health implications.
Consumers are actively trying to decrease or eliminate sugar from their diets, with a significant 42% actively looking for food labels indicating low or no added sugar, according to Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Global Consumer Trends Survey.
&amp;ldquo;Sugar is now widely perceived as a health risk, with some even equating it to tobacco in terms of toxicity,&amp;rdquo; says Gina Westbrook, Director of Strategy Briefings at Euromonitor International...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS introduces an integrated health management portal to assist employees in maintaining their well-being</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/</guid><description>Source: DBS. To introduce iHealth@DBS, DBS Asia Hub employees were encouraged to participate in a large group workout.
DBS Bank introduced iHealth@DBS, a comprehensive health management platform, to further cultivate a culture of well-being for its employees. The goal of this centralized platform is to promote lasting behavioral changes among staff. This will be achieved through interactive engagement on digital platforms, including mobile devices and wearable technology.
iHealth@DBS is the newest addition to a comprehensive package of wellness benefits offered to DBS employees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization recommends restricting the use of personal audio devices to less than one hour per day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</guid><description>Source: WHO.
The World Health Organization (WHO) cautions that over a billion adolescents and young adults risk noise-induced hearing loss. This danger stems from unsafe listening practices with personal audio devices like smartphones and exposure to high sound levels at entertainment venues, including sporting events.
WHO analysis of data from developed and developing nations reveals that nearly half of teenagers and young adults aged 12-35 experience unsafe sound levels from personal audio devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Angsana now offers allergy testing specifically for Asians</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angsana-now-offers-allergy-testing-specifically-for-asians/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angsana-now-offers-allergy-testing-specifically-for-asians/</guid><description>Angsana Molecular &amp;amp; Diagnostics Laboratory announced a partnership with Thermo Fisher Scientific to offer allergen sensitivity tests tailored for the Asian population. These tests, utilizing Thermo Fisher&amp;rsquo;s ImmunoCAP technology and conducted by Phadia Laboratory Systems, address the growing understanding that allergen sensitivities can differ across ethnicities and geographical regions due to factors like genetics, environment, diet, and social behaviors.
Angsana aims to create and validate specific allergen sensitivity tests meeting local needs by leveraging the high specificity, sensitivity, quantitative results, quality, and extensive allergen menu of ImmunoCAP technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angsana-now-offers-allergy-testing-specifically-for-asians/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angsana-now-offers-allergy-testing-specifically-for-asians/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is debate over whether mobile phones can cause cancer, with some believing they can and others disagreeing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</guid><description>There have been many concerns about mobile phones and cancer risks. Since the first mobile phone&amp;rsquo;s debut in 1984 and their rise in popularity in the 1990s, it&amp;rsquo;s taken time to study the long-term effects of mobile phone radiation, as some cancers take years to manifest. We might only now be starting to see the impact.
A recent study in Pathophysiology suggests that radiation from mobile and cordless phones could contribute to a specific brain tumor called glioma...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TomTom's latest Spark GPS fitness watches also have the capability to play music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. TomTom has introduced the Spark GPS fitness watch line. These new watches include a 3GB music player, making it simpler for fitness enthusiasts to enhance their workouts by listening to music directly from their wrist.
The TomTom Spark GPS fitness watch can stream music to a variety of Bluetooth headphones. It also includes a preloaded thirty-minute Running Trax curated by Ministry of Sound. Users can easily download playlists to the TomTom Spark from iTunes or Windows Media Player...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers at Herbal Pharm choose supplements for eye health, blood sugar management, and joint care</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-at-herbal-pharm-choose-supplements-for-eye-health-blood-sugar-management-and-joint-care/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 12:52:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-at-herbal-pharm-choose-supplements-for-eye-health-blood-sugar-management-and-joint-care/</guid><description>Source: Herbal Pharm. Herbal Pharm, the company that makes i.360, says that this product is used to relieve the symptoms of dry eyes.
Herbal Pharm, a nutraceutical company, has revealed that its three best-selling products are the i.360 eye supplement, Dia-Med Nopal Cactus vegetarian capsules, and NutraJoint Gold Flex.
The i.360 supplement is marketed toward individuals aiming to alleviate and prevent long-term eye issues, particularly dry eyes.
Dia-Med Nopal Cactus vegetarian capsules are designed to reduce blood sugar levels without causing a drop in energy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-at-herbal-pharm-choose-supplements-for-eye-health-blood-sugar-management-and-joint-care/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-at-herbal-pharm-choose-supplements-for-eye-health-blood-sugar-management-and-joint-care/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASICS introduces the versatile fuzeX TR, an all-in-one fitness solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 08:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The fuzeX TR training shoe.
ASICS has introduced the fuzeX TR, a training shoe designed for greater workout efficiency with its lightweight cushioning and versatile design. This all-in-one shoe supports athletes of all backgrounds and experience levels, accommodating activities from high-intensity interval training (HIIT) and weightlifting to treadmill running.
The fuzeX TR launch is part of ASICS&amp;rsquo;s larger expansion into the training category, a market expected to exceed US$55 billion globally by 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The turmeric latte mix simplifies the process of enjoying golden milk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/</guid><description>A sample pack of turmeric latte mix.
Nature&amp;rsquo;s Harvest Turmeric Latte Mix, produced in Western Australia and available in Singapore and Malaysia through distributor 1000Tsuru via their website Goldenmylk, leverages the increasing consumer interest in turmeric&amp;rsquo;s health advantages.
Andre Lim, based in Australia, and Paul Ong, in Singapore, co-founded 1000Tsuru to expand the reach of this vegan, naturopath-endorsed blend beyond Australia. &amp;ldquo;We are the primary distributor for Singapore and Malaysia, but we are aiming to introduce it to the broader Asian market soon,&amp;rdquo; Lim stated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FairPrice promotes healthier options and takes a stand against diabetes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fairprice-promotes-healthier-options-and-takes-a-stand-against-diabetes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fairprice-promotes-healthier-options-and-takes-a-stand-against-diabetes/</guid><description>NTUC FairPrice (FairPrice) is starting a series of initiatives this year to encourage healthy eating habits and raise awareness about diabetes. The first of these initiatives is a three-month-long 5% discount on all FairPrice housebrand wholegrain rice. Additionally, for the next two weeks, FairPrice will offer the same discount on all 1,000 products across its 133 supermarkets that carry the Healthier Choice Symbol. These discounts are anticipated to save FairPrice shoppers over half a million dollars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fairprice-promotes-healthier-options-and-takes-a-stand-against-diabetes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fairprice-promotes-healthier-options-and-takes-a-stand-against-diabetes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the Healthy MICE Programme by SilverNeedle Hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-healthy-mice-programme-by-silverneedle-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-healthy-mice-programme-by-silverneedle-hospitality/</guid><description>To address the increasing demand for healthier options at conferences, SilverNeedle Hospitality is launching &amp;ldquo;Healthy Minds, Healthy Thinking,&amp;rdquo; a new MICE (Meetings, Incentives, Conferences, and Exhibitions) program.
Watermelon salad
This program is being launched in response to a survey of 85 event organizers, in which 93% indicated that healthy food choices were a significant factor in their venue selection process.
&amp;ldquo;‘Our Healthy Minds, Healthy Thinking’ program came about because of a real need in the MICE sector,” explained Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director and Group CEO of SilverNeedle Hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-healthy-mice-programme-by-silverneedle-hospitality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-healthy-mice-programme-by-silverneedle-hospitality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The US CDC has compiled a list of airports worldwide that are smoke-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</guid><description>Of the 50 busiest airports globally, 23 have implemented completely smoke-free indoor environments. This means that 46% of the busiest airports offer protection from secondhand smoke for travelers and employees, as per a recent report from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). The remaining 27 airports permit smoking in designated areas or spaces equipped with ventilation systems.
An airport was classified as having a smoke-free policy only if smoking was completely prohibited in all indoor areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Promoting mental health resilience in the workplace: International SOS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promoting-mental-health-resilience-in-the-workplace-international-sos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 23:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promoting-mental-health-resilience-in-the-workplace-international-sos/</guid><description>Source: International SOS. People in a discussion.
In anticipation of World Mental Health Day on October 10th, International SOS, a global health and security risk services firm, highlights the growing issue of employee mental health challenges due to the persistent global crises. According to the company, &amp;ldquo;The convergence of a global pandemic, cost-of-living crisis, geopolitical unrest, and the rapidly evolving workplace dynamics has created an unparalleled level of stress for individuals and organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promoting-mental-health-resilience-in-the-workplace-international-sos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promoting-mental-health-resilience-in-the-workplace-international-sos/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>