<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jewellery on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jewellery/</link><description>Recent content in Jewellery on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:02:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jewellery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beads Actually is introducing a special merlion bead in celebration of SG50, available for a limited time only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beads-actually-is-introducing-a-special-merlion-bead-in-celebration-of-sg50-available-for-a-limited-time-only/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beads-actually-is-introducing-a-special-merlion-bead-in-celebration-of-sg50-available-for-a-limited-time-only/</guid><description>The Singaporean store Beads Actually is offering pre-orders for a merlion bead from OHM Beads. The merlion, a creature with a lion&amp;rsquo;s head and a fish&amp;rsquo;s body and tail, is a well-known symbol of Singapore.
Only two hundred of these beads are available, exclusively through Beads Actually from July 2nd to July 31st. Following this period, it will be available for individual purchase globally.
The bead, priced at S$110, is included in a starter kit featuring either a plain bangle or a snap-clasp bracelet.</description></item><item><title>TINKR combines fashion, design, and 3D printing technology in a unique way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</guid><description>TINKR, a company from Singapore, has transitioned its business model from solely offering 3D printing services. They now focus on merging fashion, design, and technology to produce unique corporate gifts.
In a recent announcement, company founders Xiaohui and Freda expressed their passion for blending craftsmanship with technology. They are excited to introduce their latest venture: high-quality, locally and regionally designed prints. They plan to collaborate with various artisans and designers in the upcoming months to create fresh, unique prints with a distinctive style.</description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace.</description></item><item><title>A duo from Singapore and Italy have introduced Oro D’ Italia at the Singapore Jewellery and Gem Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-duo-from-singapore-and-italy-have-introduced-oro-d-italia-at-the-singapore-jewellery-and-gem-fair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 10:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-duo-from-singapore-and-italy-have-introduced-oro-d-italia-at-the-singapore-jewellery-and-gem-fair/</guid><description>Source: UBM Asia, the organizers of SJGF 2016. From left: Cascapera and Lim.
Oro D’ Italia (Oro Di Italia), a purveyor of 100% Italian handmade fine jewelry, has premiered at the fourth Singapore Jewellery and Gem Fair (SJGF 2016) at Marina Bay Sands.
The platform is the creation of Rosalind Lim, a Singaporean, and Fabio Cascapera, an Italian. Lim possesses over three decades of experience in fine jewelry and has collaborated closely with affluent individuals and buyers.</description></item><item><title>Men's cufflinks that can be customized are now offered on Indiegogo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</guid><description>CuffloCs, customizable cufflinks designed for men, are seeking funding on Indiegogo. These unique cufflinks feature a secure compartment for holding small items. According to creator Josh Jablonski, CuffloCs can accommodate a variety of small objects, such as jewelry charms, pebbles, or even photographs.
Source: Indiegogo.
&amp;ldquo;The screw/on off design ensures the security of your items within the double-sided glass, and the cufflink can be effortlessly disassembled to switch up the design,&amp;rdquo; explains Jablonski on his Indiegogo page.</description></item><item><title>Tinkr provides custom calligraphy necklaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-provides-custom-calligraphy-necklaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 19:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-provides-custom-calligraphy-necklaces/</guid><description>Source: Tinkr website.
The company Tinkr is offering custom-made pendants. These pendants are unique corporate gifts because they are designed using a person&amp;rsquo;s actual handwriting.
Starting at S$78, the company will craft a pendant featuring up to two words written in the handwriting provided. For those who prefer professional calligraphy, Tinkr offers this service starting at S$98. Veronica Halim, Tinkr&amp;rsquo;s in-house calligrapher, would design the calligraphy.
Source: Tinkr newsletter.</description></item></channel></rss>