<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AccorHotels on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accorhotels/</link><description>Recent content in AccorHotels on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accorhotels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food.</description></item></channel></rss>