<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Perth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/perth/</link><description>Recent content in Perth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/perth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Vines Resort &amp; Country Club introduces a new garden venue for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</guid><description>Source: The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club. The Pavilion.
The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club, located near Perth, Australia, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Pavilion.&amp;rdquo; This new event space is a specially designed garden structure situated at the front of the resort, offering scenic views of the golf course and surrounding gardens. It&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for events such as conference gatherings or product launches.
The open-air venue, capable of hosting 100 guests, has three sides open to the elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces the Dreamliner to Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has started using Boeing 787-9 Dreamliners for flights to Perth, Australia. These planes provide passengers with larger windows, improved air quality, spacious storage, and advanced technology for a more comfortable journey.
Flight EY486, the first Dreamliner flight, arrived in Perth on June 2nd and was greeted with a water cannon salute. This daily service replaces the Airbus A330-200, increasing capacity by 14%, with Business Class seating up by 27%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality has introduced its second Sage Hotel in Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality.
SilverNeedle Hospitality, based in Singapore, is expanding its upscale Sage Hotel brand in Perth, Western Australia, with a second location. This announcement comes just weeks after the brand launched with a hotel in Brisbane.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated that Sage Hotels are designed for a specific type of business traveler: one who wants a consistent and straightforward experience while working in new cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>