<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RPM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rpm/</link><description>Recent content in RPM on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rpm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor: Spark Snubber Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</guid><description>I recently had a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor on my workbench that I had previously worked on in November 2016 due to a broken brush and a severed pickup coil lead.
The motor recently began experiencing RPM fluctuations again.
This pointed to a problem with the spark snubbers. To access the rotor, I opened the motor:
The spark snubbers, marked with red dots, are located around the commutator. The replacements are on the black pad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and RPM Stability Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor from France was received for restoration.
As is typical, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite brass bearings needed fresh oil. This requires disassembling the motor and extracting the bearings for a vacuum oiling process.
The bearings were submerged in motor oil under vacuum, forcing air out of the porous material and drawing oil in. This process generally takes about 24 hours.
This shows the bearings after the oil infusion.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of DC Motor and a Dead TR2 Transistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</guid><description>After refreshing the PCBs and the RPM trimmer scale backlighting on a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, I turned my attention to its DC motor. Most DC motors in these models need their Oilite brass bearings replenished with oil, as the oil tends to seep out over time, leading to RPM instability. To do this, the motor needs to be disassembled.
The bearings sit on a black pad within the motor. I noticed the motor had been previously repaired, evident in the bent brushes, which would have hindered its performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Replacement of Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) DC platter motor, previously restored in 2016, displayed RPM fluctuations and required attention. Although the motor&amp;rsquo;s bearings had been treated with oil at that time, the spark snubbers were not replaced. The motor had functioned correctly following the initial restoration.
Initial testing involved installing the motor in a 4002 turntable and monitoring its RPM stability over 24 hours. The results are represented by the blue line in the provided graph.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/4002/4004 Relays: Professionally Manufactured PCBs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</guid><description>I recently updated the design of the Beogram 4000/4002/4004 relay adapter boards to allow for professional manufacturing. I&amp;rsquo;ve begun taking and fulfilling orders with these new boards, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled with how they turned out.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the boards:
These boards are compatible with both the older Siemens relays and the newer National relays commonly found as RPM and signal path grounding relays in the 400x series. They are designed as direct replacements for the original relays.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and Dependence of RPM Performance on the Value of C10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</guid><description>I recently obtained two DC motors from Beogram 4002 turntables that are being refurbished. One of the motors is pictured here.
The first step in restoring these motors is addressing the brass sleeve bearings, which are often dry after more than 35 years of use. I do this through an oil infusion process, which requires complete disassembly, as shown.
The bearings, visible on the black pad in the front, are submerged in oil and placed under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: A New Tool on the Bench and the Importance of the Orientation of the Top Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was acquired for restoration. Evidence suggested prior repair attempts on the motor, including scratches on the bearing assembly and damaged brushes.
Upon disassembly, it was clear the bearings hadn&amp;rsquo;t been properly oiled. A vacuum oil infusion process was conducted on both the top and bottom bearings. After cleaning and reassembly, a short circuit was detected, pointing to faulty spark snubbers.
The old spark snubbers were replaced with modern TVS devices.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion, New Spark Snubbers and an Ultrasonic Cleaning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was recently sent in for repair. Initial testing showed the motor was barely functional. To address this, the motor was disassembled, and the bearings were removed for lubrication.
The bearings, designed to be porous and oil-filled, were treated with a vacuum oil infusion process. This process, evidenced by vigorous bubbling, helps to replenish the oil within the bearings over time. After a few days, the bubbling subsided, indicating the bearings were adequately filled with oil, and they were removed from the oil bath.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion of Bearings and New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A DC motor, removed from a Beogram 4002 in Arlington, VA, was sent in for repair.
The initial step involved taking the motor apart and extracting its bearings for lubrication.
The bearings, resembling small rings, were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied. This process causes air bubbles to emerge from the bearing material, indicating oil infusion.
After a day, the bubbling stopped, signifying that the bearings were saturated with oil.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Repair of a Strange Fault Caused by a Shorted Diode D6</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 22:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, a peculiar control system issue persisted even after replacing the reservoir capacitors.
Upon pressing START, the carriage would begin to move but halt after approximately 20 mm, coinciding with the lights turning off. A few seconds later, the lights would illuminate again, and the motor would operate at 45 RPM. In this state, the carriage could be moved using the &amp;raquo; &amp;laquo; buttons, but the arm lowering function was disabled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Too Early Arm Lowering and RPM Change During START</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5524) turntables I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing had a recurring issue: during the start-up sequence, the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consistently lower at the 30 cm mark. Occasionally, the RPM would unexpectedly switch to 45 right after pressing start.
Troubleshooting was challenging because the problem was intermittent. I replaced all the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay, and trimmers, as detailed on my blog. To test, I installed the boards in my own Beogram 4002 (5513).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor Video Published - Check It Out!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finished my Beogram DC motor restoration video due to high demand! This video will show you how to disassemble the motor and revitalize the Oilite brass bearings by infusing oil under a vacuum. If your Beogram&amp;rsquo;s RPM is inconsistent, this video is for you! Have a look:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Very Oily DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:44:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from Berlin, Germany, for restoration. The motor&amp;rsquo;s exterior was noticeably oily, likely due to an attempt to improve its RPM stability through lubrication.
Disassembly was necessary to access and treat the bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was also oil-coated. However, this is ineffective for the bearings, as they require vacuum oil infusion. This process removes air trapped within the porous Oilite brass material, enabling new oil to penetrate the bearing effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Rebuilding the Main and Output PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</guid><description>I recently got the main circuit board, output circuit board, and DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5524) turntable. A customer in the UK sent them to me to fix because the platter&amp;rsquo;s RPM wasn&amp;rsquo;t consistent and the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower to the correct position when starting.
My usual process for these is to replace the electrolytic capacitors, install a new relay, and swap the single-turn RPM adjustment knobs with 25-turn ones for more precise control.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the AC Motor Voltage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 turntable restoration, I observed a noisy motor, especially at 45 RPM. Replacing the electrolytic capacitors helped but didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem completely. To investigate further, I examined the motor voltage and the signal waveform from the Wien bridge oscillator, a clever design that uses an incandescent light bulb as a variable resistor for amplitude control. I measured the AC waveform amplitude at one of the motor leads relative to ground.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor, sent from Pennsylvania for repair, showed typical signs of needing lubrication, emitting a high-pitched noise when first turned on.
The motor was taken apart to access the bearings for oil treatment.
The bearings were placed in oil and a vacuum was applied. The appearance of bubbles showed air being pulled from the bearings, making room for oil to enter. After two days, the bubbles ceased, signaling the completion of the oil infusion process.</description></item><item><title>Another Surprise Addition To The Workshop Beogram 4004</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/another-surprise-addition-to-the-workshop-beogram-4004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/another-surprise-addition-to-the-workshop-beogram-4004/</guid><description>In 2021, I refurbished my Beogram 4004 turntable, which I call the &amp;ldquo;Workshop Beogram 4004&amp;rdquo;. Later that year, I added the Beolover Remote Commander and have enjoyed using it to play records.
This year, I made another enhancement to my Beogram 4004: a Beolover SyncDrive Platter Motor. I was eager to try it out after reading about it on the Beolover Blog.
My Beogram 4004 was already restored and in regular use, with a perfectly functional DC platter motor restored by Beolover in 2021.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Unit Switches Immediately to 45 RPM After Pressing Start</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable being restored exhibited a peculiar issue during initial testing. Upon starting, the tonearm moved as expected but the speed immediately switched to 45 RPM. Pressing the 33 RPM button temporarily resolved the issue, but the speed reverted back upon release.
This unusual behavior pointed to a potential problem with transistors TR3 or TR2. Examining the circuit diagram, we can see how speed selection operates:
The speed control mechanism utilizes a flip-flop circuit with transistors TR3 and TR4.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor and Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently obtained a main PCB and DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002. I began with the motor refurbishment, a process that often requires several days for the bearings to become saturated with oil.
The motor is depicted here:
Disassembly was necessary to access the bearings, visible as two small rings on the black component in the front:
The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was noticeably oily, suggesting prior tampering. This was supported by a damaged commutator brush that was bent out of its intended form:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and Rebuilding of the Platter RPM Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</guid><description>During the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable, the electrolytic capacitors were replaced and new relays were installed to enhance RPM stability. The aging tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail catastrophically, were replaced as a precautionary measure. The main board was refurbished, replacing the electrolytic capacitors and installing new relays, including a custom-designed replacement for the Siemens relay that ensures precise RPM control.
The original reservoir capacitor, a dual-capacitor unit no longer in production, was replaced with a 3D-printed fixture housing two modern capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Motor: A New Tool and a New Spark Suppressor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-motor-a-new-tool-and-a-new-spark-suppressor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 21:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-motor-a-new-tool-and-a-new-spark-suppressor/</guid><description>I worked on restoring a Beogram 4002 DC motor, a process that unveiled a new and interesting failure point for these motors. This experience further refines the restoration process for these motors.
The motor needed its usual oil infusion for the porous brass bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s rough operation when powered confirmed this need.
Upon disassembly, I found this motor had the older brush carrier design, notorious for being glued to the alignment posts and feedback coils.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from the Netherlands, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t use it. The top bearing suspension was damaged beyond repair.
As a result, I refurbished a different motor I had on hand.
To lubricate the bearings, I took the motor apart and submerged them in oil.
A vacuum was applied to the oil-submerged bearings. This caused significant bubbling, signifying air escaping from the bearing material and creating space for oil to enter.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: RPM Performance Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</guid><description>I recently measured the RPM performance of my restored Beogram 4000 turntable. I was curious to see how the AC motor compared to the DC motors found in other models, like the Beogram 8000/8002 with their computer-controlled linear motors. After running the 4000 for 12 hours using my BeoloverRPM device, the results were interesting.
The AC motor demonstrated excellent stability, as evidenced by the graph. However, there was an initial period of drift as both the oscillator and motor warmed up.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Comparison of the RPM Stability Between Four Motors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-comparison-of-the-rpm-stability-between-four-motors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-comparison-of-the-rpm-stability-between-four-motors/</guid><description>Sonavor is currently restoring four Beogram 4002 turntables and recently asked for assistance in refurbishing the DC motors.
The restoration process involves removing the motor bearings, cleaning them, and applying fresh oil. To ensure effectiveness, a vacuum is used to draw the oil into the porous bearing material. The bearings are then cleaned of excess oil and reinstalled.
After reassembly, each motor undergoes a 24-hour RPM stability test using a specialized device.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and Reservoir Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the tonearm and drive carriage mechanisms on this Beogram 4002 (5513), attention turned to the electronics. The initial phase involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, RPM trimmers, and the relay to guarantee smooth operation for years to come.
The main PCB in its original state is shown here.
The same PCB is pictured here after component replacement.
This image provides a detailed view of the RPM control section.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 551x: Exciting!! Replica DC Motor Bearing Prototypes from Beoparts Successfully Tested</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</guid><description>I received another set of Beogram 4002 platter motor components and an RPM panel from a customer in the Netherlands to restore. My work started with the motor, as it usually does.
I disassembled the motor to get to the bearings.
Typically, I would show a picture of the bearings being oiled in a vacuum chamber, but I received new Oilite bearings from www.beoparts-shop.com specifically for these DC motors, which I am testing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Bearings and Installation of New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 06:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor arrived from New Zealand for restoration. The upside-down pulley suggested prior repairs. Disassembly revealed a bent brush, a possible cause for the motor&amp;rsquo;s poor performance.
[Image of motor with bent brush]
The motor was fully disassembled, and the bearings underwent an oil infusion process to address potential RPM instability, a common issue.
[Image of disassembled motor] [Image of bearings in oil]
After the infusion, the bent brush was straightened.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the DC motor required attention. The bearings were making noise, indicating a need for lubrication. This is a common issue in Beogram DC motors of this age, often requiring oil replenishment for stable performance.
The motor was removed from the turntable for servicing.
The bearings, identified as two ring-shaped components, were taken out of the motor.
To lubricate them, the bearings were submerged in motor oil, and a vacuum was applied to remove trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Oil Infusion of Bearings, Replacement of Spark Snubbers, and Repair of a Disconnected Pickup Coil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-replacement-of-spark-snubbers-and-repair-of-a-disconnected-pickup-coil/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-replacement-of-spark-snubbers-and-repair-of-a-disconnected-pickup-coil/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor arrived from Michigan. Initial inspection showed no obvious external issues.
However, a bench test revealed the rotor was blocked, preventing the motor from spinning.
Upon disassembly, it was evident that someone had previously attempted a repair: the brushes were deformed and a pickup coil pin was broken. Further disassembly revealed a loose and disconnected coil near the missing pin.
To address potential bearing issues, the bearings were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</guid><description>During the ongoing restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the incandescent bulbs illuminating the RPM trimmer scales were replaced with LEDs for enhanced longevity. Custom-designed circuit boards housing SMD LEDs were crafted to seamlessly replace the original bulbs, ensuring a direct fit.
These LED assemblies are offered to fellow enthusiasts, with an instructional video demonstrating their installation available online.
The following images detail the RPM trimmer panel, initially showcasing the rear view with original bulbs in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Some Microsurgery on Disconnected Pickup Coils</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-some-microsurgery-on-disconnected-pickup-coils/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 10:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-some-microsurgery-on-disconnected-pickup-coils/</guid><description>I recently obtained a DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002 located in Norway. The motor required repair. The owner had already performed the &amp;lsquo;oil infusion&amp;rsquo; procedure for the Oilite bearings. However, after reassembling and reinstalling the motor into the Beogram, the platter&amp;rsquo;s speed was excessively high and could not be adjusted.
This image displays the motor, without the pulley, in the condition I received it:
Uncontrollably high speed in a DC platter motor usually indicates a problem with one or both of the RPM feedback pickup coils within the motor, assuming the motor control circuit is functioning correctly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Exchanging all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>After finishing most of the mechanical work, it was time to start repairing the electronics on a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable. Replacing all electrolytic capacitors is recommended, as their internal fluid often leaks or dries up. I use high-quality Japanese capacitors to ensure my repairs last as long as possible. Tantalum capacitors, in particular, must be replaced because they can fail dramatically if a short circuit occurs, potentially damaging the circuit board.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor, Main PCB and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 18:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, experiencing RPM fluctuations, recently arrived from a customer for repair. The restoration process involved addressing issues with the DC platter motor, the main PCB, and the RPM adjustment panel.
The platter motor was disassembled to lubricate the bearings. After immersing them in oil and applying a vacuum, the bearings were left undisturbed for two days to ensure proper saturation. Once the bubbling ceased, indicating full replenishment, the bearings were extracted and the motor was reassembled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 and 4004 DC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-and-4004-dc-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 01:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-and-4004-dc-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently acquired two DC motors from Beogram 4002 and 4004 turntables located in Denmark. My typical first step is an oil infusion process to address RPM fluctuations, a common issue.
The 4002 motor arrived in this condition:
Disassembly revealed the following:
The two small, donut-shaped brass bearings, visible on the black pad, were submerged in motor oil under a vacuum. Bubbles appeared immediately, indicating the oil infusion process was working.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Repair of a Damaged Pickup Coil and Oil Infusion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-repair-of-a-damaged-pickup-coil-and-oil-infusion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 14:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-repair-of-a-damaged-pickup-coil-and-oil-infusion/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from Australia was sent in for repair. The owner reported the motor always ran at high speed, suggesting a broken RPM feedback coil. Without this feedback, the motor receives maximum power and spins as fast as possible.
Disassembly revealed the motor&amp;rsquo;s brushes were improperly installed and a solder burn marked one terminal. The small pickup coils, responsible for sending an AC voltage proportional to motor RPM, were also examined.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Keypad Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with LEDs. This enhances the unit&amp;rsquo;s lifespan and prevents issues that incandescent bulbs, susceptible to vibration, can experience during shipping.
The top two bulbs illuminate the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s unique position indicator, while the vertical bulbs light the RPM trimmers. I recently designed SMD LED-based PCB replacements for the position indicator bulbs (available via email).
Standard red LEDs with current-limiting resistors can replace the RPM trimmer bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, RPM Relay and Trimmers on the Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild on this Beogram 4002 (5513), the main PCB was addressed. All electrolytic capacitors were swapped with high-quality, Japanese-made, 105C-rated capacitors. The existing Tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail dramatically, were preemptively replaced with modern equivalents to avoid any potential issues. Images illustrate the original board and the sections targeted for capacitor replacement.
The author designed a replacement for the original Siemens relay using a modern, fully encapsulated SMD relay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - The Influence of C10 on RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-the-influence-of-c10-on-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 10:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-the-influence-of-c10-on-rpm-stability/</guid><description>Another Beogram 4002 DC motor was prepped for restoration.
The process began by removing the bearings for an oil infusion.
The small brass bearings were submerged in motor oil, and a vacuum was applied.
Bubbling indicated that the oil was being drawn into the bearings. These bearings took longer than usual, approximately 48 hours, for the bubbling to cease.
After the bubbling stopped, the bearings were taken out of the oil</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs - New Capacitors, RPM Trimmers and RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the motor and reservoir capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step involved rebuilding the PCBs. This typically involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM trimmers, and the RPM relay. The main PCB, which is difficult to remove due to its hardwiring, was &amp;lsquo;flipped&amp;rsquo; for component replacement.
After replacing the components, the rebuilt board was ready for installation. A new relay was used, as the original Siemens relays often experience oxidation, hindering proper RPM switching.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Stability Test and an Updated Display on the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>I dedicated time to program the compact display integrated into my BeoloverRPM device. This enhancement enables precise RPM adjustments and long-term RPM stability analysis. The display now includes minimum and maximum values, along with the total measurement duration. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the display:
The display boasts high resolution and excellent contrast. However, those of us who are getting older might need reading glasses to decipher the small font. Is perfection ever attainable?</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Oil Infusion of the Bearings and a Shiny New Pulley from Austria</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-a-shiny-new-pulley-from-austria/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 21:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-a-shiny-new-pulley-from-austria/</guid><description>Another Beogram 4002 DC platter motor in need of repair came to my workshop from Virginia. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the motor:
The motor&amp;rsquo;s pulley was unusually worn, with a groove where the raised center, designed to keep the belt aligned, should be:
It barely functioned during the initial test. To address this, I disassembled it to lubricate the bearings:
The bearings are the two small rings on the black surface.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs and Restoring the 33 RPM Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</guid><description>Typically, my restoration process for Beogram 4002 turntables begins with the arm lowering and tracking systems. However, this particular Beogram 4002 (5513) required a different approach. The control system needed attention, so I opted to address the PCBs first.
Upon unpacking the turntable, I discovered that the platter motor would power on as soon as it was plugged in. This unusual behavior was caused by the seller connecting the motor to the standby LED header on the circuit board – a connection point rarely used on the 5513 boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4002 DC motor from France that needed some repair. My typical first step is to rejuvenate the oil-impregnated brass bearings by submerging them in oil. This process is usually successful in restoring motor function. This image displays the motor in its initial condition upon arrival:
To access the bearings, I took the motor apart:
The bearings are the two small ring-shaped components on the black surface.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of Main and Output Printed Circuit Boards, and a New Reservoir Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the PCBs after addressing the decayed transport lock bushings. The main PCB was first, as shown below:
In addition to replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay and trimmers were targeted due to their susceptibility to corrosion and impact on RPM stability. The following image highlights the RPM section in its initial condition:
Modern, encapsulated 25-turn trimmers replaced the old ones, and a new relay was installed (interested enthusiasts can obtain a replacement relay by email or through the contact form).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Oil Infusion of Bearings and Installation of New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 01:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor, in need of restoration, arrived from Washington state. Initial examination showed it needed some work.
A bench test confirmed the bearings were squeaking, a common issue. The motor was disassembled to remove the bearings for lubrication.
The bearings were placed in motor oil under a vacuum. This process forces air out of the bearing material and allows oil to penetrate it. After a few days, the bearings were removed from the oil.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit.</description></item></channel></rss>