<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pay on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pay/</link><description>Recent content in Pay on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse.</description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes.</description></item><item><title>A study conducted by INSEAD has discovered that when shareholders vote on CEO accountability, it leads to higher company returns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:02:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</guid><description>A new study titled &amp;ldquo;Say Pays! Shareholder Voice and Firm Performance,&amp;rdquo; published in the Review of Finance, suggests that shareholder votes do improve CEO accountability and reduce unnecessary spending within corporations. The study&amp;rsquo;s author, Maria Guadalupe, an Associate Professor at INSEAD, found that previous research on the impact of &amp;ldquo;say-on-pay&amp;rdquo; policies was inconclusive, possibly due to focusing on periods after say-on-pay became law.
Guadalupe&amp;rsquo;s research examined 250 instances where shareholders of S&amp;amp;P 1500 companies proposed to adopt say-on-pay policies between 2006 and 2010, before such votes were mandatory.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide.</description></item></channel></rss>