<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keyboard on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/keyboard/</link><description>Recent content in Keyboard on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/keyboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-switches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-switches/</guid><description>A significant issue with the Beogram 4000 design lies in its numerous exposed mechanical switches. Many usability problems stem from oxidized or bent contact tabs on these switches. Attempts to fix these issues often involve bending the contact tabs, which can worsen the problem. This was true for the Beogram I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring. After replacing the solenoid, the right slide transfer button malfunctioned.
While replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with SMD LEDs, I also cleaned the switch contacts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Awesome Refurbished Keypads in the House!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</guid><description>I received two refurbished Beogram 4002 keypads from Denmark today. My friend, who did the repainting, said the weather conditions were perfect for the job, and he was right! The picture shows how fantastic they look.
He&amp;rsquo;s incredibly talented! The keypads look brand new, as if they were just made in 1975. He did a phenomenal job. I had sent him a worn-out keypad from a Beogram 4002 I recently restored, and he even found another one!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of New Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 and it was time to replace the large capacitors. This is a process I enjoy, made easier with a 3D printed adapter I designed. This adapter allows for the use of smaller, modern capacitors while maintaining a neat and organized appearance. I have a previous post detailing the connections for anyone who might find it helpful, as there are several jumpers that require re-soldering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acer unveils three convertible notebooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</guid><description>Acer has expanded its line of 2-in-1 notebooks with the new 11.6&amp;quot; Aspire Switch 11 series and a new Switch 10 featuring a 1080p Full HD 10.1&amp;quot; display. The Aspire Switch 2-in-1 series combines a Microsoft Windows notebook and tablet in one device.
Source: Acer. The Aspire Switch 10.
The Aspire Switch series is thin, lightweight, and durable, designed for work and travel. It supports four modes: touch, typing, viewing, and sharing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Duracell batteries provide six times the power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</guid><description>Source: Duracell. To commemorate five decades of providing portable power, Duracell has partnered with TRANSFORMERS: AGE OF EXTINCTION, the fourth film in director Michael Bay&amp;rsquo;s globally recognized franchise, in a battle of good and evil.
Duracell, the renowned battery manufacturer, is observing 50 years of providing portable power solutions. Although the traditional battery design remains largely unchanged, battery technology advancements have significantly extended battery life.
Duracell&amp;rsquo;s latest CopperTop AA and AAA batteries, equipped with Duralock Power Preserve Technology, are ideal for devices like wireless mice and keyboards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>