<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Index on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/index/</link><description>Recent content in Index on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC).</description></item><item><title>Business confidence in China continues to be weak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</guid><description>While overall business confidence in China showed a slight improvement, activity declined in December as large companies continued to face weak demand and an uncertain business climate. According to MNI Indicators, a provider of economic data and analysis, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t anticipate significant improvement in early 2016. This is reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator, which remains close to the previous month&amp;rsquo;s low point.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator, a measure of current business sentiment, rose 5.</description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales.</description></item><item><title>Dubai ranks in the middle of the global innovation push, according to the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 03:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has published the findings from the inaugural Dubai Innovation Index. Introduced last year, this index is part of the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s plan to encourage innovation and global best practices in the private sector. The index identified medical care, media, marketing, IT, and retail industrial sectors as the most innovative, while professional services, agriculture, fisheries, construction, and energy were identified as the least innovative in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>Adyen predicts that smartphones will soon surpass tablets as the primary device for mobile payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 22:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</guid><description>Source: Adyen. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Adyen, a global payments technology provider, recently released its quarterly Mobile Payments Index for Q3. This report analyzes mobile payment data from web-based transactions across Adyen&amp;rsquo;s customer base between July and September. Notably, the Index reveals that nearly half of online transactions using specific payment methods are now conducted on mobile devices.
The Index shows that 47% of payments made with JCB, a Japanese card, were completed on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age.</description></item><item><title>Singapore ranked among the top five in the 2016 WE Cities Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</guid><description>Dell has identified the top 25 cities worldwide that cultivate high-potential women entrepreneurs (HPWE) for 2016 through their Women Entrepreneur Cities Index (WE Cities). This unique index assesses a city&amp;rsquo;s capacity to attract and promote the growth of women-led businesses. The study focused on cities rather than countries to highlight how local policies and initiatives impact women entrepreneurs, in addition to national legislation and norms.
The WE Cities findings will serve as a starting point for discussions at the seventh annual Dell Women’s Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN).</description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>The demand for jobs in Singapore is being driven by digitization, according to Robert Walters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</guid><description>Source: Robert Walters. Click on the
image to view a larger version.
According to the international recruitment firm Robert Walters, the increasing presence of digital technology was the main driver of recruitment in Singapore during the second quarter of 2015. These insights were published in the company’s Asia Job Index for Q2 2015.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, acknowledged the anticipated decrease in job advertisements during this quarter.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines has been ranked as the airline with the highest positive buzz in Singapore, according to YouGov</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</guid><description>Source: Yougov.
YouGov, a market research firm, has identified the leading brands in Singapore across various sectors based on their &amp;ldquo;buzz.&amp;rdquo; These rankings, reflecting average &amp;ldquo;Buzz&amp;rdquo; scores from January to December 2015, offer insights into brands that garnered the most positive attention from the general public.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the top-ranking brands:
Ecommerce and mCommerce: Q0010 leads the pack, followed by Groupon and Carousell. Retail: Fashion: Uniqlo secures the top spot, with H&amp;amp;M and Robinsons trailing behind.</description></item><item><title>Tourists are disappointed with shopping in Singapore, while locals are loyal to their telecommunications companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tourists-are-disappointed-with-shopping-in-singapore-while-locals-are-loyal-to-their-telecommunications-companies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tourists-are-disappointed-with-shopping-in-singapore-while-locals-are-loyal-to-their-telecommunications-companies/</guid><description>A study by the Institute of Service Excellence (ISES) at Singapore Management University reveals a drop in customer satisfaction within Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retail and info-communications sectors.
The 2014 Q1 Customer Satisfaction Index of Singapore (CSISG) indicates a 2.5 point (3.5%) decrease to 69.6 points for retail and a 0.9 point (1.3%) decrease to 66.8 points for info-communications, both compared to the previous year.
Eight retail aspects were evaluated, with supermarkets as the only sector showing improvement:</description></item><item><title>Female entrepreneurs need more than just determination to succeed, according to Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</guid><description>The first Mastercard Index of Women Entrepreneurs reveals that strong support systems, such as easy access to financial services and a business-friendly environment, are crucial for women-owned businesses to succeed. These enabling factors are essential in overcoming the two biggest hurdles women face in entrepreneurship: cultural bias and limited opportunities for advancement.
Developed economies lead the index, with New Zealand (74.4), Canada (72.4), and the US (69.9) claiming the top spots.</description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations.</description></item><item><title>Women in Saudi Arabia prefer Apple over Almarai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</guid><description>In 2019, Apple surpassed Almarai to secure the top position in YouGov MENA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Women’s Choice Brand Rankings&amp;rdquo; for Saudi Arabia. YouGov attributes Apple&amp;rsquo;s success to the buzz surrounding their new iPhones and Apple Watches, which resonated strongly with women.
Almarai&amp;rsquo;s decision to increase milk prices last year sparked consumer backlash, including calls for boycotts on social media. This negatively impacted the brand&amp;rsquo;s perception among women in Saudi Arabia, causing them to drop from first to fifth place in the rankings.</description></item><item><title>The CIER Employment Index indicates a decrease in employment rates in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</guid><description>The Chinese job platform Zhaopin and the China Institute for Employment Research (CIER) at Renmin University have published their CIER Employment Index Report for July to September 2015.
The report&amp;rsquo;s index, which measures the ease of finding a job, rose consistently from 2011 to 2014. However, mirroring the economic slowdown, the job market has weakened, leading to a decline in the CIER Index for the past two quarters. The index dropped from its peak of 2.</description></item></channel></rss>