<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Train on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/train/</link><description>Recent content in Train on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/train/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotels.com provides exclusive information on transportation options to and from the airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</guid><description>Hotels.com, a website for booking accommodations online, has put together an insider&amp;rsquo;s guide on the top transportation choices from 29 major airports globally. This guide, called the Hotels.com Airport Transportation Insider, compares taxis, private cars, and public transportation in popular international and domestic destinations using data from the recent Hotel Price Index™. Although it&amp;rsquo;s geared towards US travelers, the infographic provides helpful information for cities like Bangkok, Beijing, Singapore, and Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JR East Group provides a variety of vegan and Muslim-friendly desserts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jr-east-group-provides-a-variety-of-vegan-and-muslim-friendly-desserts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 10:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jr-east-group-provides-a-variety-of-vegan-and-muslim-friendly-desserts/</guid><description>Source: JR East via PRN Asia. JR East Group introduces its Plant Based Sweets Series. The grey dish features CAMPANELLA BROWN cookies, while the glass bowl showcases Boule de Rouge cookies.
To share its high-quality food with a global audience, the East Japan Railway Company (JR East) has introduced the Plant Based Sweets Series. These sweets are made entirely from plant-based ingredients, sourced from Tokyo. This means they are free of animal products, including bone char-refined sugar, honey, and alcohol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jr-east-group-provides-a-variety-of-vegan-and-muslim-friendly-desserts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jr-east-group-provides-a-variety-of-vegan-and-muslim-friendly-desserts/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>