<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephone Systems on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-systems/</link><description>Recent content in Telephone Systems on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TalkSwitch Supports both VoIP and Legacy PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</guid><description>Choosing between a traditional phone system (analog or digital TDM PBX) and a newer VoIP system can be tough. TalkSwitch offers a solution by supporting both technologies.
For example, the TalkSwitch 244vs desktop PBX handles 2 incoming lines, 4 extensions for analog phones, and features like voicemail and music on hold. It also supports 10 remote extensions, allowing cell phones, home phones, and phones on other systems to connect by dialing a 3-digit extension...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Becomes Of The Broken Hardware?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</guid><description>_While troubleshooting a LAN for faulty wiring, I&amp;rsquo;m haunted by thoughts of server failures. The concept of uptime seems like a cruel joke, and I&amp;rsquo;m desperate for a solution.
What happens to malfunctioning equipment that dies prematurely? I need to determine the root cause of this outage.
The list of underlying issues is extensive, and the network is collapsing. The pressure mounts daily, becoming unbearable.
I examine server logs, looking for answers while facing the frustrated stares of the staff who demand updates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Telecommunications from Packet8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</guid><description>If your company is outgrowing its current phone system but a full-blown PBX system seems like overkill, there&amp;rsquo;s a middle ground: hosted telecommunications.
Instead of housing your own PBX equipment, hosted solutions put that functionality in the cloud, similar to website hosting. You get all the features of an in-house system without the bulky hardware. Your office phones connect to the provider&amp;rsquo;s equipment through your broadband connection.
Packet8 is a leading provider of hosted telecom for small to medium businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>