<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital/</link><description>Recent content in Digital on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The US has published the 2016 Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</guid><description>The Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR) has released its annual Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets report. The 2016 review calls attention to online and physical marketplaces around the world that reportedly engage in or facilitate significant copyright infringement and trademark counterfeiting.
USTR Michael Froman emphasized the problem of piracy and counterfeiting in online markets, saying that governments need to address these issues throughout the supply chain to protect consumers from unsafe products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Kobo eReader ecosystem is now accessible in the GCC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</guid><description>Source: Kobo. The Kobo
Aura H2O eReader.
Kobo, the eBook retailer, and distributor Lionfish have announced that Kobo&amp;rsquo;s digital reading platform is launching in the GCC region. This will give readers access to Kobo&amp;rsquo;s eBookstore, which offers over 4.2 million titles. They will also be able to purchase eReaders and apps compatible with iOS, Android, Microsoft, and BlackBerry platforms.
Kobo products will be sold in 34 stores throughout the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bain details ways to make money in the era of Generation #hashtag</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bain-details-ways-to-make-money-in-the-era-of-generation-hashtag/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bain-details-ways-to-make-money-in-the-era-of-generation-hashtag/</guid><description>Bain &amp;amp; Company, in their yearly report &amp;ldquo;Generation #hashtag ascendant: Think native digital first,&amp;rdquo; advises entertainment, media, publishing, and service industries to prioritize a &amp;ldquo;native-digital-first&amp;rdquo; approach.
They define &amp;ldquo;Generation #hashtag&amp;rdquo; as individuals who favor content created and shared solely on digital platforms, especially mobile, regardless of their age. Bain notes that this group, first identified in 2014, now makes up almost half of all media consumers. Surprisingly, younger consumers are increasingly willing to pay for content even with limited budgets and access to pirated alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bain-details-ways-to-make-money-in-the-era-of-generation-hashtag/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bain-details-ways-to-make-money-in-the-era-of-generation-hashtag/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore investors who are accredited can transition to digital investing with Jachin Capital</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</guid><description>Jachin Capital, a Singapore-based independent fund manager, is now authorized to offer its digital investment platform, iAdvisor, to accredited investors in Singapore after receiving a Capital Markets Services Licence from the Monetary Authority of Singapore. The company specializes in providing investment management solutions, including discretionary and non-discretionary options, to accredited investors and private family offices throughout the Asia-Pacific region. Jachin Capital uses a transparent, rules-based approach to build and regularly rebalance investment portfolios around specific themes or ideas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Women in Business Asia Pageant hosts a workshop on digital marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</guid><description>Source: Women in Business Asia Pageant Facebook page.
To empower women entrepreneurs, the Women in Business Asia Pageant is holding a masterclass on digital marketing and social media strategies specifically for women in Singapore.
The session, titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Marketing and Social Media Hacks for Women in Business,&amp;rdquo; will run for one hour and teach participants how to build an effective, business-oriented website designed to generate leads. Attendees will discover how to incorporate both original and curated content into their marketing plans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is leading the way in digital transformation and digital leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</guid><description>Source: SAP. Agree or disagree? Management and staff in Southeast Asia and globally share their thoughts in the Leaders 2020 study.
Almost 25% of Southeast Asian companies are considered digital leaders, according to a recent study by SAP and Oxford Economics. This figure surpasses the global average of 16% reported in the Leaders 2020 study.
This new category of high-achieving companies reports greater profit increases, improved employee engagement, and more inclusive workplace environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Facebook claims that only native and video advertisements provide substantial value</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Head of Ad Tech, Dave Jakubowski, recently stated that exchanges and banners lack significant value in a blog post. He highlights that Facebook conducted a test using &amp;ldquo;a buying platform&amp;rdquo; within Atlas, their ad solution. The test revealed that despite reaching real people accurately, many ads were low-quality or fraudulent.
Although effective in removing these poor ads, Facebook was surprised by the sheer volume of ineffective inventory. The test also demonstrated that only native and video ad formats yielded substantial value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you have digital or tech skills, chances are your salary is above average</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</guid><description>Source: Willis Towers Watson. Report cover.
The financial sector, particularly in digital roles, is experiencing salary stability due to a high demand for tech professionals. This trend persists despite overall economic weakness in other industries, including banking, according to the global advisory firm Willis Towers Watson.
Businesses across all sectors are becoming progressively reliant on data and technology, and the banking industry is no exception. This shift has resulted in a talent competition where technological expertise is more valuable than financial background...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe provides a list of suggestions for creating email campaigns that are optimized for mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Adobe&amp;rsquo;s recent email survey suggests that email is not going away anytime soon, at least not in the United States. The survey, which focused on American white-collar workers, revealed that individuals frequently check both their personal and work email. Interestingly, smartphones have surpassed computers as the preferred device for email access. This trend is likely even more pronounced in Asia, a region with high mobile device adoption rates. A study by Experian highlighted that email remains a leading marketing channel in Singapore, especially for driving online traffic to physical stores...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS introduces the first mobile-only bank in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</guid><description>Source: DBS. From left: Sachin Tendulkar, Cricketer, digor
the digibank mascot, DBS CEO Piyush Gupta.
Introducing a pioneering Virtual Assistant powered by artificial intelligence. Account creation utilizes Aadhaar, the largest biometric identification system globally. DBS Bank, headquartered in Singapore and a prominent financial institution in Asia, has introduced digibank, India&amp;rsquo;s inaugural mobile-centric bank. This innovative banking platform harnesses advanced technologies, including biometrics and artificial intelligence (AI), to offer customers a novel banking experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maybank customers in Malaysia can now access Western Union remittances digitally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</guid><description>Maybank and Western Union have partnered to introduce the first digital remittance service in Malaysia. This service, accessible through the Maybank2u (M2u) mobile app and website, allows Maybank customers to send money to over 500,000 Western Union agent locations in more than 200 countries and territories. Available 24/7, the service facilitates transfers up to RM10,000 daily, with recipients typically receiving funds faster than traditional methods.
Datuk Lim Hong Tat, Maybank&amp;rsquo;s Group Head of Community Financial Services, highlighted that this launch strengthens Maybank&amp;rsquo;s online presence and promotes digital transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digital recruitment is becoming increasingly popular, with HireVue leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-recruitment-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-with-hirevue-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-recruitment-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-with-hirevue-leading-the-way/</guid><description>HireVue, a leading digital recruiting platform, facilitates thousands of interviews daily. The company&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Mark Newman, highlights the global employment paradox: millions of professionals are unemployed while companies struggle to fill open positions. HireVue aims to bridge this gap by streamlining the hiring process and creating a level playing field for all candidates, regardless of background. The company emphasizes the importance of allowing candidates to showcase their skills and connect with potential employers effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-recruitment-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-with-hirevue-leading-the-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-recruitment-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-with-hirevue-leading-the-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find joy through organizing your business travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</guid><description>Source: SAP Concur. View from a plane window.
SAP Concur draws parallels between decluttering and business travel, suggesting innovative ways to improve efficiency for travelers.
Andy Watson, SVP and GM for Asia Pacific Japan and Greater China at SAP Concur, believes that just as a messy home can be transformed into a joyful space, technology can turn the often-dreaded experience of business travel into something enjoyable.
Traditionally, business travelers face several time-consuming tasks: manually searching and booking flights and accommodations, organizing multiple bookings, obtaining internal trip approvals, managing paper receipts, and manually filing expense claims upon return...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The implementation of smart technologies is increasing revenues by up to 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</guid><description>A global Avanade study, involving Australian executives, business unit leaders, and IT decision-makers, reveals that a majority of business leaders are already investing in and seeing positive results from incorporating smart technologies in their workplaces. A key motivator is the potential for increased revenue, with business and IT leaders projecting up to a 33% revenue boost from these technologies within the next five years. Furthermore, companies anticipate retraining existing employees, generating new roles, and restructuring their organizations as they predict the repurposing of up to 20% of current roles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online travel insurance offer now available from AIG Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</guid><description>AIG Singapore has introduced a new digital travel insurance product, Travel Guard Direct, designed to improve customer experience from purchase to claim. This innovative product uses data to provide travelers with valuable insights about their destinations.
Travel Guard Direct is the first of its kind in Singapore, offering real-time claims information for popular destinations in Asia Pacific, the US, and the UK. This allows customers to make more informed decisions about their coverage by understanding the risks associated with their travel destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe Sign simplifies the process of creating digital signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</guid><description>Adobe has introduced new cloud-based digital signature solutions, Adobe Document Cloud and Adobe Sign, built on an open standard developed with the Cloud Signature Consortium. This new technology, announced following the Consortium&amp;rsquo;s formation last June, allows digital signatures on any browser or mobile device.
Adobe Sign works with over 200 providers from the European Union Trust List (EUTL) and Adobe Approved Trust List (AATL), offering users a wide selection of trusted digital IDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exchange your remaining loose change for digital currency at airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</guid><description>Source: TravelersBox. A kiosk at Singapore Changi Airport (airside).
Travelers passing through Singapore Changi Airport can now utilize their leftover foreign currency or remaining Singapore dollars more effectively. This is made possible by the new TravelersBox kiosks situated within the airport.
TravelersBox, a financial technology company, assists travelers in converting their remaining foreign currency, both bills and coins, into digital money. This digital money can be redeemed online with well-known brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are now blending their physical and digital experiences. How should companies respond?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</guid><description>A new study emphasizes the importance of personalization in merging online and offline shopping experiences for &amp;ldquo;phy-gital&amp;rdquo; consumers. The study found that while companies are embracing digital technologies, they are lagging in implementing personalization strategies that consumers desire.
The study revealed that personalized promotions significantly influence purchasing decisions, encouraging consumers to buy familiar products and explore new ones. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between consumer expectations and company investments. While consumers value enhanced search and comparison features, companies prioritize features like shopping lists and social elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Singapore is backing F&amp;B and food manufacturers with innovative digital projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</guid><description>RESTAURANT 3.0: Embracing Technology in the Food Industry Enterprise Singapore showcased new digital solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) 2018. These solutions aim to help Singaporean food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and food manufacturing companies expand internationally and enhance their operational efficiency.
The showcased digital initiatives include a B2B online platform for food manufacturers and the RESTAURANT 3.0 exhibition for F&amp;amp;B businesses.
Enterprise Singapore, in collaboration with the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF), launched the &amp;ldquo;SMF SMART App&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Pavilion during FHA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kampong Glam introduces new digital initiatives with the participation of 150 merchants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:03:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</guid><description>Haji Lane in Kampong Glam.
Kampong Glam, the first neighborhood in Singapore to embrace digital technology, has introduced five initial projects to help its traditional businesses thrive in the digital world.
This neighborhood revitalization project, spearheaded by the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), involves collaboration with Enterprise Singapore, One Kampong Gelam (OKG) association, and the Singapore Malay Chambers of Commerce and Industry (SMCCI). Its objective is to make the neighborhood more attractive to tech-savvy shoppers and tourists seeking immersive retail experiences, while enabling businesses to increase their productivity through technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singapore retailer utilizes Qlik and Deloitte Digital solution to monitor customer narratives over time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</guid><description>Inverted Edge, a Singapore-based online retailer, is enhancing the customer experience at its Scotts Square location. Using technology from Qlik, a visual analytics company, and design by Deloitte Digital, the store provides a unique and interactive digital shopping experience.
Source: Inverted Edge website.
In addition to its selection of high-quality, modern luxury clothing, the store features a dynamic display of customer photos and stories from social media. This constantly updated feed showcases how customers style their purchases and shares their experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bayara excels in creating engaging digital activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</guid><description>Bayara, a Middle Eastern brand famous for dried fruits, nuts, and spices, hosted a unique iftar (Ramadan fast-breaking meal) at The Oberoi in Dubai. The buffet featured recipes submitted by their social media followers.
Source: Bayara. Jean-Marc Lourau, CEO of Bayara, congratulated the winners whose dishes were featured at the buffet and also shared the progress that Bayara has made over the last 25 years that they have been in the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digital advertising measurement in Singapore is not meeting expectations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-advertising-measurement-in-singapore-is-not-meeting-expectations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-advertising-measurement-in-singapore-is-not-meeting-expectations/</guid><description>Source: IAB Singapore.
A new study by the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) Singapore, titled &amp;ldquo;State of Digital Measurement in Singapore,&amp;rdquo; reveals that senior marketers believe digital advertising measurement in Singapore is lagging behind.
The study shows that senior marketers rate the sophistication of digital measurement in Singapore at an average of four out of ten, with ten representing the level of advanced markets. Mobile measurement is identified as the most significant area needing improvement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-advertising-measurement-in-singapore-is-not-meeting-expectations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-advertising-measurement-in-singapore-is-not-meeting-expectations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Adobe Symposium 2016 will be sharing important digital marketing trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 16:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. Logo for Adobe Symposium 2016.
Over 1,000 professionals in digital marketing, publishing, advertising, content management, and marketing executives will come together at the Adobe Symposium in Singapore on July 28, 2016. This event will provide insights into how innovative global brands have successfully utilized digital trends to deeply understand their customers, create personalized campaigns, and effectively manage content and assets.
With over 50 sessions across four tracks, attendees will witness the latest innovations from Adobe Marketing Cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank celebrates reaching 100,000 Facebook Likes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</guid><description>Alizz Islamic Bank has achieved a significant milestone by reaching 100,000 likes on Facebook. This achievement places them among the top two banks in Oman to attain this level of popularity on the platform.
Over the past year, Alizz Islamic Bank has significantly bolstered its social media presence, driven by a strong belief in its ability to enhance customer service. In addition to their Facebook success, they have also surpassed 30,000 followers on Instagram...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating the digital landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</guid><description>Business leaders from major telecommunications and media companies recently met to talk about how to thrive in a digital world. IBM iX, the consulting firm that organized the gathering, emphasizes that these challenges are relevant to every industry.
A key takeaway was the urgent need for companies to disrupt themselves before someone else does. This involves understanding emerging digital trends and investing in ways that increase market share and profits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Minute List focuses on dining experiences created by talented chefs and baristas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</guid><description>Hurrah! Productions, a TV and digital content agency based in Asia, has introduced The Minute List, a first-of-its-kind video-driven guide for bars and restaurants in Singapore.
This online platform features one-minute videos showcasing popular restaurants, bars, and cafes in the city. It allows users to make direct reservations at these establishments. Featured venues are nominated by industry professionals, such as chefs, bartenders, and baristas. Each nominated venue is presented through a video interview with the head chef, bartender, or barista...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GMC uses Instagram to showcase PanoGrams and highlight #GMCprecision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</guid><description>Source: GMC.
GMC launched a new Instagram campaign using panoramic photography and the hashtag #GMCprecision.
The month-long US campaign, which began on May 22nd, highlights the meticulous design of GMC vehicles. Using Instagram&amp;rsquo;s new Carousel format, GMC is one of the first car companies to create “PanoGrams.&amp;quot; This format lets users swipe through a series of pictures in a single ad, similar to a multi-page spread in a magazine. These PanoGrams form one panoramic image and include a link to GMC&amp;rsquo;s website for further details...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The latest digital tools that lead to business success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</guid><description>Ebenezer Heng, Principal Consultant at Top Advertising, emphasizes that businesses must understand and leverage the connection between online and offline marketing to thrive. Speaking at the Fuji Xerox DocuWorld Conference, he argued that traditional success factors like &amp;ldquo;gut feel&amp;rdquo; are no longer enough in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
He illustrated this with the example of choosing a business location. Simply observing foot traffic isn&amp;rsquo;t sufficient; online sentiment analysis, which gauges public opinion about a location, can reveal a different picture of popularity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Optimize marketing tactics with native mobile strategies tailored for the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 15:56:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Sinead Woodley, Managing Director UK at April Six, a digital marketing agency, emphasizes that the right marketing approach can significantly enhance early buyer engagement for tech companies. Speaking at the Asia Pacific launch of April Six in Singapore, she highlighted how technology can be leveraged to achieve this.
Woodley cited EMEA-wide campaigns for VMware as a prime example, where April Six successfully reached IT professionals who are typically averse to marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Huawei P10 Plus has the potential to serve as a substitute for a digital SLR camera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:13:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</guid><description>Fashion and beauty photographer Richard Chen, also a Leica Akademie Instructor, believes the Huawei P10 Plus offers the capabilities of a professional camera in a pocket-sized device.
During a Huawei P10 Plus Masterclass held in Singapore, Chen, a professional Leica photographer, shared his growing preference for the Huawei P10 Plus&amp;rsquo;s mobile camera over traditional cameras for personal photography. He appreciates the portability and convenience of the smartphone, noting, &amp;ldquo;If I&amp;rsquo;m exploring I actually don&amp;rsquo;t bring the (conventional digital) camera nowadays&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m starting to use it as the main camera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tata Communications announces Global Scrapbook Challenge ahead of upcoming Formula 1 race</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications company, has launched its second technology challenge offering US$50,000 in prizes. This challenge focuses on harnessing innovative connectivity solutions, a key aspect of Formula 1 racing.
Leading up to the FORMULA 1 GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2014, Tata Communications is challenging the public to create a digital scrapbook celebrating the history of the Mercedes-Benz Silver Arrows in Formula 1. This Global Scrapbook Challenge aims to build a virtual museum, a captivating online archive of stories, memories, and intrigue for fans of the sport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Western Digital introduces a microSD card with a storage capacity of 400GB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/</guid><description>This is the 400GB SanDisk Ultra microSD card.
Western Digital Corporation has introduced a 400GB SanDisk Ultra microSDXC UHS-I card, boasting the largest capacity available for mobile devices.
This UHS Speed class 1 card enables smooth recording of full HD videos. Smartphones that are compatible need to support the SDXC standard.
Margaret Koh, Sales Director, Asia South at Western Digital Corporation, emphasizes, &amp;ldquo;We provide storage solutions for everyone with digital content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-digital-introduces-a-microsd-card-with-a-storage-capacity-of-400gb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The strenuous effort put into improving customer satisfaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 05:29:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</guid><description>A recent survey by Adobe and Econsultancy, involving 14,000 marketers including participants from the Asia Pacific region, reveals that marketers see customer experience as the key differentiator for businesses in 2017.
While investing in technology is important, businesses also recognize the need for a customer-focused, adaptable, and collaborative company culture. The survey indicates that 22% of client-side respondents consider “optimizing the customer experience” as the most exciting opportunity for the coming year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Brunei boot camp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in transitioning to digital platforms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</guid><description>DHgate, the APEC Business Advisory Council (ABAC) China, and ABAC Brunei have initiated the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation Cross-Border E-commerce Training (APEC CBET) boot camp in Brunei. This program aims to develop more skilled professionals within the cross-border e-commerce sector and elevate industry training standards.
E-commerce exporters see a greater first-year survival rate (60-80%) than traditional businesses (30-50%), according to the APEC CBET website. E-commerce also allows exporters to reach around 40 different economies compared to just three to four for traditional exporters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP believes that the digital printing revolution has the potential to make businesses even more agile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</guid><description>Source: HP. High-impact retail graphics, floor covering and corrugated display applications printed using HP Latex and Scitex Digital printing technologies at the new HP Graphics Solutions Centre of Excellence in Singapore.
The way businesses approach printing is being transformed by commercial digital printing presses. Unlike traditional offset printing, which requires large quantities for cost-effectiveness, digital printers can economically personalize any volume of items, from a single piece to thousands, across diverse materials...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>