<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Retail on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retail/</link><description>Recent content in Retail on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park.</description></item><item><title>ICSC's Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards honor D-Cube City, Jem, and Siam Center with gold awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</guid><description>The International Council of Shopping Centers (ICSC) Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards recently celebrated excellence in the region&amp;rsquo;s shopping center industry. Awards recognized outstanding achievements in marketing, retail property design and development, and retail store design.
The Design &amp;amp; Development category acknowledges retail properties for their overall design quality and development creativity, whether through renovation or expansion of an existing property or the innovative design of a new retail project. This category includes both new developments and renovations &amp;amp; expansions.</description></item><item><title>Checkpoint Systems in Hong Kong is dedicated to preventing shoplifting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</guid><description>Checkpoint Systems, a leading provider of retail merchandise availability solutions, has introduced innovative loss prevention and RFID solutions tailored for Hong Kong retailers. These solutions aim to safeguard valuable merchandise from loss and theft across the entire supply chain, from the manufacturer to the store shelf.
Checkpoint&amp;rsquo;s enhanced Merchandise Visibility Solution utilizes cutting-edge labeling and RFID technology, allowing manufacturers to apply RFID tags cost-effectively at the point of manufacture. These tags enable real-time tracking and location identification of individual products throughout the supply chain.</description></item><item><title>Shopee is launching the 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day in September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</guid><description>Source: Shopee website. The countdown begins 1 September.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace owned by Garena Interactive Holding, is launching its first-ever 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day. This one-day event will take place on September 9th and offer shoppers a mobile shopping experience.
The event is anticipated to be the largest mobile shopping sale in the region. Shoppers in Singapore can expect 24 hours of continuous deals and promotions. These include discounts of up to 90%, a selection of items under S$0.</description></item><item><title>Online retailing is becoming increasingly popular for smartphones in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</guid><description>Want to expand your customer base? Consider partnering with an e-mall, especially in China. A recent IDC Mobile Phone Tracker report indicates a rise in the share of e-tailers, like JD, Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Tmall, and Suning Yigou, in China&amp;rsquo;s smartphone market, from 14% in Q2 2014 to 21% in Q2 2015. This translates to a 58% year-on-year surge in the number of smartphones sold via these online platforms.
Tay Xiaohan, a Senior Market Analyst at IDC Asia/Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Client Devices team, highlights that as operators scale back smartphone subsidies, vendors find more opportunities in the open market, with e-tailers emerging as a crucial channel.</description></item><item><title>The groundbreaking ceremony for Jewel has been successfully completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Changi Airport.
Jewel Changi Airport Trustee (JCAT), a collaboration between Changi Airport Group (CAG) and CapitaMalls Asia (the shopping mall branch of CapitaLand), has initiated the construction of Jewel Changi Airport. This mixed-use development, situated in front of Terminal 1 (T1), will feature attractions, retail spaces, a hotel, and airport operational facilities.
Strategically placed at the airport&amp;rsquo;s core, Jewel aims to be a premier lifestyle destination enhancing Changi Airport&amp;rsquo;s global standing and solidifying Singapore&amp;rsquo;s attractiveness as a layover spot for travelers.</description></item><item><title>Business sentiment in Singapore for 2017 is characterized by caution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</guid><description>The Singapore government has released business sentiment data for 2017, covering both the manufacturing and retail sectors.
In the manufacturing sector, a survey conducted by the Singapore Economic Development Board revealed that a weighted 76% of firms expect business conditions in the first half of 2017 to remain similar to the previous quarter. While 13% anticipate improvement, 11% foresee a decline. Overall, the net weighted balance sits at 2%, indicating a slightly positive outlook for the manufacturing sector in early 2017.</description></item><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient.</description></item><item><title>The e-marketplace is focused on small and medium-sized retailers in Java</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 11:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</guid><description>Since its launch, Ula, a marketplace app revolutionizing distribution and credit for traditional retail, has experienced a tenfold growth. Customers are returning to make purchases up to three times their original volume.
Ula emphasizes its success by pointing out that despite the challenges of COVID-19, stores made more purchases in May than ever before.
Launched in January 2020 and headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia, Ula is a multi-category wholesale e-commerce marketplace that blends the technology and tools of modern retail with the cost-effectiveness of traditional micro-retail.</description></item><item><title>Singapore welcomes the arrival of Japanese fashion retail concepts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</guid><description>Source: WMH Group. Kafuku.
World Mode Holdings Group (WMH Group) aims to improve the Singapore fashion retail sector by establishing its first international branch, iDA Singapore (iDA’SG).
WMH Group is a Japanese fashion retail consultancy firm known for strengthening its clients&amp;rsquo; brands. As Japan&amp;rsquo;s top recruiter for beauty and fashion sales professionals, their Singapore branch will offer expert guidance and support to enhance retail staff skills.
“As Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader in retail job placements, we&amp;rsquo;ve placed 100,000 retail staff with approximately 1,000 clients, primarily in fashion and luxury.</description></item><item><title>Criteo unveils a retail sales guide for Chinese New Year in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:48:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</guid><description>Criteo, a commerce media company, has unveiled insights from the 2022 Chinese New Year (CNY) to help retailers anticipate consumer demand and leverage similar trends in 2023.
Starting in January 2022, retail sales surpassed typical levels (based on the average between December 18th and 31st, 2021) until a week prior to CNY 2022 (February 1st), indicating a strong consumer appetite for purchasing. In Southeast Asia (SEA), retail sales hit a peak of 27% on January 25th, a week before CNY.</description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available.</description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence.</description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products.</description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales.</description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances.</description></item><item><title>HP's ElitePOS is specifically designed for the retail industry 2.0</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:36:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</guid><description>HP Inc. is aiming to revolutionize the retail sector with its new HP ElitePOS system, a flexible all-in-one point-of-sale (POS) solution. The company&amp;rsquo;s goal is to enhance the in-store experience by providing a balanced technological approach that boosts sales and simplifies operations.
Research from HP highlights that 69% of customers are more inclined to make purchases in physical stores if they have access to digital self-service resources, such as interactive displays and kiosks.</description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020.</description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3.</description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life.</description></item><item><title>Sony Electronics Singapore is marking the first anniversary of the Sony Store with a celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-electronics-singapore-is-marking-the-first-anniversary-of-the-sony-store-with-a-celebration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-electronics-singapore-is-marking-the-first-anniversary-of-the-sony-store-with-a-celebration/</guid><description>Source: Sony Electronics Singapore. Sony Singapore’s Lifestyle Concept Store at Isetan Wisma Atria.
Sony Electronics is commemorating the first anniversary of its Sony Store located within Isetan Wisma Atria in Singapore. The celebration includes a store revamp and a variety of workshops and special deals offered throughout October.
Designed with the female shopper in mind, the Sony Store presents themed displays to demonstrate how the various products can complement their lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Broadband Available In A Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</guid><description>Imagine this: your new store is ready to open, everything is in place, but you can&amp;rsquo;t start selling because your internet service isn&amp;rsquo;t working. This is where Accel Networks comes in, offering a wireless solution that can get you online in just a few days.
Why choose Accel Networks? Traditional broadband often involves time-consuming installations. Accel Networks bypasses this by using existing cell tower infrastructure. Their service is secure, meets payment industry standards, and covers most of the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless for Point of Sale Authorizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</guid><description>Credit card processing is essential for modern businesses, so having a fast and reliable authorization terminal is crucial. While dial-up terminals might have been sufficient in the past, their slow speed can frustrate customers and reflect poorly on your business. Upgrading to a broadband connection is a worthwhile investment.
T1 lines have become more affordable, making them a popular choice for businesses. However, they can still be expensive for smaller companies.</description></item><item><title>Try Cloud Website Load Testing Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve established your online presence, but the question remains: how strong is it? Just like the story of the three little pigs, a website needs to be built with strong materials to withstand the elements. While a website might appear impressive when it&amp;rsquo;s not in use, the true test comes with a surge of visitors. Load testing is the only way to determine if your site can handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>Smartphone manufacturers are experimenting with various marketing strategies to stand out in the competitive Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</guid><description>Source: Zinnov website.
As the Indian smartphone market becomes more competitive, vendors are shifting their go-to-market approaches, according to management consultancy Zinnov. In their report &amp;ldquo;India Smartphone Market: Witnessing Exponential Growth,&amp;rdquo; Zinnov highlights the intense pressure local vendors face from Chinese competitors. Xiaomi, for example, recently took the lead in 4G LTE smartphone sales, and Micromax is challenging Samsung&amp;rsquo;s dominance.
To stand out, smartphone vendors are exploring different strategies. These include online-only retail partnerships (like Motorola&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Flipkart), establishing physical experience centers to enhance customer interaction (such as Xiaomi&amp;rsquo;s plan for 100 centers in India), and investing in traditional brick-and-mortar retail models (like Gionee&amp;rsquo;s plan for 250 stores).</description></item><item><title>Consumers are seeking additional retail technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 09:25:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</guid><description>Source: Zebra infographic. Almost two-thirds of shoppers surveyed in Europe and the Middle East stated that customer service directly impacts their purchasing decisions. Meanwhile, nearly a third of Asia Pacific respondents prefer collecting online purchases from a physical store.
Consumers are setting higher expectations for their shopping experience, while retailers lag in matching these expectations with their in-store technology investments. Retail customers desire a wide array of options for receiving their purchases.</description></item><item><title>The KOGEI Future Forward exhibition at Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store showcases the work of 15 artists</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</guid><description>The Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a contemporary art exhibition, KOGEI Future Forward, from February 15 to 20, 2017. The exhibition showcases the work of 15 Japanese artists, highlighting kogei as a unique form of Japanese fine art.
Kogei, meaning &amp;ldquo;craft,&amp;rdquo; emerged during the Meiji Period (1868-1912) and has evolved over time to gain recognition as fine art. This exhibition offers a fresh perspective on kogei, curated by Yuji Akimoto, a renowned art professor and museum director.</description></item><item><title>New retail and dining tenants have been announced at City Square Mall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</guid><description>City Developments (CDL) is updating the dining and retail options at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s City Square Mall.
The Decathlon store at City Square Mall, taken on 21 May.
French sporting goods retailer, Decathlon, launched its first Singaporean store on May 21, 2016. The company, known for its wide selection and reasonable prices, aims to make sports accessible.
“Our 21,500 sq ft store carries over 85,000 innovative, high-quality products across 50 sports. It will help Decathlon achieve its mission of making sports accessible to every Singaporean,” remarked Bastien Grandgeorge, CEO of Decathlon Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Dell has launched a new Dell Exclusive Store in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-a-new-dell-exclusive-store-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 16:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-a-new-dell-exclusive-store-in-singapore/</guid><description>The store opening was celebrated with a ribbon cutting.
Dell recently launched a new Exclusive Store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Plaza Singapura mall. This location was chosen for its accessibility and retail focus. The store displays Dell&amp;rsquo;s complete line of consumer products, as well as a dedicated virtual reality (VR) experience zone.
The store is set up for customers to try before they buy. It has experience suites featuring Dell&amp;rsquo;s newest XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware products.</description></item><item><title>Bricks and Mortar Apocolypse, Now?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</guid><description>The physical world is struggling while the virtual world thrives. We may be approaching a point where the internet becomes dominant, and traditional businesses may suffer for unexpected reasons.
Retail has been declining, but recently, there&amp;rsquo;s been a sharp downturn due to rising gas prices. This discourages driving, which leads to less shopping. Shopping is crucial for the economy; a decline in shopping could lead to an economic depression.
Our society relies heavily on driving.</description></item><item><title>A Singapore retailer utilizes Qlik and Deloitte Digital solution to monitor customer narratives over time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</guid><description>Inverted Edge, a Singapore-based online retailer, is enhancing the customer experience at its Scotts Square location. Using technology from Qlik, a visual analytics company, and design by Deloitte Digital, the store provides a unique and interactive digital shopping experience.
Source: Inverted Edge website.
In addition to its selection of high-quality, modern luxury clothing, the store features a dynamic display of customer photos and stories from social media. This constantly updated feed showcases how customers style their purchases and shares their experiences.</description></item><item><title>Jumei expands its online beauty offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</guid><description>Source: Jumei website.
Jumei International Holding, a Chinese online retailer specializing in beauty products, has formed several strategic alliances with international brands. The company revealed that Max Factor and OPI Products have joined its Authentic Beauty Product Alliance (ABPA) and that it has established a partnership with American fashion designer Jill Stuart.
Through its website and mobile app, the company provides a variety of products, including branded beauty items, fashionable apparel, and other lifestyle goods.</description></item><item><title>The Tmall Global report showcases the preferences of Chinese consumers in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</guid><description>A recent report on import consumption in China, the Annual Report on Tmall Global Data 2016, was released by Tmall Global, an online platform allowing businesses outside China to connect with Chinese consumers, and CBNData. The report reveals the strength of e-commerce in China, showing a growing customer base, expanding product interest, and notable trends influenced by significant events.
The report highlights several key findings. First, cross-border e-commerce is entering a new phase, supported by favorable policies from both the Chinese government and global trade organizations.</description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter.</description></item><item><title>Local computer vendor in Singapore raided by police, counterfeit Microsoft software discovered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-computer-vendor-in-singapore-raided-by-police-counterfeit-microsoft-software-discovered/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-computer-vendor-in-singapore-raided-by-police-counterfeit-microsoft-software-discovered/</guid><description>Microsoft is urging consumers and small businesses to be cautious when buying software, warning them about the risks of accidentally purchasing and using counterfeit products. This advisory comes after a recent raid on a computer vendor in Kembangan Plaza by the Intellectual Property Rights Branch (IPRB) of the Singapore Police Force.
The shop in question had been advertising unauthorized &amp;ldquo;Microsoft license keys&amp;rdquo; as genuine and offering computers bundled with counterfeit software at heavily discounted prices through their online store.</description></item><item><title>Tourists are disappointed with shopping in Singapore, while locals are loyal to their telecommunications companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tourists-are-disappointed-with-shopping-in-singapore-while-locals-are-loyal-to-their-telecommunications-companies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tourists-are-disappointed-with-shopping-in-singapore-while-locals-are-loyal-to-their-telecommunications-companies/</guid><description>A study by the Institute of Service Excellence (ISES) at Singapore Management University reveals a drop in customer satisfaction within Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retail and info-communications sectors.
The 2014 Q1 Customer Satisfaction Index of Singapore (CSISG) indicates a 2.5 point (3.5%) decrease to 69.6 points for retail and a 0.9 point (1.3%) decrease to 66.8 points for info-communications, both compared to the previous year.
Eight retail aspects were evaluated, with supermarkets as the only sector showing improvement:</description></item><item><title>SingEx has introduced Last Mile Fulfilment Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 06:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</guid><description>Last Mile Fulfilment Asia (LMFAsia), a debut trade show and conference centered around last-mile fulfillment in logistics and e-commerce, will premiere in Singapore next year.
This is the first event of its kind to hone in on last-mile fulfillment challenges and prospects in Asia. SingEx anticipates the event will attract around 1,500 attendees, representatives, and exhibitors from the Asian region in its first year. LMFAsia aims to unite four crucial sectors – e-commerce, retail, logistics, and parcel delivery – under one roof to maximize business opportunities for e-commerce in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains.</description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay International introduces a new cross-border marketing campaign with global promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</guid><description>Source: UnionPay International. Ge Huayong, Chairman of China UnionPay (sixth from the right), Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International (fifth from the right), and representatives from initial partners were present at the ceremony.
UnionPay International, in collaboration with Bank of China, China Merchants Bank, CYTS, Ctrip, Spring Airlines, SaSa Hong Kong, Prince Jewellery &amp;amp; Watch, LUKFOOK JEWELLERY, and ISA, has introduced 优计划 (Youjihua), translating to &amp;lsquo;a beneficial strategy&amp;rsquo; and playing on the &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; in UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s Chinese name.</description></item><item><title>INVADE aims to connect landlords and retailers in Singapore through matchmaking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/invade-aims-to-connect-landlords-and-retailers-in-singapore-through-matchmaking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/invade-aims-to-connect-landlords-and-retailers-in-singapore-through-matchmaking/</guid><description>INVADE, the first real-time retail space booking platform in Singapore, has officially launched. The platform allows businesses to instantly find and book retail spaces. Over 35,000 retail businesses, startups, and entrepreneurs have already become INVADE members.
The idea for INVADE came from Singaporeans Koh Cheng Guan and Kent Teo. Having experience working with major landlords, marketing pop-up and retail spaces, and organizing flea markets, they recognized the challenges entrepreneurs face in finding suitable retail spaces and the landlords&amp;rsquo; need to utilize vacant space.</description></item><item><title>Australian consumers are pleased to use contactless cards for payment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard survey highlights the increasing popularity of digital payment methods among Australians. Over 80% of Australians use contactless payments, also known as &amp;ldquo;tap and go,&amp;rdquo; weekly. This preference is so strong that a significant number of consumers get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer this option, with some even choosing to shop elsewhere.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and petrol stations are the most common places where Australians use contactless cards. Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, Garry Duursma, emphasizes that Australians view tap and go as a faster and more convenient payment method.</description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4.</description></item><item><title>The first GYOMU and Megumi-no-Sato stores have opened in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-gyomu-and-megumi-no-sato-stores-have-opened-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-gyomu-and-megumi-no-sato-stores-have-opened-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: G-7 Holdings. Pictures of GYOMU Supermarket and
Megumi-no-Sato.
G7 International, a subsidiary of the Kobe-based G-7 Holdings responsible for international operations, has launched a GYOMU supermarket and the first overseas Megumi-no-Sato store in Singapore. Both stores will be managed by BB&amp;amp;G-7 Retail, a joint venture between G7 International and a local Singaporean company.
GYOMU Japan is a wholesale franchise chain known for offering imported products under its own private label at competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils new flagship store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-new-flagship-store/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 07:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-new-flagship-store/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. From left: Anna Yip, Deputy CEO, Singtel Singapore; Yuen Kuan Moon, Group CEO, Singtel; Ng Tian Chong, CEO, Singtel Singapore; and Lionel Chng, MD, Customer Success, Singtel Singapore.
Singtel just launched its latest flagship store, Singtel Shop 313@Somerset, in the middle of Orchard Road. This 4,900 square foot space showcases cutting-edge retail technology to create an enhanced customer experience for shopping, creating, and entertainment. This new store represents Singtel Singapore&amp;rsquo;s renewed dedication to improving the customer experience.</description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor.</description></item><item><title>Utilize online brand ambassadors to add a personal touch to your online presence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</guid><description>Source: Oomph! Lee.
Oomph!, a Singapore-based staffing agency, has introduced ENGAGE, a new online platform and service for brand ambassadors. This platform aims to replicate the personalized customer service of physical stores in the digital world.
ENGAGE connects businesses with trained online brand ambassadors who can interact with customers through a chat box, including video chat options. These ambassadors can help customers find suitable products, answer their questions, and even book in-person store visits for a more traditional shopping experience.</description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new mobile POS printer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 22:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</guid><description>Epson, a company known for its printing and digital imaging solutions, has introduced the TM-m30 point of sale (POS) printer. Created specifically for tablet-based systems, the TM-m30 stands out as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most compact desktop receipt printers, making it a perfect fit for retail and hospitality businesses aiming to transition to a POS system managed by smart devices.
Source: Epson Singapore. The Epson TM-m30 POS printer.
The TM-m30 is engineered for swift and effortless setup on iOS, Android, and Windows mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Belstaff has opened its flagship store in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Belstaff.
The renowned British heritage brand, Belstaff, recently celebrated the grand opening of its flagship store in Tokyo, Japan. Situated within the expansive Ginza Six retail complex, the new store occupies a prime location within this 47,000 square meter shopping destination. This strategic move underscores Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s growing presence in the Japanese market and its commitment to global retail expansion.
Upon its debut, the Tokyo flagship presents a curated selection of Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s offerings, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s complete menswear collection and, for the first time in Tokyo, its womenswear line.</description></item><item><title>Shoppers are interested in clothes, cosmetics, and baby products on 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 22:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</guid><description>Source: Alizila blog. The 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival logo is illuminated in neon.
Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival is surpassing the sales of the previous year. Alizila reports show that it took a mere 1 minute and 25 seconds for the festival to reach over US$1 billion in total gross merchandise volume (GMV).
By 1:15 p.m., Tmall Global had already exceeded its total GMV from the entire 2017 11.</description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult.</description></item><item><title>Shopee reveals birthday flash sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</guid><description>Shopee, a prominent mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is marking its first anniversary. To commemorate the occasion, they are holding hourly flash sales with discounts of up to 70% on December 12, 2016.
Two products will be discounted every hour on December 12th, from 12 pm to 7 pm.
Along with the hourly flash sales on December 12th, Shopee is running a lucky draw for users who take advantage of daily category vouchers.</description></item><item><title>Easy Way to Build an Online Store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-way-to-build-an-online-store/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 10:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-way-to-build-an-online-store/</guid><description>You possess products or services that have the potential to truly impress your customers. You&amp;rsquo;ve experienced local success and believe you can replicate that online. All you need is a visually appealing and fully functional e-commerce platform.
Perhaps you lack design expertise and worry about creating an unprofessional site that might malfunction, harming your reputation and driving away customers. The complexities of setting up a shopping cart can also seem daunting.</description></item><item><title>InPost has officially started its operations in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: InPost.
InPost, a global leader in automated parcel locker networks, has expanded its services to Malaysia. The launch was accompanied by a roadshow, themed &amp;ldquo;Malaysia E-commerce Day (MED) 2015,&amp;rdquo; aimed at raising awareness about the latest advancements in e-commerce, e-payments, and logistics.
According to InPost Malaysia Managing Director Rosland Mohd Jannes, the initiative seeks to connect with businesses and individuals, boosting consumer confidence in online shopping and alleviating delivery-related anxieties.</description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app.</description></item><item><title>Imperva cautions about potential scams on Singles Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imperva-cautions-about-potential-scams-on-singles-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imperva-cautions-about-potential-scams-on-singles-day/</guid><description>Imperva, a leading cybersecurity firm dedicated to safeguarding data, has released a new report on e-commerce security and provided recommendations for secure online shopping in light of the upcoming global shopping event on November 11th.
The company highlighted that Chinese e-commerce giants Alibaba and JD.com achieved a record-breaking US$115 billion in sales during Singles Day 2020, emphasizing that the rise in online shoppers is accompanied by a parallel increase in scams.</description></item></channel></rss>