<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Expense on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-expense/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Expense on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-expense/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage.</description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent.</description></item><item><title>5x5 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 18:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</guid><description>Businesses often want greater internet bandwidth, lower telecommunication costs, or both. A relatively new service called 5x5 Ethernet might be the solution.
Ethernet services are a recent development. Before their rise in popularity, the best bandwidth options were T1 lines and fractional DS3 bandwidth. Fixed location wireless service has sometimes been available, but only for locations with a direct line of sight to their provider.
How do Ethernet services improve upon previous options?</description></item></channel></rss>