<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Capital on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/capital/</link><description>Recent content in Capital on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 02:34:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/capital/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Golden Equator Consulting assists small and medium-sized enterprises and startups in advancing towards success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 02:34:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</guid><description>Golden Equator Consulting (GE Consulting), a business consultancy firm, has established a presence in Singapore to serve small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups in the region. Sharon Chong, CEO of GE Consulting, noted that these businesses need strategic and operational support to streamline their growth and focus on core business functions.
GE Consulting offers comprehensive business consultancy services, covering areas such as business strategy, sales positioning, financial support, marketing, technology, human resources, and legal compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Thomas Piketty to bring about reform in both capitalism and democracy within the European Union?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</guid><description>Steve Peers
French economist Thomas Piketty unexpectedly became a prominent intellectual figure, especially in the UK and US, with his book &amp;ldquo;Capital,&amp;rdquo; which presents a new perspective on the relationship between capitalism and democracy.
Maintaining his engagement with current issues, Piketty has contributed to a proposal for EU reform, connecting his academic work to practical solutions.
The EU, once adept at managing capitalism but less so democracy, now struggles with both...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>