<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HQ on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hq/</link><description>Recent content in HQ on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hubspot's new, modern Asia Pacific headquarters in Singapore is designed with Millennials in mind</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot. Pictured at the official opening ceremony, from left: Jeetu Mahtani and JD Sherman.
HubSpot has officially launched its Singapore office and revealed plans to add 150 employees to its Singapore-based team over the next three years. Currently, HubSpot Singapore has 30 employees.
The Singapore office, warmly referred to as SingSpot, joins the Sydney, Australia office as HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s second location in the Asia Pacific region and will serve as the company’s Asia Pacific headquarters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Leong Group has decided to establish its global headquarters at Damansara City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</guid><description>Source: Damansara City website.
GuocoLand Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s key project, Damansara City, will soon house the Hong Leong Group&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters. The 33-story, top-tier office building, situated on the southwest side of this notable development, will be a major tenant within Damansara City when fully occupied by the second quarter of next year.
The Hong Leong Group is a prominent Malaysian conglomerate with interests in banking, financial services, manufacturing, distribution, property development, investment, hospitality, leisure, and principal investment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing productivity and employee satisfaction at Garena Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-productivity-and-employee-satisfaction-at-garena-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-productivity-and-employee-satisfaction-at-garena-singapore/</guid><description>The abundance of natural light, calming greenery, and plants creates an incredibly serene atmosphere. Situated on the 17th floor of One-North in Singapore, the office boasts breathtaking panoramic views. And then there&amp;rsquo;s the sheer size of the space&amp;hellip;
Garena Online, a Singapore-based Asian internet company offering services like digital content, e-commerce, and payments, has gone above and beyond to design a welcoming 7,500 square meter office. This effort aims to attract and retain top talent, essential for maintaining a leading position in the digital economy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-productivity-and-employee-satisfaction-at-garena-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-productivity-and-employee-satisfaction-at-garena-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>