<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>External Borders on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-borders/</link><description>Recent content in External Borders on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-borders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Border and Coast Guard a completely new entity or just a revamped version of Frontex?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</guid><description>Herbert Rosenfeldt, Research Assistant and PhD candidate, University of Passau
Introduction
Celebrating the new European Border and Coast Guard Agency, also known as Frontex, at the Bulgarian external border with Turkey might seem like an odd festivity. However, last Thursday, high-ranking EU and Member State officials gathered at Bulgaria&amp;rsquo;s Kapitan Andreevo Border Checkpoint for this inauguration. This event marked the implementation of the European Border and Coast Guard Regulation, a significant step towards strengthening external border control in the wake of recent migration challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to suspend Schengen due to Greece? Is it necessary to do so?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</guid><description>A recent leak of a Council document proposes a potential suspension of the Schengen system for a duration of up to two years. This proposal stems from what are being termed &amp;ldquo;systemic deficiencies&amp;rdquo; in Greece&amp;rsquo;s management of its external borders, particularly concerning the influx of refugees and migrants. Such a suspension would provide any Schengen country the option to reinstate or implement border controls along their shared internal borders. While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely that every Schengen country would exercise this option, it&amp;rsquo;s anticipated that several would choose to do so, especially given that a number already have active border controls in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accountability of Frontex: a challenging journey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 22:27:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</guid><description>Laura Salzano, PhD student in Constitutional Law, Barcelona University
Since its establishment in 2004, Frontex&amp;rsquo;s role and duties have been heavily scrutinized by the EU and human rights advocates. This attention stems from various concerns, including allegations of power abuse, opacity, and lack of cooperation. These concerns have been raised by diverse voices, such as policy experts, legal professionals, academics, activists, and NGOs.
Critiques of Frontex originate from both within and outside the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's new law on travel authorization for non-EU citizens creating a brave new world?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A new European Union (EU) law regarding travel authorization for non-EU citizens visiting the EU was recently announced. This new law will impact millions of travelers annually, potentially including British citizens post-Brexit. This law, though not immediately applicable, holds significant future implications. This explanation aims to clarify its reach and functionality. (Update: the final law was officially published in September 2018).
Basics of the system..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Summary of a new report: Is Restoring the Borderless Schengen Area an Impossible Mission?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: BlueMars, via Wikimedia Commons
A new report I wrote for the Swedish Institute of European Policy Studies (SIEPS) analyzes the potential effects of the recently approved changes to the Schengen Borders Code. This blog post summarizes the key findings of the report.
The report addresses concerns regarding the increasing trend of Schengen countries reinstating border checks within the zone for extended periods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>