<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Line Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-line-service/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Line Service on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-line-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IP T1 Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been around for a long time, initially used by phone companies to carry multiple calls between their facilities. Eventually, businesses adopted them for their phone systems. When the Internet became widespread, T1 lines were adapted to serve as dedicated internet connections. This might seem odd given their history, but in today&amp;rsquo;s internet-centric world, T1 lines can indeed function as IP connections.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/) While T1 technology was originally designed for voice calls, the fundamental principle is that digital data is just a series of ones and zeros.</description></item><item><title>Double Bonded T1 Cost and Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 23:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</guid><description>Many businesses appreciate their reliable T1 service, but eventually, the 1.5 Mbps bandwidth becomes insufficient. Instead of abandoning T1, companies can opt for double bonded T1 service, which combines two lines to provide 3 Mbps. This bonding is implemented within customer premises equipment, usually a router with two T1 inputs.
The bandwidth can be further increased by triple bonding (4.5 Mbps) or quadruple bonding (6 Mbps), up to a practical limit of eight bonded lines for 12 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Same Budget, More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Is Slow Network Speed Affecting Your Business?
Are you experiencing frustrating network issues like slow downloads, choppy calls, interrupted streaming, and sluggish website loading?
Do You Need More Bandwidth?
There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance your internet connection needs more bandwidth. While your internal network might be fast enough, your external connection (WAN) might not be able to handle your current needs.
Signs You Need More Bandwidth
If your internet service hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years but your business relies more on multimedia and online tools, you probably need more bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>