<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Package on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/package/</link><description>Recent content in Package on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/package/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Special promotions for the Fireworks Celebration at the Mandarin Oriental, Macau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Macau has special Fireworks Celebration packages perfect for corporate events, team building, or client appreciation. These packages provide a unique opportunity to experience the 26th Macau International Fireworks Display Contest.
Source: Mandarin Oriental Macau website.
Available on September 8th, 13th, 20th, 27th, and October 1st, 2014, the package starts at MOP4,388 and includes:
Overnight accommodations in a room or suite with panoramic fireworks views through expansive windows. A special four-course fireworks-themed dinner for two at the Vida Rica Restaurant, showcasing Chef Dominique Bugnand’s modern take on classic French cuisine.</description></item><item><title>StarHub reintroduces 12GB mobile data bundles and additional features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced a new, budget-friendly package called SurfHub, combining mobile and home internet services.
For a starting price of S$96.56 per month on a 24-month contract, SurfHub customers receive a 4G mobile plan with a minimum of 12GB of data and a 1Gbps fiber broadband connection for their homes. This combined offer costs roughly half the price of a standalone 12GB mobile plan. SurfHub also includes generous benefits like up to 700 minutes of local calls, 1,500 local SMS/MMS messages, and a subsidy for a new mobile phone.</description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities.</description></item><item><title>Circles.Life offers 20GB for just S$20 per month</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-offers-20gb-for-just-s-20-per-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-offers-20gb-for-just-s-20-per-month/</guid><description>Circles.Life subscribers can now enjoy a nearly unlimited data plan. For an extra S$20 each month, users can receive 20GB of data on top of their existing plan and bonus data.
Circles.Life, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fourth postpaid carrier and sole digital telco, now offers a plan with almost unlimited data for S$20 per month.
Circles.Life Co-Founder and Director Rameez Ansar stated, &amp;ldquo;Our mission is providing an exceptional customer experience to customers and giving them control.</description></item></channel></rss>