<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Night on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/night/</link><description>Recent content in Night on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 17:53:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/night/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Today marks the grand opening of Singapore's most Instagram-worthy nightclub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</guid><description>MARQUEE Singapore, a massive new nightclub, is launching at Marina Bay Sands on April 12, 2019. The opening weekend will feature world-renowned DJs Tiësto and Afrojack, with a special appearance by American rapper A$AP Rocky.
The 8K screen serves as a backdrop for TAO&amp;rsquo;s
co-founders Tepperberg (left) and Strauss (right).
This marks the first expansion into Asia for MARQUEE, a brand with clubs in New York, Las Vegas, and Sydney. The Singapore location is also the 35th project for TAO Group, the nightlife and hospitality company partnering with Marina Bay Sands on this venture...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-grand-opening-of-singapore-s-most-instagram-worthy-nightclub/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vivid Sydney will once again enchant audiences starting on May 27th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</guid><description>The longest-running Vivid Sydney will illuminate Sydney Harbour and other beloved locations for 23 nights, from May 27 to June 18, 2016. This year marks the eighth anniversary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest festival of light, music, and ideas. The festival is owned, managed, and produced by Destination NSW, the NSW Government&amp;rsquo;s tourism and major events agency.
Sandra Chipchase, Destination NSW Chief Executive Officer and Executive Producer of Vivid Sydney, stated that this year&amp;rsquo;s Vivid Sydney promises an incredible program where art, creativity, and innovation converge, captivating both local and international visitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escaping from the Asian Civilisations Museum: A Great Adventure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escaping-from-the-asian-civilisations-museum-a-great-adventure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escaping-from-the-asian-civilisations-museum-a-great-adventure/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Asian Civilisations Museum is hosting &amp;ldquo;Night at the Museum: The Great Escape from Asian Civilisations Museum,&amp;rdquo; featuring two evenings of movies and interactive games.
This event, possibly the first of its kind globally, is designed as a museum-wide escape room. Participants will solve puzzles, uncover museum secrets, and decipher the meanings behind ancient artifacts to &amp;ldquo;escape.&amp;rdquo; Winners have a chance to win movie tickets to Night at the Museum: Secret of the Tomb...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escaping-from-the-asian-civilisations-museum-a-great-adventure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escaping-from-the-asian-civilisations-museum-a-great-adventure/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>