<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visa on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/visa/</link><description>Recent content in Visa on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/visa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visa Eco Benefits promote sustainability in every transaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</guid><description>Visa, a digital payment company, has introduced Visa Eco Benefits in the Asia Pacific region. This suite of sustainability solutions aims to help Visa cardholders understand the environmental effects of their everyday spending. They can track their carbon footprint from Visa transactions and explore options for offsetting their impact through carbon offsets or charitable donations via their bank&amp;rsquo;s app or website.
Banks in the Asia Pacific region that adopt Eco Benefits can offer these solutions to their Visa cardholders, addressing the increasing demand for environmentally conscious financial services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Obtain a prepaid virtual Visa account through Singtel Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one mobile payments app, Dash, now features Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first virtual Visa account. All Dash users, new and existing, will automatically receive a Dash Visa Virtual Account. This account can be used for mobile payments at over 50,000 merchant locations in Singapore.
To use the mobile payment feature, customers sign in to the Dash app, add funds to their Dash Visa accounts, and make purchases at Dash merchants and participating e-commerce websites like Qoo10, Zalora, and HungryGoWhere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Citizens of Thailand holding ordinary passports can travel to Taiwan without a visa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 07:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</guid><description>Holders of regular Thai passports can now travel without a visa to 26 countries, along with Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau. Beginning August 1st, Taiwan initiated a year-long trial program waiving visa requirements for Thai citizens with regular passports visiting for tourism purposes.
This program permits eligible travelers to stay in Taiwan for a maximum of 30 days. To qualify, Thai nationals must possess a valid regular passport with at least six months of validity remaining, hold a return or onward ticket to another destination, and meet Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s entry requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UnionPay cardholders in Singapore can now enjoy exclusive visa privileges for travel to China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</guid><description>UnionPay International (UPI), a branch of China UnionPay, partnered with Chinese Visa Application Service Centre to offer special VIP treatment to UnionPay cardholders in Singapore applying for a Chinese visa. This express service features a dedicated VIP counter and a faster queue for UnionPay cardholders (card numbers starting with 62).
UnionPay is currently the only international card brand offering expedited Chinese visa applications at Chinese embassies, consulates, and participating visa processing centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa introduces Visa Business Hub to assist small and medium-sized businesses with technology and strategic planning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</guid><description>Visa has launched the Visa Business Hub, a platform designed to assist small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in navigating technology and improving their management practices. The hub, initially launched in Singapore and Malaysia, offers software-as-a-service (SaaS) solutions that can potentially reduce IT costs by up to 25% through a pay-as-you-use model. This approach minimizes upfront expenses and implementation time.
Research indicates that a significant number of businesses in Singapore (80%) view SaaS/cloud adoption as a strategic move rather than a passing trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>