<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eid on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eid/</link><description>Recent content in Eid on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA announces transport service timings for Eid al Fitr holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) has released the operating schedules for its services during the Eid al-Fitr holidays. The schedule covers various services, including customer service centers, parking, public buses, Dubai Metro and Tram, marine transit, driving institutes, and vehicle testing and registration centers.
Source: RTA. Al Marri.
Moaza Al Marri, RTA&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communication, stated that Customer Service Centers will be closed for the Eid al-Fitr holiday from Sunday, July 3rd, 2016, and will reopen on Sunday, July 10th, 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fireworks will be held at Al Majaz Waterfront to celebrate Eid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</guid><description>Al Majaz Waterfront, a popular destination located in Sharjah, UAE, will be hosting a fireworks show to celebrate the beginning of Eid al-Adha.
As reported by the Emirates News Agency (WAM), a three-minute fireworks display will take place at 9pm on the first and second days of Eid. The fireworks will be launched above the Sharjah Musical Fountain, and additional entertainment will be offered.
Source: Al Majaz Waterfront website. Fireworks on Marwa Obaid Al Shamsi, the Manager of Al Majaz Waterfront, emphasized that Eid al-Adha is a joyous celebration for families and especially children...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>