<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tips on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tips/</link><description>Recent content in Tips on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices.</description></item><item><title>Tips for achieving success with your startup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-achieving-success-with-your-startup/</guid><description>Thinking about launching a business from your great idea? Fabian Vandenreydt, a leader at Innotribe and the SWIFT Institute, who has witnessed the ups and downs of fintech startups, highlights key success factors.
First, clearly define the problem you&amp;rsquo;re addressing and ensure it&amp;rsquo;s a genuine issue. Developing a fantastic product is futile without a problem to solve. Vandenreydt emphasizes that starting with a problem is crucial for success.
Second, articulate a detailed solution implementation plan and understand your target market.</description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances.</description></item><item><title>Trend Micro demonstrates ways to enhance the security of Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</guid><description>In 2014, Android controlled the global smartphone market, shipping one billion units and representing 81% of all smartphones shipped, as reported by Strategy Analytics.
Trend Micro researcher, Paul Oliveria, points out that Android&amp;rsquo;s popularity stems from its affordability, efficient data storage, and availability across various brands and price points.
This widespread use makes Android a prime target for hackers. To combat this, Trend Micro proposes seven security measures for mobile users:</description></item><item><title>Avoid Payroll and Tips at all costs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of handling payroll, tips, sales tax, and analytical accounting, I recently discovered something interesting in Dynamics GP. Tax-sheltered deductions (TSAs) can affect how tips are taxed. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at an example:
We have Adam Smith, an employee paid hourly with a rate of $15/hr. He also earns tips and has a tax-sheltered health deduction of $10 per pay period, exempt from federal and FICA taxes.</description></item><item><title>Visa introduces Visa Business Hub to assist small and medium-sized businesses with technology and strategic planning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</guid><description>Visa has launched the Visa Business Hub, a platform designed to assist small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in navigating technology and improving their management practices. The hub, initially launched in Singapore and Malaysia, offers software-as-a-service (SaaS) solutions that can potentially reduce IT costs by up to 25% through a pay-as-you-use model. This approach minimizes upfront expenses and implementation time.
Research indicates that a significant number of businesses in Singapore (80%) view SaaS/cloud adoption as a strategic move rather than a passing trend.</description></item></channel></rss>