<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trend on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trend/</link><description>Recent content in Trend on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The World Bank has released its 2017 forecast for the Thai economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</guid><description>The 2016 Thailand Economic Monitor, published today by the World Bank, projects Thailand&amp;rsquo;s economic growth to reach 3.1% in 2016 and 3.2% in 2017, surpassing the previous year&amp;rsquo;s 2.8%.
The report identifies private consumption and public investments, such as rail infrastructure projects, as primary growth drivers. Tourism has also performed well in 2016, with tourist arrivals, particularly from China, rising by 13.1% in the third quarter. A temporary slowdown and economic inactivity following the passing of HM King Bhumibol Adulyadej in October are anticipated to be partially counterbalanced by year-end holiday tax incentives for shopping and domestic tourism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Four fashion trends from New York Fashion Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</guid><description>Milanoo.com, an online retailer for apparel and other goods, has recently highlighted the major trends observed during February&amp;rsquo;s New York Fashion Week.
Source: Milanoo website.
One trend was wrapped skirts that sit above the knee. This is a departure from the more revealing styles seen in past fashion events, which Milanoo refers to as &amp;ldquo;the consistent sexy style.&amp;rdquo; The company observed, &amp;ldquo;Skirts have been very popular these years. But things are changing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The demand for milk and yogurt-based beverages is increasing in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Increased advertising in mass media, along with more television shows and magazine content focused on health topics, have made Indonesian consumers more aware of the advantages of drinking milk from 2011 to 2016, according to Euromonitor.
Ultrajaya Milk Industry &amp;amp; Trading Company leads the drinking milk market, holding a 23% value share in 2016. Its most recognized brand is Ultra. Euromonitor attributes the company&amp;rsquo;s success in flavored milk to its strong marketing and enhanced distribution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Switch to organic bath and shower products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</guid><description>According to research firm Technavio, consumers are increasingly interested in bath and shower products that offer both organic ingredients and convenience. The company&amp;rsquo;s report on the global bath and shower products market highlights that rising living standards and disposable income are driving consumers towards higher-priced, aesthetically pleasing products with unique fragrances and effective ingredients. This trend is projected to propel the market to a value of at least US$15 billion by 2019, reflecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of approximately 4% from 2015 to 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Be cautious of insiders when it comes to protecting data privacy: Infowatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</guid><description>The most significant danger to data privacy in Southeast Asia comes from internal actors. Cybersecurity firm InfoWatch Group&amp;rsquo;s recent study reveals that careless top executives and employees with access to sensitive data are the primary cause of data leaks in ASEAN nations.
The company states that executives, employees, IT administrators, and other authorized personnel caused slightly more than 56% of compromised data incidents in Southeast Asia. External attacks and former employees were responsible for the remaining 44%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emojis are sweeping the world by storm 🌩</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/</guid><description>On July 17, in honor of World Emoji Day, App Annie wanted to learn more about the world&amp;rsquo;s love for emojis. They teamed up with Leanplum to publish a report called &amp;ldquo;Winning App ❤ (&amp;amp; 💸 ) With Emojis&amp;rdquo; which explores mobile marketing trends.
The report highlights some interesting findings, including the fact that the word &amp;ldquo;emoji&amp;rdquo; is now officially in the Oxford Dictionary. Additionally:
The use of emojis grew significantly in 2016, increasing by 163%, and the range of emojis used by marketers also expanded by 10%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emojis-are-sweeping-the-world-by-storm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yahoo has published its 2016 Year in Review for Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 02:37:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</guid><description>Yahoo, a popular online platform, has released its &amp;ldquo;2016 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; (YIR) for Singapore. This yearly recap highlights the major search trends and events that captivated Singaporean internet users, based on their search history and online activity on Yahoo throughout 2016.
Topping the list of &amp;ldquo;Top 10 Singapore Headlines&amp;rdquo; is swimmer Joseph Schooling winning Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first Olympic gold medal. Significant political events like changes to the Elected Presidency and MP David Ong&amp;rsquo;s resignation also feature prominently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The keto diet market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 5%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</guid><description>Technavio reports that the keto diet is gaining popularity, as overweight and obese individuals experience faster weight loss and body fat reduction compared to other diets.
This diet emphasizes extremely low carbohydrate intake and high fat consumption, aiming to initiate a metabolic state called ketosis. Ketosis enables the body to burn fat more effectively.
Technavio forecasts that the keto diet market will grow at a rate close to 5% by 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IWG: The Transformation of the World of Work in 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 19:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</guid><description>This image, created using the AI tool Dream by WOMBO, depicts a concept of modern office work.
As the leading global provider of flexible workspaces, IWG, known for brands like Regus and Spaces, has identified ten significant workplace trends anticipated to influence global work dynamics in 2024. The company predicts the continuation of hybrid work models, citing ongoing research by institutions like Stanford University that suggests a significant portion of white-collar workers will maintain this approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IPO activity in Singapore is expected to exceed that of 2016 in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</guid><description>During the first half of 2017, Singapore saw a surge in initial public offerings (IPOs), attracting US$329 million in investments, as reported by PwC Singapore. This momentum is projected to continue, potentially exceeding the total funds raised in 2016. Professional services are emerging as a leading sector, with HRnetGroup and Shopper360&amp;rsquo;s IPOs securing a combined US$134 million, a significant leap from the previous year.
While Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) and business trusts, a traditional strength for the Singapore Exchange (SGX), constituted 33% of IPO proceeds, the anticipated listing of NetLink Trust, estimated at US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is increasing interest in cold pressed juices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</guid><description>Source: Techsci Research.
A TechSci Research report projects the global cold-pressed juice market to experience a significant growth rate, exceeding 10% annually, between 2016 and 2022. This anticipated growth is attributed to several factors, including increased disposable incomes, heightened consumer awareness, effective marketing campaigns by industry leaders, widespread product availability, and a strong global distribution network.
Global GDP per capita, adjusted for purchasing power parity, rose from US$14,020.31 in 2012 to US$15,470...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Economic Community has the potential to be a goldmine for B2C businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, has published a white paper outlining a strategic framework for marketing to ASEAN consumers.
The establishment of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in December 2015 will unify the ten ASEAN member states into a single market and production hub. This development is anticipated to draw significant attention from multinational corporations that have traditionally focused on China and India. Euromonitor suggests that the AEC is on track to become a global economic powerhouse due to its projected robust economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There has been an increase in crypto giveaway scams</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</guid><description>Source: Group-IB. A screen capture from a fake YouTube video that appears to show Elon Musk.
Group-IB, a cybersecurity firm based in Singapore, has detected a significant surge in websites promoting cryptocurrency giveaway scams using fake YouTube live streams during the first half of 2022. These scams have become increasingly organized, evolving into a distinct market segment with various services supporting fraudulent activities.
The firm&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that while 63% of these new scam domains are registered with Russian registrars, they primarily target English and Spanish-speaking individuals interested in cryptocurrency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CEOs are of the opinion that soft skills will be more important than hard skills in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/</guid><description>Asian CEOs view soft skills as more vital than hard skills for future business success, according to a report by The Economist Corporate Network (ECN), an advisory service for senior executives. The report highlights communication, structural support for skill development, and CEO time constraints as key challenges.
The ECN&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Skills 4.0: How CEOs Shape the Future of Work in Asia&amp;rdquo; report, based on a survey of over 500 clients, reveals that most CEOs acknowledge the impact of major global trends (&amp;ldquo;megatrends&amp;rdquo;) on their companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collagen, probiotics, and plant-based protein were popular subjects at Vitafoods Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</guid><description>Vitafoods Asia, a nutraceutical event showcasing the newest ingredients, product advancements, and technology driving innovation in the industry, revealed emerging trends.
Chris Lee, MD, Global Health &amp;amp; Nutrition Network Europe, Informa Markets, stated, &amp;ldquo;Nutraceuticals are a booming industry in Asia, and Informa Markets aims to support its growth in the region by providing a knowledge base and platform.&amp;rdquo;
First-time attendee Rikhia Mazumdar, Global Senior Brand Manager for Reckitt Benckiser, expressed her intention to return the following year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mergers and acquisitions in the early stages are decelerating in Southeast Asia and Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 11:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</guid><description>Announcements for early-stage mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in Q4 2016 are predicted to be similar to the same period last year. This is attributed to reduced early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity in Southeast Asia and South Korea, as per the latest Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor (DFP) report released by Intralinks Holdings. Intralinks provides software and services, including virtual data rooms (VDRs), for managing M&amp;amp;A transactions.
Southeast Asia, encompassing Singapore, Malaysia, and Indonesia, is experiencing a significant 47...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TechSci Research believes that the organic dairy market has significant potential</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</guid><description>A recent report by TechSci Research, a global management consulting firm, predicts significant growth in the global organic dairy products market. Driven by factors like increased health consciousness, a growing urban population, and rising spending on organic foods, the market is expected to achieve a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of over 11% between 2016 and 2021.
The report, titled Global Organic Dairy Products Market By Product Type, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, identifies expanding product lines, readily available organic dairy products, strong distribution networks, increasing internet access, and proactive marketing strategies from key players as contributing factors to this projected growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</a></p></description></item><item><title>"Credit Suisse identifies three major trends for 2018"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Cavalli.
The sixth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference 2018, held in Singapore, focused on three significant trends: technology designed to benefit humanity, including AI and robotics; a future shaped by Millennials; and the expanding silver economy.
Benjamin Cavalli, Head of Private Banking Southeast Asia and Singapore CEO of Credit Suisse, explained in his opening remarks that these megatrends represent investment themes based on Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s expert insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo unveils a retail sales guide for Chinese New Year in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:48:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</guid><description>Criteo, a commerce media company, has unveiled insights from the 2022 Chinese New Year (CNY) to help retailers anticipate consumer demand and leverage similar trends in 2023.
Starting in January 2022, retail sales surpassed typical levels (based on the average between December 18th and 31st, 2021) until a week prior to CNY 2022 (February 1st), indicating a strong consumer appetite for purchasing. In Southeast Asia (SEA), retail sales hit a peak of 27% on January 25th, a week before CNY...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The true desires of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-desires-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:41:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-desires-of-millennials/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Yak, Szpitalak, Sun, and Huterstein, with Dan Murphy from _CNBC _moderating.
Millennials don&amp;rsquo;t stay with one company throughout their careers. They crave consistent feedback and embrace failure as a learning opportunity on the path to success. They&amp;rsquo;re comfortable investing in startups and don&amp;rsquo;t conform to the traditional 9-to-5 office schedule.
These characteristics and perspectives of Millennials were openly discussed at the 2018 Credit Suisse Global Megatrends conference, yielding some unexpected insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-desires-of-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-desires-of-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bioactive ingredients will drive growth in the personal care industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</guid><description>A global shift from synthetic to natural active ingredients in personal care products is driving significant investments in the market, according to research firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. This trend is fueled by a growing consumer belief that natural ingredients are safer for human health and the environment.
Source: Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. Generic personal care dispensers.
Currently, natural active ingredients represent 25% to 30% of the total market share. However, this is predicted to double by 2023, leading to increased innovation in addressing the challenges of incorporating these often delicate ingredients...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>More than half of the worldwide facial aesthetics market is made up of Botox</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</guid><description>The global demand for facial aesthetic procedures is growing, driven by consumers who are increasingly interested in their appearance and prefer less invasive treatments, according to a report on the Facial Aesthetics Market from 2016-2020 by Technavio.
Technavio&amp;rsquo;s research shows that Botox holds the largest share of the facial aesthetics market, making up roughly 52% of the total. They attribute this dominance to changing cultural perceptions of beauty, higher disposable incomes, and the growing popularity of the brand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Limited edition experiences are a popular trend in the food service industry in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</guid><description>In 2015, Australian diners increasingly embraced their inner foodies, craving novel culinary experiences. Food service operators responded with innovation, experimenting with formats, menus, and dining concepts, according to a Euromonitor blog post.
One example highlighted by the research firm is Hotel Marriott in Melbourne&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Table for 12&amp;rdquo; concept, launched in October 2015. This exclusive dining experience offered a four-course degustation menu for a limited group of twelve guests, available only one night a week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Project management is expected to face challenges in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</guid><description>ESI International, a company that provides project management training, believes that in the coming year, project managers (PMs) will experience several changes. These include dealing with combined in-person and remote work environments, needing stronger talent management skills, and aligning project results with company goals.
Raed Haddad, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at ESI International, noted that strategy and execution are often discussed separately. He anticipates a stronger emphasis on connecting these two aspects, as more companies start seeing strategic execution as a crucial skill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australians are worried about the amount of sugar in fizzy drinks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</guid><description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s carbonated soft drink (CSD) market is experiencing ongoing challenges due to consumer worries about sugar content, as reported by Mintel, a global market intelligence firm.
Mintel predicts that the total sales volume of CSDs in Australia will likely decrease by 2.3% in 2017, following a 4.7% drop from 2014 to 2016.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research suggests that growing awareness of sugar&amp;rsquo;s negative effects has prompted many Australians to reevaluate their sugar consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Watching 100 trends in the MENA region for 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:22:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: JWT website. Cover for the report.
J. Walter Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Middle East and Africa Innovation Group recently published their sixth yearly consumer trends report, focusing on the MENA region for 2018. Future 100 Trends and Change to Watch in MENA highlights the significant themes that are changing how consumers in Egypt, North Africa, Lebanon, Jordan, the Gulf, and Saudi Arabia live and consume.
A key takeaway from the Future 100 MENA Report is that Middle Eastern consumers are seeing themselves more as global citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technology usage in 2015 could be vastly different</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</guid><description>Source: Intel infographic. Learn more here.
Our current world relies on multiple connected devices, and this trend will only intensify. Intel believes that while we currently utilize various devices like wearables, smartphones, tablets, and PCs, the future holds even more significant changes.
Hermann Eul, VP and GM, Mobile and Communications Group at Intel, points out that users constantly demand better device performance. He highlights that in 2015, devices will need to meet the need for improved imaging, extended battery life without sacrificing performance, integrated experiences, and enhanced responsiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The premium image of cheese is advantageous in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesian families, especially those residing in major urban areas, are anticipated to increasingly incorporate cheese as a staple ingredient in their meals. This trend is linked to a growing consumer preference for preparing Western dishes, such as pizzas, pastas, cakes, pastries, and toast, which often feature cheese, within their own homes, as indicated by research conducted by Euromonitor. A notable shift in preference is the rising popularity of cheese paired with white bread, replacing traditional spreads like chocolate sprinkles, jam, or honey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intralinks APAC respondents predict that waves in China will have an impact on M&amp;A</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</guid><description>Dealmakers in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region believe that China&amp;rsquo;s economic and market activity will be the biggest influence on mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in the region over the coming six months.
This insight comes from a survey of over 1,600 global M&amp;amp;A professionals conducted by Intralinks, a leading provider of M&amp;amp;A deal management and secure collaboration solutions. The survey, conducted between October 4 and 11, 2016, gathered responses from dealmakers across APAC, Europe, the Middle East and Africa, North America, and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson has unveiled its 10 top consumer trends for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson website. Infographic summarizing the 10 hot consumer trends for 2019.
· Consumers anticipate that smart speakers will participate in family disagreements, much like human family members do.
· Users of virtual assistants believe that devices capable of understanding human emotions will be commonplace within the next three years.
· Users of augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) express a desire for interactive, virtual assistance with practical tasks such as cooking or completing repairs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are seeking additional retail technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 09:25:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</guid><description>Source: Zebra infographic. Almost two-thirds of shoppers surveyed in Europe and the Middle East stated that customer service directly impacts their purchasing decisions. Meanwhile, nearly a third of Asia Pacific respondents prefer collecting online purchases from a physical store.
Consumers are setting higher expectations for their shopping experience, while retailers lag in matching these expectations with their in-store technology investments. Retail customers desire a wide array of options for receiving their purchases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top 10 global consumer trends for 2015 focus on multitasking and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor.
Market research firm Euromonitor International recently published their findings on the top 10 global consumer trends for 2015.
Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Global Consumer Trends 2015 report states that consumers, pressed for time, are seeking convenience, diverse options, global product availability, and instant satisfaction. They aim to get the most out of their time and money, looking for products and services that meet multiple needs. As an illustration, a Swedish taxi service provides in-car therapists for their stressed and busy clients at a rate of US$165 per hour...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap reveals his forecasts for the Year of the Earth Boar, 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</guid><description>Over 5,000 attendees were present at Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap&amp;rsquo;s yearly Feng Shui &amp;amp; Astrology seminar in January 2019.
During the seminar, Dato&amp;rsquo; Yap provided insights into the Year of the Earth Boar, covering both the year&amp;rsquo;s forecasts and the projected global economic climate.
He specifically highlighted February 8th, 11th, and 12th as auspicious dates to resume work in 2019.
A notable collaboration with EZ-Link resulted in the launch of special edition EZ-Link cards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The beauty industry acknowledges the growing demand in Asia for products that promote relaxation and stress relief</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</guid><description>A recent report by market intelligence agency Mintel reveals that the Asia-Pacific region produced one-third of all new beauty and personal care products aimed at relaxation and stress relief in the first nine months of 2018. This represents a significant increase from 2015 when the region accounted for only 26% of similar global product launches.
Sharon Kwek, Senior Innovation and Insights Analyst, Beauty and Personal Care at Mintel, addressed the in-cosmetics Asia event stating that today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, demanding world has normalized stress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 12: 2023's Work Trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</guid><description>Source: Deel playbook. 12 work
trends for 2023.
Deel, a provider of payroll and compliance solutions for global teams, has identified twelve emerging workplace trends for 2023:
Overemployed
Deel found that remote workers are increasingly taking on multiple jobs simultaneously, leveraging flexible schedules and asynchronous communication tools.
The Chief Remote Officer (CRO)
The role of CRO is gaining traction, with companies seeking individuals to oversee all aspects of remote work, including in-person events, time-zone management, compensation, and communication tools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's top business travel destinations are Tokyo and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</guid><description>A recent Samsonite survey explored the preferences of Singaporean business travelers, revealing Tokyo and Bangkok as the top choices for both business and leisure.
The survey, conducted by YouGov, involved over 500 Singaporean respondents who travel for business frequently. It found that Tokyo was the top business destination overall, particularly favored by those aged 35 to 44. Bangkok was the preferred choice for those over 45. Among younger travelers (under 34), Tokyo and London tied for the top spot...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2024, 80% of service professionals in Singapore anticipate that customer service will play a larger role in generating revenue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</guid><description>A recent Salesforce report highlights the growing expectation for customer service to become a significant revenue driver in 2024. The report suggests that AI-powered personalized customer experiences empower service teams to capitalize on upselling, cross-selling, and customer retention to boost revenue.
This new &amp;ldquo;State of Service&amp;rdquo; report is based on insights from over 5,500 service professionals globally, including 100 from Singapore. It examines current trends, challenges, and strategies shaping the customer service landscape, emphasizing how service teams utilize AI and data to enhance revenue, efficiency, and customer satisfaction amidst rising customer expectations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers now prioritize sustainable travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 20:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</guid><description>Trip.com Group, a leading travel service company, recently published its first-ever Sustainable Travel Consumer Report to coincide with World Tourism Day. The report highlights the growing popularity of sustainable travel and its significant effects on the travel industry and the world at large.
Sustainable travel is increasingly becoming a top priority for travelers worldwide, with over 68% in Singapore and 90% in Thailand recognizing its importance.
Source: Trip.com. Despite regional variations, there is a clear upward trend of individuals adopting sustainable travel habits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>80% of Singaporeans living abroad are interested in returning to work in their home country</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 07:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</guid><description>A new report from Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, suggests that competition for skilled workers in Singapore will increase in 2016. This demand will likely lead to more attempts to recruit Singaporeans working abroad. Hiring managers believe that these experienced professionals could help alleviate the tight labor market, benefiting both companies and the &amp;ldquo;Fair Consideration Framework,&amp;rdquo; which promotes local hiring.
Returning Singaporeans are desirable candidates because they often have international experience and a broader range of skills compared to their counterparts who haven&amp;rsquo;t worked overseas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent Euromonitor survey reveals sugar as a new culprit in the food industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has observed a growing global trend of consumers turning against sugar. This shift in attitude stems from heightened awareness of its health implications.
Consumers are actively trying to decrease or eliminate sugar from their diets, with a significant 42% actively looking for food labels indicating low or no added sugar, according to Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Global Consumer Trends Survey.
&amp;ldquo;Sugar is now widely perceived as a health risk, with some even equating it to tobacco in terms of toxicity,&amp;rdquo; says Gina Westbrook, Director of Strategy Briefings at Euromonitor International...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is a growing trend of adults purchasing toys and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</guid><description>In 2016, games and puzzles experienced an 8% surge in the global market, surpassing construction toys as the fastest-growing toy category, according to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm. This impressive growth also marks the highest for the category since 2002.
Although construction toys saw a growth of 7.8% in 2016, a dip compared to the double-digit growth of 2015, they still dominated the traditional toys and games market with a value of US$10 billion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Attract retail attention with apps and promotions leading up to a holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</guid><description>Criteo has noticed a major shift from websites to apps for online shopping. They found a 25% decrease in website traffic but a 4% rise in app traffic, with Thailand (18%) and Singapore (9%) experiencing the largest gains.
All Southeast Asian nations saw growth in overall app traffic volume, with Singapore (207%) and Indonesia (128%) leading the way.
When compared to October 2020, Thailand and Singapore had the highest increases in indexed sales in the app environment, at 12% and 10%, respectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By 2022, consumers are projected to spend over $155 billion on apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 18:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</guid><description>Source: App Annie. App Annie predicts app trends will change by 2022. Figures are in US dollars.
A new report by App Annie, a mobile app data and insights company, projects global consumer spending on apps to reach US$156.5 billion by 2022, a 92% increase from 2017.
The App Annie Forecast 2017-2022 highlights major trends expected to shape the app economy in the coming years. Global first-time app downloads are predicted to rise by 45% between 2017 and 2022, hitting 258...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SiteMinder: Travelers are projected to spend in 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</guid><description>A recent global survey of over 8,000 travelers reveals a growing desire for international travel, even with increasing living expenses.
Source: SiteMinder Changing Traveller Report 2022. Global accommodation momentum from 2020 to 2022.
The report identified five key travel trends:
Macro-travel: The desire to travel outweighs concerns about inflation.
Digital influence: Travelers are currently the most receptive to marketing efforts.
Bleisure: Business travelers seek modern hotel amenities.
Trust: Digital interactions are crucial for building trust with travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KPMG has identified gaps in global corporate responsibility reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</guid><description>A 2015 KPMG study reveals inconsistencies in how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies report their carbon emissions, making it challenging to compare their performance. While 80% of the top 250 companies address carbon in their reports, the information provided varies significantly. For instance, only half declare carbon reduction goals, and among those, two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t explain their rationale.
The reported emissions types also differ. Most companies (84%) report emissions from their operations and purchased power (79%), but only half include supply chain emissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports that skincare is a popular trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has reported that the global beauty industry is experiencing growth, particularly in emerging markets, as consumers increasingly adopt more comprehensive beauty routines and upgrade to premium products.
Skincare stands out as the dominant segment in most markets, with global sales projected to exceed US$130 billion by 2019. &amp;ldquo;Consumers are allocating a significant portion of their beauty spending on skincare, averaging US$15 per person annually,&amp;rdquo; notes Irina Barbalova, Head of Beauty and Personal Care at Euromonitor International...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top five consumer trends for 2015 according to Canadean</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:33:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</guid><description>In 2015, market research company Canadean predicts five key trends will shape consumer behavior in the fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) industry:
From Mass Production to Personalization
Canadean anticipates a growing consumer preference for artisanal and handcrafted products. Consumers are seeking out products made on a smaller scale, believing this signifies higher quality and a stronger connection to the brand. Brands can capitalize on this trend by highlighting a product&amp;rsquo;s exclusivity and the care taken in its creation, appealing to consumers moving away from mass-produced FMCG items...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Female entrepreneurs need more than just determination to succeed, according to Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</guid><description>The first Mastercard Index of Women Entrepreneurs reveals that strong support systems, such as easy access to financial services and a business-friendly environment, are crucial for women-owned businesses to succeed. These enabling factors are essential in overcoming the two biggest hurdles women face in entrepreneurship: cultural bias and limited opportunities for advancement.
Developed economies lead the index, with New Zealand (74.4), Canada (72.4), and the US (69.9) claiming the top spots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2015 Vuclip Global Video Insights reveals that Malaysian consumers are seeking uncomplicated entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Vuclip, a leading mobile video-on-demand (VOD) service in emerging markets, has published its Global Video Insights (GVI) 2015 Survey. The study examines video consumption trends and device preferences among Malaysian consumers.
Source: Vuclip. Prakash.
Malaysian consumers value several features in an over-the-top (OTT) content player. The most important are a seamless user interface (61%), uninterrupted viewing experience (58%), high-definition video quality (56%), and access to the newest videos (54%). Other desirable features include adjustable streaming quality (47%), video downloads (46%), and simultaneous multiple video downloads (45%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Childcare centers are emerging in Chinese workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</guid><description>Government policy changes are fueling the growth of the preschool or childcare market in China. Technavio forecasts a CAGR exceeding 6% for this market between 2016 and 2020. This growth is largely attributed to recent policy adjustments, notably the 2015 amendment to the one-child policy, now permitting couples to have two children. This shift aims to balance population development and, coupled with rising disposable incomes among middle-class families, is driving increased preschool enrollment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discovering the latest trends on Orchard Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discovering-the-latest-trends-on-orchard-road/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discovering-the-latest-trends-on-orchard-road/</guid><description>This year, I participated in a Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk called &amp;ldquo;Trend Safari: Innovations in Your Backyard in Singapore,&amp;rdquo; led by Nathania Christy, TrendWatching&amp;rsquo;s Insight &amp;amp; Community Lead for the Asia-Pacific region. The walk provided a condensed version of TrendWatching&amp;rsquo;s client activity focused on identifying trends and sparking business innovation.
Our group explored parts of Orchard Road, a major shopping district, to uncover emerging societal, retail, and commercial trends. Our starting point was a recent pop-up booth outside Crate &amp;amp; Barrel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discovering-the-latest-trends-on-orchard-road/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discovering-the-latest-trends-on-orchard-road/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The beauty industry is increasingly prioritizing sustainability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</guid><description>The beauty industry needs a complete overhaul in its approach to sustainability and zero waste, focusing on every part of the process, according to market intelligence agency Mintel. The company highlights &amp;ldquo;Sub-Zero Waste&amp;rdquo; as a major trend that will shape the global beauty and personal care markets in the years to come.
The zero-waste movement is picking up speed as consumers become increasingly affected by environmental problems like natural disasters and water scarcity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Deliveroo predicts future food trends in Asia with "Snack to the Future"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 17:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</guid><description>Deliveroo, a food delivery platform, has released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Snack To The Future Report&amp;rdquo; predicting how technology and evolving consumer habits will shape food consumption patterns in the region by 2040.
The report, developed by Deliveroo in collaboration with Singaporean food specialists Yip Hon Mun and Luke Tay, along with other global experts, identifies emerging food trends driven by technological advancements and changing consumer behaviors. Key predictions include personalized dietary recommendations based on breath analysis (&amp;ldquo;Breath-prints&amp;rdquo;), AI-powered customized diets (&amp;ldquo;Me-ganism&amp;rdquo;), and immersive dining experiences using augmented reality (&amp;ldquo;FOODGASMS&amp;rdquo;)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>40% of Singaporeans have experienced a data breach within the last year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</guid><description>Parvinder Walia, during his presentation, revealed that 72% of consumers react negatively to news of a company suffering a cyberattack or data breach.
ESET, a cybersecurity software company, conducted a survey to examine consumer online behavior and perspectives on cybersecurity in light of recent data breaches.
The ESET 2018 APAC Consumer Behaviour Survey found that 42% of Singaporeans had experienced some form of data breach in the preceding year. These breaches included theft and misuse of personal information, bank account fraud, social media account compromise, and attacks from malware and viruses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The popularity of home remedies for teeth whitening is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 05:27:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</guid><description>Technavio, a research company specializing in technology, found that self-applied teeth whitening products have significantly changed the global oral care market. Consumers are increasingly choosing at-home treatments over professional ones. The firm attributes this shift to the affordability and convenience of oral care products like whitening strips, pens, and trays, which have become popular alternatives to professional whitening procedures.
According to a new Technavio report on the global teeth whitening product market, the industry is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 4% between 2015 and 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2030 Food: Sustainable, Healthier, Personalized</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</guid><description>- Businesses for Good: In the future, successful companies will be those committed to improving the well-being of both the planet and its people.
- Personalized Nutrition: Technological advancements will allow consumers to create highly customized approaches to enhance their physical and mental health.
Source: Mintel.
- Tech-Driven Food Solutions: Consumer confidence in food science and technology will grow as these become essential for securing the food supply. Mintel, a market research firm focused on consumer insights, has identified three significant trends expected to shape the global food, drink, and food service industries in the coming decade:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo measures the passion for travel among Singaporeans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</guid><description>Mobile travel purchases saw a 35% surge between 2011 and 2016, a trend predicted to continue its upward trajectory. Accessibility (74%) and convenience (69%) are the primary motivators for respondents&amp;rsquo; preference to browse travel products online. A significant 78% choose smartphones over desktops/laptops for browsing due to their on-the-go functionality.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology firm, highlights the continuous growth of mobile travel sales, emphasizing it as a prime growth avenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2019 Year in Review by Yahoo highlights Singapore's obsession with celebrity, wealth, and the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 05:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s 2019 Year in Review (YIR) reveals that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s internet users were captivated by stories surrounding Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s former PM Najib Razak, NUS student Monica Baey, and the Hong Kong protests.
The YIR, which analyzes search trends on Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s platforms, highlighted Najib Razak&amp;rsquo;s connection to the 1MDB scandal as a topic of significant interest. The Orchard Towers murder case, particularly Natalie Siow&amp;rsquo;s involvement, also drew considerable attention.
Actor Aloysius Pang&amp;rsquo;s passing during reservist training prompted searches related to training safety, while his girlfriend, actress Jayley Woo, also became a top search...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top four visual trends for 2020 according to Adobe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</guid><description>Adobe has predicted the biggest visual trends for 2020, sharing four key themes brands should embrace in a recent blog post.
_Inclusivity for All Ages _
Marketing is moving away from solely youth-focused campaigns. Recognizing the influence and engagement of older demographics, brands are showcasing diverse, energetic individuals from various age groups.
_Authenticity in Expression _
Consumers are increasingly drawn to genuine representations of themselves and their experiences. This desire for authenticity extends to brands, public figures, and politicians, who are expected to reflect real life in their messaging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>