<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4000/</link><description>Recent content in 4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Main Capacitor Array with Integrated Efficient 24V Power Supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 is known to get quite hot, primarily due to its outdated voltage regulator-based power supply. To address this, a modern PCB design with a buck converter-based 24V supply was created as a replacement for the original power supply and capacitors.
The new design features high-quality Panasonic electrolytic capacitors, Samsung ceramic capacitors for the motor phase, and a buck converter for the 24V power supply. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to be easily installed in place of the original components.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Choppily Rotating AC Platter Motor - Repair of Wien-Bridge Oscillator Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-choppily-rotating-ac-platter-motor-repair-of-wien-bridge-oscillator-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 12:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-choppily-rotating-ac-platter-motor-repair-of-wien-bridge-oscillator-circuit/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project presented a recurring issue: a malfunctioning oscillator circuit responsible for powering the AC platter motor. This was unusual, as previous 4002 and 4000 models hadn&amp;rsquo;t shown this problem. Although the light bulbs managing the circuit&amp;rsquo;s Automatic Gain Control (AGC) weren&amp;rsquo;t visually illuminated during motor operation, suggesting a longer lifespan compared to indicator bulbs, this unit proved otherwise. It&amp;rsquo;s likely that factors like mechanical vibrations, particularly during transport, could have damaged the bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Wiring Sleeve of Carriage Harness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable, previously restored in 2020, was brought in for repairs due to an oscillating solenoid issue. However, upon inspection, a more critical problem was discovered: the wiring harness sleeve was severely damaged, exposing the wires.
This level of damage had never been encountered before. Thankfully, the wires themselves were still intact. The timing of the solenoid problem was fortunate, as further use could have led to wire damage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Gold Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Spring Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring an early model Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, and it&amp;rsquo;s captivating to trace the evolution of its design from the original Beogram 4000. Having already tackled the arm lowering mechanism, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the carriage position switches, a particularly interesting aspect of the 4002&amp;rsquo;s design.
While the design echoes that of the 4000, it features some notable refinements. The 4000&amp;rsquo;s 7&amp;quot; record set-down point switch, for instance, was a break switch prone to issues stemming from oxidation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control panel (keypad), the next step was to focus on the carriage position switches. These switches are vital for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s digital control system, and even one faulty switch can render the entire device unusable. Similar to the keypad switches, these are prone to oxidation, making gold plating a reliable solution to prevent future contact problems. The image below displays the circuit board with the switches after detaching the carriage position indicator component.</description></item><item><title>Bang&amp;Olufsen MMC20EN Vintage Cartridge Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc20en-vintage-cartridge-test/</guid><description>The MMC20EN cartridge that came with my recently restored Beogram 4004 parts was tested using my evolving cartridge testing methodology.
My approach involves evaluating the frequency range and trackability of a cartridge. For this, I utilize three test records: the Analogue Audio Ultimate Test LP for checking frequency response up to 20kHz, the Fisher Test &amp;amp; Performance Standard Quadradisc to observe 30kHz carrier frequency reproduction, and the Clearaudio Trackability Test Record to assess the cantilever suspension&amp;rsquo;s condition at different groove amplitudes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair and Exploration of an Intermittently Oscillating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</guid><description>This section details the work done on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s oscillating solenoid, and what was learned about winding solenoid coils and comparing them to the original.
The arm lowering mechanism is shown here:
When the control logic initiates arm lowering, the solenoid pushes the solenoid lever forward. The lever opens the solenoid switch when fully extended, decreasing the current flowing through the solenoid to a level just enough to keep it engaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Arm, Replacement of the Damper Gasket and Re-Glueing of a Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 required a few final adjustments before it could be returned to its owner following a wiring sleeve replacement on the carriage harness and a fix for an intermittent solenoid.
During its initial restoration in 2020, I was unfamiliar with some common problems that these turntables develop. One such issue involves the damper gasket, which tends to harden over time. This hardening can lead to uneven arm lowering due to inconsistent airflow around the gasket.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Exploration of Photocell Function in Sensor Arm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:24:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is going well, but it appears someone attempted repairs before. The sensor arm insert, containing the light bulb and photocell for record detection, was in disarray.
Upon inspection, a photocell wire was disconnected, another was damaged from being forced back into the aluminum profile, and the lens insert had heat damage, likely from improper soldering. Thankfully, the lenses were unharmed.
After reconnecting the wire, replacing the non-standard light bulb with a Beolover LED insert, and adjusting the TR14 bias to 1.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Packaging for Shipping: An Update on How to Secure the Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</guid><description>This article outlines a packaging update for the Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 turntables. Instead of taping the arm cover to the platter, the author now advises using an M3 screw to secure the carriage directly to the chassis.
This change is due to the risk of damaging the arm cover&amp;rsquo;s labeling with tape during shipping. While the author previously suggested using paper to protect the lettering, damage continued to occur.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Signal Path between DIN5 Plug and Cartridge, Plug Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</guid><description>I recently decided to update my Beogram 4002 turntable for the 21st century. While it was functional, the DIN 5 plug was noticeably worn and corroded. To address this, I swapped it out with a modern, high-quality Neutrik AG Rean NYS 322G plug featuring gold-plated pins, aiming for a reliable, long-lasting connection with my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s auxiliary input. The old plug was in rough shape, leaving me curious about its past.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Newly Designed Beolover RIAA Pre-Amplifier Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</guid><description>Due to demand, I designed an internal RIAA pre-amplifier board for the Beogram 4000, adapting the circuit from my recent redesign for the DC motor Beogram 4002 and 4004. I installed this new board in a Beogram 4000 that was in for a warranty repair. This post details the installation process; for technical data, refer to my previous post about the 4002/4 version&amp;rsquo;s performance, as the circuits are identical.
The current prototype board has some features that will be absent in the final version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Afternoon Exploring the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem arose with its record detection system. While it functioned correctly at the 12-inch LP position, it frequently failed to detect records at the 7-inch singles position. This malfunction was observed when the turntable, starting without a record on the platter, bypassed the LP position but stopped at the singles position.
An examination of the circuit diagram revealed the signal path of the detection system.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Stability Test and an Updated Display on the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>I dedicated time to program the compact display integrated into my BeoloverRPM device. This enhancement enables precise RPM adjustments and long-term RPM stability analysis. The display now includes minimum and maximum values, along with the total measurement duration. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the display:
The display boasts high resolution and excellent contrast. However, those of us who are getting older might need reading glasses to decipher the small font. Is perfection ever attainable?</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Evening Exploring the Differential Stop Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</guid><description>Before returning a refurbished unit to a customer, we put it through rigorous real-world testing. This involves playing music for several weeks to ensure consistent functionality. This listening process is a delightful part of working with Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen equipment, as our workshop is always filled with music! A recent case involving a restored Beogram 4000 turntable highlights the value of this testing phase.
During playback, I noticed the arm occasionally failed to return to its resting position after reaching the record&amp;rsquo;s end.</description></item></channel></rss>