<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Calling Cards on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/calling-cards/</link><description>Recent content in Calling Cards on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/calling-cards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Special Triple Savings To Call International</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-triple-savings-to-call-international/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-triple-savings-to-call-international/</guid><description>Calling other countries from the USA or Canada? You need to know about the special triple savings offer from TEL3Advantage.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how it works: you get a 30% discount off their already low international calling rates for 30 days. Plus, you receive up to $9 in free talk time, which equates to 900 international minutes. This offer allows you to make calls globally at incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-triple-savings-to-call-international/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-triple-savings-to-call-international/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International Cell Phone Calls for Pennies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</guid><description>Imagine making international calls for as little as two cents a minute! It might sound impossible, but with a new service, you can make calls from the US and Canada to other countries at incredibly low rates.
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about rates like 2.36 cents per minute to China. Yes, you read that right. Still paying exorbitant rates? Get with the times and switch to the TEL3AdvantageMobile Plan before you make another call!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Capability To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 04:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of wireless phones allows mobile professionals to stay connected consistently. However, international calls remain a challenge due to expensive rates. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: international dial-around services.
These services, such as TEL3Advantage, seamlessly integrate with existing cell phone plans. Essentially, they allow users to make international calls at significantly reduced rates by routing them through the dial-around service instead of their regular carrier.
For example, TEL3Advantage offers a rate of 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>