<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT Budget on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-budget/</link><description>Recent content in IT Budget on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-budget/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies.</description></item><item><title>Preserve Your IT Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserve-your-it-budget/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 17:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserve-your-it-budget/</guid><description>As we enter a new year and budget cycle, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to consider how to maximize your IT budget, even if funds seem plentiful. Economic uncertainty could lead to cutbacks, making it crucial to get the most value from your spending.
Maintaining your IT budget amidst pressure for upgrades and new projects requires smart strategies. One approach is negotiating better deals for the same services or products. While this might have been challenging during prosperous times, the current economic climate means businesses are eager for sales and more likely to negotiate.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>