<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web Servers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/web-servers/</link><description>Recent content in Web Servers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/web-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Low Cost Cloud Backup For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</guid><description>Lots of companies are exploring cloud services these days. While not every business needs its own data center or web servers, every business has critical data they can&amp;rsquo;t afford to lose. Imagine a natural disaster like a tornado or fire destroying all your physical and digital files – the impact would be significant. Even something as common as a hard drive crash can be devastating.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a simple and cost-effective way to protect your business without complex outsourcing contracts: backing up your important files to a secure offsite location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Easy Way To Host Lots Of Domains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-easy-way-to-host-lots-of-domains/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-easy-way-to-host-lots-of-domains/</guid><description>As more businesses establish an online presence, they&amp;rsquo;re discovering that a single domain name is often insufficient. Companies may desire individual domain names for each product line, and online marketers might create separate websites tailored to specific products or demographics. This then raises the question of how to host multiple domains effectively.
While purchasing separate hosting services for each domain is an option, it can become costly. This approach might be suitable for a limited number of domains, but it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for businesses with larger websites or multiple online presences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-easy-way-to-host-lots-of-domains/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-easy-way-to-host-lots-of-domains/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 04:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</guid><description>When you have a website or online store, you&amp;rsquo;re already familiar with web hosting. But did you know there are different types of web hosting? One type you might not know about is managed hosting, which can be more reliable and affordable than trying to handle everything yourself.
In the early days of the internet, businesses often set up their websites by getting server software and using one computer as the web host...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>