<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Optimise on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/optimise/</link><description>Recent content in Optimise on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:49:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/optimise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asians struggle with their comfort levels when it comes to using air conditioning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</guid><description>A Hong Kong-based startup, Ambi Labs, has initiated a crowdsourcing campaign for their latest product, Ambi Climate. This innovative device is designed to optimize air conditioning systems based on two years of user feedback gathered from ten Asian markets.
Source: Ambi Labs.
Ambi Labs conducted extensive online surveys across ten major Asian markets, engaging with over 4,000 participants. The findings revealed that the most significant challenge with air conditioners lies in maintaining a comfortable room temperature.</description></item><item><title>Google prefers websites that are optimized for mobile devices. Have you taken any steps to ensure your site is mobile-friendly?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</guid><description>World Markets Korea, a Seoul-based online marketing firm, has outlined some of the factors Google now considers when evaluating websites for mobile friendliness. These include text size, spacing between links, and whether the content fits comfortably on a mobile screen. Google uses these criteria to determine if a website is &amp;ldquo;Mobile Friendly.&amp;rdquo;
The company recommends that businesses engage their web designers to update their sites accordingly. World Markets Korea also provides services to optimize websites for mobile devices.</description></item></channel></rss>