<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infographic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infographic/</link><description>Recent content in Infographic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infographic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Caution: Superman is poisonous</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</guid><description>According to a McAfee blog post, Superman poses a significant online threat. The company argues that the widespread presence of superheroes beyond comic books allows hackers and scammers to exploit them for cybercrime.
McAfee&amp;rsquo;s survey, which used their SiteAdvisor site ratings, revealed that Superman is the &amp;ldquo;Most Toxic Superhero.&amp;rdquo; The study found that searches combining &amp;ldquo;Superman&amp;rdquo; with terms like &amp;ldquo;free torrent download,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;watch,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;free app,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; have a 16.5% chance of leading to websites containing threats like spyware, adware, spam, phishing, viruses, and other malware.</description></item><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions.</description></item><item><title>Why Such a Stampede to The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is everywhere you turn. This raises the question: are businesses truly shifting from traditional data centers to cloud-based solutions? And if so, what motivates this transition and what are their objectives?
Unveiling the Hidden Potential of Cloud Technology
Cloud storage receives significant attention, but the vast server capacity offered by the cloud is equally compelling. One often overlooked application is Hosted PBX or Hosted VoIP, which replaces traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Pi Day is on July 22nd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pi-day-is-on-july-22nd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 01:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pi-day-is-on-july-22nd/</guid><description>Pi Day is observed twice a year. The date March 14 (3/14) reflects the constant&amp;rsquo;s value. It&amp;rsquo;s also celebrated on July 22, referencing the common fractional representation of Pi, 22/7.
To mark the occasion, Parallels has designed an infographic with fascinating information about Pi and suggestions for celebrating.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th).</description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever.</description></item><item><title>Brewing the ideal cup of coffee at work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brewing-the-ideal-cup-of-coffee-at-work/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 01:27:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brewing-the-ideal-cup-of-coffee-at-work/</guid><description>Teabox, an online retailer specializing in premium Indian teas, emphasizes the importance of specific brewing methods for different tea varieties.
&amp;ldquo;Water quality is paramount for tea, as it constitutes the majority of the beverage. Excessive boiling can deplete oxygen levels in water, hindering proper flavor infusion. Similarly, over-steeping can lead to flavor loss and excessive bitterness,&amp;rdquo; explains Kaushal Dugar, CEO of Teabox.
The company provides a useful guide for brewing a perfect cup of tea:</description></item><item><title>IDC reveals the preferences of APAC consumers when it comes to mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 05:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</guid><description>The International Data Corporation (IDC) has released an infographic that reveals how consumers in the Asia Pacific region make decisions about mobile devices. Key findings from the Essential Guide to Device Decisions of a Connected Consumer in Asia Pacific report include:
Source: IDC infographic. What consumers like about bigger phone screens.
77% of surveyed consumers reported having a larger smartphone now than their previous device, while only 8% opted for a smaller one.</description></item><item><title>Balancing work and play on your smartphone: Four helpful tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. View the full infographic.
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming harder to separate our work and personal lives with smartphones being used for both. For instance, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Lumia 640 and 640 XL come with an Office 365 subscription.
Dr. Mark Batey, an Organizational Psychologist at Manchester Business School in the UK, collaborated with Microsoft to offer advice on finding a good balance:
1. Capture inspiration immediately.
He says, &amp;ldquo;Make use of note-taking apps on your phone to jot down brilliant ideas as they come, anytime and anywhere.</description></item><item><title>Lessons for small and medium-sized enterprises from successful viral campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</guid><description>4imprint, a company that sells promotional products, has created a new infographic called &amp;ldquo;Going Viral.&amp;rdquo; This infographic explains how small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) can learn from viral marketing campaigns.
One suggestion is to connect a campaign with something already trending, like a popular TV show or book. This can effectively help a marketing effort gain traction with a specific audience.
The infographic also encourages businesses to consider product trials and giveaways.</description></item><item><title>The key to e-commerce success according to Akamai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</guid><description>Akamai, a content delivery network (CDN) provider, emphasizes the importance of speed in e-commerce, stating that slow loading times can lead to customer loss. They suggest two key ways online retailers can improve their businesses: by understanding modern customer behavior and by prioritizing speed, intelligence, and security in their online operations.
Mobile shopping is a growing trend. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s data shows that mobile and tablet shoppers make purchases 20% more often and spend US$500 more than desktop users in the same timeframe, highlighting the need for strong mobile optimization.</description></item><item><title>What’s to Become of Data Centers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</guid><description>The increasing costs and rapid technological advancements are putting pressure on both large colocation facilities and traditional in-house data centers. This infographic from David Vellante on Wikibon provides a concise overview of the current situation:
Exploring Data Center Alternatives
If you&amp;rsquo;re reconsidering the viability of investing in a new data center or maintaining your existing one, you have numerous options. These range from colocation services at large commercial data centers to cloud-based solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>