<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0x000216</title><link>https://x.com/0x000216/</link><description>Recent content on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://x.com/0x000216/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terms Of Service</title><link>https://x.com/0x000216/termsofservice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://x.com/0x000216/termsofservice/</guid><description>&lt;p>These Terms And Conditions Do Not Affect Your Statutory Rights.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These Terms And Conditions Govern Your Use Of The Nexus Website And Your Relationship With Us. Please Read These Terms And Conditions And Our Privacy Policy Carefully Before Using The Site As They Affect Your Rights And Liabilities Under The Law. If You Do Not Agree To These Terms And Conditions, Please Do Not Use Our Site.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="use-of-the-site">Use Of The Site&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Site Is Provided To You Free Of Charge For Your Personal Use Subject To These Terms And Conditions. By Using The Site You Agree To Be Bound By These Terms And Conditions.&lt;br>
All Orders And Purchases Made On The Site Will Also Be Governed By These Terms And Conditions.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="accepting-these-terms">Accepting These Terms&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If You Access Or Use The Service, It Means You Agree To Be Bound By All Of The Terms Below. Please Read All Of The Terms Before You Use The Service. If A Term Does Not Make Sense To You, Please Let Us Know. If You Don’t Agree To All Of The Terms Below, You May Not Use The Service.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="amendments">Amendments&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We May Update These Terms And Conditions From Time To Time And Any Changes Will Be Notified To You Via A Suitable Announcement On The Site. The Changes Will Apply To The Use Of The Site After We Have Given Notice. If You Do Not Wish To Accept The New Terms And Conditions You Should Not Continue To Use The Site. If You Continue To Use The Site After The Date The Change Comes Into Effect, Your Use Of The Site Indicates Your Agreement To Be Bound By The New Terms And Conditions.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="availability-of-the-site">Availability Of The Site&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Although We Aim To Offer You The Best Service Possible, We Make No Promise That The Services At The Site Will Meet Your Requirements. We Cannot Guarantee That The Service Will Be Fault Free.&lt;br>
Your Access To The Site May Be Occasionally Restricted To Allow For Repairs, Maintenance Or The Introduction Of New Facilities Or Services. We Will Attempt To Minimise The Periods During Which Access To The Site Is Restricted For These Reasons.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="provision-of-information">Provision Of Information&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When You Order Any Items From Us You Will Need To Provide Us With Your Name, Address, Daytime Telephone Number, Home Telephone Number, Email Address And Credit Card Details. We Will Use These Details In Accordance With Our Privacy Policy.&lt;br>
You Must Ensure That The Details Provided By You At Any Time Are Correct And Complete. You Must Inform Us Of Any Change In Your Details Immediately.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="excluded-services">Excluded Services&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Services Provided By The Site Do Not Include The Provision Of Computer Or Other Necessary Equipment To Access The Site. To Use The Site You Will Require Internet Connectivity And Appropriate Telecommunications Links. We Shall Not Be Liable For Any Telephone Or Other Costs That You May Incur.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="our-intellectual-property-rights">Our Intellectual Property Rights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We, Or People We Have Contracted With, Own Or Are Licensed To Use All The Copyright, Database Rights Or Similar Rights And Information Within The Site. You May Use The Information And Reproduce It In Hard Copy For Your Personal Non-commercial Use And Reference Only. Except Where You Are Using A Feature Of The Site, Such As “e-mail A Friend”, For Personal Non-commercial Use And Reference Only, The Information On The Site May Not Otherwise Be Reproduced, Distributed Or Transmitted To Any Other Person Or Incorporated In Any Way Into Another Document Or Other Material Without Our Prior Written Approval. Any Hard Copies You Make Must Retain All Copyright And Proprietary Notices. You Must Not Alter Or Try To Alter Any Words, Data, Image Or Another Item On The Site Other Than Those Items That Are Intended To Be Completed Or Changed By You.&lt;br>
Nexus Reserve The Right To Authorize The Website Licensing Agency And Similar Reprographic Rights Organizations In Other Jurisdictions (“rros”) To Distribute Or License The Distribution Of Featured Material/contributions/commissions Throughout The World For Rros’ Licensed Acts And Purposes As Amended From Time To Time.&lt;br>
Limitations&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="you-may-not-use-the-site-for-any-of-the-following-purposes">You May Not Use The Site For Any Of The Following Purposes:&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Disseminating Any Unlawful, Harassing, Libelous, Abusive, Threatening, Harmful, Vulgar, Obscene, Otherwise Objectionable &lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="advertising-and-sponsorship">Advertising And Sponsorship&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Part Of The Site May Contain Advertising And Sponsorship. Advertisers And Sponsors Are Responsible For Ensuring That Material Submitted For Inclusion On The Site Complies With Relevant Laws And Codes. We Will Not Be Responsible For Any Error Or Inaccuracy In Advertising And Sponsorship.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="governing-law">Governing Law&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>These Terms And Conditions Are Governed And Construed In Accordance With The Laws Of Us. You Agree That The Court Shall Have Exclusive Jurisdiction But We May Use Another Court If We Choose.&lt;br>
Unless Otherwise Specified, The Site Is Directed Solely At Individuals From The Us. If You Choose To Access The Site From Locations Outside The Us, You Do So On Your Own Initiative And Are Responsible For Compliance With Local Laws.&lt;br>
The Comments And Information Contained On This Website Do Not Constitute Advice And You Should Not Rely On Any Content On This Website To Make (Or Refrain From Making) Any Decision Or Take (Or Refrain From Taking) Any Action.&lt;br>
Miscellaneous&lt;br>
You May Not Assign, Sub-license Or Otherwise Transfer Any Of Your Rights Under These Terms And Conditions.&lt;br>
If Any Provision Of These Terms And Conditions Is Found To Be Invalid By Any Court Having Competent Jurisdiction, The Invalidity Of That Provision Will Not Affect The Validity Of The Remaining Provisions Of These Terms And Conditions, Which Shall Remain In Full Force And Effect.&lt;br>
We Shall Not Be Responsible For Any Breach Of These Terms And Conditions Caused By Circumstances Beyond Its Control.&lt;br>
A Person Who Is Not A Party To These Terms And Conditions Shall Have No Right Under The Contract (Rights Of Third Parties) Act 1999 To Enforce Any Term Of These Terms And Conditions But This Shall Not Affect Any Right To Remedy Of A Third Party Which Exists Or Is Available Apart From The Act.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="changes-to-these-terms">Changes To These Terms&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We Encourage You To Review The Terms Regularly To Know About Our Practices. We May Change These Terms From Time To Time. For Example, We May Change These Terms If We Come Out With A New Feature. If We Make Changes, We Will Let You Know By Revising The Date At The Bottom Of The Policy And, In Some Cases, Provide You With Additional Notice (Such As Sending You An Email Notification). Any Changes We Make To These Terms Will Be Effective When We Post Them. If You Use The Service After We Have Posted The Changed Terms, Then You Have Accepted The Changes To These Terms.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="privacy-policy">Privacy Policy&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For Information About How We Collect, Use And Share Information About Users Of The Service, Please See Our Privacy Policy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="right-to-use-the-service">Right To Use The Service&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>On The Condition That You Fully Comply With These Terms, Nexus Grants You A Limited, Non-exclusive, Non-transferable And Revocable License To Access And Use The Service. Except As Expressly Authorized By These Terms, You May Not (A) Modify, Nexus, Alter, Translate Or Create Derivative Works Of The Service, (B) License, Sublicense, Resell, Distribute, Lease, Rent, Lend, Transfer, Assign Or Otherwise Dispose Of The Service, (C) Disassemble, Decompile Or Reverse Engineer Any Of The Software Components Of The Service, (D) Copy, Frame Or Mirror Any Part Of The Service, (E) Interfere With Or Disrupt The Integrity Or Performance Of The Service Or (F) Attempt To Gain Unauthorized Access To The Service Or Its Related Systems Or Networks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="reporting-and-removal">Reporting And Removal&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nexus Users May Report Usg (User-generated Content) To Nexus That They Think Violate These Terms, And Nexus May Remove That Usg, Suspend Or Terminate The Account Of The User Who Posted, Stored Or Otherwise Made Available Usg And/or Take Additional Action To Enforce These Terms Against Such User.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="feedback">Feedback&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Any Suggestions, Comments Or Other Feedback You Give Us About The Service Will Be Our Confidential Information. We Are Free To Use, Nexus, Reproduce, License, Distribute And Exploit This Feedback As We See Fit, Without Compensation To You Or Any Obligation Or Restriction Because Of Any Intellectual Property Rights Or Otherwise.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="third-party-materials">Third Party Materials&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We May Make Third Party Content Or Services Available On Or Through The Service As A Convenience To Our Users (For Example, Links To Third Party Websites) (“third Party Materials”). Our Users May Also Include Third Party Materials In The User Content That They Post, Store Or Otherwise Make Available To The Service. We Do Not Control Or Endorse Any Third Party Materials Nor Are We Responsible For Reviewing The Accuracy Of Any Third Party Materials. Your Business Dealings Or Correspondence With Third Parties, And Any Terms, Conditions, Warranties Or Representations Applicable To Any Third Party Materials, Are Solely Between You And The Applicable Third Party. When You Leave Our Service, You Should Be Aware That These Terms And All Other Nexus Policies No Longer Govern Your Use Of Other Websites And Services.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="links">Links&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Service May Contain Links To Third Party Websites That Are Not Owned Or Controlled By Nexus Is Not Affiliated With Those Websites, Has No Control Over, And Assumes No Responsibility For, The Content, Privacy Policies, Or Practices Of Any Third Party Websites. In Addition, Nexus Will Not And Cannot Censor Or Edit The Content Of Any Third-party Site. By Using The Service, You Expressly Release Nexus From Any And All Liability Arising From Your Use Of Any Third-party Website. Accordingly, We Encourage You To Be Aware When You Have Left The Service And To Read The Terms And Privacy Policy Of Each Other Website That You Visit.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="changes-to-the-service">Changes To The Service&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nexus Reserves The Right In Our Discretion To Review, Improve, Change Or Discontinue, Temporarily Or Permanently, The Service And/or Any Features, Information, Materials Or Content On The Service With Or Without Providing Notice To You. Nexus Will Not Be Liable To You Or Any Third Party For Any Changes Or Discontinuance Of The Service Or Any Part Of The Service.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="third-party-infrastructure">Third-party Infrastructure&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Notwithstanding Any Terms To The Contrary In These Terms, You Acknowledge And Agree That Nexus Uses A Third Party Hosting Infrastructure In Connection With The Service (“third-party Infrastructure”), The Provider(S) Of The Third-party Infrastructure Disclaim And Make No Representation Or Warranty With Respect To Such Third-party Infrastructure, And Nexus Assumes No Liability For Any Claim That May Arise With Respect To Such Third-party Infrastructure.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="electronic-communications">Electronic Communications&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>By Using The Service, You Agree That We May Communicate With You Electronically Regarding Your Use Of The Service And That Any Notices, Agreements, Disclosures Or Other Communications That We Send To You Electronically Will Satisfy Any Legal Communication Requirements, Including That The Communications Be In Writing. To Withdraw Your Consent From Receiving Electronic Notice, Please Notify Us Via Contact Form&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="severability">Severability&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If Any Provision Of These Terms Is Invalid, Illegal, Or Incapable Of Being Enforced By Any Rule Of Law Or Public Policy, All Other Provisions Of These Terms Will Nonetheless Remain In Full Force And Effect So Long As The Economic And Legal Substance Of The Transactions Contemplated By These Terms Is Not Affected In Any Manner Adverse To Any Party. Upon Such Determination That Any Provision Is Invalid, Illegal, Or Incapable Of Being Enforced, The Parties Will Negotiate In Good Faith To Modify These Terms So As To Effect The Original Intent Of The Parties As Closely As Possible In An Acceptable Manner To The End That The Transactions Contemplated Hereby Are Fulfilled.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="force-majeure">Force Majeure&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nexus Is Not Responsible For Any Failure To Perform Or Delay Attributable In Whole Or In Part To Any Cause Beyond Its Reasonable Control Including, But Not Limited To, Acts Of God (Fire, Storm, Floods, Earthquakes, Etc.), Acts Of Terrorism, Civil Disturbances, Disruption Of Telecommunications, Disruption Of Power Or Other Essential Services, Interruption Or Termination Of Services Provided By Any Service Providers Used By Nexus, Labor Disturbances, Vandalism, Cable Cut, Computer Viruses Or Other Similar Occurrences, Or Any Malicious Or Unlawful Acts Of Any Third Party.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions-">Questions ?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If You Have Any Questions Regarding The Use Of The Service Please Email Us.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://x.com/0x000216/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://x.com/0x000216/about/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="who-are-we">Who Are We&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Nexus Is A Leading Web-based Science, Research And Technology News WebSite Which Covers A Full Range Of Topics. These Include Physics, Earth Science, Medicine, Nanotechnology, Electronics, Space, Biology, Chemistry, Computer Sciences, Engineering, Mathematics And Other Sciences And Technologies.Nexus Publishes Quality Articles Every Day, Offering Some Of The Most Comprehensive Coverage Of Sci-tech Developments World-wide. Nexus Community Members Enjoy Access To Many Personalized Features Such As Social Networking, A Personal Home Page Set-up, Article Comments And Ranking, The Ability To Save Favorite Articles, A Daily Newsletter, And Other Options.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="our-mission">Our Mission&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The Nexus Staff Mission Statement Is To Provide The Most Complete And Comprehensive Daily Coverage Of The Full Sweep Of Science, Technology, And Medicine News. Sci-tech Readers Will Find Coverage Of Relevant And Interesting Current Events. We Strive To Bring Our Readers A Large Assortment Of Stories, Catering For Scientists, Researchers, Engineers, Academia, Tech Geeks, Students, And Graduates Alike. With A Highly Educated And Sophisticated Readership And Target Audience, Nexus Stories Go Beyond Mere Catchy Jargon. We Find Out The Who, The What, The Where, The How, And The Why Of A Story - And The Why Not. Our Job Is To Find The Interesting Science And Technology Stories, Uncover The Details, And Give Our Readers Their Daily Dose Of News At A Single Source.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://x.com/0x000216/contact/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://x.com/0x000216/contact/</guid><description>
&lt;style>
@import url(https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Montserrat:400,700);
form { max-width:420px; margin:50px auto; }
.form-input {
color:white;
font-family: Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;
font-weight:500;
font-size: 18px;
border-radius: 5px;
line-height: 22px;
background-color: transparent;
border:2px solid #CC6666;
transition: all 0.3s;
padding: 13px;
margin-bottom: 15px;
width:100%;
box-sizing: border-box;
outline:0;
}
.form-input:focus { border:2px solid #CC4949; }
textarea {
height: 150px;
line-height: 150%;
resize:vertical;
}
[type="submit"] {
font-family: 'Montserrat', Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;
width: 100%;
background:#CC6666;
border-radius:5px;
border:0;
cursor:pointer;
color:white;
font-size:24px;
padding-top:10px;
padding-bottom:10px;
transition: all 0.3s;
margin-top:-4px;
font-weight:700;
}
[type="submit"]:hover { background:#CC4949; }
&lt;/style>
&lt;form action="https://formspree.io/f/mrgknyvk" method="post" target="hidden_iframe" onsubmit="submitted=true">
&lt;label>Name&lt;/label>
&lt;input type="text" placeholder="Name*" class="form-input" name="entry.719211028" required>
&lt;label>Email&lt;/label>
&lt;input type="email" placeholder="Email address*" class="form-input" name="entry.1119409224" required>
&lt;label>Subject&lt;/label>
&lt;input type="text" placeholder="Subject*" class="form-input" name="entry.1043109960" required>
&lt;label>Message&lt;/label>
&lt;textarea rows="5" placeholder="Message" class="form-input" name="entry.1348223678" >&lt;/textarea>
&lt;button type="submit">Send&lt;/button>
&lt;/form></description></item><item><title>Disclaimer</title><link>https://x.com/0x000216/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://x.com/0x000216/disclaimer/</guid><description>&lt;p>Usage Of Any Information Or Materials On This Blog Is Entirely At Your Own Risk, For Which We Shall Not Be Liable.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="third-party-notice">Third Party Notice&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You Understand, Acknowledge, And Accept The Fact That We At Nexus Decode Are Not Affiliated With Any Company, Person, Or Organization Of Any Kind Mentioned On This Nexus Decode Website In Any Way.  Company Names, Products, Logos, Trade Marks And Any Other Proprietary Intellectual Property Or Otherwise Belongs To The Rightful Owner, Which Is Not Us.  You Should Not Assume, Even If A Company Name Is In The Website/domain Name Of This Website, That There Is An Express, Implied, Or Otherwise Agreement, Joint Venture, Partnership, Or Other Relationship Between Us As Website Proprietors And Any Of These Companies That Are Discussed Merely For Educational Or Other Purposes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Nexus Decode Does Not Accept Any Liability Arising Out Of The Application Or Use Of Any Information Provided Herein. This Blog Shall Not Be Liable For Any Loss Or Damage Arising From, Or In Any Way Connected With, Your Usage Of This Blog. This Includes, Without Limitation, Any Damage For Loss Of Profits, Loss Of Data, Loss Of Business, Loss Of Reputation, Loss Of Opportunity, Loss Of Good Will Or Injury To Reputation, Losses Suffered By Third Parties Or Any Indirect, Consequential, Special Or Exemplary Damages.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Nexus Decode Blog Makes Available Information And Materials (The &amp;ldquo;Information&amp;rdquo;) On Nexus Decode Blog, Subject To The Terms Of Service And This Disclaimer. This Disclaimer Governs The Use Of Our Website; By Accessing This Website, You Agree To The Terms And Conditions As Outlined In The Terms Of Service And This Disclaimer. If You Disagree, Please Do Not Access This Website. We Reserve The Right To Modify The Terms Of Service And/or Disclaimer From Time To Time Without Any Notice And At Our Sole Discretion By Posting Amended Terms Of Service And Disclaimer On This Website. By Using This Website After The Changes / Modifications Have Been Posted You Agree To Accept Those Changes/modifications, Whether Or Not You Have Reviewed The Changes/modifications.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If You Have Any Questions About The Contents Of This Page, Or Simply Wish To Reach Us For Any Other Reason, You May Do So By Using Our Contact Information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://x.com/0x000216/privacypolicy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://x.com/0x000216/privacypolicy/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="collection-of-information">Collection Of Information&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We Collect Information You Provide Directly To Us. For Example, We Collect Information When You Create An Account, Participate In Any Interactive Features Of The Service, Fill Out A Form, Participate In A Contest Or Promotion, Make A Purchase, Apply For A Job, Communicate With Us Via Third-party Social Media Sites, Request Customer Support Or Otherwise Communicate With Us. The Types Of Information We May Collect Include Your Name, Email Address, Postal Address, Phone Number, Fax Number, Credit Card Information And Any Other Information You Choose To Provide.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="information-you-provide-to-us">Information You Provide To Us&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Information We Collect Automatically When You Use The Service&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When You Access Or Use Our Service, We Automatically Collect Information About You Including:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Log Information: We Log Information About Your Use Of The Service, Including The Type Of Browser You Use, Access Times, Pages Viewed, Your Ip Address And The Page You Visited Before Navigating To Our Service.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Device Information: We Collect Information About The Computer Device You Use To Access Our Service, Including The Hardware Model, Operating System And Version, Unique Device Identifiers And Mobile Network Information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Location Information: We May Collect Information About The Location Of Your Device Each Time You Access Or Use One Of Our Mobile Applications Or Otherwise Consent To The Collection Of This Information. For More Details, Please See “your Choices” Below.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Information Collected By Cookies And Other Tracking Technologies: We Use Various Technologies To Collect Information, And This May Include Sending Cookies To Your Computer Or Mobile Device. Cookies Are Small Data Files Stored On Your Hard Drive Or In Device Memory That Help Us To Improve Our Service And Your Experience, See Which Areas And Features Of Our Service Are Popular And Count Visits. We May Also Collect Information Using Web Beacons (Also Known As “tracking Pixels”). Web Beacons Are Electronic Images That May Be Used In Our Service Or Emails And Help Deliver Cookies, Count Visits, Understand Usage And Campaign Effectiveness And Determine Whether An Email Has Been Opened And Acted Upon. For More Information About Cookies, And How To Disable Them, Please See &amp;ldquo;Your Choices&amp;rdquo; Below.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="information-we-collect-from-other-sources">Information We Collect From Other Sources&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We May Also Obtain Information From Other Sources And Combine That With Information We Collect Through Our Service. For Example, We May Collect Information About You From Third Parties, Including But Not Limited To Identity Verification Services, Credit Bureaus, Mailing List Providers And Publicly Available Sources. If You Create Or Log Into Your Account Through A Social Media Site, We Will Have Access To Certain Information From That Site, Such As Your Name, Account Information And Friends Lists, In Accordance With The Authorization Procedures Determined By Such Social Media Site.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="social-sharing-features">Social Sharing Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Service May Offer Social Sharing Features And Other Integrated Tools (Such As The Facebook “like” Button), Which Let You Share Actions You Take On Our Service With Other Media, And Vice Versa. The Use Of Such Features Enables The Sharing Of Information With Your Friends Or The Public, Depending On The Settings You Establish With The Entity That Provides The Social Sharing Feature. For More Information About The Purpose And Scope Of Data Collection And Processing In Connection With Social Sharing Features, Please Visit The Privacy Policies Of The Entities That Provide These Features.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Advertising And Analytics Services Provided By Others&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We May Allow Others To Serve Advertisements On Our Behalf Across The Internet And To Provide Analytics Services. These Entities May Use Cookies, Web Beacons And Other Technologies To Collect Information About Your Use Of The Service And Other Websites, Including Your Ip Address, Web Browser, Pages Viewed, Time Spent On Pages, Links Clicked And Conversion Information. This Information May Be Used By Nexus And Others To, Among Other Things, Analyze And Track Data, Determine The Popularity Of Certain Content, Deliver Advertising And Content Targeted To Your Interests On Our Service And Other Websites And Better Understand Your Online Activity.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="security">Security&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nexus Takes Reasonable Measures To Help Protect Information About You From Loss, Theft, Misuse And Unauthorized Access, Disclosure, Alteration And Destruction.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="account-information">Account Information &lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You May Update, Correct Or Delete Information About You At Any Time By Logging Into Your Online Account. If You Wish To Delete Or Deactivate Your Account, Please Email Us Via Our Contact Form, But Note That We May Retain Certain Information As Required By Law Or For Legitimate Business Purposes. We May Also Retain Cached Or Archived Copies Of Information About You For A Certain Period Of Time.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="location-information">Location Information&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When You First Launch Any Of Our Mobile Applications That Collect Location Information, You Will Be Asked To Consent To The Application&amp;rsquo;s Collection Of This Information. If You Initially Consent To Our Collection Of Location Information, You Can Subsequently Stop The Collection Of This Information At Any Time By Changing The Preferences On Your Mobile Device. You May Also Stop Our Collection Of Location Information By Following The Standard Uninstall Process To Remove All Of Our Mobile Applications From Your Device.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="cookies">Cookies&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Most Web Browsers Are Set To Accept Cookies By Default. If You Prefer, You Can Usually Choose To Set Your Browser To Remove Or Reject Browser Cookies. Please Note That If You Choose To Remove Or Reject Cookies, This Could Affect The Availability And Functionality Of Our Service.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>