<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The success of Dubai as a business hub will depend on talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-success-of-dubai-as-a-business-hub-will-depend-on-talent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-success-of-dubai-as-a-business-hub-will-depend-on-talent/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Crown Prince and Chairman of The Executive Council, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, emphasized the importance of skill development, talent discovery, and attracting skilled professionals to establish Dubai as a future-forward city during his visit to LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s regional headquarters.
He attributed Dubai&amp;rsquo;s success in drawing entrepreneurs and multinational corporations to its conducive investment climate, fostering a hub of exceptional talent. This aligns with the vision of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister and Ruler of Dubai, to shape Dubai into a knowledge-based, innovation-driven economy.</description></item><item><title>The Jewish heritage of Thomas Matthew Crooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jewish-heritage-of-thomas-matthew-crooks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jewish-heritage-of-thomas-matthew-crooks/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/nR7lbvh.png" alt="Featured image of post The Jewish heritage of Thomas Matthew Crooks" />Thomas Matthew Crooks was born in September 2003, making him 20 years old today. He resides with his parents, Matthew and Mary, who are in their 50s. The Crooks family is deeply religious and observes Jewish traditions and practices devoutly. Faith plays a significant role in their lives, guiding their values and shaping their worldview.
Family Background Matthew Brian and Mary Elizabeth, the parents of Thomas, have a rich Jewish heritage passed down through their Scottish and English ancestry.</description></item><item><title>Emirates reveals updated interiors for its Boeing 777 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced redesigned interiors for its Boeing 777 fleet, featuring upgraded seats and entertainment systems across all cabins. This multi-million dollar investment reflects the airline&amp;rsquo;s focus on enhancing the customer experience.
The new First Class cabins, designed in collaboration with several firms, offer private suites with sliding doors inspired by Mercedes-Benz S-Class. These suites prioritize comfort and luxury with features like soft leather seats, mood lighting, and ample storage. Retained features include personal minibars and wireless controls for seat adjustment and entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Most Singaporean women believe they are compensated fairly and that their employers value their opinions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</guid><description>Milieu Insight, a Southeast Asian consumer research firm, recently surveyed women in Singapore, Indonesia, and the Philippines to gauge their perceptions of workplace support, opportunities, and rewards.
Concept art featuring a woman
generated by dream by WOMBO.
Some key takeaways include:
While 67% of Singaporean women feel adequately compensated for their work, only half believe they are appropriately rewarded for exceeding expectations.
Although 65% believe their employers welcome their input, only 50% feel that feedback is acted upon.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank has released its 2017 forecast for the Thai economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</guid><description>The 2016 Thailand Economic Monitor, published today by the World Bank, projects Thailand&amp;rsquo;s economic growth to reach 3.1% in 2016 and 3.2% in 2017, surpassing the previous year&amp;rsquo;s 2.8%.
The report identifies private consumption and public investments, such as rail infrastructure projects, as primary growth drivers. Tourism has also performed well in 2016, with tourist arrivals, particularly from China, rising by 13.1% in the third quarter. A temporary slowdown and economic inactivity following the passing of HM King Bhumibol Adulyadej in October are anticipated to be partially counterbalanced by year-end holiday tax incentives for shopping and domestic tourism.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches.</description></item><item><title>The LASALLE Show will begin in April 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</guid><description>From the beginning of April to the end of May, the public and industry professionals are invited to view almost 900 graduating student projects at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s LASALLE College of the Arts yearly graduation showcase.
The projects featured at The LASALLE Show are developed throughout the students&amp;rsquo; final year and embody the culmination of their artistic growth and the realization of their aspirations. The LASALLE Show also provides insights into current trends in contemporary arts and design and highlights the emerging work of young artists.</description></item><item><title>Amber is the sole Hong Kong restaurant featured in the World's 50 Best Restaurants 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</guid><description>Source: World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants website. Dishes from Amber. Amber, located in The Landmark Mandarin Oriental hotel in Hong Kong, has secured a place on the esteemed World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list for the sixth consecutive year, achieving the ranking of 20th. Notably, Amber is the sole representative from Hong Kong to be featured on this prestigious list. The World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list, likened to the Oscars of fine dining, serves as an annual global celebration of gastronomy, acknowledging restaurants worldwide for their culinary excellence.</description></item><item><title>In 2021, digitalization will be the driving force behind recruitment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Randstad Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 2021 Market Outlook Report examines the economic and hiring trends anticipated for 2021.
Jaya Dass, Managing Director for Randstad Malaysia and Singapore, emphasizes that digital transformation will be a key driver of talent demand in 2021. She predicts a surge in demand for tech professionals and digitally skilled individuals across various sectors. While acknowledging the cautious optimism of businesses in the wake of the pandemic, Dass highlights the need for agility and innovation to adapt to the evolving landscape.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Free Twitter Followers Every Hour Using Toolkity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 17:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/NhEKjvI.png" alt="Featured image of post How to Get Free Twitter Followers Every Hour Using Toolkity" />Social media presence is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age. Having a robust Twitter following can enhance your online visibility, influence, and credibility. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to grow your Twitter followers without spending a dime, Toolkity offers a simple solution. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to get free Twitter followers every hour using Toolkity.
Step 1: Visit Toolkity&amp;rsquo;s Free Twitter Followers Page First, head over to Toolkity&amp;rsquo;s Free Twitter Followers page.</description></item><item><title>The MyNumber service from Hashtag assists businesses in reducing their hotline expenses in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>PLDT, through its corporate business group PLDT ALPHA Enterprise, has launched the PLDT #MyNumber service. This service streamlines a business&amp;rsquo;s hotline system into a memorable four to eight-digit contact number that starts with the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; symbol (for example, #8888). This single number can be reached by consumers nationwide using PLDT landlines, Smart, Talk N’ Text, and Sun mobile phones.
This service is designed for businesses that currently advertise different hotline numbers for different regions.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new premium offerings in First and Business Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced new luxury products for its First and Business Class passengers, partnering with brands like BYREDO, Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, and Bulgari to elevate the travel experience.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgd9y3iVi6anaC1N4Cso7QmgPJovqGEwEKcXCffrreFoqNcy3Bnr-B79U45k6PqBzF2gV2uzc94przcIphwRp2ecePtOYdspt9-PjYc3KQTh976kDvFOItJfkbCCO02xL93YGyDNrANYHYE/s1600/Emirates+byredo+wellness.jpg)
Source: Emirates. The BYREDO for Emirates Wellness kit.
First Class passengers in Emirates&amp;rsquo; private suites will receive a specially designed BYREDO travel wellness kit. This hypoallergenic skincare line, featuring chamomile, was created specifically for Emirates and introduced initially on the airline&amp;rsquo;s new Boeing 777 suites.</description></item><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking.</description></item><item><title>Apple has revealed that the Apple Watch will be available in additional countries starting on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Apple has announced the availability of the Apple Watch in more countries, including Singapore, South Korea, and Taiwan, starting June 26th. The smartwatch will be sold through Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, and authorized retailers.
Select retailers such as BOONTHESHOP Cheongdam in Seoul and Malmaison by The Hour Glass in Singapore will offer a curated collection of Apple Watch models at launch. In the Asia Pacific region, the Apple Watch is already for sale in Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, and Japan.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry.</description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong government confirms the schedule for releasing statistics from March to May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</guid><description>Companies interested in monitoring the Hong Kong economy can stay informed through press release schedules published by the Hong Kong government. These releases provide insights into various economic indicators.
A schedule of upcoming releases for March to May 2014 is provided below, starting with March 3rd.
March 2014
3rd: January 2014 Retail Sales Statistics
7th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Statistics on Vessels, Port Cargo, and Containers
10th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Quarterly Business Receipts Indices for Service Industries</description></item><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides leasing options for high-end smartphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first mobile phone leasing program to make high-end devices more accessible.
Subscribers with SIM Only plans can choose to pay a low monthly fee to use premium Apple and Samsung handsets instead of buying them outright. They can lease the newest Apple iPhone and Samsung Galaxy models for two years and have the option to upgrade in the twelfth month for a S$200 fee.
With prices starting at S$35 per month for a Samsung Galaxy S9 (64 GB), customers can save up to S$578 off the regular retail price if they lease the phone for a year or S$358 if they keep it for two years.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn Black Badge provides luxurious open-top driving in a striking black color</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</guid><description>Source: Rolls-Royce Motor Cars. The Rolls-Royce Dawn Black Badge.
Rolls-Royce Motor Cars has introduced the Dawn Black Badge, a new addition to their lineup.
This model joins the Wraith Black Badge and Ghost Black Badge, offering a luxurious and bold take on open-top driving with a darker and more sensual aesthetic. The Dawn Black Badge was revealed in a strikingly deep black shade, achieved through a meticulous painting and polishing process that is the most extensive ever employed by Rolls-Royce for a solid paint color.</description></item><item><title>Vietnam receives report card from World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economy shows resilience due to strong domestic demand and export-focused manufacturing, as highlighted in the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s recent Taking Stock report. The country&amp;rsquo;s mid-term economic outlook appears positive, with GDP projected to grow by 6% in the current year.
The report, a semi-annual assessment of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economic performance, notes that economic growth decelerated to 5.9% in the first nine months of the year. This slowdown is largely attributed to a severe drought that hampered agricultural output, reduced oil production, and weakened external demand.</description></item><item><title>Overview and analysis of the relaunched negotiations for EU accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The potential inclusion of the EU into the ECHR has been a long-awaited development. With the necessary Treaty modifications in the Lisbon Treaty and a negotiated accession treaty by 2013, it appeared that the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s December 2014 ruling would solidify this union. However, the Court&amp;rsquo;s judgment (Opinion 2/13), which was subject to criticism on this blog, unexpectedly disrupted the accession process.
However, the process was resurrected in 2019 and has advanced quickly since then.</description></item><item><title>Now in Hong Kong, exclusive to employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</guid><description>Source: Employees Only. View of the interior.
Employees Only (EO), the speakeasy and restaurant established in downtown Manhattan in 2004, has now opened a branch in Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s vibrant nightlife area, at 19 Lan Kwai Fong, Central.
This marks the group&amp;rsquo;s fourth global location and their second in Asia, following the successful launch of EO Singapore in June 2016.
Co-founder Igor Hadzismajlovic leads this project alongside Singapore-based partners Joshua and Sarissa Rodriguez Schwartz, GM Rachel Tow, and Beverage Director Owen Gibler.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has released its annual festive film about a lost phone just before Christmas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest holiday film centers around the importance of family connection during the Christmas season, particularly in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s tech-savvy environment.
The film, titled The Gift, portrays a teenager excessively focused on her digital life and how this affects her family&amp;rsquo;s Christmas traditions. The creators were inspired by research indicating that people of all ages, across demographics, are spending a significant amount of time on their phones, even more so than quality time with their families.</description></item><item><title>Running SQL DDL scripts using a Dynamics GP VS Tools AddIn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/running-sql-ddl-scripts-using-a-dynamics-gp-vs-tools-addin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 01:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/running-sql-ddl-scripts-using-a-dynamics-gp-vs-tools-addin/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP, shares his insights on deploying SQL scripts with Visual Studio Tools AddIns for Dynamics GP. He highlights the challenge of managing complex queries and Data Definition Language (DDL) scripts during deployment, especially for customizations requiring custom tables in multiple company databases.
Endow emphasizes the convenience of deploying AddIns by simply copying the DLL file and seeks to automate SQL script execution. He introduces a method to check for table existence and addresses the limitation of ADO.</description></item><item><title>What impact could Brexit have on the younger generation? EU Referendum Briefing 2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A UK exit from the European Union, or &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; could have significant implications for young people, impacting their education, travel opportunities, and economic prospects.
Education
The EU does not control educational content or matters like tuition costs. Instead, its involvement lies in cross-border educational aspects, including promoting student and teacher mobility through initiatives like the Erasmus program. Established in 1987, this EU law-based program facilitates student exchanges across various educational levels.</description></item><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24.</description></item><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Smile Singapore in Clarke Quay Central and share your beautiful smile with us!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</guid><description>The installation of the Smile project at Clarke Quay Central is currently underway.
Clarke Quay Central mall is promoting a happier Singapore with its Smile Singapore campaign. Launched as part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Jubilee celebrations, this project gives companies a platform to share their happy moments in the nation.
Caine Teo, head of Ape Works, the Creative Partner of the Smile Singapore Campaign, believes happiness is infectious. By showcasing pictures of smiling faces, they hope to remind Singaporeans of the many reasons to smile in their country.</description></item><item><title>Turning Junk Frequencies Into Gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/turning-junk-frequencies-into-gold/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/turning-junk-frequencies-into-gold/</guid><description>The 2.4 GHz WiFi band we use every day wasn&amp;rsquo;t originally designed for WiFi at all. It was part of the ISM band - Industrial, Scientific, and Medical - a section of the radio spectrum designated for devices that unintentionally emit radiation as a byproduct of their operation. These bands, ranging from 6.78 MHz to 245 GHz, were meant for devices like microwave ovens, industrial heaters, and medical equipment.
The 2.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some Cabinet Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I made progress reassembling the Beogram 4002, focusing on the cabinet trim and deck cover. To prevent damage, I had previously removed the rosewood trim.
The trim is attached to a metal frame that slides in and out to lock and unlock the cabinet. This frame relies on five guide washers, which are commonly broken in Beogram 4002 units. This one was no different. These washers have a unique design, as detailed in a past Beolover blog post.</description></item><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage.</description></item><item><title>Webinars diving deep into GP 2010</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on in-depth GP 2010 webinars for Microsoft Certified Trainers (MCTs) and Partners. These webinars offer step-by-step guidance on setting up and using the new features in GP 2010. As a bonus, all were created and presented by MCTs. Check them out – we hope they help you get your clients ready for GP 2010!
Business Intelligence &amp;amp; Reporting (This one is mine!)
This demonstration-based presentation covers the setup and use of new reporting and business intelligence enhancements in Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010.</description></item><item><title>Acuvue by Johnson &amp; Johnson excels in tests conducted in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acuvue-by-johnson-johnson-excels-in-tests-conducted-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acuvue-by-johnson-johnson-excels-in-tests-conducted-in-japan/</guid><description>Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson Vision Care&amp;rsquo;s 1-Day Acuvue Define and Acuvue 2 Define contact lenses were favorably mentioned in a report by Japan&amp;rsquo;s National Consumer Affairs Center (NCAC) concerning popular colored and limbal ring contact lenses in the Asia Pacific region.
The NCAC report, &amp;ldquo;Safety of Color Contact Lenses,&amp;rdquo; highlighted that while some manufacturers falsely claimed their lenses had &amp;ldquo;no pigment on the surface,&amp;rdquo; 1-Day Acuvue Define and Acuvue 2 Define lenses genuinely lacked surface pigments.</description></item><item><title>VPN Internet Access Links Facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpn-internet-access-links-facilities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpn-internet-access-links-facilities/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations into a unified network can be a costly endeavor. While traditional solutions like private lines and Frame Relay have their merits, a newer method is gaining traction, especially for businesses with numerous sites.
Private lines offer unparalleled reliability, consistent bandwidth, and robust security due to their dedicated nature. They are well-suited for connecting phone systems or transmitting video between locations. However, the need for a separate line between each pair of sites makes them expensive, particularly as the network expands.</description></item><item><title>Lenovo issues global recall for Thinkpad batteries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</guid><description>Lenovo has expanded a battery recall that was first announced on March 27, 2014. This recall now includes all affected lithium-ion batteries globally. The batteries, as announced in late April 2015, were manufactured for ThinkPad notebook computers shipped between February 2010 and June 2012.
Lenovo stated that they are offering free-of-charge replacement batteries for all recalled batteries in the interest of public safety.
The batteries were sold with new notebook computers or as optional or replacement batteries for the following models:</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber has announced the launch of the Dubai Smartpreneur Competition for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, working with the Smart Dubai Office, launched the second annual Dubai Smartpreneur Competition. This aligns with the vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, to make Dubai a leading smart city.
Source: Dubai Chamber. The event featured a panel discussion about the UAE government&amp;rsquo;s progress on smart city and innovation initiatives, and what will drive future sustainable growth.</description></item><item><title>The Swag employment superapp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises as well as job seekers in Singapore and Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</guid><description>Employment Hero, a company specializing in HR, payroll, and employee engagement, is launching Swag, an employment superapp designed to modernize the employer-employee relationship.
Building on its existing platform that streamlines HR and payroll processes for SMEs, Employment Hero is shifting its focus to enhance the job hunting experience for both employers and job seekers. Swag utilizes AI-powered recruitment tools to simplify and expedite the process of finding, onboarding, and rewarding talent.</description></item><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS).</description></item><item><title>Can Hotels Afford to Upgrade Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hotels-afford-to-upgrade-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 19:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hotels-afford-to-upgrade-bandwidth/</guid><description>Hotels and motels face a challenge: guests love fast internet, but providing it is expensive. Upgrading bandwidth seems like the obvious solution, but it&amp;rsquo;s costly, especially since guests expect free Wi-Fi.
While it seems logical that faster internet costs more, that&amp;rsquo;s not always true. Hotels can sometimes secure better internet speeds for less money. This depends on where they get their internet service and the age of their contracts.
The internet landscape has changed rapidly.</description></item><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation.</description></item><item><title>The Great Repeal Bill and the Legacy of Henry VIII: Threatening Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</guid><description>Joelle Grogan, Lecturer, Middlesex University
The Great Repeal Bill is ironically named because it won&amp;rsquo;t actually repeal much EU law. Instead, when Brexit concludes, it will initially shift existing EU law into British law. While this maintains some stability during the transition, the bill also includes a concerning element: a Henry VIII clause. This clause, named after the king who gave himself sweeping legislative power, allows the government to alter primary legislation with minimal parliamentary scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Now, you have the ability to answer calls directly on your Apple Watch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple Watch 3 includes phone capabilities.
Apple has launched the Apple Watch Series 3, a smartwatch with built-in cellular capabilities. With this new feature, users can make and receive calls and texts, and stay connected even when they don&amp;rsquo;t have their iPhone nearby.
This third-generation Apple Watch is designed for health and fitness, offering smart coaching features, water resistance up to 50 meters, and a new barometric altimeter for measuring elevation changes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Alternate "Circuit Diagram 2" with 24V Scale Illumination Lamps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-alternate-circuit-diagram-2-with-24v-scale-illumination-lamps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-alternate-circuit-diagram-2-with-24v-scale-illumination-lamps/</guid><description>I recently acquired a well-preserved Beogram 4000 service manual containing a unique supplementary diagram. This diagram, Circuit Diagram 2, outlines the control system and features a notable difference in the position scale illumination. Instead of the typical two 12V bulbs wired in series, it depicts two 24V bulbs connected in parallel to the 24V power source.
This discovery complicated a recent interaction with Sonavor, who is currently restoring his own Beogram 4000.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the RAM Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 utilizes a 3V battery to power its 16-word memory chip, an MCM144102, which is described as a peripheral memory unit in the Motorola 6804 manual but lacks readily available detailed specifications. This chip is responsible for storing calibration data and potentially the system time, although further investigation is required. A visual representation of the circuit is included below.
A positive aspect of the design is the inclusion of diode D27, which safeguards the battery against reverse polarity connection.</description></item><item><title>Four fashion trends from New York Fashion Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</guid><description>Milanoo.com, an online retailer for apparel and other goods, has recently highlighted the major trends observed during February&amp;rsquo;s New York Fashion Week.
Source: Milanoo website.
One trend was wrapped skirts that sit above the knee. This is a departure from the more revealing styles seen in past fashion events, which Milanoo refers to as &amp;ldquo;the consistent sexy style.&amp;rdquo; The company observed, &amp;ldquo;Skirts have been very popular these years. But things are changing.</description></item><item><title>When Dial-Up Internet Service Makes Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-dial-up-internet-service-makes-sense/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 04:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-dial-up-internet-service-makes-sense/</guid><description>While many have transitioned to residential broadband and dedicated business internet, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that approximately half of US internet users still rely on dial-up. Despite its age, dial-up has significantly improved and remains a viable option for many, even in professional settings.
Is dial-up outdated? Not really. Consider how you would access email or websites during a broadband outage. Even the most reliable DSL and cable providers experience occasional disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Error in Integration Manager eConnect Adapter: SQL Exception occurred in the GetNextNumber method.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-integration-manager-econnect-adapter-sql-exception-occurred-in-the-getnextnumber-method/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-integration-manager-econnect-adapter-sql-exception-occurred-in-the-getnextnumber-method/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
While testing the eConnect GetNextNumber methods in Integration Manager, I encountered an error. My simple GL transaction import, using the eConnect destination adapter, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t run. After several minutes, I stopped the process, and eventually, an error message appeared indicating a SQL Exception in the GetNextNumber method.
[Image]
My initial troubleshooting, including checking SQL Server for errors, running a SQL Profiler trace, and monitoring SQL Activity, yielded no clues.</description></item><item><title>2015 Singapore Christmas Gift Guide: The Joyful Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</guid><description>The holiday season is here, and with it comes the need for corporate gift ideas. Fortunately, there are many options to choose from this year.
Source: Kaizer Leather website.
Kaizer Leather offers a variety of leather business gifts, ranging from handcrafted luggage to smaller leather accessories. One notable option is the Cavalry Business Bag (shown above), crafted from high-quality Italian calf leather and featuring a detachable, adjustable shoulder strap.
~ o ~</description></item><item><title>The more specific the mobile advertisement, the higher its earnings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</guid><description>Smaato, a mobile advertising company, has observed that the most successful advertising categories in China during the first quarter of the year were shopping, e-commerce, communication, and technology. These categories achieved high eCPMs (effective cost per mille), reaching up to US$0.30.
When analyzing mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad expenditures in China during the same period, entertainment (30%) and games (22%) were the top two categories.
Ajitpal Pannu, Smaato&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, noted that both monetization and brand spending increased when essential parameters were shared globally with advertising partners.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Lubrication of Platter Motor Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the DC motor was lubricated. This particular motor uses brushes and has simple sleeve bearings.
To access the bearings for lubrication, the pulley and outer housing were removed. The pulley is attached to the shaft with glue, allowing for easy removal. After taking out two small screws, the housing can be opened and the motor taken out.
Next, the black rubber vibration insulation boot was removed, revealing the circuit board connected to the brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer.</description></item><item><title>Entrepreneurs in South Malaysia are receiving support from BAHTERA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-in-south-malaysia-are-receiving-support-from-bahtera/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 10:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-in-south-malaysia-are-receiving-support-from-bahtera/</guid><description>The Malaysian Ministry of Finance (MoF) has revealed that the upcoming BAHTERA series will be held on October 14th and 15th at the PERSADA Convention Centre in Johor Bahru.
BAHTERA aligns with the Malaysian government&amp;rsquo;s 11th Malaysia Plan to strengthen the Bumiputera economy. The event aims to equip Bumiputera entrepreneurs with valuable business insights, effective branding techniques, and relevant technology. This year, BAHTERA anticipates over 6,000 attendees.
Themed Bumipreneurs of Tomorrow, BAHTERA (Southern Edition) is tailored for entrepreneurs and Bumiputera businesses in Southern Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>Vizury monitors users on various screens to gain a better understanding of them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vizury-monitors-users-on-various-screens-to-gain-a-better-understanding-of-them/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vizury-monitors-users-on-various-screens-to-gain-a-better-understanding-of-them/</guid><description>For marketers aiming to cultivate customer relationships, providing a consistent and tailored experience is crucial. In anticipation of ad:tech Tokyo, Vizury, a digital CRM company, has presented insights into developing a comprehensive cross-device targeting strategy.
Understanding a user completely requires gathering data from various touchpoints such as desktop browsers, mobile websites, and apps. Vizury emphasizes that a successful cross-device strategy hinges on accurately identifying users across different devices. This allows marketers to track the customer journey from initial product view to the final purchase.</description></item><item><title>The TomTom City portal offers real-time traffic and travel updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</guid><description>TomTom (TOM2) introduces TomTom City, a digital platform providing real-time traffic data and travel details to both individuals and traffic management professionals.
This new service showcases the wide array of traffic information available for specific cities and acts as a hub for connecting traffic authorities, businesses, and citizens to collaborate on sustainable and efficient mobility solutions. Building on the traffic information already available through TomTom navigation devices and partners in automotive, consumer, and government sectors, TomTom City expands upon the historical congestion data provided in reports like the TomTom Traffic Index.</description></item><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th.</description></item><item><title>Samsung MM-A940 Two Megapixel Camera Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-mm-a940-two-megapixel-camera-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-mm-a940-two-megapixel-camera-phone/</guid><description>We regret to inform you that the Samsung MM-A940 special offer is no longer active. To discover the latest enticing cell phone promotions, including those featuring complimentary phones, we recommend utilizing our Cell Phone Plan Finder. This tool will guide you towards the leading phone choices and their corresponding wireless plans.
The realms of cell phones and digital cameras are converging with the emergence of the Samsung MM-A940 camera phone. In contrast to most cameraphones equipped with VGA or, at best, 1.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport Group announces the closure of Terminal 2 for a period of 18 months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Changi Airport.
Due to a significant decrease in air travel and the low likelihood of a return to pre-pandemic levels soon, Changi Airport Group (CAG) has decided to consolidate operations at Changi Airport. This move aims to reduce operating costs like utilities and cleaning for CAG and its partners while optimizing resource allocation across the airport&amp;rsquo;s terminals.
Starting May 1, 2020, Terminal 2 (T2) will halt operations for 18 months, relocating airlines to other terminals*.</description></item><item><title>Push The Zone" - A Fresh Read for Gardeners by David The Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/push-the-zone-a-fresh-read-for-gardeners-by-david-the-good/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 18:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/push-the-zone-a-fresh-read-for-gardeners-by-david-the-good/</guid><description>Dateline: 27 January 2017
David The Good&amp;rsquo;s latest book, Push The Zone, is out now on Amazon. I finished reading it this morning and really enjoyed it (Click Here for details).
The book&amp;rsquo;s introduction provides a solid overview, which I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize in the following paragraphs:
This book won&amp;rsquo;t perform miracles, such as teaching you to cultivate limes in Minnesota or cocoa in Manhattan. It also won&amp;rsquo;t help with your dating life, but you probably already knew that.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean IT leaders are concerned that a shortage of skills could impede the progress of the Smart Nation initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-it-leaders-are-concerned-that-a-shortage-of-skills-could-impede-the-progress-of-the-smart-nation-initiative/</guid><description>93% of Singaporean Chief Information Officers (CIOs) are worried that Singapore lacks the IT talent pool needed to successfully implement Smart Nation initiatives.
Six out of 10 CIOs believe Smart Nation initiatives will lead to more IT jobs, and 53% believe these initiatives will boost average IT salaries.
New independent research* commissioned by specialized recruiter Robert Half reveals that over 9 in 10 (93%) Singaporean IT leaders are concerned about the lack of readily available IT talent in Singapore to build a Smart Nation-ready workforce.</description></item><item><title>Caution: Superman is poisonous</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-superman-is-poisonous/</guid><description>According to a McAfee blog post, Superman poses a significant online threat. The company argues that the widespread presence of superheroes beyond comic books allows hackers and scammers to exploit them for cybercrime.
McAfee&amp;rsquo;s survey, which used their SiteAdvisor site ratings, revealed that Superman is the &amp;ldquo;Most Toxic Superhero.&amp;rdquo; The study found that searches combining &amp;ldquo;Superman&amp;rdquo; with terms like &amp;ldquo;free torrent download,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;watch,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;free app,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; have a 16.5% chance of leading to websites containing threats like spyware, adware, spam, phishing, viruses, and other malware.</description></item><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration.</description></item><item><title>How the EU Migration and Asylum Pact Can Address its Blind Spot on Statelessness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</guid><description>Chris Nash, the Director of the European Network on Statelessness, highlights their recent analysis of the EU Pact on Migration and Asylum. The analysis focuses on how the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposals within the Pact could affect the fundamental rights of stateless migrants and refugees. It offers suggestions for addressing these concerns during Pact negotiations and implementation.
The Pact, as it stands, fails to directly address the rights of stateless individuals or offer solutions to the specific protection issues they encounter.</description></item><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk.</description></item><item><title>DED allows for the licensing of eight additional business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</guid><description>Source: DED. Bushahab.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Economic Development (DED) has expanded its list of permissible business activities, increasing the total to 2,133. This decision stems from regular feedback gathered from various industry sectors regarding local market needs and the balance of supply and demand. The goal is to simplify business operations and offer essential resources for growth.
The new additions encompass several specialized activities. These include assembling industrial robots, providing tax consultancy services, printing secure documents, manufacturing scanners, collecting and transporting hazardous waste, offering health consultancy, brokering financing deals, and developing and managing applications for social media.</description></item><item><title>Adobe and Microsoft software will now collaborate more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</guid><description>Adobe has enhanced Adobe Document Cloud as part of their partnership with Microsoft. Both companies want to provide excellent digital document experiences to their many shared customers.
Adobe Sign is now more integrated with Microsoft Dynamics 365. This provides real-time access to customer information from LinkedIn Sales Navigator and allows for more automated sales processes. New PDF integrations will enable all Office 365 users who subscribe to Adobe Acrobat DC for teams or enterprises to create, edit, and view secure, high-quality PDFs.</description></item><item><title>Vote MPLS &amp; Ethernet for Better Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</guid><description>The 2008 election season is upon us. To determine which candidates best serve your interests, we suggest considering MPLS and Ethernet for reliable bandwidth, improved performance, and reduced costs over 1-3 years. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into their platforms to see if they deserve your vote.
IP Networking is currently the leading technology. Initially confined to local offices, IP has expanded to WANs at state, regional, and national levels. Today, almost all network designs are centered around IP or Internet Protocol.</description></item><item><title>Sipping on the Trunk Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</guid><description>The history of telephone trunks goes back to the early days of telephones. Trunks are lines that carry multiple phone conversations, initially connecting switchboards and switching offices. They&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from wire bundles to analog and now digital circuits, with T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and SONET being common digital trunking services. However, SIP trunking is emerging as a popular alternative.
Telephone trunking saves money by combining multiple phone lines into a single high-bandwidth connection.</description></item><item><title>The launch of Fairfield by Marriott Belitung has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its Fairfield by Marriott brand with the opening of a new hotel in Belitung, Indonesia.
Source: Fairfield by Marriott Belitung website. The Fairfield by Marriott Belitung.
Mike Fulkerson, Vice President of Brand &amp;amp; Marketing for Marriott International Asia Pacific, stated that Fairfield by Marriott is experiencing rapid growth in the region, with 47 properties in development in Asia Pacific and over 400 globally. He highlighted the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing a relaxing and dependable experience at a good value, enhanced by Indonesian hospitality, making the Belitung location an ideal retreat for travelers.</description></item><item><title>Samsung D307 is Built For Messaging</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-d307-is-built-for-messaging/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 08:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-d307-is-built-for-messaging/</guid><description>We apologize, but the Samsung D307 is no longer available. To explore the latest cell phone deals and free phone offers, use our convenient Cell Phone Plan Finder.
The Samsung D307 combines the functionality of a computer, phone, and personal stenographer. This phone is perfect for those who prioritize messaging.
While many phones offer texting, it&amp;rsquo;s often cumbersome due to limited keys and multiple functions. Alternatively, bulky PDA-style phones are available but not pocket-friendly.</description></item><item><title>A Thousand VARs Can't Be Wrong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-thousand-vars-cant-be-wrong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 04:32:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-thousand-vars-cant-be-wrong/</guid><description>Telarus, the parent company of Shop For T1 and the VAR Network, has recruited over 1,000 Value Added Resellers (VARs), according to Chief Technical Officer Patrick Oborn. This is a significant achievement in the telecommunications industry, which is characterized by independent small businesses. The key motivators for telephone system installers and network consultants to join this nationwide database are customer leads and residual income.
Businesses specializing in computer network and telephone sales and service usually operate locally or regionally.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Capacitor Replacement on Unit #2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</guid><description>The first Beomaster 1900 receiver is fully operational and undergoing testing in a listening room. However, the second unit still requires restoration.
Initial assessment of the second Beomaster 1900 has already been completed, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to begin replacing capacitors on the main circuit board.
The main circuit board houses most of the capacitors that need replacing. Unfortunately, it cannot be removed for servicing and must remain connected to the wire harness.</description></item><item><title>European academics are appealing for the EU to avoid becoming a lawless zone.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</guid><description>The situation at the Polish-Belarusian border briefly gained public awareness, with images of suffering refugees stranded in terrible conditions sparking outrage. While there were discussions and reactions, the humanitarian crisis persists.
Since September 2021, the Polish government has restricted access to the border zone, putting migrants in danger and denying aid organizations access. People are facing dire circumstances, including death, due to lack of basic necessities and medical help.</description></item><item><title>Increase Bandwidth Without Increasing Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</guid><description>Companies need more bandwidth, especially for their wide area networks (WANs), but it can be very expensive. While high speeds are affordable within a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN, connecting to the outside world traditionally comes with much higher costs.
This is because WAN connections were typically provided by telecom companies using technology initially meant for phone services. While more modern providers have entered the market with updated infrastructure, even traditional providers are adapting to the demand for data services.</description></item><item><title>Numerous White Papers Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through a phase where white papers feel incredibly relevant to challenges we face internally and with clients. I wanted to share some of my top picks:
Microsoft Dynamics GP and SQL Server 2008
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false This paper offers valuable insights into leveraging SQL Server 2008 compression, including performance benchmarks.
Choosing a Development Tool for Microsoft Dynamics GP 10
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false A must-read for developers and consultants, this paper provides a comprehensive overview of development tools, licensing costs, required skillsets, and tool capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Error in the positioning of the Visual Studio Tools window in GP 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-the-positioning-of-the-visual-studio-tools-window-in-gp-2013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-the-positioning-of-the-visual-studio-tools-window-in-gp-2013/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
This week, I completed a custom Dynamics GP 2013 eConnect integration created as a Visual Studio Tools AddIn. The client wanted a GP menu item to open the integration window, so I used the Menus for Visual Studio Tools library to create a custom menu item.
The integration worked perfectly, and I packaged it for deployment at the client site.
However, during final testing and verification, I encountered unusual window behavior.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Xbox CosPups inspired by the Chinese zodiac</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-xbox-cospups-inspired-by-the-chinese-zodiac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-xbox-cospups-inspired-by-the-chinese-zodiac/</guid><description>Source: Xbox. The Xbox Cospups.
To celebrate the Year of the Dog, Xbox has created the Xbox CosPups. This group of canine characters embodies traits of the Chinese zodiac through their portrayal of famous gaming characters and worlds.
&amp;ldquo;Cospups&amp;rdquo; refers to dogs participating in &amp;ldquo;cosplay,&amp;rdquo; which involves dressing up as characters from different forms of media like books, games, and movies.
The Xbox CosPups have names such as Master Chihuahua, Sea of Fleas, Mutt-cus Fenix, Fur-za, and the small but mighty PUG-G.</description></item><item><title>Dubai-Opoly aims to showcase Dubai as a premier business destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-opoly-aims-to-showcase-dubai-as-a-premier-business-destination/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-opoly-aims-to-showcase-dubai-as-a-premier-business-destination/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Dubai Chamber creates Dubai-Opoly game to promote
Dubai.
The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced Dubai-Opoly, a board game designed to highlight Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing as a global business and trade hub.
Inspired by the classic game Monopoly, Dubai-Opoly will soon be available in stores across the UAE and GCC region. The game will showcase some of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most iconic landmarks and attractions. This initiative aligns with the Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s efforts to strengthen the emirate&amp;rsquo;s image as a thriving commercial center and top tourist destination.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp.</description></item><item><title>Two JW Marriott hotels have been ranked in the top 10 TripAdvisor Travelers' Choices for Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Lotte Hotel Seoul.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for hotels in Korea ranked the following as the top ten:
Lotte Hotel Seoul, with a rating of 4.5 out of 5 from 1,849 reviews. The Plaza Conrad Seoul JW Marriott Dongdaemun Square Seoul Park Hyatt Seoul The Shilla Seoul Sheraton Seoul D Cube City Hotel The Westin Chosun Seoul The Ritz-Carlton, Seoul The JW Marriott Seoul Curious?</description></item><item><title>CASIO introduces the G-SHOCK x ITZY SS2024 collection in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-the-g-shock-x-itzy-ss2024-collection-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-the-g-shock-x-itzy-ss2024-collection-in-singapore/</guid><description>CASIO is promoting their new G-SHOCK shock-resistant watches for spring 2024 with the help of K-pop group ITZY, who have been G-SHOCK brand ambassadors since February 2023.
ITZY is shown wearing the new GMA-P2100SG-1A, GMA-P2100SG-4A, GMA-S120VA-7A, and GMA-S140VA-7A watches in a promotional image. Ryujin and Chaeryeong showcase the GMA-P2100SG-1A and GMA-P2100SG-4A, which are inspired by sunset hues on a beach. These watches are based on the GMA-P2100, a smaller version of the well-liked GMA-S2100 analog-digital combination watch.</description></item><item><title>It's Wireless Cleanup Time Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-wireless-cleanup-time-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-wireless-cleanup-time-again/</guid><description>This New Year&amp;rsquo;s, consider a resolution that benefits both your wallet and the environment: declutter your old cell phones!
It&amp;rsquo;s common to accumulate unused phones after upgrading contracts or switching carriers. Technological advancements and tempting free offers often lead us to replace phones before they&amp;rsquo;re truly unusable. While understandable, this habit results in drawers and boxes filled with neglected devices. These phones quickly lose value and often end up discarded, contributing to electronic waste and releasing harmful substances like lead and cadmium into landfills.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Reunification of Ireland from an EU Legal Viewpoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</guid><description>Nikos Skoutaris, Lecturer in EU law at the University of East Anglia; website on Secessions, Constitutions and EU law.
When the UK voted to leave the EU on June 23, 2016, Northern Ireland voted to remain. This result has led Sinn Féin to call for a referendum on Irish unification, which would allow Northern Ireland to stay in the EU. This discussion has gained momentum following the most recent Northern Ireland Assembly election, which saw a significant decrease in the Unionist vote.</description></item><item><title>Shared Internet Service for Apartment Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shared-internet-service-for-apartment-buildings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shared-internet-service-for-apartment-buildings/</guid><description>Property owners and managers are recognizing the increasing importance of broadband internet access, much like essential utilities. They are exploring ways to provide this service, similar to phone and cable companies. Offering high-speed internet can be a significant advantage in attracting and retaining tenants.
Becoming an internet service provider, even for a single building, requires reliable, dedicated internet access. T1 or Dedicated Internet provides this, ensuring the full bandwidth is dedicated to your use, unlike shared services like DSL and Cable.</description></item><item><title>Dial-Up is Alive and Kicking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world of high-speed internet, it might seem strange to talk about dial-up. Many people consider it outdated technology.
However, dial-up internet access is still relevant. Millions of people still use and appreciate it for browsing the internet and checking emails. This &amp;ldquo;outdated&amp;rdquo; technology remains profitable.
One of the main advantages of dial-up is its affordability. Unlimited access is available for a low monthly cost, making it a budget-friendly option compared to DSL or cable internet.</description></item><item><title>Azerai offers affordable luxury in Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Azerai invites discerning travelers to experience attainable luxury in Vietnam through a collection of acclaimed boutique resorts. Founded by Adrian Zecha, the visionary behind Aman Resorts, the Azerai concept is already present in the culturally rich destinations of Ke Ga, Can Tho, and Hue.
Source: Azerai. Each Azerai resort is designed to envelop guests in sophisticated, understated luxury.
Every Azerai resort aims to immerse guests in refined yet understated luxury. At Azerai Can Tho, this translates to seclusion within low-rise structures on a private islet in the Hau River, reachable only by boat.</description></item><item><title>Consumer Card achieves outstanding success, according to DIB's report</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</guid><description>Source: DIB website. Banner for the Consumer Card page.
The Consumer Card, a collaboration between the Department of Economic Development (DED) in Dubai and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the largest Islamic bank in the UAE, has surpassed expectations in a very competitive market by the close of 2016. This success highlights how much customers value the card&amp;rsquo;s transparency and customer-centric approach.
Customers appreciate the card&amp;rsquo;s straightforward rewards system, which focuses on everyday transactions rather than requiring increased spending.</description></item><item><title>The demand for milk and yogurt-based beverages is increasing in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Increased advertising in mass media, along with more television shows and magazine content focused on health topics, have made Indonesian consumers more aware of the advantages of drinking milk from 2011 to 2016, according to Euromonitor.
Ultrajaya Milk Industry &amp;amp; Trading Company leads the drinking milk market, holding a 23% value share in 2016. Its most recognized brand is Ultra. Euromonitor attributes the company&amp;rsquo;s success in flavored milk to its strong marketing and enhanced distribution.</description></item><item><title>Is Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union considered valid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart
Introduction
The Treaty of Lisbon introduced Article 50 to the Treaty on European Union (TEU), establishing the legal framework for exiting the European Union (EU). This article acknowledges the possibility of withdrawal, a concept many legal experts believed existed even before the Treaty of Lisbon. Article 50 TEU outlines the withdrawal procedure. However, some argue that it contradicts the EU&amp;rsquo;s fundamental nature and weakens member states&amp;rsquo; commitment to European integration, raising questions about the ideal withdrawal mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Copper WAN Bandwidth Headed to 500 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</guid><description>Ericsson has developed a new technology that could significantly boost data transmission speeds over existing copper wire infrastructure. This innovation allows for WAN connections over copper, achieving speeds up to 500 Mbps.
While Gigabit Ethernet is achievable with Cat-6 wiring for LAN connections, this technology focuses on connecting businesses to broadband providers using existing copper infrastructure. This is significant because many businesses require increased bandwidth for various purposes, including server farms, internet access, data transfer between locations, and the growing need for electronic medical record transfers.</description></item><item><title>In 2017, a settlement network powered by blockchain announced that it would waive fees for transfers to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</guid><description>OKLink, a global settlement platform, has introduced the first entirely free remittance corridor. The company stated that transfers up to US$100,000 each month to Singapore will be free throughout 2017.
Previously, OKLink applied a 0.1% fee on cross-border payments to Singapore, while other companies might charge up to US$5 per transaction.
&amp;ldquo;As the world&amp;rsquo;s largest blockchain-powered global settlement network, we can process cross-border payments faster and more affordably as more partners join,&amp;rdquo; explained Jack Liu, Chief Strategy Officer at OKLink.</description></item><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Get Ready For The Recovery With Bandwidth on Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>The economy is recovering, benefiting some businesses while others struggle. Maintaining earnings through cost-cutting instead of increased sales won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable. When the economy fully recovers, rapid adaptation will be crucial, but increased expenses are only justifiable with increased revenue. Bandwidth on demand offers a solution.
Bandwidth on demand allows businesses to access and pay for only the bandwidth they currently need, scaling usage up or down as required. This differs from the traditional approach of installing full capacity in advance, which poses financial risks if projected growth doesn&amp;rsquo;t materialize.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>The Bleisure app emerged as the winner of the Sabre hackathon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</guid><description>Source: Sabre. From left: Isolda Josy and Pranay Roy, Moments; Mendis from Sabre Travel Network Asia Pacific; and Marco Angeles, Moments.
A team from Singapore won the 24-hour Destination Hack: Singapore, Sabre&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Asia Pacific hackathon. Participants were tasked with designing a new technology app that could revolutionize travel – from planning and booking to the overall experience.
The winning app, Moments, caters to the increasing demand for &amp;ldquo;bleisure&amp;rdquo; travel in the Asia Pacific region.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>My work on restoring the 4002 continues, and today involved polishing the hood – a task that&amp;rsquo;s quite a workout! The plexiglass hood had some noticeable scratches:
I began by using 200 grit sandpaper to create a consistent surface:
Then I gradually polished it using Micromesh polishing cloths:
The final stage involved Micromesh Micro-Gloss:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>Visualizations in the style of Tableau help to make content more memorable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visualizations-in-the-style-of-tableau-help-to-make-content-more-memorable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visualizations-in-the-style-of-tableau-help-to-make-content-more-memorable/</guid><description>Ben Jones, Director of Marketing, Outreach Programs at Tableau Software, highlights the numerous advantages of data visualizations for content creators. During a media workshop introducing Tableau Public, a free version of Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization platform, Jones outlined several key benefits:
Data visualizations are attention-grabbing, providing a visual anchor within text and effectively conveying the story&amp;rsquo;s central theme.
They simplify the presentation of trends compared to using words alone.
Visualizations make comparisons clear and effortless.</description></item><item><title>Cloud vs Premises Contact Center Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</guid><description>Lots of small businesses can get by with just a local or toll-free number for customer calls. But as companies grow, they usually dedicate staff and resources to handle customer interactions, creating a dedicated department known as a contact center. While contact centers are important, they can be expensive to run. Is there a way to reduce the cost?
Until recently, outsourcing to different locations was an option, but that often led to issues with language barriers and inconsistent service quality.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks.</description></item><item><title>The Dark Side of Spectrum Renewal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</guid><description>Half a century ago, the government embraced urban renewal, demolishing and rebuilding deteriorated urban areas for housing projects or highways leading to suburbs. Similarly, today, we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing &amp;ldquo;spectrum renewal,&amp;rdquo; where sections of the radio frequency spectrum are deemed too valuable for older technologies like analog TV and cell phone service, despite their widespread use.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by lack of public demand. Millions of analog TV sets and cell phones are still functional.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Neutrik Gold Plated DIN5 Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</guid><description>A common improvement for the Beogram 4000 is replacing the DIN5 plug with a gold-plated version. The older plugs, often corroded, benefit from the upgrade. This particular Beogram 4000 was no exception.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a comparison of the old plug and the new, gleaming Neutrik plug (Newark 27B4483):
The old plug was removed, and the cable was prepped for the new plug. Stripping the outer insulation to this length works well:</description></item><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both.</description></item><item><title>Your Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple locations often need to share data, traditionally relying on T1 lines for connectivity. While multiple T1 lines can increase bandwidth, this approach might not be the most cost-effective solution, especially in metropolitan areas.
Point-to-point Ethernet offers a compelling alternative, often at a lower cost per Mbps, particularly for higher bandwidth needs. Ethernet streamlines data transmission by maintaining its format throughout the network, potentially allowing locations to function as a single bridged LAN.</description></item><item><title>The future was examined at the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>The second day of the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong brought together over 50 prominent figures from various industries to discuss the future of living. The event, which ran until March 24th, featured experts, business leaders, and creatives sharing their insights with attendees from around the world.
With a focus on the prediction that 70% of the global population will reside in urban areas by 2050, the festival examined the implications for how we live, eat, travel, and interact with the natural world through panels and demonstrations.</description></item><item><title>Orchard Road in Singapore is adorned with Christmas lights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road is aglow with Disney magic this holiday season. The &amp;ldquo;Disney Magical Moments — Christmas on A Great Street!&amp;rdquo; celebration features illuminated displays of beloved characters. The lights were officially switched on the evening of November 10.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the Toy Story-themed lights outside Plaza Singapura from the opening night.
The lights are arranged in four color-themed zones:
- Orange: Pixar’s Toy Story characters, including Woody, Buzz Lightyear, and their friends.</description></item><item><title>The Al Ain Cultural Programme for 2017/2018 is currently in full swing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</guid><description>The Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi recently held three events showcasing Emirati culture and heritage as part of the annual Al Ain Cultural Programme.
On October 19th, Qasr Al Muwaiji (Al Muwaiji Palace) hosted the Bisht Workshop, which delved into the history of the traditional garment worn by UAE rulers and the unique patterns associated with each ruler. Attendees also participated in a hands-on workshop, learning to create their own bisht.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft renegotiation deal a legitimate rejection? Tusk's suggestion and the role of national parliaments.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</guid><description>Dr. Katarzyna Granat, Junior Research Fellow &amp;amp; Marie Curie Fellow, Durham Law School Donald Tusk&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A New Settlement for the United Kingdom within the European Union&amp;rdquo; (Draft Decision of the Heads of State or Government), presented on February 2, 2016, provides an initial concrete outline for enhancing the role of national parliaments within the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiation efforts. This note compares the proposed changes with existing mechanisms under the Lisbon Treaty.</description></item><item><title>Farewell, VB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-vb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-vb/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been close since I started with programming on my Commodore 64. From creating basic applications in school to more complex projects later on, you were there.
We tackled various challenges, from writing a Windows application for a psychology thesis to automating tasks with WordPerfect macros. You adapted well to new environments, proving valuable in Microsoft Office VBA and early ERP systems.
Our journey continued with web applications, e-commerce integrations, and custom desktop apps.</description></item><item><title>Is Brexit Causing the British Mind to Close? The Impact on EU Academics and Government Guidance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Brexit vote is often seen as an attack on both academic expertise and EU citizens in the UK, whether accurate or not. These two issues intersect in a recent dispute involving the Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO) and the London School of Economics (LSE). The FCO allegedly barred EU citizens from advising the government on Brexit, though the details are unclear.
The LSE reportedly informed staff that the FCO no longer sought Brexit advice from EU nationals, sparking a controversy that made its way to social media and prominent news outlets like The Guardian.</description></item><item><title>The financial consequences of the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-financial-consequences-of-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-financial-consequences-of-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s potential in fostering trust within networks is significant.
The World Bank Group has been actively supporting clients throughout the COVID-19 pandemic. William Zhang, a Lead Information Security Architect and Blockchain Specialist at the World Bank Group, highlighted the severe economic impact of COVID-19, including a US$4 trillion global GDP decline, significant job losses, and numerous business closures.
Zhang, speaking at a webinar titled &amp;ldquo;Leveraging Blockchain Innovations to Cope with the COVID-19 New Normal,&amp;rdquo; organized by the 10x1000 Tech for Inclusion Programme, noted that projections indicate a 9% increase in both poverty and extreme poverty.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Comparison Shopping</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-comparison-shopping/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 17:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-comparison-shopping/</guid><description>Voice over IP (VoIP) is becoming increasingly popular for both home and business phone service. With this new technology rapidly evolving, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep up with the latest companies and deals. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to switch to VoIP or simply want a better deal, you need a way to compare your options. That&amp;rsquo;s where a comparison shopping service comes in handy, allowing you to easily evaluate available services and choose the best fit.</description></item><item><title>Business Ethernet Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</guid><description>For decades, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have relied heavily on T1 lines. However, a new service called Business Ethernet is emerging as a strong competitor, offering comparable performance at a lower cost.
Business Ethernet, also referred to as Metro Ethernet, Ethernet over Copper, or Ethernet over Fiber, provides advantages such as scalable bandwidth options, reduced cost per Mbps, and wider availability. Its name emphasizes that Ethernet is no longer limited to Local Area Networks (LANs) and carriers, as it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly being adopted by SMBs.</description></item><item><title>Hosting Nation Offers Low Cost Web Hosting For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosting-nation-offers-low-cost-web-hosting-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 09:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosting-nation-offers-low-cost-web-hosting-for-everyone/</guid><description>Are you searching for the perfect balance of affordability and quality in web hosting? Look no further than Hosting Nation.
Gone are the days of expensive, self-managed servers. Hosting services have become incredibly affordable, allowing you to establish a global presence for less than ten dollars a month.
If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; hosting services that compromise your website&amp;rsquo;s aesthetics or expensive &amp;ldquo;professional&amp;rdquo; hosting plans, Hosting Nation offers a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor outlines four key pillars for a successful expansion into emerging markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, has published an e-book titled &amp;ldquo;Succeed in Emerging Markets: Selection, Strategy and First Steps&amp;rdquo;. This e-book presents a four-pillar model designed to guide businesses entering emerging markets.
The first pillar, &amp;ldquo;market,&amp;rdquo; examines macroeconomic stability, consumer market size, growth, and openness.
The second pillar, &amp;ldquo;population,&amp;rdquo; delves into demographics to help businesses assess how their products or services align with the competitive landscape.
The third pillar, &amp;ldquo;access,&amp;rdquo; evaluates the ease of market entry.</description></item><item><title>Flat Rate vs Pay As You Go Conference Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-vs-pay-as-you-go-conference-calling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-vs-pay-as-you-go-conference-calling/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve already seen how conference calls and web conferencing can save your company a lot of money. So why worry about the small costs involved? Firstly, saving money is always a good thing. Secondly, the more affordable conference calls are, the more you can use them to boost productivity.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine AccuConference, a leading teleconferencing provider, and see their pricing options. AccuConference offers both flat rate and pay-as-you-go conference calls.</description></item><item><title>Using eConnect to import Analytical Accounting data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-econnect-to-import-analytical-accounting-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 17:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-econnect-to-import-analytical-accounting-data/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP, shares his insights on troubleshooting eConnect integrations, particularly when importing Dynamics GP transactions that include Analytical Accounting distributions.
Users successfully importing transactions might find that the associated Analytical Accounting data is missing in GP. This issue often stems from incorrect import procedures and misleading error messages from eConnect. To clarify, this article outlines how to correctly include Analytical Accounting data in an eConnect import.</description></item><item><title>Life is full of challenges, and then you have to deal with the third extension of EU membership.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This extension was unexpected. Despite the Benn Act, which mandated the Prime Minister to request a three-month extension for EU membership if Parliament failed to approve a withdrawal agreement by October 19, the Prime Minister insisted he would rather resign than comply. Fueled by ambiguous sources within Downing Street, there was persistent speculation that the Benn Act was unconstitutional, riddled with loopholes, would be superseded by emergency powers, or violated EU law.</description></item><item><title>Creating a RESTful JSON web service integration for Dynamics GP - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-a-restful-json-web-service-integration-for-dynamics-gp-part-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-a-restful-json-web-service-integration-for-dynamics-gp-part-1/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP and a Dynamics GP Certified IT Professional based in Los Angeles, recently completed a fascinating Dynamics GP integration project.
This project involved creating a RESTful JSON web service that enables a website to seamlessly integrate with Dynamics GP, Authorize.net, and the k-eCommerce/Azox Credit Card Extension. Given its role in handling sensitive credit card data, the web service prioritizes security by incorporating HMAC authentication, AES encryption, and operating exclusively over HTTPS.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs VPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</guid><description>Virtual Private Servers (VPS) offer a hosting solution for websites that have outgrown shared hosting but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for the cost and responsibility of a fully dedicated server. However, a new option allows for flexible scaling and a pay-as-you-go model: cloud server hosting.
Discussions about cloud computing versus managing your own data center are becoming increasingly common. However, many companies haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the stage where investing in a complete in-house data center is necessary.</description></item><item><title>The Hasso Plattner Institute is offering a free six-week MOOC on the Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hasso-plattner-institute-is-offering-a-free-six-week-mooc-on-the-internet/</guid><description>The Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) is offering a free, six-week online course in English about the fundamentals of the Internet. Starting on March 31st, HPI&amp;rsquo;s director, Professor Christoph Meinel, will teach participants about the technical basis of the Internet through a massive open online course (MOOC) titled &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Internetworking with TCP/IP.&amp;rdquo; The course is available to anyone and can be accessed through free registration.
Professor Meinel believes that anyone who uses the Internet for daily tasks like online shopping, reading news articles, or sending emails should understand the technologies that make these actions possible.</description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub.</description></item><item><title>EZVIZ introduces new action cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</guid><description>Source: EZVIZ. The FIVE action cam.
EZVIZ, a company specializing in Wi-Fi cloud cameras and video surveillance equipment, will introduce a new action camera series at CES 2016, designed for sports enthusiasts and content creators.
Priced at US$299.99, the EZVIZ FIVE action camera boasts an Ambarella A12 chipset, a built-in 2-inch IPS touchscreen with 320x240 resolution, a 900mAh battery, and the capability to record continuously at 4K resolution at 15 frames per second.</description></item><item><title>The DAG.exe in GP 2015 crashes due to the inability to load the type 'Microsoft.Dynamics.GP.BusinessObjects.Payroll.Timecard'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dag-exe-in-gp-2015-crashes-due-to-the-inability-to-load-the-type-microsoft-dynamics-gp-businessobjects-payroll-timecard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dag-exe-in-gp-2015-crashes-due-to-the-inability-to-load-the-type-microsoft-dynamics-gp-businessobjects-payroll-timecard/</guid><description>The Dynamics GP Visual Studio Tools &amp;ldquo;Dictionary Assembly Generator&amp;rdquo; (dag.exe) is a tool that I was aware of but hadn&amp;rsquo;t needed until a recent project. This project required me to access custom fields in modified GP windows.
I installed the VS Tools SDK on my GP 2015 server and ran the DAG. However, the DAG would crash during the &amp;ldquo;Generating IL code&amp;rdquo; step.
Even after upgrading to the latest hotfix, the issue persisted.</description></item><item><title>Resolve problems with Dynamics GP scaling and font size on high DPI screens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolve-problems-with-dynamics-gp-scaling-and-font-size-on-high-dpi-screens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolve-problems-with-dynamics-gp-scaling-and-font-size-on-high-dpi-screens/</guid><description>This blog has a new home at https://blog.steveendow.com/. Future posts will be published there.
Update: For those experiencing Remote Desktop difficulties with high DPI screens, Nathan Hayden from BKD has a helpful workaround available at: http://dynamicsinsights.com/2018/10/05/remote-desktop-high-dpi-dynamics-gp/
Modern Windows laptops and desktops with high-resolution or 4K displays often encounter display issues with some software. These &amp;ldquo;high DPI&amp;rdquo; screens can make text appear minuscule at full resolution. To counteract this, Windows uses &amp;ldquo;scaling&amp;rdquo; to enlarge text and graphics for readability and usability.</description></item><item><title>Sony Singapore's year-end promotions are valid until the beginning of January 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</guid><description>Are you looking for some of Sony&amp;rsquo;s top products from 2019? Here are a few:
Digital imaging
Sony A7 III
Source: Sony. The α7 III.
The A7 III boasts five-axis stabilization, 4D Focus for reliable focusing in low light (down to EV-3), and the capability to record 4K HDR videos.
Promotional price: S$2,699 (usual price S$2,899)
Sony α7 III with 35mm full-frame image sensor (ILCE7M3K) Sony RX100 VII
The compact RX100 VII features an extensive zoom range and remarkable speed.</description></item><item><title>Changes have been made to the User Setup window in GP 2013 R2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changes-have-been-made-to-the-user-setup-window-in-gp-2013-r2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:54:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changes-have-been-made-to-the-user-setup-window-in-gp-2013-r2/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
After installing GP 2013 R2, a few changes and new features are noticeable. One notable difference is the redesigned User Setup window.
GP 2013 SP2:
GP 2013 R2:
The R2 window features the noticeable ribbon at the top, a standard change in R2. Additionally, the User Setup window incorporates a few key additions.
User Type: This option, offering Full or Limited access, dictates user permissions. A Limited user is restricted to inquiries and reports.</description></item><item><title>Heineken 0.0 promotes inclusivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heineken-0-0-promotes-inclusivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:35:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heineken-0-0-promotes-inclusivity/</guid><description>Heineken 0.0 is available in Singapore.
Heineken 0.0, a non-alcoholic malt beverage with a unique recipe, launched in the US on January 9th. It boasts a distinct, balanced taste and contains only 69 calories per bottle (70 calories per 330ml can). Although announced back in May 2017, it is also currently available in Singapore. Heineken&amp;rsquo;s Master Brewers created this alcohol-free option using only natural ingredients.
Jonnie Cahill, CMO of HEINEKEN USA, believes Heineken 0.</description></item><item><title>Solstice Before The Solstice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait for the winter solstice to experience the Samsung Solstice, a touchscreen phone designed for social networking. This sleek phone boasts a vibrant 3-inch color touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable app widgets for easy access to platforms like Facebook and MySpace.
Staying connected is effortless with the Solstice&amp;rsquo;s virtual keyboard and high-resolution screen, perfect for messaging. Its slim, half-inch profile, achieved through advanced virtual technology, surpasses bulkier models with slide-out keyboards.</description></item><item><title>Do Dynamics GP upgrades still require a test environment?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-dynamics-gp-upgrades-still-require-a-test-environment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-dynamics-gp-upgrades-still-require-a-test-environment/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP, discusses the necessity of a test environment for &amp;ldquo;typical&amp;rdquo; Dynamics GP upgrades. He observes that while some customers have complex setups requiring thorough testing, many others have simpler environments where upgrading directly in production might be feasible.
Endow acknowledges that GP upgrades in the past were often complicated, necessitating a separate test server. However, he notes that Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Dynamics GP led to a streamlined and more reliable upgrade process.</description></item><item><title>The EC is proposing an AI Liability Directive to provide assistance.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ec-is-proposing-an-ai-liability-directive-to-provide-assistance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ec-is-proposing-an-ai-liability-directive-to-provide-assistance/</guid><description>Ida Varošanec (PhD student, University of Groningen) and Nynke Vellinga (post-doc researcher, University of Groningen)
Photo credit: Cryteria, via Wikimedia commons
1. Proposal Goals
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposal for an AI Liability Directive, published on September 28, 2022, alongside an updated Product Liability Directive, aims to address the risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) while acknowledging its potential benefits. The proposal stems from a report recognizing the potential harm AI systems can cause due to their connectivity, unpredictable nature, and opacity, which makes it difficult to assign responsibility for AI-related incidents.</description></item><item><title>Tea Forté Singapore presents three mooncake collections as part of the Autumn in Abundance series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</guid><description>Source: Tea Forté.
Tea Forté Singapore, a specialty tea company, has introduced its new Autumn in Abundance mooncake collection, featuring traditional baked mooncakes with reduced sugar, the Creative Infused line, and a special Luxury selection.
The company suggests pairing the traditional mooncakes with its organic white ginger pear tea, the Creative Infused collection with the organic green mango peach tea, and the Luxurious selections with its orchid vanilla tea.</description></item><item><title>Styletag is known for identifying the latest fashion trends globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</guid><description>Want to stay stylish at work? South Korea&amp;rsquo;s SK Planet has refreshed its Styletag mobile app using trends from New York Fashion Week, which wrapped up on February 13th.
Source: Styletag page at the Play Store
Styletag gathers and organizes user-submitted fashion content worldwide, offering both style inspiration and shopping details. The app includes contributions from professional photographers, amateur enthusiasts, and invited fashion experts.
This free app is compatible with iOS 7 (iPad, iPhone, and iPod) via iTunes and Android devices through the Google Play store.</description></item><item><title>Do crime victims now have additional rights under EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
*This analysis is taken from the upcoming 4th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Victims of crime are often disheartened not just by the crime itself but also by the criminal justice system&amp;rsquo;s indifference to their needs. To tackle this issue, the EU introduced a Directive on crime victims’ rights in 2012 that Member States were required to implement by November 16, 2015. This law supersedes an earlier Framework Decision on this matter from 2001.</description></item><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints.</description></item><item><title>The FastGig app has been released to connect flexible workers with job opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</guid><description>FastCo, the company known for its Asian non-executive job platform FastJobs, has launched FastGig, an app designed for the expanding gig economy. FastCo claims this is one of the first apps specifically for gig workers in Southeast Asia.
FastGig, operating as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first workforce-as-a-service (WaaS) platform, connects skilled flexible workers with companies facing staffing shortages, particularly during peak seasons.
Julian Tan, FastCo&amp;rsquo;s Founder &amp;amp; CEO, highlights FastGig as a solution to a significant market gap, providing flexibility for both workers and businesses and transforming Singapore&amp;rsquo;s gig economy.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls.</description></item><item><title>Identifying SQL Server Users without a Corresponding Login</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-sql-server-users-without-a-corresponding-login/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-sql-server-users-without-a-corresponding-login/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s imagine two situations: First, you set up a test Dynamics GP server for a client by installing SQL Server and Dynamics GP, then restoring database copies. Second, a client&amp;rsquo;s Dynamics GP SQL server crashes, you rebuild it, and restore databases from backups.
Both scenarios present a common problem: restoring a database from one SQL Server to another doesn&amp;rsquo;t transfer the associated SQL Server logins.
Scenario 1 offers a solution: a &amp;ldquo;Capture Logins&amp;rdquo; script (KB 878449) efficiently transfers SQL logins to the new server.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Massachusetts - First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from a Massachusetts customer for a complete restoration. Thankfully, it was properly packaged and arrived without damage.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s dust cover shows typical signs of use, but it will be replaced with a new one. The aluminum surfaces are in good shape overall.
However, there are some minor flaws. The keypad has a corner ding, suggesting it might have come loose during past transportation. Additionally, there are small scratches on the aluminum, possibly from the keypad moving around.</description></item><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?</description></item><item><title>SQL script for verifying Dynamics GP GL batch control totals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-script-for-verifying-dynamics-gp-gl-batch-control-totals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-script-for-verifying-dynamics-gp-gl-batch-control-totals/</guid><description>A customer encountered a bug in their Dynamics GP integration that caused discrepancies between the actual number of imported GL transactions and the batch control totals. To identify these discrepancies, a SQL query was created to compare the number of GL transactions and JE totals with the batch control totals stored in SY00500.
The query utilizes a Common Table Expression (CTE) to efficiently calculate and compare the data. This approach helps pinpoint differences between the expected transaction count and total amount against the recorded batch control totals.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade Your Business Image</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-business-image/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:47:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-business-image/</guid><description>Your image as a business professional is largely controlled by your company when you work for a large corporation. However, as a small business owner, independent sales agent, or consultant, you are responsible for managing your own image. One important aspect of this is your business card.
The design and printing of your business card contribute to a polished and professional look, but an unprofessional email address can quickly ruin that impression.</description></item><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013.</description></item><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>600,000 Inquiries, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</guid><description>Purchasing important items can be a hassle, especially telecommunications services. It&amp;rsquo;s a maze of confusing calls, endless hold music, and tedious forms with long wait times.
But imagine getting a price for a T1 line or finding nearby Metro Ethernet services in under a minute, any time, day or night. That&amp;rsquo;s where GeoQuote (tm) comes in. This innovative telecom pricing application is changing how businesses buy voice and data services.</description></item><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>Delicious Medallions from Swensen's</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</guid><description>Swensen&amp;rsquo;s is offering early bird discounts on their chocolate-covered Sweet Medallions mooncakes until September 20th, 2017.
The mooncakes are available in a variety of flavors like cookies &amp;rsquo;n cream surprise, durian royale, Rocher crunch, and sticky chewy chocolate.
Source: Swensen&amp;rsquo;s website. Four chocolate-covered flavours are on offer in Swensen&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017. Place your order to take advantage of the 20% early bird discount available to Swensen&amp;rsquo;s Cool Rewards and Kids&amp;rsquo; Club members.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning of the Tone Arm Carriage Position Switches and a Non-Returning Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</guid><description>As a preliminary step in the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I chose to verify the functionality of its control system. Prior testing had shown that the arm carriage would not return to its home position when moved across the platter without a record in place. Instead, it would travel to the center of the platter and stop. Ideally, the carriage should trigger the End Switch (ES) at this point and subsequently return to its home position on the right, turning off the turntable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>The release of eConnect 2010 Service Pack 1 is now available!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-release-of-econnect-2010-service-pack-1-is-now-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:34:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-release-of-econnect-2010-service-pack-1-is-now-available/</guid><description>Dynamics GP 2010 Service Pack 1 is now available. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to review the details before installation.
https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/downloads/servicepacks/mdgp2010_patchreleases.htm
More importantly, eConnect 2010 Service Pack 1 has also been released.
https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/downloads/servicepacks/MDGP2010_eConnectservicepackshotfixes
The update includes separate files for x86 and x64 systems.
While the list of fixes is not yet available, this update will likely be applied to GP 2010 development servers shortly.</description></item><item><title>The six-port USB desktop charger solves all your charging problems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</guid><description>Poweradd, a company known for its mobile device accessories, has introduced a new six-port desktop USB charger with a 50W capacity. This charger is designed to meet the growing demand for charging multiple devices simultaneously when outlets are limited.
The compact charger measures 4&amp;quot; x 2.9&amp;quot; x 1&amp;quot; and supports voltages from 100V to 240V, making it suitable for international use. It features two ports that provide 2.4A, two ports with 2.</description></item><item><title>Adidas Originals is reintroducing the Superstar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</guid><description>Source: adidas.
This year, adidas Originals launches a campaign exploring the meaning of being a superstar, coinciding with the anniversary of the iconic Superstar shoe, first released in 1969.
A short film by adidas Originals, directed by Karim Huu Do, examines what it means to be a superstar in 2015. Footballer David Beckham states, &amp;ldquo;It’s not about trying to be the next big thing.&amp;rdquo; Entertainer Pharrell Williams believes &amp;ldquo;It’s not about the number of views, likes or shares.</description></item><item><title>Should User Account Control be disabled?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-user-account-control-be-disabled/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-user-account-control-be-disabled/</guid><description>Increasingly, as clients transition to Windows 7 or Vista, user account control issues are becoming more prevalent in Dynamics GP support, particularly with Dynamics GP Utilities. Users frequently encounter BCP utility errors after successfully launching utilities and logging in.
A quick fix is to launch Dynamics GP Utilities as an administrator. While this is straightforward, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed a concerning trend of simply recommending the disabling of user account control altogether. This approach raises concerns for me.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): Removing the Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Note: This post documents an outdated method. There&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way to remove the drive that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve lifting the Pre-Amplifier board or disconnecting the solenoid linkage. See my later post for the updated procedure.
Following advice from &amp;lsquo;chartz&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;sonavor&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org (link to thread), I began replacing the belts in my Beocord 5000 (4716), which had become loose and stretched over time.
The first step is removing the drive mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Acronis has launched Blockchain-supported data protection through Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-launched-blockchain-supported-data-protection-through-acronis-true-image-2017-new-generation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-launched-blockchain-supported-data-protection-through-acronis-true-image-2017-new-generation/</guid><description>Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation offers four key advantages: comprehensive backup, Blockchain-based authentication to ensure data integrity, protection against ransomware, and secure e-signatures.
Acronis, a global provider of hybrid-cloud data protection and storage solutions, has introduced Acronis True Image 2017 New Generation. This release builds upon the existing backup features of Acronis True Image with three significant additions:
Acronis Active Protection safeguards user data against ransomware attacks in real time.</description></item><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>India and Bangladesh have initiated connectivity projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</guid><description>The Prime Ministers of India and Bangladesh, Narendra Modi and Sheikh Hasina, respectively, along with West Bengal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Minister, Mamata Banerjee, inaugurated multiple connectivity initiatives between the two nations.
These projects include the inauguration of the second Bhairab and Titas Railway Bridges, situated on the 320-km Dhaka-Chittagong railway line in Bangladesh. Additionally, the International Rail Passenger Terminus in Kolkata, India, was also inaugurated.
The dignitaries also launched the first run of the Bandhan Express, connecting Kolkata to Khulna in southwest Bangladesh, covering a distance of over 150km.</description></item><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light.</description></item><item><title>BEAM offers self-storage services in Singapore through a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beam-offers-self-storage-services-in-singapore-through-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>BEAM, a new self-storage company, has launched in Singapore, offering a unique approach to traditional storage solutions. Their services are managed entirely through a mobile app.
Unlike conventional self-storage providers that lease fixed spaces, BEAM offers flexible per-item storage. This means users only pay for the space their belongings occupy, eliminating wasted costs. Additionally, while traditional facilities are often inconveniently located, BEAM provides free pick-up and delivery to their secure 6,000 sq ft facility, equipped with CCTV and access control.</description></item><item><title>Delta is launching Delta Innovation Classes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines has devised a novel method for premium customers to distinguish themselves and share contact information, using a compelling offer.
As stated on the Delta Innovation Class website, the airline is offering a &amp;ldquo;mentoring program – that just so happens to take place at 35,000 feet.&amp;rdquo;
This program, Delta Innovation Class, a play on flight classes, gives one fortunate customer a complimentary seat next to a notable figure or celebrity on a designated flight.</description></item><item><title>Business Telephone Systems Hosted VoIP Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes have various choices for their telephone systems. Small businesses can buy systems from local stores, while medium-sized businesses often work with contractors for key telephone systems or small PBXs. Larger companies may have internal teams that handle complex telephone systems. Nowadays, hosted VoIP is a cost-effective option for companies of all sizes.
How can one solution meet the needs of different-sized businesses affordably? It&amp;rsquo;s not a one-size-fits-all solution but a scalable technology adaptable to different demands—hosted VoIP, also known as hosted PBX or cloud telephone systems.</description></item><item><title>What is the purpose of using the system password in Dynamics GP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-purpose-of-using-the-system-password-in-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-purpose-of-using-the-system-password-in-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>A client recently brought up the Dynamics GP System Password, a feature I find comparable to User Classes – widely used in the past but less common in modern implementations. For those unfamiliar, the System Password in Dynamics GP (found under Administration Page &amp;gt; Setup &amp;gt; System Password) safeguards all system menus (Setup, Cards, Reports, etc.) with a password. This means users need to enter the password to access these windows, even if they technically have permission.</description></item><item><title>Tableau offers free data visualization for iPad users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-offers-free-data-visualization-for-ipad-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:55:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-offers-free-data-visualization-for-ipad-users/</guid><description>Tableau Software released Vizable, a free mobile app designed for iPad, that allows users to visualize and understand data.
Vizable makes data analysis accessible to a wider audience. The app enables users to interact with data through gestures like pinching, swiping, and dragging to create visualizations within seconds.
&amp;ldquo;There isn&amp;rsquo;t a great app that allows you to visually analyze a spreadsheet using only a tablet,&amp;rdquo; says Dave Story, Tableau&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Mobile and Strategic Growth.</description></item><item><title>What qualities define exceptional training?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:35:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading training sessions, including a Dynamics GP Distribution Partner Academy and a customized Forecaster training. These distinct classes got me thinking about the elements of exceptional training and what makes it truly valuable. I&amp;rsquo;d love to share my thoughts and hear yours!
Relevant Content: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for training content to align with student needs. While this can be challenging with pre-determined classes, instructors can bridge the gap by connecting content to real-world scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Main PCB and Installation of a Biasing Trimmer for TR3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</guid><description>After getting the Beogram 4002 (5513) operational again, I focused on fully restoring the main PCB. This involved installing a trimmer to correctly calibrate TR3, the transistor responsible for amplifying the signal from the record detection sensor. The board&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown below:
The RPM relay and trimmers had already been replaced by the owner. I finished the restoration by replacing all electrolytic capacitors
and adding a trimmer to enable bias adjustment at the base of TR3.</description></item><item><title>SmartList Builder and SQL Tables/Views</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-builder-and-sql-tables-views/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:57:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-builder-and-sql-tables-views/</guid><description>Many of you may already know this, but I encountered a problem this week deploying a SmartList Builder item. Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened:
I created two SQL views based on GP and custom tables. I granted the SmartList Builder access to these views (Tools &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder &amp;raquo; Security &amp;raquo; SQL Table Security). I created my SmartList (Tools &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder). After testing, the SmartList worked correctly. I deployed the views to the client&amp;rsquo;s environment.</description></item><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce.</description></item><item><title>Users of Forecaster and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>Have you ever encountered a problem where you vaguely recall a solution but can&amp;rsquo;t seem to locate the specific article or link? This happened to me recently with a client attempting to use their Dynamics GP user ID for Forecaster 7. As expected, it was unsuccessful due to GP&amp;rsquo;s encryption method when generating user IDs in SQL. This encryption prevents the same ID from functioning in Forecaster, even with proper database permissions.</description></item><item><title>3x3 Mbps Ethernet Doubles Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t benefit from additional internet speed? Websites, software, and files continue to grow larger, but unfortunately, technology budgets haven&amp;rsquo;t kept pace. Imagine doubling your internet speed without increasing your current expenses – an appealing proposition, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
It might sound illogical to suggest that doubling your internet speed wouldn&amp;rsquo;t cost more, especially since internet providers aren&amp;rsquo;t known for giving things away for free. The secret lies in adopting newer, more cost-effective technology instead of simply replacing your existing service with an identical one from another provider.</description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing the most rapid growth for SWIFT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</guid><description>SWIFT, a financial messaging service, has announced a significant increase in new corporate clients from the Asia Pacific region between May and December 2015, with 29 new companies joining the network.
SWIFT provides a unified platform for corporations to communicate financial information with their banks globally, leading to enhanced visibility and more efficient treasury operations. This connection allows for greater automation and standardization of financial processes. Currently, over 1,500 corporate groups, representing roughly 30,000 entities, utilize SWIFT to manage their banking relationships worldwide.</description></item><item><title>IT Departments are Wearin' the Green</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</guid><description>Maintaining IT budgets requires more than just good fortune these days. Many companies are discovering that environmentally friendly practices can save them money. These eco-conscious choices benefit both the planet and their bottom line.
One of the first areas to examine is electricity consumption. Power usage can be deceptive because it often occurs in small, unnoticeable increments. Every desktop computer, even when idle, contributes to the overall energy use, measured in watt-hours and kilowatt-hours.</description></item><item><title>The discussion on drones in the UK and its impact on the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 05:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</guid><description>By Chris Jones
A new report, Back from the battlefield: domestic drones in the UK, investigates the use of drones by public and private entities in the UK. It focuses on law enforcement and border control agencies, examining the laws, regulations, and public and private funding surrounding drone technology development. The report analyzes the current situation and potential future applications, advocating for public discussion and decision-making before widespread drone use, particularly for surveillance, becomes commonplace.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Xiaomi's latest flagship smartphone is the MIX Fold 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:33:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</guid><description>Source: Xiaomi. The MIX Fold 2 is available in Black and Gold colourways.
Xiaomi recently debuted its most advanced foldable phone, the Xiaomi MIX Fold 2, in Mainland China. The company also introduced the Xiaomi Pad 5 Pro, Redmi K50 Ultra, and a variety of other ecosystem devices.
When unfolded, the Xiaomi MIX Fold 2 measures a mere 5.4mm1, providing a seamless viewing experience across its inner and outer screens.</description></item><item><title>Store Your Files For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</guid><description>With the current state of the economy, you&amp;rsquo;d expect the best price for file storage to be free – and you&amp;rsquo;d be right! Anything more would be asking too much.
Of course, this applies to storing digital files, not physical ones. Don&amp;rsquo;t show up at a self-storage facility with boxes of papers expecting free storage – they won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to show you the door!
Instead, try storing your computer files for free with Mozy (http://www.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Border and Coast Guard a completely new entity or just a revamped version of Frontex?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</guid><description>Herbert Rosenfeldt, Research Assistant and PhD candidate, University of Passau
Introduction
Celebrating the new European Border and Coast Guard Agency, also known as Frontex, at the Bulgarian external border with Turkey might seem like an odd festivity. However, last Thursday, high-ranking EU and Member State officials gathered at Bulgaria&amp;rsquo;s Kapitan Andreevo Border Checkpoint for this inauguration. This event marked the implementation of the European Border and Coast Guard Regulation, a significant step towards strengthening external border control in the wake of recent migration challenges.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to suspend Schengen due to Greece? Is it necessary to do so?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</guid><description>A recent leak of a Council document proposes a potential suspension of the Schengen system for a duration of up to two years. This proposal stems from what are being termed &amp;ldquo;systemic deficiencies&amp;rdquo; in Greece&amp;rsquo;s management of its external borders, particularly concerning the influx of refugees and migrants. Such a suspension would provide any Schengen country the option to reinstate or implement border controls along their shared internal borders. While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely that every Schengen country would exercise this option, it&amp;rsquo;s anticipated that several would choose to do so, especially given that a number already have active border controls in place.</description></item><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages.</description></item><item><title>Disable all Dynamics GP posting reports in the Fabrikam test company.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disable-all-dynamics-gp-posting-reports-in-the-fabrikam-test-company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:06:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disable-all-dynamics-gp-posting-reports-in-the-fabrikam-test-company/</guid><description>Steve Endow
No More Clicking &amp;ldquo;Cancel&amp;rdquo; Update: Victoria Yudin accurately pointed out that posting reports are sometimes useful or even necessary, for example, in training or when troubleshooting errors. She&amp;rsquo;s absolutely right - posting reports are definitely needed in certain situations, even in Fabrikam. I personally disabled posting reports in my testing environment because I frequently run repetitive tests on batch posting for my projects. I already know that my data, transactions, and postings are all accurate.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new, healthier menu choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has partnered with the Department of Health – Abu Dhabi to introduce Weqaya, a selection of healthy food choices, on flights and in its Abu Dhabi lounges.
Weqaya, meaning &amp;ldquo;prevention&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, is a program created by the Department of Health - Abu Dhabi to encourage healthy and balanced eating habits for improved health and well-being.
Etihad now offers several Weqaya dishes on First and Business Class long-haul and ultra-long-haul flights departing from Abu Dhabi.</description></item><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider.</description></item><item><title>What Is Toll Free?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-toll-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-toll-free/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;toll free number&amp;rdquo; is widely recognized, with most people having used one. But what exactly does it mean and how do businesses acquire them?
Unlike standard phone numbers automatically assigned with landline, VoIP, or cellular services, toll free numbers require a separate process. In the US and Canada, phone numbers follow the North American Numbering Plan (NANP) format: 1-NPA-NXX-XXXX.
In this format, &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo; represents the country code, NPA stands for Numbering Plan Area (area code), and the remaining digits are unique to your line.</description></item><item><title>The LG Stylus 2 will make its first appearance at MWC 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</guid><description>LG will introduce the LG Stylus 2 at the upcoming Mobile World Congress 2016 in Barcelona, Spain.
Source: LG. The LG Stylus 2.
The LG Stylus 2 is slimmer and lighter than its predecessor, measuring 7.4mm thick and weighing 145g. This follow-up to the G4 Stylus boasts a 5.7&amp;quot; HD display for an enhanced viewing experience.
Using the LG Stylus 2 mimics the experience of writing with a traditional pen and notepad.</description></item><item><title>The Hyper-V virtual machine running Server 2012 R2 is unable to start and displays an error message stating "We were unable to finish the updates.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyper-v-virtual-machine-running-server-2012-r2-is-unable-to-start-and-displays-an-error-message-stating-we-were-unable-to-finish-the-updates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 18:22:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyper-v-virtual-machine-running-server-2012-r2-is-unable-to-start-and-displays-an-error-message-stating-we-were-unable-to-finish-the-updates/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
While attempting to set up the GP 2016 Web Client on a new Server 2012 R2 virtual machine, I encountered an error message stating &amp;ldquo;We couldn&amp;rsquo;t complete the updates. Undoing changes.&amp;rdquo; The VM became unresponsive.
After some searching, I came across a TechNet forum thread discussing similar issues with Windows 8. Unfortunately, the suggested fix of disabling Secure Boot on the VM was unsuccessful in my case.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>Strategies For The Hunkered Down Economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</guid><description>While the new year has arrived, the economic situation remains challenging. Unemployment is still high, companies are focusing on cost-cutting over revenue growth, and uncertainty about the future persists. Consumers are tightening their belts and spending less, leaving businesses with little choice but to do the same. It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to hesitate before making significant moves when the path ahead is unclear.
Does this mean your business is stuck or in irreversible decline?</description></item><item><title>The Legal Standing of a Third Country before the CJEU: AG Hogan's Opinion in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council in Relation to State Immunity and Comity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
In a legal opinion issued on February 20, 2021, Advocate General Hogan addressed a crucial procedural issue: Can a non-EU country legally challenge EU actions before the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)? This question holds significance because the Court has never directly ruled on it within the context of sanctions, and it delves into the principles governing the relationship between EU law and other international law subjects.</description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore.</description></item><item><title>Conference 2016: Redeeming The Dirt</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-2016-redeeming-the-dirt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-2016-redeeming-the-dirt/</guid><description>Dateline: 23 August 2016 AD
Noah Sanders, who wrote Born-Again Dirt: Farming to the Glory of God, is hosting another one of his Redeeming The Dirt conferences in Alabama.
Brian Oldreive, the founder of Foundations For Farming, will be speaking at the conference. Foundations For Farming is a Christian ministry based in Africa that teaches people, mainly the poor, how to become self-sufficient through growing their own food. I&amp;rsquo;ve written about Foundations For Farming several times on my previous blog.</description></item><item><title>Scale Into Toll Free Number Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scale-into-toll-free-number-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 01:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scale-into-toll-free-number-service/</guid><description>You might be considering toll-free numbers for your business, but the cost and commitment feel like a gamble. What if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work out as planned?
Instead of a large investment, try a trial run with a single toll-free number. This allows you to experience the features and benefits without a major financial commitment.
Kall8 offers a scalable toll-free service ideal for businesses of all sizes. Manage your numbers and settings easily through their online platform.</description></item><item><title>Update the notes in Dynamics GP through an eConnect integration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-the-notes-in-dynamics-gp-through-an-econnect-integration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-the-notes-in-dynamics-gp-through-an-econnect-integration/</guid><description>Steve Endow
While I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with eConnect integrations extensively, I recently encountered a situation where I needed to update existing Dynamics GP Note records. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recall having done this before, and online searches didn&amp;rsquo;t provide any solutions. If you know of an easier approach, please share, as I&amp;rsquo;m curious if I&amp;rsquo;ve overlooked something.
Let&amp;rsquo;s imagine your .NET eConnect integration needs to update a customer&amp;rsquo;s address and phone number, and simultaneously append an update message to the existing customer note.</description></item><item><title>NIST has chosen the SHA-3 cryptographic hash.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nist-has-chosen-the-sha-3-cryptographic-hash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:52:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nist-has-chosen-the-sha-3-cryptographic-hash/</guid><description>The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) has chosen the &amp;ldquo;Keccak&amp;rdquo; algorithm as the new SHA-3 cryptographic hash algorithm.
Notably, Bruce Schneier, a finalist in the SHA-3 competition, recently expressed his opinion that NIST should not select any of the candidate algorithms.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with cryptographic hash algorithms, the Wikipedia page on the subject provides a clear explanation.
Simply put, they are essential for computer security.
_Steve Endow is a Dynamics GP Certified Trainer and Dynamics GP Certified IT Professional in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item></channel></rss>