<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:05:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Jewish heritage of Thomas Matthew Crooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jewish-heritage-of-thomas-matthew-crooks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jewish-heritage-of-thomas-matthew-crooks/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/nR7lbvh.png" alt="Featured image of post The Jewish heritage of Thomas Matthew Crooks" />Thomas Matthew Crooks was born in September 2003, making him 20 years old today. He resides with his parents, Matthew and Mary, who are in their 50s. The Crooks family is deeply religious and observes Jewish traditions and practices devoutly. Faith plays a significant role in their lives, guiding their values and shaping their worldview.
Family Background Matthew Brian and Mary Elizabeth, the parents of Thomas, have a rich Jewish heritage passed down through their Scottish and English ancestry.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Free Twitter Followers Every Hour Using Toolkity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 17:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/NhEKjvI.png" alt="Featured image of post How to Get Free Twitter Followers Every Hour Using Toolkity" />Social media presence is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age. Having a robust Twitter following can enhance your online visibility, influence, and credibility. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to grow your Twitter followers without spending a dime, Toolkity offers a simple solution. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to get free Twitter followers every hour using Toolkity.
Step 1: Visit Toolkity&amp;rsquo;s Free Twitter Followers Page First, head over to Toolkity&amp;rsquo;s Free Twitter Followers page.</description></item><item><title>Overview and analysis of the relaunched negotiations for EU accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The potential inclusion of the EU into the ECHR has been a long-awaited development. With the necessary Treaty modifications in the Lisbon Treaty and a negotiated accession treaty by 2013, it appeared that the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s December 2014 ruling would solidify this union. However, the Court&amp;rsquo;s judgment (Opinion 2/13), which was subject to criticism on this blog, unexpectedly disrupted the accession process.
However, the process was resurrected in 2019 and has advanced quickly since then.</description></item><item><title>Running SQL DDL scripts using a Dynamics GP VS Tools AddIn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/running-sql-ddl-scripts-using-a-dynamics-gp-vs-tools-addin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 01:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/running-sql-ddl-scripts-using-a-dynamics-gp-vs-tools-addin/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP, shares his insights on deploying SQL scripts with Visual Studio Tools AddIns for Dynamics GP. He highlights the challenge of managing complex queries and Data Definition Language (DDL) scripts during deployment, especially for customizations requiring custom tables in multiple company databases.
Endow emphasizes the convenience of deploying AddIns by simply copying the DLL file and seeks to automate SQL script execution. He introduces a method to check for table existence and addresses the limitation of ADO.</description></item><item><title>What impact could Brexit have on the younger generation? EU Referendum Briefing 2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A UK exit from the European Union, or &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; could have significant implications for young people, impacting their education, travel opportunities, and economic prospects.
Education
The EU does not control educational content or matters like tuition costs. Instead, its involvement lies in cross-border educational aspects, including promoting student and teacher mobility through initiatives like the Erasmus program. Established in 1987, this EU law-based program facilitates student exchanges across various educational levels.</description></item><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use.</description></item><item><title>Turning Junk Frequencies Into Gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/turning-junk-frequencies-into-gold/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/turning-junk-frequencies-into-gold/</guid><description>The 2.4 GHz WiFi band we use every day wasn&amp;rsquo;t originally designed for WiFi at all. It was part of the ISM band - Industrial, Scientific, and Medical - a section of the radio spectrum designated for devices that unintentionally emit radiation as a byproduct of their operation. These bands, ranging from 6.78 MHz to 245 GHz, were meant for devices like microwave ovens, industrial heaters, and medical equipment.
The 2.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some Cabinet Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I made progress reassembling the Beogram 4002, focusing on the cabinet trim and deck cover. To prevent damage, I had previously removed the rosewood trim.
The trim is attached to a metal frame that slides in and out to lock and unlock the cabinet. This frame relies on five guide washers, which are commonly broken in Beogram 4002 units. This one was no different. These washers have a unique design, as detailed in a past Beolover blog post.</description></item><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage.</description></item><item><title>Webinars diving deep into GP 2010</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webinars-diving-deep-into-gp-2010/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on in-depth GP 2010 webinars for Microsoft Certified Trainers (MCTs) and Partners. These webinars offer step-by-step guidance on setting up and using the new features in GP 2010. As a bonus, all were created and presented by MCTs. Check them out – we hope they help you get your clients ready for GP 2010!
Business Intelligence &amp;amp; Reporting (This one is mine!)
This demonstration-based presentation covers the setup and use of new reporting and business intelligence enhancements in Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010.</description></item><item><title>VPN Internet Access Links Facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpn-internet-access-links-facilities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpn-internet-access-links-facilities/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations into a unified network can be a costly endeavor. While traditional solutions like private lines and Frame Relay have their merits, a newer method is gaining traction, especially for businesses with numerous sites.
Private lines offer unparalleled reliability, consistent bandwidth, and robust security due to their dedicated nature. They are well-suited for connecting phone systems or transmitting video between locations. However, the need for a separate line between each pair of sites makes them expensive, particularly as the network expands.</description></item><item><title>Can Hotels Afford to Upgrade Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hotels-afford-to-upgrade-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 19:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hotels-afford-to-upgrade-bandwidth/</guid><description>Hotels and motels face a challenge: guests love fast internet, but providing it is expensive. Upgrading bandwidth seems like the obvious solution, but it&amp;rsquo;s costly, especially since guests expect free Wi-Fi.
While it seems logical that faster internet costs more, that&amp;rsquo;s not always true. Hotels can sometimes secure better internet speeds for less money. This depends on where they get their internet service and the age of their contracts.
The internet landscape has changed rapidly.</description></item><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation.</description></item><item><title>The Great Repeal Bill and the Legacy of Henry VIII: Threatening Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</guid><description>Joelle Grogan, Lecturer, Middlesex University
The Great Repeal Bill is ironically named because it won&amp;rsquo;t actually repeal much EU law. Instead, when Brexit concludes, it will initially shift existing EU law into British law. While this maintains some stability during the transition, the bill also includes a concerning element: a Henry VIII clause. This clause, named after the king who gave himself sweeping legislative power, allows the government to alter primary legislation with minimal parliamentary scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Alternate "Circuit Diagram 2" with 24V Scale Illumination Lamps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-alternate-circuit-diagram-2-with-24v-scale-illumination-lamps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-alternate-circuit-diagram-2-with-24v-scale-illumination-lamps/</guid><description>I recently acquired a well-preserved Beogram 4000 service manual containing a unique supplementary diagram. This diagram, Circuit Diagram 2, outlines the control system and features a notable difference in the position scale illumination. Instead of the typical two 12V bulbs wired in series, it depicts two 24V bulbs connected in parallel to the 24V power source.
This discovery complicated a recent interaction with Sonavor, who is currently restoring his own Beogram 4000.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the RAM Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 utilizes a 3V battery to power its 16-word memory chip, an MCM144102, which is described as a peripheral memory unit in the Motorola 6804 manual but lacks readily available detailed specifications. This chip is responsible for storing calibration data and potentially the system time, although further investigation is required. A visual representation of the circuit is included below.
A positive aspect of the design is the inclusion of diode D27, which safeguards the battery against reverse polarity connection.</description></item><item><title>When Dial-Up Internet Service Makes Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-dial-up-internet-service-makes-sense/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 04:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-dial-up-internet-service-makes-sense/</guid><description>While many have transitioned to residential broadband and dedicated business internet, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that approximately half of US internet users still rely on dial-up. Despite its age, dial-up has significantly improved and remains a viable option for many, even in professional settings.
Is dial-up outdated? Not really. Consider how you would access email or websites during a broadband outage. Even the most reliable DSL and cable providers experience occasional disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Error in Integration Manager eConnect Adapter: SQL Exception occurred in the GetNextNumber method.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-integration-manager-econnect-adapter-sql-exception-occurred-in-the-getnextnumber-method/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-integration-manager-econnect-adapter-sql-exception-occurred-in-the-getnextnumber-method/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
While testing the eConnect GetNextNumber methods in Integration Manager, I encountered an error. My simple GL transaction import, using the eConnect destination adapter, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t run. After several minutes, I stopped the process, and eventually, an error message appeared indicating a SQL Exception in the GetNextNumber method.
[Image]
My initial troubleshooting, including checking SQL Server for errors, running a SQL Profiler trace, and monitoring SQL Activity, yielded no clues.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Lubrication of Platter Motor Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the DC motor was lubricated. This particular motor uses brushes and has simple sleeve bearings.
To access the bearings for lubrication, the pulley and outer housing were removed. The pulley is attached to the shaft with glue, allowing for easy removal. After taking out two small screws, the housing can be opened and the motor taken out.
Next, the black rubber vibration insulation boot was removed, revealing the circuit board connected to the brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer.</description></item><item><title>Samsung MM-A940 Two Megapixel Camera Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-mm-a940-two-megapixel-camera-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-mm-a940-two-megapixel-camera-phone/</guid><description>We regret to inform you that the Samsung MM-A940 special offer is no longer active. To discover the latest enticing cell phone promotions, including those featuring complimentary phones, we recommend utilizing our Cell Phone Plan Finder. This tool will guide you towards the leading phone choices and their corresponding wireless plans.
The realms of cell phones and digital cameras are converging with the emergence of the Samsung MM-A940 camera phone. In contrast to most cameraphones equipped with VGA or, at best, 1.</description></item><item><title>Push The Zone" - A Fresh Read for Gardeners by David The Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/push-the-zone-a-fresh-read-for-gardeners-by-david-the-good/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 18:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/push-the-zone-a-fresh-read-for-gardeners-by-david-the-good/</guid><description>Dateline: 27 January 2017
David The Good&amp;rsquo;s latest book, Push The Zone, is out now on Amazon. I finished reading it this morning and really enjoyed it (Click Here for details).
The book&amp;rsquo;s introduction provides a solid overview, which I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize in the following paragraphs:
This book won&amp;rsquo;t perform miracles, such as teaching you to cultivate limes in Minnesota or cocoa in Manhattan. It also won&amp;rsquo;t help with your dating life, but you probably already knew that.</description></item><item><title>How the EU Migration and Asylum Pact Can Address its Blind Spot on Statelessness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</guid><description>Chris Nash, the Director of the European Network on Statelessness, highlights their recent analysis of the EU Pact on Migration and Asylum. The analysis focuses on how the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposals within the Pact could affect the fundamental rights of stateless migrants and refugees. It offers suggestions for addressing these concerns during Pact negotiations and implementation.
The Pact, as it stands, fails to directly address the rights of stateless individuals or offer solutions to the specific protection issues they encounter.</description></item><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk.</description></item><item><title>Vote MPLS &amp; Ethernet for Better Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</guid><description>The 2008 election season is upon us. To determine which candidates best serve your interests, we suggest considering MPLS and Ethernet for reliable bandwidth, improved performance, and reduced costs over 1-3 years. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into their platforms to see if they deserve your vote.
IP Networking is currently the leading technology. Initially confined to local offices, IP has expanded to WANs at state, regional, and national levels. Today, almost all network designs are centered around IP or Internet Protocol.</description></item><item><title>Sipping on the Trunk Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</guid><description>The history of telephone trunks goes back to the early days of telephones. Trunks are lines that carry multiple phone conversations, initially connecting switchboards and switching offices. They&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from wire bundles to analog and now digital circuits, with T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and SONET being common digital trunking services. However, SIP trunking is emerging as a popular alternative.
Telephone trunking saves money by combining multiple phone lines into a single high-bandwidth connection.</description></item><item><title>Samsung D307 is Built For Messaging</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-d307-is-built-for-messaging/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 08:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-d307-is-built-for-messaging/</guid><description>We apologize, but the Samsung D307 is no longer available. To explore the latest cell phone deals and free phone offers, use our convenient Cell Phone Plan Finder.
The Samsung D307 combines the functionality of a computer, phone, and personal stenographer. This phone is perfect for those who prioritize messaging.
While many phones offer texting, it&amp;rsquo;s often cumbersome due to limited keys and multiple functions. Alternatively, bulky PDA-style phones are available but not pocket-friendly.</description></item><item><title>A Thousand VARs Can't Be Wrong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-thousand-vars-cant-be-wrong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 04:32:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-thousand-vars-cant-be-wrong/</guid><description>Telarus, the parent company of Shop For T1 and the VAR Network, has recruited over 1,000 Value Added Resellers (VARs), according to Chief Technical Officer Patrick Oborn. This is a significant achievement in the telecommunications industry, which is characterized by independent small businesses. The key motivators for telephone system installers and network consultants to join this nationwide database are customer leads and residual income.
Businesses specializing in computer network and telephone sales and service usually operate locally or regionally.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Capacitor Replacement on Unit #2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</guid><description>The first Beomaster 1900 receiver is fully operational and undergoing testing in a listening room. However, the second unit still requires restoration.
Initial assessment of the second Beomaster 1900 has already been completed, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to begin replacing capacitors on the main circuit board.
The main circuit board houses most of the capacitors that need replacing. Unfortunately, it cannot be removed for servicing and must remain connected to the wire harness.</description></item><item><title>European academics are appealing for the EU to avoid becoming a lawless zone.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</guid><description>The situation at the Polish-Belarusian border briefly gained public awareness, with images of suffering refugees stranded in terrible conditions sparking outrage. While there were discussions and reactions, the humanitarian crisis persists.
Since September 2021, the Polish government has restricted access to the border zone, putting migrants in danger and denying aid organizations access. People are facing dire circumstances, including death, due to lack of basic necessities and medical help.</description></item><item><title>Increase Bandwidth Without Increasing Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</guid><description>Companies need more bandwidth, especially for their wide area networks (WANs), but it can be very expensive. While high speeds are affordable within a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN, connecting to the outside world traditionally comes with much higher costs.
This is because WAN connections were typically provided by telecom companies using technology initially meant for phone services. While more modern providers have entered the market with updated infrastructure, even traditional providers are adapting to the demand for data services.</description></item><item><title>Numerous White Papers Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through a phase where white papers feel incredibly relevant to challenges we face internally and with clients. I wanted to share some of my top picks:
Microsoft Dynamics GP and SQL Server 2008
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false This paper offers valuable insights into leveraging SQL Server 2008 compression, including performance benchmarks.
Choosing a Development Tool for Microsoft Dynamics GP 10
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false A must-read for developers and consultants, this paper provides a comprehensive overview of development tools, licensing costs, required skillsets, and tool capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Error in the positioning of the Visual Studio Tools window in GP 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-the-positioning-of-the-visual-studio-tools-window-in-gp-2013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-the-positioning-of-the-visual-studio-tools-window-in-gp-2013/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
This week, I completed a custom Dynamics GP 2013 eConnect integration created as a Visual Studio Tools AddIn. The client wanted a GP menu item to open the integration window, so I used the Menus for Visual Studio Tools library to create a custom menu item.
The integration worked perfectly, and I packaged it for deployment at the client site.
However, during final testing and verification, I encountered unusual window behavior.</description></item><item><title>It's Wireless Cleanup Time Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-wireless-cleanup-time-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-wireless-cleanup-time-again/</guid><description>This New Year&amp;rsquo;s, consider a resolution that benefits both your wallet and the environment: declutter your old cell phones!
It&amp;rsquo;s common to accumulate unused phones after upgrading contracts or switching carriers. Technological advancements and tempting free offers often lead us to replace phones before they&amp;rsquo;re truly unusable. While understandable, this habit results in drawers and boxes filled with neglected devices. These phones quickly lose value and often end up discarded, contributing to electronic waste and releasing harmful substances like lead and cadmium into landfills.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Reunification of Ireland from an EU Legal Viewpoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</guid><description>Nikos Skoutaris, Lecturer in EU law at the University of East Anglia; website on Secessions, Constitutions and EU law.
When the UK voted to leave the EU on June 23, 2016, Northern Ireland voted to remain. This result has led Sinn Féin to call for a referendum on Irish unification, which would allow Northern Ireland to stay in the EU. This discussion has gained momentum following the most recent Northern Ireland Assembly election, which saw a significant decrease in the Unionist vote.</description></item><item><title>Shared Internet Service for Apartment Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shared-internet-service-for-apartment-buildings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shared-internet-service-for-apartment-buildings/</guid><description>Property owners and managers are recognizing the increasing importance of broadband internet access, much like essential utilities. They are exploring ways to provide this service, similar to phone and cable companies. Offering high-speed internet can be a significant advantage in attracting and retaining tenants.
Becoming an internet service provider, even for a single building, requires reliable, dedicated internet access. T1 or Dedicated Internet provides this, ensuring the full bandwidth is dedicated to your use, unlike shared services like DSL and Cable.</description></item><item><title>Dial-Up is Alive and Kicking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world of high-speed internet, it might seem strange to talk about dial-up. Many people consider it outdated technology.
However, dial-up internet access is still relevant. Millions of people still use and appreciate it for browsing the internet and checking emails. This &amp;ldquo;outdated&amp;rdquo; technology remains profitable.
One of the main advantages of dial-up is its affordability. Unlimited access is available for a low monthly cost, making it a budget-friendly option compared to DSL or cable internet.</description></item><item><title>Is Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union considered valid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart
Introduction
The Treaty of Lisbon introduced Article 50 to the Treaty on European Union (TEU), establishing the legal framework for exiting the European Union (EU). This article acknowledges the possibility of withdrawal, a concept many legal experts believed existed even before the Treaty of Lisbon. Article 50 TEU outlines the withdrawal procedure. However, some argue that it contradicts the EU&amp;rsquo;s fundamental nature and weakens member states&amp;rsquo; commitment to European integration, raising questions about the ideal withdrawal mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Copper WAN Bandwidth Headed to 500 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</guid><description>Ericsson has developed a new technology that could significantly boost data transmission speeds over existing copper wire infrastructure. This innovation allows for WAN connections over copper, achieving speeds up to 500 Mbps.
While Gigabit Ethernet is achievable with Cat-6 wiring for LAN connections, this technology focuses on connecting businesses to broadband providers using existing copper infrastructure. This is significant because many businesses require increased bandwidth for various purposes, including server farms, internet access, data transfer between locations, and the growing need for electronic medical record transfers.</description></item><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Get Ready For The Recovery With Bandwidth on Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>The economy is recovering, benefiting some businesses while others struggle. Maintaining earnings through cost-cutting instead of increased sales won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable. When the economy fully recovers, rapid adaptation will be crucial, but increased expenses are only justifiable with increased revenue. Bandwidth on demand offers a solution.
Bandwidth on demand allows businesses to access and pay for only the bandwidth they currently need, scaling usage up or down as required. This differs from the traditional approach of installing full capacity in advance, which poses financial risks if projected growth doesn&amp;rsquo;t materialize.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>My work on restoring the 4002 continues, and today involved polishing the hood – a task that&amp;rsquo;s quite a workout! The plexiglass hood had some noticeable scratches:
I began by using 200 grit sandpaper to create a consistent surface:
Then I gradually polished it using Micromesh polishing cloths:
The final stage involved Micromesh Micro-Gloss:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower.</description></item><item><title>Cloud vs Premises Contact Center Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-vs-premises-contact-center-costs/</guid><description>Lots of small businesses can get by with just a local or toll-free number for customer calls. But as companies grow, they usually dedicate staff and resources to handle customer interactions, creating a dedicated department known as a contact center. While contact centers are important, they can be expensive to run. Is there a way to reduce the cost?
Until recently, outsourcing to different locations was an option, but that often led to issues with language barriers and inconsistent service quality.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks.</description></item><item><title>The Dark Side of Spectrum Renewal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</guid><description>Half a century ago, the government embraced urban renewal, demolishing and rebuilding deteriorated urban areas for housing projects or highways leading to suburbs. Similarly, today, we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing &amp;ldquo;spectrum renewal,&amp;rdquo; where sections of the radio frequency spectrum are deemed too valuable for older technologies like analog TV and cell phone service, despite their widespread use.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by lack of public demand. Millions of analog TV sets and cell phones are still functional.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Neutrik Gold Plated DIN5 Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</guid><description>A common improvement for the Beogram 4000 is replacing the DIN5 plug with a gold-plated version. The older plugs, often corroded, benefit from the upgrade. This particular Beogram 4000 was no exception.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a comparison of the old plug and the new, gleaming Neutrik plug (Newark 27B4483):
The old plug was removed, and the cable was prepped for the new plug. Stripping the outer insulation to this length works well:</description></item><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both.</description></item><item><title>Your Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple locations often need to share data, traditionally relying on T1 lines for connectivity. While multiple T1 lines can increase bandwidth, this approach might not be the most cost-effective solution, especially in metropolitan areas.
Point-to-point Ethernet offers a compelling alternative, often at a lower cost per Mbps, particularly for higher bandwidth needs. Ethernet streamlines data transmission by maintaining its format throughout the network, potentially allowing locations to function as a single bridged LAN.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft renegotiation deal a legitimate rejection? Tusk's suggestion and the role of national parliaments.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</guid><description>Dr. Katarzyna Granat, Junior Research Fellow &amp;amp; Marie Curie Fellow, Durham Law School Donald Tusk&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A New Settlement for the United Kingdom within the European Union&amp;rdquo; (Draft Decision of the Heads of State or Government), presented on February 2, 2016, provides an initial concrete outline for enhancing the role of national parliaments within the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiation efforts. This note compares the proposed changes with existing mechanisms under the Lisbon Treaty.</description></item><item><title>Farewell, VB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-vb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-vb/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been close since I started with programming on my Commodore 64. From creating basic applications in school to more complex projects later on, you were there.
We tackled various challenges, from writing a Windows application for a psychology thesis to automating tasks with WordPerfect macros. You adapted well to new environments, proving valuable in Microsoft Office VBA and early ERP systems.
Our journey continued with web applications, e-commerce integrations, and custom desktop apps.</description></item><item><title>Is Brexit Causing the British Mind to Close? The Impact on EU Academics and Government Guidance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Brexit vote is often seen as an attack on both academic expertise and EU citizens in the UK, whether accurate or not. These two issues intersect in a recent dispute involving the Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO) and the London School of Economics (LSE). The FCO allegedly barred EU citizens from advising the government on Brexit, though the details are unclear.
The LSE reportedly informed staff that the FCO no longer sought Brexit advice from EU nationals, sparking a controversy that made its way to social media and prominent news outlets like The Guardian.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Comparison Shopping</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-comparison-shopping/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 17:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-comparison-shopping/</guid><description>Voice over IP (VoIP) is becoming increasingly popular for both home and business phone service. With this new technology rapidly evolving, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep up with the latest companies and deals. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to switch to VoIP or simply want a better deal, you need a way to compare your options. That&amp;rsquo;s where a comparison shopping service comes in handy, allowing you to easily evaluate available services and choose the best fit.</description></item><item><title>Business Ethernet Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</guid><description>For decades, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have relied heavily on T1 lines. However, a new service called Business Ethernet is emerging as a strong competitor, offering comparable performance at a lower cost.
Business Ethernet, also referred to as Metro Ethernet, Ethernet over Copper, or Ethernet over Fiber, provides advantages such as scalable bandwidth options, reduced cost per Mbps, and wider availability. Its name emphasizes that Ethernet is no longer limited to Local Area Networks (LANs) and carriers, as it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly being adopted by SMBs.</description></item><item><title>Hosting Nation Offers Low Cost Web Hosting For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosting-nation-offers-low-cost-web-hosting-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 09:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosting-nation-offers-low-cost-web-hosting-for-everyone/</guid><description>Are you searching for the perfect balance of affordability and quality in web hosting? Look no further than Hosting Nation.
Gone are the days of expensive, self-managed servers. Hosting services have become incredibly affordable, allowing you to establish a global presence for less than ten dollars a month.
If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; hosting services that compromise your website&amp;rsquo;s aesthetics or expensive &amp;ldquo;professional&amp;rdquo; hosting plans, Hosting Nation offers a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Flat Rate vs Pay As You Go Conference Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-vs-pay-as-you-go-conference-calling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flat-rate-vs-pay-as-you-go-conference-calling/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve already seen how conference calls and web conferencing can save your company a lot of money. So why worry about the small costs involved? Firstly, saving money is always a good thing. Secondly, the more affordable conference calls are, the more you can use them to boost productivity.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine AccuConference, a leading teleconferencing provider, and see their pricing options. AccuConference offers both flat rate and pay-as-you-go conference calls.</description></item><item><title>Using eConnect to import Analytical Accounting data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-econnect-to-import-analytical-accounting-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 17:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-econnect-to-import-analytical-accounting-data/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP, shares his insights on troubleshooting eConnect integrations, particularly when importing Dynamics GP transactions that include Analytical Accounting distributions.
Users successfully importing transactions might find that the associated Analytical Accounting data is missing in GP. This issue often stems from incorrect import procedures and misleading error messages from eConnect. To clarify, this article outlines how to correctly include Analytical Accounting data in an eConnect import.</description></item><item><title>Life is full of challenges, and then you have to deal with the third extension of EU membership.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This extension was unexpected. Despite the Benn Act, which mandated the Prime Minister to request a three-month extension for EU membership if Parliament failed to approve a withdrawal agreement by October 19, the Prime Minister insisted he would rather resign than comply. Fueled by ambiguous sources within Downing Street, there was persistent speculation that the Benn Act was unconstitutional, riddled with loopholes, would be superseded by emergency powers, or violated EU law.</description></item><item><title>Creating a RESTful JSON web service integration for Dynamics GP - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-a-restful-json-web-service-integration-for-dynamics-gp-part-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-a-restful-json-web-service-integration-for-dynamics-gp-part-1/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP and a Dynamics GP Certified IT Professional based in Los Angeles, recently completed a fascinating Dynamics GP integration project.
This project involved creating a RESTful JSON web service that enables a website to seamlessly integrate with Dynamics GP, Authorize.net, and the k-eCommerce/Azox Credit Card Extension. Given its role in handling sensitive credit card data, the web service prioritizes security by incorporating HMAC authentication, AES encryption, and operating exclusively over HTTPS.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs VPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</guid><description>Virtual Private Servers (VPS) offer a hosting solution for websites that have outgrown shared hosting but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for the cost and responsibility of a fully dedicated server. However, a new option allows for flexible scaling and a pay-as-you-go model: cloud server hosting.
Discussions about cloud computing versus managing your own data center are becoming increasingly common. However, many companies haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the stage where investing in a complete in-house data center is necessary.</description></item><item><title>The DAG.exe in GP 2015 crashes due to the inability to load the type 'Microsoft.Dynamics.GP.BusinessObjects.Payroll.Timecard'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dag-exe-in-gp-2015-crashes-due-to-the-inability-to-load-the-type-microsoft-dynamics-gp-businessobjects-payroll-timecard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dag-exe-in-gp-2015-crashes-due-to-the-inability-to-load-the-type-microsoft-dynamics-gp-businessobjects-payroll-timecard/</guid><description>The Dynamics GP Visual Studio Tools &amp;ldquo;Dictionary Assembly Generator&amp;rdquo; (dag.exe) is a tool that I was aware of but hadn&amp;rsquo;t needed until a recent project. This project required me to access custom fields in modified GP windows.
I installed the VS Tools SDK on my GP 2015 server and ran the DAG. However, the DAG would crash during the &amp;ldquo;Generating IL code&amp;rdquo; step.
Even after upgrading to the latest hotfix, the issue persisted.</description></item><item><title>Resolve problems with Dynamics GP scaling and font size on high DPI screens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolve-problems-with-dynamics-gp-scaling-and-font-size-on-high-dpi-screens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolve-problems-with-dynamics-gp-scaling-and-font-size-on-high-dpi-screens/</guid><description>This blog has a new home at https://blog.steveendow.com/. Future posts will be published there.
Update: For those experiencing Remote Desktop difficulties with high DPI screens, Nathan Hayden from BKD has a helpful workaround available at: http://dynamicsinsights.com/2018/10/05/remote-desktop-high-dpi-dynamics-gp/
Modern Windows laptops and desktops with high-resolution or 4K displays often encounter display issues with some software. These &amp;ldquo;high DPI&amp;rdquo; screens can make text appear minuscule at full resolution. To counteract this, Windows uses &amp;ldquo;scaling&amp;rdquo; to enlarge text and graphics for readability and usability.</description></item><item><title>Changes have been made to the User Setup window in GP 2013 R2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changes-have-been-made-to-the-user-setup-window-in-gp-2013-r2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:54:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changes-have-been-made-to-the-user-setup-window-in-gp-2013-r2/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
After installing GP 2013 R2, a few changes and new features are noticeable. One notable difference is the redesigned User Setup window.
GP 2013 SP2:
GP 2013 R2:
The R2 window features the noticeable ribbon at the top, a standard change in R2. Additionally, the User Setup window incorporates a few key additions.
User Type: This option, offering Full or Limited access, dictates user permissions. A Limited user is restricted to inquiries and reports.</description></item><item><title>Solstice Before The Solstice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait for the winter solstice to experience the Samsung Solstice, a touchscreen phone designed for social networking. This sleek phone boasts a vibrant 3-inch color touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable app widgets for easy access to platforms like Facebook and MySpace.
Staying connected is effortless with the Solstice&amp;rsquo;s virtual keyboard and high-resolution screen, perfect for messaging. Its slim, half-inch profile, achieved through advanced virtual technology, surpasses bulkier models with slide-out keyboards.</description></item><item><title>Do Dynamics GP upgrades still require a test environment?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-dynamics-gp-upgrades-still-require-a-test-environment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-dynamics-gp-upgrades-still-require-a-test-environment/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Microsoft MVP for Dynamics GP, discusses the necessity of a test environment for &amp;ldquo;typical&amp;rdquo; Dynamics GP upgrades. He observes that while some customers have complex setups requiring thorough testing, many others have simpler environments where upgrading directly in production might be feasible.
Endow acknowledges that GP upgrades in the past were often complicated, necessitating a separate test server. However, he notes that Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Dynamics GP led to a streamlined and more reliable upgrade process.</description></item><item><title>The EC is proposing an AI Liability Directive to provide assistance.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ec-is-proposing-an-ai-liability-directive-to-provide-assistance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ec-is-proposing-an-ai-liability-directive-to-provide-assistance/</guid><description>Ida Varošanec (PhD student, University of Groningen) and Nynke Vellinga (post-doc researcher, University of Groningen)
Photo credit: Cryteria, via Wikimedia commons
1. Proposal Goals
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposal for an AI Liability Directive, published on September 28, 2022, alongside an updated Product Liability Directive, aims to address the risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) while acknowledging its potential benefits. The proposal stems from a report recognizing the potential harm AI systems can cause due to their connectivity, unpredictable nature, and opacity, which makes it difficult to assign responsibility for AI-related incidents.</description></item><item><title>Do crime victims now have additional rights under EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
*This analysis is taken from the upcoming 4th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Victims of crime are often disheartened not just by the crime itself but also by the criminal justice system&amp;rsquo;s indifference to their needs. To tackle this issue, the EU introduced a Directive on crime victims’ rights in 2012 that Member States were required to implement by November 16, 2015. This law supersedes an earlier Framework Decision on this matter from 2001.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls.</description></item><item><title>Identifying SQL Server Users without a Corresponding Login</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-sql-server-users-without-a-corresponding-login/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-sql-server-users-without-a-corresponding-login/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s imagine two situations: First, you set up a test Dynamics GP server for a client by installing SQL Server and Dynamics GP, then restoring database copies. Second, a client&amp;rsquo;s Dynamics GP SQL server crashes, you rebuild it, and restore databases from backups.
Both scenarios present a common problem: restoring a database from one SQL Server to another doesn&amp;rsquo;t transfer the associated SQL Server logins.
Scenario 1 offers a solution: a &amp;ldquo;Capture Logins&amp;rdquo; script (KB 878449) efficiently transfers SQL logins to the new server.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Massachusetts - First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from a Massachusetts customer for a complete restoration. Thankfully, it was properly packaged and arrived without damage.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s dust cover shows typical signs of use, but it will be replaced with a new one. The aluminum surfaces are in good shape overall.
However, there are some minor flaws. The keypad has a corner ding, suggesting it might have come loose during past transportation. Additionally, there are small scratches on the aluminum, possibly from the keypad moving around.</description></item><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?</description></item><item><title>SQL script for verifying Dynamics GP GL batch control totals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-script-for-verifying-dynamics-gp-gl-batch-control-totals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-script-for-verifying-dynamics-gp-gl-batch-control-totals/</guid><description>A customer encountered a bug in their Dynamics GP integration that caused discrepancies between the actual number of imported GL transactions and the batch control totals. To identify these discrepancies, a SQL query was created to compare the number of GL transactions and JE totals with the batch control totals stored in SY00500.
The query utilizes a Common Table Expression (CTE) to efficiently calculate and compare the data. This approach helps pinpoint differences between the expected transaction count and total amount against the recorded batch control totals.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade Your Business Image</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-business-image/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:47:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-business-image/</guid><description>Your image as a business professional is largely controlled by your company when you work for a large corporation. However, as a small business owner, independent sales agent, or consultant, you are responsible for managing your own image. One important aspect of this is your business card.
The design and printing of your business card contribute to a polished and professional look, but an unprofessional email address can quickly ruin that impression.</description></item><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013.</description></item><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>600,000 Inquiries, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</guid><description>Purchasing important items can be a hassle, especially telecommunications services. It&amp;rsquo;s a maze of confusing calls, endless hold music, and tedious forms with long wait times.
But imagine getting a price for a T1 line or finding nearby Metro Ethernet services in under a minute, any time, day or night. That&amp;rsquo;s where GeoQuote (tm) comes in. This innovative telecom pricing application is changing how businesses buy voice and data services.</description></item><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning of the Tone Arm Carriage Position Switches and a Non-Returning Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</guid><description>As a preliminary step in the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I chose to verify the functionality of its control system. Prior testing had shown that the arm carriage would not return to its home position when moved across the platter without a record in place. Instead, it would travel to the center of the platter and stop. Ideally, the carriage should trigger the End Switch (ES) at this point and subsequently return to its home position on the right, turning off the turntable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>The release of eConnect 2010 Service Pack 1 is now available!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-release-of-econnect-2010-service-pack-1-is-now-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:34:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-release-of-econnect-2010-service-pack-1-is-now-available/</guid><description>Dynamics GP 2010 Service Pack 1 is now available. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to review the details before installation.
https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/downloads/servicepacks/mdgp2010_patchreleases.htm
More importantly, eConnect 2010 Service Pack 1 has also been released.
https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/downloads/servicepacks/MDGP2010_eConnectservicepackshotfixes
The update includes separate files for x86 and x64 systems.
While the list of fixes is not yet available, this update will likely be applied to GP 2010 development servers shortly.</description></item><item><title>Should User Account Control be disabled?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-user-account-control-be-disabled/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-user-account-control-be-disabled/</guid><description>Increasingly, as clients transition to Windows 7 or Vista, user account control issues are becoming more prevalent in Dynamics GP support, particularly with Dynamics GP Utilities. Users frequently encounter BCP utility errors after successfully launching utilities and logging in.
A quick fix is to launch Dynamics GP Utilities as an administrator. While this is straightforward, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed a concerning trend of simply recommending the disabling of user account control altogether. This approach raises concerns for me.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): Removing the Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Note: This post documents an outdated method. There&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way to remove the drive that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve lifting the Pre-Amplifier board or disconnecting the solenoid linkage. See my later post for the updated procedure.
Following advice from &amp;lsquo;chartz&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;sonavor&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org (link to thread), I began replacing the belts in my Beocord 5000 (4716), which had become loose and stretched over time.
The first step is removing the drive mechanism.</description></item><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light.</description></item><item><title>Business Telephone Systems Hosted VoIP Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes have various choices for their telephone systems. Small businesses can buy systems from local stores, while medium-sized businesses often work with contractors for key telephone systems or small PBXs. Larger companies may have internal teams that handle complex telephone systems. Nowadays, hosted VoIP is a cost-effective option for companies of all sizes.
How can one solution meet the needs of different-sized businesses affordably? It&amp;rsquo;s not a one-size-fits-all solution but a scalable technology adaptable to different demands—hosted VoIP, also known as hosted PBX or cloud telephone systems.</description></item><item><title>What is the purpose of using the system password in Dynamics GP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-purpose-of-using-the-system-password-in-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-purpose-of-using-the-system-password-in-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>A client recently brought up the Dynamics GP System Password, a feature I find comparable to User Classes – widely used in the past but less common in modern implementations. For those unfamiliar, the System Password in Dynamics GP (found under Administration Page &amp;gt; Setup &amp;gt; System Password) safeguards all system menus (Setup, Cards, Reports, etc.) with a password. This means users need to enter the password to access these windows, even if they technically have permission.</description></item><item><title>What qualities define exceptional training?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:35:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading training sessions, including a Dynamics GP Distribution Partner Academy and a customized Forecaster training. These distinct classes got me thinking about the elements of exceptional training and what makes it truly valuable. I&amp;rsquo;d love to share my thoughts and hear yours!
Relevant Content: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for training content to align with student needs. While this can be challenging with pre-determined classes, instructors can bridge the gap by connecting content to real-world scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Main PCB and Installation of a Biasing Trimmer for TR3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</guid><description>After getting the Beogram 4002 (5513) operational again, I focused on fully restoring the main PCB. This involved installing a trimmer to correctly calibrate TR3, the transistor responsible for amplifying the signal from the record detection sensor. The board&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown below:
The RPM relay and trimmers had already been replaced by the owner. I finished the restoration by replacing all electrolytic capacitors
and adding a trimmer to enable bias adjustment at the base of TR3.</description></item><item><title>SmartList Builder and SQL Tables/Views</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-builder-and-sql-tables-views/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:57:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-builder-and-sql-tables-views/</guid><description>Many of you may already know this, but I encountered a problem this week deploying a SmartList Builder item. Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened:
I created two SQL views based on GP and custom tables. I granted the SmartList Builder access to these views (Tools &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder &amp;raquo; Security &amp;raquo; SQL Table Security). I created my SmartList (Tools &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder &amp;raquo; SmartList Builder). After testing, the SmartList worked correctly. I deployed the views to the client&amp;rsquo;s environment.</description></item><item><title>Users of Forecaster and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>Have you ever encountered a problem where you vaguely recall a solution but can&amp;rsquo;t seem to locate the specific article or link? This happened to me recently with a client attempting to use their Dynamics GP user ID for Forecaster 7. As expected, it was unsuccessful due to GP&amp;rsquo;s encryption method when generating user IDs in SQL. This encryption prevents the same ID from functioning in Forecaster, even with proper database permissions.</description></item><item><title>3x3 Mbps Ethernet Doubles Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t benefit from additional internet speed? Websites, software, and files continue to grow larger, but unfortunately, technology budgets haven&amp;rsquo;t kept pace. Imagine doubling your internet speed without increasing your current expenses – an appealing proposition, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
It might sound illogical to suggest that doubling your internet speed wouldn&amp;rsquo;t cost more, especially since internet providers aren&amp;rsquo;t known for giving things away for free. The secret lies in adopting newer, more cost-effective technology instead of simply replacing your existing service with an identical one from another provider.</description></item><item><title>IT Departments are Wearin' the Green</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-departments-are-wearin-the-green/</guid><description>Maintaining IT budgets requires more than just good fortune these days. Many companies are discovering that environmentally friendly practices can save them money. These eco-conscious choices benefit both the planet and their bottom line.
One of the first areas to examine is electricity consumption. Power usage can be deceptive because it often occurs in small, unnoticeable increments. Every desktop computer, even when idle, contributes to the overall energy use, measured in watt-hours and kilowatt-hours.</description></item><item><title>The discussion on drones in the UK and its impact on the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 05:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</guid><description>By Chris Jones
A new report, Back from the battlefield: domestic drones in the UK, investigates the use of drones by public and private entities in the UK. It focuses on law enforcement and border control agencies, examining the laws, regulations, and public and private funding surrounding drone technology development. The report analyzes the current situation and potential future applications, advocating for public discussion and decision-making before widespread drone use, particularly for surveillance, becomes commonplace.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Store Your Files For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</guid><description>With the current state of the economy, you&amp;rsquo;d expect the best price for file storage to be free – and you&amp;rsquo;d be right! Anything more would be asking too much.
Of course, this applies to storing digital files, not physical ones. Don&amp;rsquo;t show up at a self-storage facility with boxes of papers expecting free storage – they won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to show you the door!
Instead, try storing your computer files for free with Mozy (http://www.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Border and Coast Guard a completely new entity or just a revamped version of Frontex?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</guid><description>Herbert Rosenfeldt, Research Assistant and PhD candidate, University of Passau
Introduction
Celebrating the new European Border and Coast Guard Agency, also known as Frontex, at the Bulgarian external border with Turkey might seem like an odd festivity. However, last Thursday, high-ranking EU and Member State officials gathered at Bulgaria&amp;rsquo;s Kapitan Andreevo Border Checkpoint for this inauguration. This event marked the implementation of the European Border and Coast Guard Regulation, a significant step towards strengthening external border control in the wake of recent migration challenges.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to suspend Schengen due to Greece? Is it necessary to do so?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</guid><description>A recent leak of a Council document proposes a potential suspension of the Schengen system for a duration of up to two years. This proposal stems from what are being termed &amp;ldquo;systemic deficiencies&amp;rdquo; in Greece&amp;rsquo;s management of its external borders, particularly concerning the influx of refugees and migrants. Such a suspension would provide any Schengen country the option to reinstate or implement border controls along their shared internal borders. While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely that every Schengen country would exercise this option, it&amp;rsquo;s anticipated that several would choose to do so, especially given that a number already have active border controls in place.</description></item><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages.</description></item><item><title>Disable all Dynamics GP posting reports in the Fabrikam test company.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disable-all-dynamics-gp-posting-reports-in-the-fabrikam-test-company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:06:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disable-all-dynamics-gp-posting-reports-in-the-fabrikam-test-company/</guid><description>Steve Endow
No More Clicking &amp;ldquo;Cancel&amp;rdquo; Update: Victoria Yudin accurately pointed out that posting reports are sometimes useful or even necessary, for example, in training or when troubleshooting errors. She&amp;rsquo;s absolutely right - posting reports are definitely needed in certain situations, even in Fabrikam. I personally disabled posting reports in my testing environment because I frequently run repetitive tests on batch posting for my projects. I already know that my data, transactions, and postings are all accurate.</description></item><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider.</description></item><item><title>What Is Toll Free?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-toll-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-toll-free/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;toll free number&amp;rdquo; is widely recognized, with most people having used one. But what exactly does it mean and how do businesses acquire them?
Unlike standard phone numbers automatically assigned with landline, VoIP, or cellular services, toll free numbers require a separate process. In the US and Canada, phone numbers follow the North American Numbering Plan (NANP) format: 1-NPA-NXX-XXXX.
In this format, &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo; represents the country code, NPA stands for Numbering Plan Area (area code), and the remaining digits are unique to your line.</description></item><item><title>The Hyper-V virtual machine running Server 2012 R2 is unable to start and displays an error message stating "We were unable to finish the updates.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyper-v-virtual-machine-running-server-2012-r2-is-unable-to-start-and-displays-an-error-message-stating-we-were-unable-to-finish-the-updates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 18:22:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyper-v-virtual-machine-running-server-2012-r2-is-unable-to-start-and-displays-an-error-message-stating-we-were-unable-to-finish-the-updates/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
While attempting to set up the GP 2016 Web Client on a new Server 2012 R2 virtual machine, I encountered an error message stating &amp;ldquo;We couldn&amp;rsquo;t complete the updates. Undoing changes.&amp;rdquo; The VM became unresponsive.
After some searching, I came across a TechNet forum thread discussing similar issues with Windows 8. Unfortunately, the suggested fix of disabling Secure Boot on the VM was unsuccessful in my case.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>Strategies For The Hunkered Down Economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</guid><description>While the new year has arrived, the economic situation remains challenging. Unemployment is still high, companies are focusing on cost-cutting over revenue growth, and uncertainty about the future persists. Consumers are tightening their belts and spending less, leaving businesses with little choice but to do the same. It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to hesitate before making significant moves when the path ahead is unclear.
Does this mean your business is stuck or in irreversible decline?</description></item><item><title>The Legal Standing of a Third Country before the CJEU: AG Hogan's Opinion in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council in Relation to State Immunity and Comity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
In a legal opinion issued on February 20, 2021, Advocate General Hogan addressed a crucial procedural issue: Can a non-EU country legally challenge EU actions before the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)? This question holds significance because the Court has never directly ruled on it within the context of sanctions, and it delves into the principles governing the relationship between EU law and other international law subjects.</description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore.</description></item><item><title>Conference 2016: Redeeming The Dirt</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-2016-redeeming-the-dirt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-2016-redeeming-the-dirt/</guid><description>Dateline: 23 August 2016 AD
Noah Sanders, who wrote Born-Again Dirt: Farming to the Glory of God, is hosting another one of his Redeeming The Dirt conferences in Alabama.
Brian Oldreive, the founder of Foundations For Farming, will be speaking at the conference. Foundations For Farming is a Christian ministry based in Africa that teaches people, mainly the poor, how to become self-sufficient through growing their own food. I&amp;rsquo;ve written about Foundations For Farming several times on my previous blog.</description></item><item><title>Scale Into Toll Free Number Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scale-into-toll-free-number-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 01:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scale-into-toll-free-number-service/</guid><description>You might be considering toll-free numbers for your business, but the cost and commitment feel like a gamble. What if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work out as planned?
Instead of a large investment, try a trial run with a single toll-free number. This allows you to experience the features and benefits without a major financial commitment.
Kall8 offers a scalable toll-free service ideal for businesses of all sizes. Manage your numbers and settings easily through their online platform.</description></item><item><title>Update the notes in Dynamics GP through an eConnect integration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-the-notes-in-dynamics-gp-through-an-econnect-integration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-the-notes-in-dynamics-gp-through-an-econnect-integration/</guid><description>Steve Endow
While I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with eConnect integrations extensively, I recently encountered a situation where I needed to update existing Dynamics GP Note records. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t recall having done this before, and online searches didn&amp;rsquo;t provide any solutions. If you know of an easier approach, please share, as I&amp;rsquo;m curious if I&amp;rsquo;ve overlooked something.
Let&amp;rsquo;s imagine your .NET eConnect integration needs to update a customer&amp;rsquo;s address and phone number, and simultaneously append an update message to the existing customer note.</description></item><item><title>NIST has chosen the SHA-3 cryptographic hash.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nist-has-chosen-the-sha-3-cryptographic-hash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:52:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nist-has-chosen-the-sha-3-cryptographic-hash/</guid><description>The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) has chosen the &amp;ldquo;Keccak&amp;rdquo; algorithm as the new SHA-3 cryptographic hash algorithm.
Notably, Bruce Schneier, a finalist in the SHA-3 competition, recently expressed his opinion that NIST should not select any of the candidate algorithms.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with cryptographic hash algorithms, the Wikipedia page on the subject provides a clear explanation.
Simply put, they are essential for computer security.
_Steve Endow is a Dynamics GP Certified Trainer and Dynamics GP Certified IT Professional in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements.</description></item><item><title>EV-DO Expands In The Face of WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ev-do-expands-in-the-face-of-wimax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ev-do-expands-in-the-face-of-wimax/</guid><description>The arrival of 4G technology, specifically Sprint&amp;rsquo;s nationwide WiMAX network, raises questions about the future of 3G. While WiMAX boasts speeds up to 70 Mbps, suggesting a potential shift, the reality is more nuanced.
Sprint&amp;rsquo;s commitment to a national WiMAX network, with its impressive 31-mile range and 70 Mbps bandwidth, signals a potential shift in mobile technology. Realistically, users can expect speeds around 2-4 Mbps, especially when mobile. This rivals the current leading 3G service, EV-DO.</description></item><item><title>Presenting my latest innovative concept... The Chickenhead Door Knocker!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/presenting-my-latest-innovative-concept-the-chickenhead-door-knocker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/presenting-my-latest-innovative-concept-the-chickenhead-door-knocker/</guid><description>Dateline: 11 February 2017
Take a look at the video linked above.
You can explore the new website here:
Chickenhead Door Knocker
If you know anyone who loves chickens, please feel free to pass along the video and website link.
Thanks!</description></item><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is.</description></item><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>Poken Enhances Face to Face Social Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</guid><description>Is jotting down contact information on scraps of paper your go-to method? Do you find yourself hoping your hand-written notes survive the journey home? Perhaps you rely on traditional business cards?
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, those methods are outdated.
Just like Facebook, MySpace, LinkedIn, and Twitter revolutionized online networking, Poken is ushering in a new era for in-person connections with a device aptly named &amp;ldquo;Poken.&amp;rdquo; Think of it as a modern-day amulet, powered by cutting-edge technology.</description></item><item><title>Predictor Line Arrangements Over Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/predictor-line-arrangements-over-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:03:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/predictor-line-arrangements-over-time/</guid><description>In the past, using special characters in Forecaster 6.7 often led to problems, so avoiding even periods was recommended. While things have improved in Forecaster 7.0, it&amp;rsquo;s still best to avoid special characters in name and ID fields. Recently, a period caused confusion in Forecaster again.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened:
A line set was named with a period at the end (e.g., &amp;ldquo;HR.&amp;rdquo;). This line set was used as an override on an input set.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Lines Connect Dealerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 05:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</guid><description>Many businesses, from car dealerships to restaurants, benefit from having multiple locations. However, managing these locations as a unified company requires connecting them effectively. Point-to-point lines and MPLS networks offer solutions for this need.
Consider a car dealership expanding by acquiring another dealership. While this offers strategic advantages, consolidating operations like accounting, marketing, and IT can lead to cost savings. Centralizing these functions requires reliable and efficient connectivity between locations.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Services over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:35:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</guid><description>Connecting networks logically often involves Ethernet, a technology that has recently expanded its reach beyond local boundaries. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) connections are increasing in availability and often come at a lower cost compared to other options.
EoC enables standard Ethernet services to be delivered through existing copper telephone wiring. Unlike typical Cat 5E or Cat 6 wiring, EoC is compatible with older copper infrastructure not initially intended for Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>Is 5G Bandwidth Slicing The New Private Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet is great for connecting, but it&amp;rsquo;s not always reliable. While it provides widespread access, low costs, and supports most applications, it can fall short when high performance and reliability are crucial. Issues like latency, packet loss, and congestion can hinder or even prevent interactive applications from working correctly. The solution? Private networks.
What is a Private Network?
The internet is a public network, accessible to almost anyone.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow.</description></item><item><title>A Kissing Hand For The Sandy Hook Elementary Students</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-kissing-hand-for-the-sandy-hook-elementary-students/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-kissing-hand-for-the-sandy-hook-elementary-students/</guid><description>A children&amp;rsquo;s book about a raccoon hesitant to start school offers a heartwarming solution for children struggling with the idea of returning to the classroom.
The recent tragedy at Sandy Hook Elementary School in Newtown, Connecticut, has left many young students grappling with trauma and fear. The horrific event, where students and educators lost their lives, has created a sense of anxiety about returning to school for the spring semester. Finding a way to comfort these children and help them cope with their fears is a significant challenge.</description></item><item><title>No-Till Gardening Using Minibeds-on-Plastic: The Importance of Glomalin and Mycorrhizae</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-till-gardening-using-minibeds-on-plastic-the-importance-of-glomalin-and-mycorrhizae/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 19:59:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-till-gardening-using-minibeds-on-plastic-the-importance-of-glomalin-and-mycorrhizae/</guid><description>Dateline: 11 March 2017
Amazing beauty, on a microscopic level
My new Minibeds-on-Plastic experimental garden is designed as a no-till system for growing vegetables. While there will be no soil disturbance under the plastic covering most of the garden, the &amp;ldquo;island&amp;rdquo; minibeds themselves will also remain mostly undisturbed. This minimal-till approach is central to the Minibeds-on-Plastic method, and I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why.
Contrary to common belief, tilling the soil does not enhance its structure.</description></item><item><title>Merchant Account Credit Card Processing Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/merchant-account-credit-card-processing-made-easy/</guid><description>Even the smallest businesses need a way to process credit card payments. Instead of making it a difficult process, choose a reliable credit card processing company to simplify things. Elite Processing Systems handles the complexities of electronic payments, allowing you to concentrate on your customers and what you offer. They provide a full range of financial services for small businesses, going above and beyond traditional credit card processing.
You might have heard of Elite Processing Systems (EPS).</description></item><item><title>Zero Dollar Checks and Mekorma MICR are both essential tools for managing your finances effectively.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</guid><description>I recently encountered a situation with zero-dollar checks and Mekorma MICR software. To clarify, Dynamics GP software generates zero-dollar checks when an invoice is fully paid through methods like credit memos or manual payments. This often happens before a check run or when opting for automatic application of unapplied documents during check runs.
These zero-dollar checks, appearing on the edit list after a check batch is created, act as placeholders, allowing for a remittance advice to be printed within the check run, confirming the invoice was settled using existing credits.</description></item><item><title>The resolution of disputes and the role of the ECJ in the proposed withdrawal agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A key point of contention in post-Brexit EU/UK relations is the degree to which the UK remains bound to the EU Court of Justice (ECJ). This issue arises first in the withdrawal agreement being negotiated, a draft of which was recently proposed by the EU Commission. While it will eventually affect the future relationship between the two, this post focuses on the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed.</description></item><item><title>What Makes a Great MAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</guid><description>Access to Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs), previously limited to large corporations, is now feasible for small and medium-sized businesses. If your company requires communication between multiple locations within a city, a metro network might be beneficial.
Metro Ethernet is the modern solution for data connections in major cities and surrounding areas. There are two main types: E-Line and E-LAN. E-Line provides a direct Ethernet connection between two points, such as a business and its data center, warehouse, factory, or branch office.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Exchange Email Service Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</guid><description>POP3 email, while widely used by both businesses and individuals, has limitations that might make you reconsider your email service. While convenient, its client-server model, where emails are downloaded to your device, poses risks such as data loss and limited accessibility.
What exactly is POP3? It stands for Post Office Protocol, an internet standard for retrieving emails from a server to a client, like Microsoft Outlook or Mac Mail, installed on your computer.</description></item><item><title>Finally, a Directive safeguarding platform work - What's next?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</guid><description>Catherine Jacqueson, Professor of EU law and Alberto Barrio, postdoctoral researcher on the WorkWel-project, Law Faculty, University of Copenhagen
Photo credit: conceptphoto.info, via Flickr On April 24th, the European Parliament officially approved the directive designed to protect platform workers. Although formal endorsement from the Council is still pending, this is largely a formality. The directive&amp;rsquo;s passage, despite the challenges and last-minute negotiations, signifies a victory. Initially, the Council presented resistance, making its unexpected adoption of the compromise agreement on March 11th surprising.</description></item><item><title>Version 2 of the Project Accounting Timesheet Recalc has been released.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/version-2-of-the-project-accounting-timesheet-recalc-has-been-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 10:42:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/version-2-of-the-project-accounting-timesheet-recalc-has-been-released/</guid><description>A new version of the Project Accounting Timesheet Recalc Utility (Version 2.0) has been released to address a customer&amp;rsquo;s need.
This utility is designed for Dynamics GP users who utilize Project Accounting Timesheets to track salaried employees&amp;rsquo; time.
Salaried employees receive fixed payroll costs. However, when their worked hours fluctuate from the standard hours within a pay period, the general ledger project timesheet costs don&amp;rsquo;t align with their actual payroll expenses.</description></item><item><title>Accruals of revenue in project accounting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accruals-of-revenue-in-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 05:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accruals-of-revenue-in-project-accounting/</guid><description>Discussions about revenue recognition in Microsoft Dynamics GP Project Accounting often take a familiar turn. People ask about managing revenue recognition, only to discover that many handle it by simply recognizing revenue alongside expenses and fees. This leads to the assumption that revenue recognition isn&amp;rsquo;t necessary, overlooking the need for accruals at the end of each month for unbilled amounts.
Sometimes, the conversation shifts to using the revenue recognition module for accruals.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure as a Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</guid><description>Cloud computing is widely understood to have three main levels: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS). The most fundamental of these is IaaS, which forms the basis for the other two. IaaS essentially refers to providing basic hardware and operating system software over the internet.
Infrastructure is fairly self-explanatory: it&amp;rsquo;s the foundational hardware and software needed for computing. When considering cloud infrastructure, the comparison is often made with having your own data center.</description></item><item><title>Why is it important to pay attention to eConnect importing data with leading spaces?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-is-it-important-to-pay-attention-to-econnect-importing-data-with-leading-spaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-is-it-important-to-pay-attention-to-econnect-importing-data-with-leading-spaces/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
A simple Dynamics GP customer query unexpectedly returned zero results, even though the customer existed in the system. Upon closer inspection, it was discovered that the customer ID had a leading space.
While Dynamics GP prevents users from entering leading spaces directly, eConnect allows them during import. This discrepancy can cause issues when querying data, as SQL differentiates between values with and without leading spaces.
This highlights the importance of trimming leading and trailing white space from data during integration.</description></item><item><title>The free sample has now increased in size by seven times.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-sample-has-now-increased-in-size-by-seven-times/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 09:21:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-sample-has-now-increased-in-size-by-seven-times/</guid><description>Dateline: 24 January 2017
The initial free sample of the &amp;ldquo;Minibeds-on-Plastic Report #1&amp;rdquo; has been expanded. Instead of just the introduction, cover, and contents page, it now includes seven pages in total. This larger sample provides a better overview of the report&amp;rsquo;s content.
You can find more information and a free order button at this link: http://minibedsonplastic.blogspot.com/2017/01/blank-15.html.
Thank you to everyone for the feedback. :-)</description></item><item><title>T1 Lines to Support Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-to-support-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-to-support-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>T1 lines are commonly known for their ability to combine multiple phone calls onto a single line using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). However, they can also be used for Voice over IP (VoIP) communication between company locations or to connect with the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) through gateways.
Traditional T1 lines were designed to carry 24 simultaneous high-quality phone calls over a copper wire pair. Each call is digitized and placed into one of 24 eight-bit time slots, synchronized precisely using atomic clocks.</description></item><item><title>Generalized MPLS Improves Optical Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generalized-mpls-improves-optical-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generalized-mpls-improves-optical-networks/</guid><description>Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS) is a technology that accelerates network speeds and supports various protocols, including IP, ATM, Frame Relay, and SONET. It achieves this by encapsulating these protocols within its own tunnels upon entering the network and restoring them to their original format upon exit. Within the MPLS network, routing occurs based on simplified tags inserted into packet headers.
Constructing this specialized network for transporting other network traffic offers the advantage of defining service classes.</description></item><item><title>Is it appropriate for the outcome of the European Parliament elections to dictate the selection of the next President of the European Commission, or are there valid concerns about this democratic process?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s doubtful the European Court of Justice will decide the next European Commission President. Election laws typically set the stage but don&amp;rsquo;t directly determine the winner, although there are notable exceptions like the 2000 US election.
The 2014 Commission President election is unique because the rules changed, and their interpretation is debated. Previously, the European Council appointed the President after European Parliament approval. The Treaty of Lisbon introduced new rules, applied for the first time, stating the Parliament &amp;ldquo;elects&amp;rdquo; the President based on the Council&amp;rsquo;s nomination, &amp;ldquo;taking account&amp;rdquo; of Parliament election results.</description></item><item><title>Vanity Numbers for Small Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vanity-numbers-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 11:03:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vanity-numbers-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>The significance of your business phone number cannot be overstated. It&amp;rsquo;s your lifeline to customers. If they can&amp;rsquo;t easily recall your number, they might dial a competitor&amp;rsquo;s instead. This is where vanity numbers come into play.
What exactly are vanity numbers? They are standard phone numbers designed for easy memorization.
There are two main categories of vanity numbers. The first type spells a word or phrase, similar to personalized license plates.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need a Content Delivery Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The way we deliver content online is evolving rapidly. While you could once manage a website with just a computer and a few phone lines, today&amp;rsquo;s high-definition video and nationwide audiences demand far more resources. This is where content delivery networks (CDNs) come in.
Think of a CDN as a specialized web hosting service. Just as you can host your website on your own server or outsource it, you can also choose between managing your content distribution or relying on a CDN.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>The Cyber Resilience Act as it relates to the Internet of Things.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cyber-resilience-act-as-it-relates-to-the-internet-of-things/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cyber-resilience-act-as-it-relates-to-the-internet-of-things/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip, PhD candidate, Radboud University
Image credit: Grafiker61, via Wikicommons Media
The Internet of Things (IoT), encompassing devices with integrated hardware and software like smartwatches and WiFi security cameras, is becoming increasingly prevalent in homes and industries. However, the cybersecurity of these connected devices is a growing concern. Hackers have exploited vulnerabilities in these devices, as demonstrated by the Mirai botnet attack, where thousands of devices were compromised to disrupt websites and businesses.</description></item><item><title>Why PRI Over T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-pri-over-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 01:54:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-pri-over-t1/</guid><description>PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a popular digital telephone service used by call centers, PBX systems, and internet providers. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN standards.
PRI is often referred to as T1 PRI in regions like the USA, Canada, and Japan because it utilizes a T1 carrier trunk. However, there&amp;rsquo;s also a service simply called T1, making PRI appear as a variation of T1.
Traditional T1, known as channelized T1, carries 24 digitized conversations simultaneously using 24 channels of 8 bits each.</description></item><item><title>The Deceptive Client: The case that confused the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
John Grisham&amp;rsquo;s novels often feature a recurring theme: a determined but outmatched lawyer battling a powerful corporation that exploits the legal system, a vulnerable client harmed by the corporation, a polished corporate law firm doing the company&amp;rsquo;s bidding, and an eccentric judge striving for courtroom order. This formula has been a mainstay of his books for over two decades. However, the settings rarely venture beyond the Southern United States, except for occasional plot-driven trips to Caribbean islands.</description></item><item><title>The complex human rights protection system in Europe: facing challenges, embracing opportunities, and managing risks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</guid><description>Lecture at Waseda University Tokyo, 14 March 2016
Jörg Polakiewicz
Professor at the Europainstitut of the University of Saarbrücken and Director of Legal Advice and Public International Law (Legal Adviser), Council of Europe.[1]
Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to be presenting at Waseda University in Tokyo. Thank you to Professor Koji Tonami and Professor Kaoru Obata for making this lecture possible.
I am consistently impressed by the comprehensive understanding of fundamental rights protection within Japan&amp;rsquo;s legal system.</description></item><item><title>The Year End Update for GP 9 is causing blank sections in the Report Writer when VBA is used.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-year-end-update-for-gp-9-is-causing-blank-sections-in-the-report-writer-when-vba-is-used/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-year-end-update-for-gp-9-is-causing-blank-sections-in-the-report-writer-when-vba-is-used/</guid><description>A client recently requested changes to their Dynamics GP 9 Purchase Order report. Due to limitations with Report Writer, VBA and RetrieveGlobals9.dll were used to modify the report.
Following a recent update (GP 9 2010 YE Payroll Update - KB2435598, version 9.00.0386), the client reported issues with the report printing incorrectly, with edges being cut off. The problem persisted across different workstations and printers.
Testing revealed that the issue occurred when printing directly to a printer, but not when printing to screen first.</description></item><item><title>Is The End Of Cellular Phone Near?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</guid><description>Cell phones are essential to modern life, but a recent development calls into question the future of cellular service. The release of the Apple iPad and its allowance of VoIP applications over 3G cellular networks, along with AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network adjustments for this capability, signal a potential shift in the telecommunications landscape.
Why is this significant? Cellular networks have historically blocked VoIP due to its potential to congest networks and cannibalize voice call revenue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs.</description></item><item><title>1,000,000 Miles of Metro Ethernet Fiber And Growing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t assume Metro Ethernet is a small, insignificant service. XO Communications alone has a vast network of metro fiber, connecting thousands of buildings. And that&amp;rsquo;s just one provider, not even counting Ethernet over Copper options.
Metro Ethernet and its long-distance counterpart, Carrier Ethernet, are the future of telecommunications. The world is shifting from traditional circuit-based communication to packet-based IP networks. While your current internet might be a T1 line, your data likely transitions to an IP-based backbone at your provider&amp;rsquo;s location.</description></item><item><title>The reason I do not accept foreign checks is due to the complexities of North American banking.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-reason-i-do-not-accept-foreign-checks-is-due-to-the-complexities-of-north-american-banking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:48:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-reason-i-do-not-accept-foreign-checks-is-due-to-the-complexities-of-north-american-banking/</guid><description>Years ago, I received a US dollar check from a Canadian Dynamics partner paying their invoice. They used their Canadian bank&amp;rsquo;s US dollar account, thinking it would simplify things.
I assumed a US dollar check for a US dollar invoice would be straightforward. I was wrong.
My local Bank of America ATM wouldn&amp;rsquo;t accept the check. Inside, the teller and even the manager were perplexed. The manager confidently declared they couldn&amp;rsquo;t accept the check because it was a US dollar check from a Canadian bank.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>Comparing Payroll Reconciliation and Tax Flags</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-payroll-reconciliation-and-tax-flags/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-payroll-reconciliation-and-tax-flags/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always simpler to reconcile payroll regularly, handling it incrementally rather than tackling large periods at once. Reconciling means performing these steps after each payroll:
Print the Check Register: This document, usually generated automatically after posting payroll, details your tax liabilities. Print the Payroll Summary Report: Covering the current quarter up to the payroll check date (accessible via Reports-Payroll-Period End), this report should match your cumulative payroll check registers in terms of wages, taxes, etc.</description></item><item><title>Add a Toll Free Number For Next to Nothing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-a-toll-free-number-for-next-to-nothing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-a-toll-free-number-for-next-to-nothing/</guid><description>Upgrading your business phone system can be pricey, but there&amp;rsquo;s a budget-friendly way to add a toll-free number to any phone, even your cell phone, for a minimal monthly cost.
Toll-free numbers are beneficial for businesses with a public phone number. Local customers can call without long-distance charges, but even calls from nearby areas can become expensive. Out-of-state prospects might hesitate to call due to high long-distance rates.
Offering a toll-free number encourages calls from anywhere, as the business covers the cost.</description></item><item><title>Last Minute Online Gifts For Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</guid><description>_On Christmas Eve, instead of the typical peaceful house,
your home is filled with stress as you realize you forgot a gift.
Despite your best efforts, you overlooked someone on your list.
The pressure is on to find a solution quickly.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that can save your holiday!
Search online and find the K.I.N.D site for the perfect gift.
You&amp;rsquo;ll not only deliver a thoughtful present but also make a difference.</description></item><item><title>Don't waste a valuable opportunity: the importance and methods of reforming the governance of European football following the collapse of the 'SuperLeague'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 05:07:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-waste-a-valuable-opportunity-the-importance-and-methods-of-reforming-the-governance-of-european-football-following-the-collapse-of-the-superleague/</guid><description>Professor Stephen Weatherill, Faculty of Law and Somerville College, University of Oxford, analyzes the attempted formation of a European SuperLeague and what it reveals about the weaknesses in European football governance and legal frameworks. He argues that while the SuperLeague ultimately failed, the desire for such a league persists and requires proactive legal and structural reforms to safeguard the European model of sport.
A Persistent Threat
The proposed SuperLeague, driven by wealthy and commercially successful clubs, posed a significant challenge to UEFA, the governing body of European football.</description></item><item><title>Xperience the Sony Ericsson Xperia X10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</guid><description>The Xperia X10 might be the perfect smartphone you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for. It boasts an 8.1 Megapixel camera and a 4-inch touchscreen, which begs the question: do you really need to carry a separate camera?
The Xperia&amp;rsquo;s camera eliminates that need with features like flash, 16x zoom, touch focus, geo-tagging, smile detection, and a &amp;lsquo;send to web&amp;rsquo; option. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable for landscape, portrait, night, beach, and various other settings. You can even edit photos directly on the phone using apps from the Android Market.</description></item><item><title>VPLS Is The Ethernet Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re all familiar with cloud networks, but wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have a private cloud connecting all your business locations?
Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS) offers a solution. While not a fully private cloud, it comes close.
VPLS allows you to share a private multipoint network built on technology like Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS). MPLS networks can handle various traffic types, including Ethernet, making it ideal for diverse needs.</description></item><item><title>ATM Networks: Little Cells Doing Big Things</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atm-networks-little-cells-doing-big-things/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 20:41:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atm-networks-little-cells-doing-big-things/</guid><description>While the ATM acronym might make you think of cash machines, in the networking world, it stands for Asynchronous Transfer Mode. This core transmission protocol, unlike its namesake, isn&amp;rsquo;t something most consumers encounter directly.
ATM is a technology that falls into the same family as Ethernet, Frame Relay, and TDM. Although once considered a potential universal networking solution, it didn&amp;rsquo;t achieve that status. Nonetheless, a significant portion of telecom providers, around 80%, currently utilize ATM within their networks.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper DS3 Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</guid><description>Your business needs more bandwidth, but the price of a DS3 connection might seem daunting. While upgrading from a T1 line to a DS3 might have seemed expensive in the past, prices have gone down. Even with the current economic climate, a DS3 connection could now be within your budget.
DS3, or Data Service level 3, is a digital telecommunications standard initially designed for telephone systems. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the T-Carrier system and works seamlessly with SONET fiber optic networks.</description></item><item><title>Cheap Business Continuity Insurance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-business-continuity-insurance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-business-continuity-insurance/</guid><description>What happens when your business can&amp;rsquo;t operate? It&amp;rsquo;s a disaster, leading to lost sales and potentially losing valuable customers. If customers go elsewhere during downtime, they may never return, putting your business at risk.
While numerous risks can disrupt your business, connectivity is one you can control. Most businesses, even traditional brick-and-mortar ones, rely heavily on electronic connections like phones and the internet to operate.
Losing these vital connections can be devastating.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Phone Service Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes might be considering upgrading their phone systems but are unsure of the best approach. Should they stick with their existing Key Telephone or PBX system and upgrade it, or is it time to transition to VoIP? What many businesses may not realize is the wide range of options that VoIP solutions offer.
The key difference between VoIP and traditional phone systems lies in its network-based approach. While even a single-line phone or cell phone operates on a network, known as the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), this network has limitations.</description></item><item><title>The extent of the 'household exception' to EU data protection law: Is it like Big Brother's Little Brother?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, co-author of &amp;ldquo;EU Law&amp;rdquo; by Steiner and Woods, examines a case about data protection and CCTV use.
Introduction
The Czech Supreme Administrative Court referred a question to the Court of Justice regarding the &amp;ldquo;household activity&amp;rdquo; exception in the EU Data Protection Directive. This case, Ryneš, involved CCTV footage capturing images beyond the operator&amp;rsquo;s property, raising questions about the exception&amp;rsquo;s scope, especially since the Directive states data processing must be &amp;ldquo;exclusively&amp;rdquo; for personal and household purposes.</description></item><item><title>There is an issue with sending PDF reports via email using GP 2010 and Office 2010.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-an-issue-with-sending-pdf-reports-via-email-using-gp-2010-and-office-2010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-an-issue-with-sending-pdf-reports-via-email-using-gp-2010-and-office-2010/</guid><description>During a recent Electronic Funds Transfer setup for a client, I encountered an error in Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010 R2 while trying to email remittance documents as PDFs. The error message, &amp;ldquo;You must have the Microsoft Save as PDF or XPS Add-in for 2007 Microsoft Office installed to send documents,&amp;rdquo; persisted even with Office 2010 (32-bit) installed.
This error, encountered by others as well, hinted at a problem with GP&amp;rsquo;s ability to convert and email reports as PDFs.</description></item><item><title>Cellular Netbooks Are Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Do you spend most of your computing time on the go? If so, a computer designed for mobility might be perfect for you, like one of the new netbooks with built-in 3G cellular internet access.
You might be thinking laptops aren&amp;rsquo;t that bulky and work fine at a coffee shop.
That&amp;rsquo;s true. A laptop with a wireless modem aircard would be comparable to a netbook in functionality. However, laptops are heavier and often carry unnecessary extras.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met.</description></item><item><title>The garden right before the snowstorm.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-right-before-the-snowstorm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:49:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-right-before-the-snowstorm/</guid><description>Dateline: 21 November 2016
(click on picture for larger view)
November in New York&amp;rsquo;s Finger Lakes region has been delightfully mild. I even took this photo of my garden from the roof two days ago.
The tarp in the foreground is full of shredded leaves ready to be spread. The leaves will act as mulch for the winter. You can see several raised beds on the garden&amp;rsquo;s right side with oats and mustard cover crops.</description></item><item><title>Evaluation of the updated EU Council Guidelines on Freedom of Expression in both digital and physical spaces.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods from the University of Essex, and co-author of Steiner and Woods, EU Law, discusses new EU guidelines on freedom of expression.
The European Union Council recently established guidelines for freedom of expression. These guidelines, falling under the Foreign Affairs Council, are designed for application within the framework of the Union’s Common Foreign and Security Policy, similar to previous guidelines addressing issues like torture, capital punishment, and human rights advocates.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Carpenter's Falls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-carpenter-s-falls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-carpenter-s-falls/</guid><description>Published on: 28 March 2017
A recent conversation about knots, sparked by my post on un-bungee cords, reminded me of a daring experience from the early 1980s: my first rappelling adventure.
At the time, I was working as a carpenter for Clancy Edmonds, who had hired Dan, a machinist, for the summer. Dan, a memorable character who rode a Harley Davidson and carried a .357 magnum, even convinced me to get my handgun permit, arguing it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be as easy in the future.</description></item><item><title>The European Union should consider the UK police's use of live facial recognition technology when developing regulations for law enforcement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-should-consider-the-uk-police-s-use-of-live-facial-recognition-technology-when-developing-regulations-for-law-enforcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 14:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-should-consider-the-uk-police-s-use-of-live-facial-recognition-technology-when-developing-regulations-for-law-enforcement/</guid><description>Divergent Approaches to Regulating Live Facial Recognition Dr. Asress Adimi Gikay, a Senior Lecturer in AI, Disruptive Innovation, and Law at Brunel University London, explores the contrasting approaches to regulating live facial recognition (LFR) in the UK and the European Union.
Recent suggestions by UK officials to use LFR for searching national passport databases to combat shoplifting have sparked debate, particularly as London, a city with a high concentration of CCTV cameras, grapples with AI safety concerns.</description></item><item><title>Interview with Eliot Coleman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interview-with-eliot-coleman/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interview-with-eliot-coleman/</guid><description>Dateline: 9 August 2016 AD
Eliot Coleman
(photo link)
I first discovered Eliot Coleman in the 1970s through an article in Organic Farming &amp;amp; Gardening magazine, which I believe I still have. Now 77 years old, Eliot is considered a leading expert among American organic gardeners.
Any serious gardener likely has at least one of Eliot Coleman&amp;rsquo;s books. By clicking the photo link, you can find twelve gardening books he endorses, in addition to his own works.</description></item><item><title>Is the free movement of people in the European Economic Area (EEA) distinct from that in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Karin Fløistad: PhD Candidate, European University Institute; practicing lawyer at Norwegian law firm Simonsen Vogt Wiig
The UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit relationship with the EU often involves discussions about the free movement of people, with the EEA Agreement frequently cited as a potential model. This piece will analyze two key distinctions between the EEA Agreement&amp;rsquo;s approach to the free movement of people and that of full EU membership.
The EEA Agreement integrates the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market with three members of the European Free Trade Association (EFTA): Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition.</description></item><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in C-582/14 Breyer establishes IP addresses as personal data.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The opinions presented are solely those of the author and should not be interpreted as representing the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s official stance.
Background
The Breyer case saw the German Supreme Court (Bundesgerichtshof) request clarification from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on whether dynamic IP addresses constitute personal data under the EU Data Protection Directive and to what extent their storage and processing is permissible for maintaining website functionality.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own Private Cloud Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</guid><description>Lots of small and midsize businesses are using cloud storage, particularly for disaster recovery. However, local storage is still necessary. While Storage Attached Networks (SANs) are a common solution, they&amp;rsquo;re expensive and complex. A simpler option exists.
Introducing Drobo, an advanced hard disk storage solution that&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to use. It works with standard 3.5&amp;quot; SATA drives of any capacity, resembling a straightforward multi-bay drive enclosure. Adding or removing drives, even swapping a 1 TB for a 2 TB, is always possible.</description></item><item><title>Migration of General Ledger Balances - Net Change Compared to Debit and Credit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-of-general-ledger-balances-net-change-compared-to-debit-and-credit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-of-general-ledger-balances-net-change-compared-to-debit-and-credit/</guid><description>I was talking with a client yesterday about their General Ledger (GL) balances from before they started using our system in May. They were puzzled by the activity in a particular account from January to March, seeing only a $100 credit in January, a $50 debit in February, and a $200 credit in March. They wondered why each month didn&amp;rsquo;t show both debits and credits.
It took me a moment to realize that, unlike my usual practice of migrating both debit and credit activity for complete GL history, someone else had migrated only the net change for each period from their old system.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Service Manual Adjustments &amp; Preparing for Use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</guid><description>In the previous post, I finished cleaning and deoxidizing the keypad and RPM panel. The keypad is now responsive, but the cueing up and down button is overly sensitive and needs further attention.
The RPM panel re-installation was put on hold because the plastic mounting fixtures were cracked, a common issue with Beogram 4002 turntables. I was fortunate that the cracks weren&amp;rsquo;t severe and the fixtures were still usable. To repair them, I used acrylic repair fluid while pressing the pieces together.</description></item><item><title>Divergence in regulations after Brexit: Copyright law as a preview of future changes.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</guid><description>Martin Kretschmer, Professor of Intellectual Property Law (CREATe Centre, University of Glasgow)
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the European Union has resulted in the first instance of regulatory divergence. As the UK exits the single market, existing regulations are starting to show cracks.
In response to a question from MP Jo Stevens, former Intellectual Property Minister Chris Skidmore indicated the UK would not implement the latest EU Copyright Directive, despite the UK&amp;rsquo;s prior support for it in the EU Council.</description></item><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU establishes significant limitations on the Commission's power to initiate actions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</guid><description>Steve Peers
It is a fundamental principle of EU law, as taught to every student of the subject, that the Commission has a near-monopoly on proposing new EU legislation - it is the &amp;lsquo;motor&amp;rsquo; of EU integration. This near-monopoly is often called the Commission&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;right of initiative&amp;rsquo;. But does this right also imply a right to withdraw proposals? And if it does, are there any limitations to this power? These questions were addressed by the CJEU in a significant ruling.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth To Support Branch Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</guid><description>Many businesses need multiple locations in a region to stay close to their customers. Connecting these branches seamlessly without breaking the bank is a common challenge. Thankfully, two high-performance networking technologies, Metro Ethernet and MPLS Networks, offer affordable solutions that weren&amp;rsquo;t available even a decade ago.
Carrier Ethernet takes the local networking capabilities of Ethernet and extends them across entire cities. This means easy connection and efficient transmission without needing protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>Please don't end my year...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s debunk some common misconceptions about year-end closing in Dynamics GP:
Myth #1: All adjusting entries must be finalized before closing the General Ledger.
This is false. Dynamics GP allows posting to the most recent historical year. After closing 2009, for instance, adjustments can still be made to it, just not to 2008. This requires enabling &amp;ldquo;allow posting to history&amp;rdquo; in GL setup and ensuring the fiscal period is open in Fiscal Period Setup.</description></item><item><title>Clearing the Dynamics GP User ID field on Terminal Servers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clearing-the-dynamics-gp-user-id-field-on-terminal-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clearing-the-dynamics-gp-user-id-field-on-terminal-servers/</guid><description>This article addresses a known issue in Dynamics GP, specifically regarding user ID retention on Terminal Servers. While convenient for single users, this feature can be disruptive in multi-user environments.
The issue arises when multiple users log in and out of Dynamics GP on a Terminal Server. The system tends to remember the last user&amp;rsquo;s ID, forcing subsequent users to manually replace it with their own. This behavior, though seemingly minor, can be perceived as a security concern or simply an annoyance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Replacement of Carriage Position Sensor Photocell</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</guid><description>Over many years of working with the Beogram 400x, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a wide array of issues, but these turntables never cease to present new challenges. In this instance, a Beogram 4002 exhibited inconsistent behavior when attempting to locate the record&amp;rsquo;s setdown point after pressing start. This pointed to a potential fault in the carriage position sensor.
Initially, I suspected the IR LED, a common culprit in later models like this 5513 Type.</description></item><item><title>T1 PRI For Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 04:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-for-call-centers/</guid><description>When deciding on phone service for your call center, digital options are essential. While individual analog lines work for small setups, they lack integration capabilities and become costly as you expand beyond a few lines.
For call centers with 10-12 lines using traditional PBX systems, digital T1 carrier service is a cost-effective solution. T1 lines offer two configuration options: channelized and PRI (Primary Rate Interface). Channelized T1 provides 24 independent lines suitable for various call types but lacks advanced features like Caller ID.</description></item><item><title>The Rose Is On The Bloom</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rose-is-on-the-bloom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 01:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rose-is-on-the-bloom/</guid><description>Bloom Energy recently introduced its &amp;ldquo;Energy Server&amp;rdquo; fuel cell, presenting it as a significant step towards greener energy and energy independence. This begs the question: how impactful will this new technology actually be?
While it&amp;rsquo;s early to definitively say, Bloom Energy&amp;rsquo;s generators could become a vital part of energy production and management, or even revolutionize our relationship with energy entirely.
The Bloom Energy Server originated from a NASA project aimed at generating air and fuel from electricity for Mars expeditions.</description></item><item><title>My fondest memory from my time at Sterling College in Vermont is from the Dirt Class in 1976.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/my-fondest-memory-from-my-time-at-sterling-college-in-vermont-is-from-the-dirt-class-in-1976/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/my-fondest-memory-from-my-time-at-sterling-college-in-vermont-is-from-the-dirt-class-in-1976/</guid><description>Dated: March 18, 2017
Remembering &amp;lsquo;76 and a Class About Dirt
Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s blog post about soil microbes reminded me of my college soil science class back in the fall of 1976. I was attending Sterling College, although at the time it was a far cry from the established institution it is today. Back then, it was a former prep school attempting to reinvent itself, offering a unique one-year program called The Grassroots Project in Vermont - a very &amp;rsquo;70s endeavor.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics GP OLE Container and Note Files - Part Two</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamics-gp-ole-container-and-note-files-part-two/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamics-gp-ole-container-and-note-files-part-two/</guid><description>Mariano recently provided additional insights on the file format Dynamics uses for its OLE Container files in an update to his informative article about OLE Containers. Utilizing a file compression tool, 7-Zip, he was able to partially deconstruct these OLE files, hinting at a promising discovery. Hopefully, he will share his findings on whether he&amp;rsquo;s successfully deciphered the OLE file format.
Regarding GP Notes, my experience suggests limited consistent usage of the GP Note fields and even less utilization of the OLE Container feature for file attachments or embedding content.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable.</description></item></channel></rss>