<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2006/24 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2006/24/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2006/24 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2006/24/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the UK's new data retention bill in violation of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Despite the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidating the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive in April, the UK government is pushing for continued data retention authority. This piece examines whether the proposed law aligns with EU law and if it violates the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.
The connection to EU law lies in Article 15(1) of the EU&amp;rsquo;s e-privacy Directive. This article allows Member States to restrict certain rights concerning communication confidentiality for safeguarding national security and other serious matters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do national data retention laws fall under the jurisdiction of the Charter?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
After the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidated the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive, a crucial question emerged: do those same rules affect national data retention laws? This post will explain why that&amp;rsquo;s the case.
We begin with Article 51 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights. It states that the Charter applies to EU institutions and bodies, but to Member States &amp;lsquo;only&amp;rsquo; when &amp;lsquo;implementing&amp;rsquo; EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Data Retention Directive's content and implementation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 07:48:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</guid><description>EU Data Retention Directive: A Closer Look By Chris Jones, Statewatch researcher
This article, the second in a series examining the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, dives into the Directive&amp;rsquo;s details and its implementation across EU member states. It builds upon the background information presented in the first post and precedes a final post focusing on legal challenges.
Dissecting the Directive
Article 1 outlines the Directive&amp;rsquo;s goal: harmonizing data retention laws across member states to aid investigations of serious crime, with each country defining &amp;ldquo;serious crime&amp;rdquo; individually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tele 2 and Watson case: Human Rights and National Data Retention Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The Advocate General recently issued an opinion on two cases referred by national courts. These cases stem from the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in Digital Rights Ireland, which invalidated the Data Retention Directive. Both cases examine whether the mass retention of communications data aligns with EU law, raising a critical question: can such broad data retention ever truly comply with human rights?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Data Retention Directive provides the context for the background.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</guid><description>By Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
As the Snowden leaks continue to make waves, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) is set to rule on a case (Digital Rights Ireland, Seitlinger and Others) that could potentially invalidate the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive in its present form. This directive mandates that private companies retain large amounts of their users&amp;rsquo; telecommunications data, just in case law enforcement needs it for criminal or terrorism investigations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An open letter regarding the UK's Data Retention and Investigatory Powers Bill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-letter-regarding-the-uk-s-data-retention-and-investigatory-powers-bill/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-letter-regarding-the-uk-s-data-retention-and-investigatory-powers-bill/</guid><description>Tuesday 15th July 2014
To all Members of Parliament,
Re: An open letter from UK internet law academic experts
The Coalition Government, with support from the Opposition, introduced the Data Retention and Investigatory Powers Bill (&amp;ldquo;DRIP&amp;rdquo;) on July 10th. The bill was presented as a simple extension of existing data retention powers under the EU Data Retention Directive. This Directive was recently found incompatible with European human rights law by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-letter-regarding-the-uk-s-data-retention-and-investigatory-powers-bill/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-letter-regarding-the-uk-s-data-retention-and-investigatory-powers-bill/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on data retention: Mass surveillance is prohibited.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</guid><description>Steve Peers
On July 7, 2005, a relative of mine was on her way to work on a London tube train when terrorists detonated bombs on her train and three others across the city. While my relative was unharmed, dozens of people tragically lost their lives.
This event, along with the prior attacks on 9/11 and in Madrid, understandably fueled public anxiety around terrorism and spurred the EU to introduce additional anti-terrorism measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</a></p></description></item><item><title>National legal challenges to the Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
This article delves into the numerous legal obstacles faced by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, both at national and EU levels. This is the third installment in a series examining this controversial legislation, which has recently been overturned by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The information presented is a result of research conducted by Statewatch as part of the SECILE project, which focuses on the impact, legitimacy, and effectiveness of counter-terrorism measures in securing Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>