<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Letter on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/letter/</link><description>Recent content in Letter on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:53:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/letter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dear UK Members of Parliament, We are writing to urge you to prioritize democratic scrutiny of any proposed changes to UK surveillance laws. Thank you.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:53:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</guid><description>Steve Peers
I have concerns about the lack of democratic oversight regarding UK law changes that impact privacy rights, especially those connected to EU law. Because of this, I joined others in signing an open letter to MPs. This letter was published in the Guardian and other publications. I want to recognize Andrew Murray and Paul Bernal for leading this effort.
This is the complete letter to all members of the House of Commons:</description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion.</description></item></channel></rss>