<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yunnan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/yunnan/</link><description>Recent content in Yunnan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/yunnan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Air China and Kunming Airlines have initiated a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Source: Air China. The image shows representatives from Air China and Kunming Airlines at a signing ceremony for a codeshare agreement on September 3.
Air China and Kunming Airlines launched a codeshare partnership on September 15, 2014.
This agreement allows the airlines to link their respective networks through the city of Kunming. Air China will place its &amp;ldquo;CA&amp;rdquo; code on 26 Kunming Airlines routes, encompassing nearly 500 weekly flights. This expands Air China&amp;rsquo;s reach to various cities within Yunnan province and its neighboring areas.</description></item><item><title>Sofitel Kunming provides convenient access to the city center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 07:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</guid><description>Sofitel, the luxury hotel brand under AccorHotels, has launched its newest property, Sofitel Kunming. Located in the city center, it&amp;rsquo;s the only international luxury hotel in Kunming.
Situated in Kunming&amp;rsquo;s central business district, the 400-room hotel spans the 27th to 52nd floors. It showcases a blend of French elegance and art de vivre with touches of Yunnan&amp;rsquo;s vibrant ethnic cultures and customs.
&amp;ldquo;The debut of Sofitel Kunming signifies a period of rapid growth for AccorHotels in China, as we continue to solidify our dedication to delivering world-renowned, refined French hospitality to discerning Chinese travelers,&amp;rdquo; shared Paul Richardson, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China.</description></item></channel></rss>