<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Holiday on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/holiday/</link><description>Recent content in Holiday on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/holiday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customize SPD paper and electronic greeting cards with your own branding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</guid><description>Source: SPD website.
The SPD, a Singaporean organization supporting individuals with disabilities, operates a supported employment facility that creates physical and digital greeting cards. These cards are suitable for various events like birthdays and holidays such as Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, and Chinese New Year.
Customization options are available for these cards, including adding company branding, personalized notes, or designs for other special events.
Interested parties can explore the complete selection of cards on the SPD e-shop.</description></item><item><title>Immerse yourself in the holiday spirit with the Holiday fragrance by House of Sillage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</guid><description>Source: House of Sillage.
House of Sillage, a high-end perfume maker, introduces its Holiday fragrance for the Christmas season. The perfume features a blend of mandarin, peach, and vetiver, creating a festive aroma.
The design of the fragrance bottle draws inspiration from the illuminated Rockefeller Center Christmas tree in New York City. Its snow globe cap, crafted from 18-karat gold and white gold, depicts a scene of falling snow. The floral and citrus perfume is housed in a hand-polished glass bottle with an ombre lacquer finish.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA announces transport service timings for Eid al Fitr holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) has released the operating schedules for its services during the Eid al-Fitr holidays. The schedule covers various services, including customer service centers, parking, public buses, Dubai Metro and Tram, marine transit, driving institutes, and vehicle testing and registration centers.
Source: RTA. Al Marri.
Moaza Al Marri, RTA&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communication, stated that Customer Service Centers will be closed for the Eid al-Fitr holiday from Sunday, July 3rd, 2016, and will reopen on Sunday, July 10th, 2016.</description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales.</description></item><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</guid><description>Wishing you a cozy and enjoyable Thanksgiving!
We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share a special Black Friday surprise with you tomorrow&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year From Telexplainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-new-year-from-telexplainer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 02:03:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-new-year-from-telexplainer/</guid><description>Have a wonderful and safe New Year&amp;rsquo;s holiday, and a successful 2015!
If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of this Happy New Year Tie, grab one for yourself here</description></item></channel></rss>