<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet Connections on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why The WAN Lags The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</guid><description>Corporate networks are often set up to ensure smooth data flow within the organization (LAN), but the real bottleneck often lies in the connection to the outside world (WAN).
LANs typically use Ethernet standards with speeds of 10/100/1000 Mbps, while WAN connections like T1 or DS3 lines operate at much slower speeds (1.5 Mbps to 45 Mbps). This disparity in speed results in significant slowdowns when transferring files outside the organization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LAN to WAN Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard protocol for local area networks (LANs), but connecting beyond a single location requires a way to bridge the gap to wide area network (WAN) technologies. Traditionally, this meant converting between protocols, which was inefficient. However, Metro and Carrier Ethernet connections now offer a seamless way to link LANs and WANs.
Packet-based networks, especially those using IP, benefit significantly from using the same technology across the entire network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Takes Over, Mbps Prices Fall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/</guid><description>The current economic slump is causing a major shift in the telecommunications industry. While it may seem like a downturn, it&amp;rsquo;s actually creating opportunities for new technologies to emerge, replacing traditional telephone systems with IP-based Ethernet connections.
What&amp;rsquo;s behind this transformation? Surprisingly, it&amp;rsquo;s the high cost of doing business. Although some companies are downsizing, others are seeking better network services at lower costs. As their contracts expire, these businesses are exploring the market for competitive deals, looking beyond just pricing to consider newer technologies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>