<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EU Reform on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-reform/</link><description>Recent content in EU Reform on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-reform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the draft renegotiation deal a legitimate rejection? Tusk's suggestion and the role of national parliaments.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</guid><description>Dr. Katarzyna Granat, Junior Research Fellow &amp;amp; Marie Curie Fellow, Durham Law School Donald Tusk&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A New Settlement for the United Kingdom within the European Union&amp;rdquo; (Draft Decision of the Heads of State or Government), presented on February 2, 2016, provides an initial concrete outline for enhancing the role of national parliaments within the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiation efforts. This note compares the proposed changes with existing mechanisms under the Lisbon Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a 'fast-track' Treaty amendment on the free movement of workers with the Cameron express?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Experts in EU law see Treaty amendments as a monumental event. After the Treaty of Lisbon, significant changes to the Treaty seemed improbable in the near future. However, this prospect is becoming more likely due to David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s push to renegotiate free movement regulations within the EU, a sentiment somewhat shared by the UK Labour party.
This brings us to the crucial question of what form such a Treaty amendment would take...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The immigration issues in the UK renegotiation deal have been finalized.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
David Cameron has successfully negotiated a deal regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the EU. This post, the first in a series about the deal, focuses on &amp;ldquo;EU immigration&amp;rdquo; or, in terms of EU law, the free movement of EU citizens. I will delve into other important matters (competitiveness, Eurozone relations, sovereignty) and the legal structure of the deal later.
The deal comprises seven legal documents: a Decision by the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government (the &amp;ldquo;Decision&amp;rdquo;); a Statement from the Heads of State and Government (an agreed Council Decision); a Declaration by the European Council (representing the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government); and four declarations by the Commission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Analysis of Article 50(1) TEU: Member States' Right to Decide on Withdrawal from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) outlines the process for a Member State to withdraw from the European Union (EU). While seemingly straightforward, the first paragraph of this article raises questions about its interpretation.
Can a Member State unilaterally decide to withdraw under Article 50(1) TEU?
The primary question surrounding the first paragraph of Article 50 TEU is if it permits a unilateral withdrawal decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the draft UK/EU renegotiation deal considered to be 'legally binding and irreversible'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The draft agreement regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership has sparked significant debate. While some, mostly within the UK, believe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough, others, primarily from the remaining EU member states, argue it grants excessive revisions to EU law for a single member state. These are primarily substantive concerns. While I have previously addressed some immigration-related issues within the draft, I will delve into other substantive matters later...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can the EU be reformed without making changes to the Treaties?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is about to begin renegotiating its European Union membership, a process some call &amp;ldquo;EU reform.&amp;rdquo; However, several member states have already rejected the idea of treaty changes. So, is a renegotiation or reform package even possible?
While amending secondary EU legislation (or convincingly promising to do so) without altering the treaties is possible, there&amp;rsquo;s always a risk that such changes won&amp;rsquo;t happen or could be reversed later...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Juncker capable of being a reformist Commission President, like Nixon was in going to China?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 22:41:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A common saying in American politics, &amp;ldquo;only Nixon could go to China,&amp;rdquo; suggests that only a politician with a well-established reputation can persuade their base to accept a major policy shift. Nixon, a staunch anti-Communist, was able to convince American conservatives that engaging with Communist China was in their best interest. This principle might apply to the European Union as well. The recent European Parliament (EP) elections saw a rise in support for anti-EU parties in several Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for humans to make a legally binding commitment to Treaty change?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British Prime Minister David Cameron has surprised many by securing concessions from the EU, such as a smaller EU budget and a Conservative majority in the House of Commons. However, his goal of renegotiating the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership raises the question: are his demands even achievable?
This question arises from Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recently confirmed intention to secure not immediate Treaty changes, but rather a &amp;ldquo;legally binding&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;irreversible&amp;rdquo; agreement that would commit to future Treaty changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The legal status and impact of the UK/EU renegotiation deal.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 14:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</guid><description>Is the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiated EU membership deal legally binding? Steve Peers explores whether the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiated EU membership deal is legally binding and what implications this has. He examines various aspects of the deal, including its legal status, enforceability, and potential for reversibility.
Legal Complexity and Forms The renegotiation deal is comprised of seven legal documents: a Decision by EU Heads of State and Government, a Statement by the same group (including a draft Council Decision), a European Council Declaration, and four Commission declarations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who should have control over the 'emergency brake' on benefits for EU citizens: the Commission or the Council?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
During the UK&amp;rsquo;s negotiations to leave the European Union, a key point of contention arose: the process for enacting an &amp;ldquo;emergency brake&amp;rdquo; to restrict EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to in-work benefits. Should a Member State have the authority to implement this measure independently, perhaps with a requirement to inform the Commission and Council? Or should it be required to submit a request, leaving the decision of authorization to the Commission and/or Council?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>