<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guardian on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guardian/</link><description>Recent content in Guardian on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:53:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guardian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dear UK Members of Parliament, We are writing to urge you to prioritize democratic scrutiny of any proposed changes to UK surveillance laws. Thank you.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:53:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</guid><description>Steve Peers
I have concerns about the lack of democratic oversight regarding UK law changes that impact privacy rights, especially those connected to EU law. Because of this, I joined others in signing an open letter to MPs. This letter was published in the Guardian and other publications. I want to recognize Andrew Murray and Paul Bernal for leading this effort.
This is the complete letter to all members of the House of Commons:</description></item><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Thomas Piketty to bring about reform in both capitalism and democracy within the European Union?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</guid><description>Steve Peers
French economist Thomas Piketty unexpectedly became a prominent intellectual figure, especially in the UK and US, with his book &amp;ldquo;Capital,&amp;rdquo; which presents a new perspective on the relationship between capitalism and democracy.
Maintaining his engagement with current issues, Piketty has contributed to a proposal for EU reform, connecting his academic work to practical solutions.
The EU, once adept at managing capitalism but less so democracy, now struggles with both.</description></item></channel></rss>