<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heat on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/heat/</link><description>Recent content in Heat on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:55:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/heat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Main Capacitor Array with Integrated Efficient 24V Power Supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 12:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 is known to get quite hot, primarily due to its outdated voltage regulator-based power supply. To address this, a modern PCB design with a buck converter-based 24V supply was created as a replacement for the original power supply and capacitors.
The new design features high-quality Panasonic electrolytic capacitors, Samsung ceramic capacitors for the motor phase, and a buck converter for the 24V power supply. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to be easily installed in place of the original components...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-main-capacitor-array-with-integrated-efficient-24v-power-supply/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International SOS offers three tips for managing heatwaves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 02:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/</guid><description>As temperatures remain high in mid-2023, individuals may experience heat-related illness symptoms like rashes, cramps, dizziness, headaches, weakness, nausea/vomiting, or even collapse, according to Dr. Chan Yanjun, Medical Director (Singapore and Malaysia) at International SOS.
Dr. Chan emphasizes that heat-related illnesses and fatalities are preventable with appropriate measures.
Increased Risks
Certain groups are more susceptible to heat-related issues like cramps, exhaustion, and stroke: individuals over 65, pregnant or nursing women, those with medical conditions or taking medications, people frequently outdoors, employees near heat sources or in poorly ventilated areas, and those working with hot objects, wearing heavy clothing/gear, or on long shifts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>