<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tonearm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tonearm/</link><description>Recent content in Tonearm on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tonearm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Germany En Route to California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4000 turntable from Germany, intended for a customer in California. My task is to refurbish the unit and deliver it to its new owner.
The turntable was poorly packaged for shipment, resulting in the keypad plates becoming detached during transit. This led to minor damage to the plates themselves and some cosmetic imperfections on other internal surfaces.
The aluminum surfaces are in surprisingly good shape considering the loose keypad plates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Final Adjustments, Repair of a Damaged Pinth Corner and Test Drive with Bobby Hutcherson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration is nearing completion. Following the installation of new gold-plated RCA plugs, I made adjustments to the sub-chassis, platter height, and meticulously cleaned the aluminum surfaces. To prevent the needle from contacting the platter ribs if the record detection mechanism fails, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit.
Subsequently, I calibrated the tracking weight scale and enhanced the counterweight adjustment mechanism. The original flimsy circlip was replaced with a more durable M3 nut and washer setup, enhancing its resistance to transport-related stress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Final Touches - AC Motor Calibration, Adjusting Platter and Sub-Chassis and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration is nearly complete. After deep cleaning the aluminum panels and platter, I adjusted the sub-chassis and platter height, tonearm lowering limit, and tracking weight.
There are videos on my YouTube channel demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, similar for the 4000 and 4002 models. Another video covers the crucial adjustment of lowering limits, essential because the 4002&amp;rsquo;s system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent damage from photosensor failure. Proper adjustment acts as a safeguard, potentially saving an expensive cartridge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Stopover From Arizona on the Way to Portugal - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</guid><description>Our company provides a service where we assist customers in buying vintage audio equipment from online marketplaces and other sellers. We arrange shipping to our facility, restore the unit, and then deliver it to the customer. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like taking a trip back in time to buy a brand new unit! This post documents the unboxing of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable purchased on eBay from an Arizona seller for a customer in Portugal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway recently arrived for restoration. The packaging was excellent, using the original styrofoam inserts, and the only issue was two loose control pads, which were prevented from causing damage due to tape and foam inside. This highlights the importance of securing these pads with non-residue tape during shipping.
Fortunately, this is an easy repair. Cosmetically, the Beogram is in excellent condition.
The aluminum panels will gleam like new with a thorough cleaning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments, a New Solenoid, and Test Drive with Christoph Spendel &amp; Wolfgang Schlüter Group on MPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</guid><description>The final steps of restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) involved replacing the sensor arm light bulb with an LED assembly and performing standard adjustments. These included calibrating the tracking feedback, platter height, level, sub-chassis height, and arm lowering limit, which prevents stylus damage.
To ensure accurate tracking weight calibration, the C-clip securing the counterweight adjustment screw was replaced with an M3 nut and washer for permanent fixation. This guarantees that the calibration remains consistent during shipping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's "The Love Connection"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project is finished after some final tuning. I made adjustments to the platter height and sub-chassis alignment, documenting the process for my YouTube channel. While my videos feature a Beogram 4000, the method for adjusting the platter bearing and sub-chassis are quite similar for the 4002 model.
The arm lowering limit was the next step, a crucial adjustment to safeguard the cantilever if the record detection malfunctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter Height, Tonearm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>After successfully positioning the top aluminum plates, I could adjust the sub-chassis and platter. This step is crucial as it sets the foundation for adjusting the arm lowering limits and, ultimately, the tracking force. This Beogram will be ready for an initial test run once this is completed. I&amp;rsquo;ve previously provided detailed explanations of the chassis and platter adjustment process on my blog and YouTube channel. Two videos demonstrate the platter bearing adjustment and the subchassis adjustment (using a Beogram 4000 as an example, although the procedure is almost identical for the 4002)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Final Adjustments, Some Odds and Ends and a Test Drive with Cal Tjader</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</guid><description>After switching the original black plinth with a teak one from a Beogram 4002, it was time for the final adjustments and a test run of the Beogram 4000 turntable. I started by setting the platter height, tilt, and alignment with the surrounding aluminum panels. Next, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowest point to make sure the needle wouldn&amp;rsquo;t touch the black ribs on the platter if the platter detection system malfunctioned...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Chico Hamilton on Auto-Repeat!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</guid><description>It was time for the final adjustments on the Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration project. Adjusting the platter and sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking force is always a satisfying part of the process. It means the turntable is ready for its initial post-restoration playback. Observing the intricate mechanics in motion, bringing out the best in vintage vinyl, is always captivating.
This Beogram presented a unique sub-chassis and platter adjustment challenge. The platter was positioned too close to the front right edge of the aluminum plate cutout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Fit and Finish Rework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</guid><description>Restoring Beogram 4002 turntables is a fulfilling endeavor, though it often necessitates revisiting steps multiple times. Despite getting this particular Beogram functioning properly, I was dissatisfied with the fit of some components.
The tonearm cover wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting flush, as evidenced by its crooked appearance in the photo, with the center divider visibly off-center between the fixed arm and tonearm.
A head-on perspective further highlights this issue, along with the misaligned deck trim, showing an undesirably wide gap between the panels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Strange Solenoid and an Alien 7812 Impostor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</guid><description>As I was testing the restored tonearm carriage on my Beogram 8000 with some recently purchased Genesis reissues (Trespass, Foxtrot, Nursery Crime, etc.), I decided to turn my attention to the Beogram 4000 I had recently acquired from Italy. The most critical issue was its malfunctioning solenoid, which appeared unusual and unlike standard B&amp;amp;O components.
Upon disassembling the damper/solenoid assembly, I discovered a makeshift repair job. The original solenoid had been replaced with a different one, and a nail was used as a plunger to activate the solenoid linkage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Very Corroded New Arrival from Sweden</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the Beogram 4000 from Sweden is a mixed bag. Positively, the aluminum surfaces, platter, arm cover lettering, and panels are in good shape, though a thorough cleaning is needed to determine their true condition. The internal components appear original, and the red position indicator is intact. However, there are significant drawbacks.
The black enclosure parts have an unprecedented amount of corrosion, exceeding typical wear and tear. This corrosion is present even on the underside and has also affected the chassis&amp;rsquo;s leaf springs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Arrival from Arizona - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) from Arizona. It needed complete functional restoration. The unit arrived without its cover, shipped in a Beolover container, which is a great way to ensure safe transportation.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the unit as it looked when unpacked:
While a little dirty, it&amp;rsquo;s in decent condition except for the worn-out keypad:
Hopefully, these keypads can be professionally refurbished. On a positive note, the base is in good shape, with almost pristine corners:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival From West Virginia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from West Virginia recently arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was in good condition and shipped in a Beolover container.
Initial inspection revealed no significant damage to the dust cover or hinges. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, but the keypad has some wear. This will be addressed by installing a Beolover Commander remote control module, which allows for keypad-free operation.
The plinth is well-preserved, with minimal damage to the front corners, which are prone to wear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddy Hubbard's 1975 Album "Polar AC"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable to its former glory is always fulfilling. This particular restoration involved several meticulous adjustments before I could relish Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s music.
The first crucial step was aligning the platter and arms flawlessly. Next, I had to align the platter with its surrounding aluminum panels while ensuring the chassis remained suspended, delicately balanced on its spring-loaded arms. This procedure requires precision as the tolerances for these adjustments are minimal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's Liquid Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</guid><description>Following the installation of the Beolover 4002 Commander remote control and internal RIAA pre-amplifier, it was time for final adjustments before testing the turntable. The first step was tracking feedback adjustment. A blue trimmer on the tracking sensor LED light source simplified the fine-tuning of the feedback after the coarse mechanical adjustment of the sensor housing.
Next, the subclasses and platter height were adjusted, followed by the arm lowering limit. The lowering limit ensures the needle can descend below the record surface without hitting the platter ribs if the record detection fails...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 20:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) AC-motor turntable purchased from eBay. I had sent the seller specific packaging instructions and a sturdy double-boxed container, which they thankfully followed, resulting in the unit arriving undamaged. Initial observations are as follows:
The aluminum surfaces are generally in good shape, just needing a cleaning. The platter, in particular, has remarkably few imperfections.
The keypad shows typical signs of use, with fingerprints visible on the most frequently pressed keys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Look (What a Packaging Mess!)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</guid><description>I recently purchased a Beogram 4002 (5513) on eBay for a customer. Although the seller described it as being in very good cosmetic condition and included a new Soundsmith SMMC20 EN cartridge, the turntable arrived poorly packaged in a damaged box. Thankfully, the turntable itself was inside a second box with better protective materials.
Upon opening the inner box, I was relieved to find the Beogram 4002 in pristine condition, as advertised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, which was exciting to receive in its original box and packaging. Upon opening it, I was greeted by a pleasant surprise—a pristine MMC20CL cartridge was mounted on the tonearm. Thankfully, it was protected by a cover and had been gently pressed against the styrofoam, keeping it safe during shipping.
Carefully, I removed the styrofoam and cartridge, relieved to find the cantilever was still centered and undamaged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 02:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, known for its unstable RPM, recently arrived for repair. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in excellent cosmetic condition with only minor blemishes.
The keypad appears barely used. However, the hood has some deep scratches, likely from improper storage. Internally, the turntable looks completely original.
Initial testing revealed the arm lowering mechanism is slow, and the automatic RPM switching from 33 to 45 is not functioning, although manual switching works...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>The recent arrival of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable from the UK marks the end of a summer break for one turntable enthusiast. This particular model is unique, showcasing transitional design elements between the Beogram 4000 and the later 4002 models.
ParcelHero, a shipping company offering swift and trackable service between the UK and US, delivered the turntable securely. Its efficient service, comparable in cost to standard international mail, is commendable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustments, Cleaning the Aluminum Surfaces and a First Spin with Freddie Hubbard!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</guid><description>Following the installation of a new gold-plated DIN 5 plug, the Beogram 4000 was ready for its initial test. The RPM was fine-tuned using a custom Beolover RPM device, aided by the recently installed precision multi-turn trimmers. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that allowing the unit to warm up for approximately 15 minutes before this adjustment is recommended, as the RPM can fluctuate slightly during this period. For fellow enthusiasts, the Beolover RPM device is available upon request via email or the contact form and includes a separate base for convenient setup and occasional RPM checks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Lubricating and Adjusting the Solenoid to Tonearm Linkages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</guid><description>Following the solenoid replacement and removal of the faulty voltage regulator on my Beogram 4000 restoration project, the arm mechanism remained sluggish. This indicated a need to lubricate the connection between the damper and tonearm lift. Additionally, the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s horizontal alignment was significantly off. While attempting to adjust this with the set screw on the tonearm counterweight&amp;rsquo;s connecting arm, I discovered it was glued in place with epoxy, preventing screwdriver access - likely another consequence of a previous repair attempt...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Seattle en Route to Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</guid><description>An Australian customer purchased a Beogram 4002 on eBay from the US and sent it to me for restoration. Upon its arrival, I discovered it was in poor condition, likely due to storage in a basement or attic. The dust cover was particularly damaged, with scratches on the aluminum trim and the surface itself.
Despite the dust cover&amp;rsquo;s condition, the internal components appeared undamaged, including the hinges, suggesting a successful restoration is possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Platter, Sub-Chassis, Arm Lowering Limit and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>To prepare the Beogram 4002 (5513) for testing, several mechanical adjustments were required. The platter needed to be perfectly aligned with the surrounding aluminum plates. This involved balancing the floating sub-chassis within its support brackets. After aligning the chassis and platter, the arm lowering limit was addressed. Finally, the tracking force was calibrated to match the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s weight dial.
Prior to adjusting the sub-chassis, damaged cabinet guidance washers, crucial for securing the top aluminum plates, were replaced with 3D-printed replicas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000, recently acquired in Germany, is about to undergo a complete restoration before being sent to its new home in the UK. A preliminary assessment reveals the aluminum surfaces to be in quite good condition.
The teak plinth is similarly well-preserved, with notably sharp corners.
While the original arm cover shows significant dirt accumulation, thorough cleaning is likely to improve its appearance. Sourcing a replacement would be challenging due to the unique labeling on this model – &amp;ldquo;tracking weight adjusting&amp;rdquo; instead of the &amp;ldquo;tracking force adjustment&amp;rdquo; found on the 4002...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Changing out the tonearm phono cartridge connector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 restoration project was paused until a new batch of Beolover replacement parts for the Beogram 400x tonearm cartridge mounts became available. With the parts in hand, the installation process could begin.
One of the cartridge connector contacts on this particular Beogram 4002 was defective. Whether this was a factory issue or a result of wear and tear is unclear, but the owner&amp;rsquo;s prior problems with cartridge mounting made replacing the connector a necessary step...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Increasing Tonearm Lowering Delay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</guid><description>After installing a new hood on a Beogram 4000 turntable, the author noticed the tonearm descended too quickly. Adjusting the damper&amp;rsquo;s screw didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem, as the tonearm still dropped rapidly despite the damper slowing down.
Further inspection revealed the damper&amp;rsquo;s linkage was positioned very close to the damper plunger. This proximity meant the linkage moved immediately when the damper activated, even before the damper could build up enough vacuum to slow the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s descent effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Colorado - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 08:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable arrived from Colorado for restoration, carefully packaged in a specialized box. The outer cover had several scratches but could potentially be polished to an acceptable condition. The hinges seemed fine, and the aluminum underneath the cover appeared to be in good shape. The control keypad showed only minor signs of wear.
The corners of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s base were almost pristine. However, upon inspection, the metal frames attached to the plinth were loosening, a common issue caused by deteriorating glue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Evaluation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable arrived for refurbishment, carefully packaged to prevent damage during shipping. The unit appears to be mostly original and in good cosmetic condition, with the exception of a worn keypad.
The keypad&amp;rsquo;s stamped metal sheet is not scratched, suggesting a straightforward restoration using a specialized technique. Interestingly, the STOP key shows more wear than the START key.
Further inspection revealed minor damage to the plinth corners and non-original screws securing the dust cover...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustment of the Tonearm Height and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and with the major tasks complete, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the finer points. One detail that caught my eye was the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s resting position, which was noticeably higher than the sensor arm when lifted.
[Image]
Although this doesn&amp;rsquo;t impact sound quality, it was aesthetically displeasing. After consulting the manual, which recommended aligning the tonearm height with the sensor arm, I made the adjustment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism, and Tracking Sensor Bulb Replacement and Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</guid><description>The initial step for restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable typically involves reconditioning the arm lowering mechanism and calibrating the tracking system. In this instance, hardened lubricants had affected the mechanical operation, and excessive sensitivity in the tracking sensor led to uncontrolled carriage movement after the arm lowered. The solenoid and damper assembly is depicted below:
The restoration began by disassembling the mechanism, cleaning all parts, and applying fresh lubrication:
A video illustrating the tracking sensor adjustment process is available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Another New Arrival - A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable that needs some care. After unboxing it, I was pleased to see the effective packing method, similar to what I demonstrate in my 4002 shipping video. The sturdy metal construction of the 4002 makes it relatively easy to ship safely with proper double boxing and precautions.
My initial assessment is positive. The aluminum surfaces are in great shape and will gleam with a thorough cleaning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Idris Muhammad (KU-17) After Platter and Tonearm Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day at the shop, where another Beogram 4002 (5513) is looking and sounding fantastic! The finishing touches involved adjusting the sub-chassis and platter to ensure they float freely and sit flush with the deck&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface. My YouTube channel features two videos demonstrating these adjustments for a Beogram 4000, which are very similar to the 4002 model.
Afterward, the tonearm lowering limit was adjusted, a crucial procedure given the 4002&amp;rsquo;s control system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent photosensor malfunctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): First Contact and Two Dead Transistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 that was already being repaired but needed further troubleshooting. The unit is in good cosmetic condition with minor wear. Upon inspection, the platter motor ran when turned on, but the carriage remained static.
Further investigation revealed that transistor TR20, responsible for the carriage motor control, was faulty. Replacing this component restored carriage movement.
However, the carriage would move only slightly before returning to its starting position...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from California with a Bit of Shipping Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived needing some care, but unfortunately experienced additional damage during shipping. Upon opening the box, it was discovered that the carriage had detached from the pulley, which was stuck to tape residue. Thankfully, the tonearm was secured with tape, preventing it from ejecting through the platter opening and causing more severe damage. However, the tonearm did sustain some impact. This highlights the importance of securing the carriage during transport using foam and tape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From New York</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 18:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently purchased on eBay was shipped using a specialized container to protect it in transit. Thankfully, the seller mostly followed the provided packing guidelines, resulting in no damage during shipping. Upon opening, the turntable was in good condition, with only minor issues.
While the blue tape used on the aluminum surfaces didn&amp;rsquo;t cause any damage to the lettering, there were a few scratches on the platter. These were likely caused by attempts to remove it improperly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter and Tonearm Weight and Limits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</guid><description>The final stage of restoring the Beogram 4002 (5503) involved balancing the sub-chassis, setting the correct platter height, and adjusting the tonearm. To ensure the best range of motion, the sub-chassis must be carefully positioned between the transport lock clamps. The platter height and vertical alignment need to be set so that the platter sits level with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s aluminum covers. This allows for the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit to be established and the tracking weight to be calibrated against the adjustment dial located on the arm weight housing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Floating Chassis, Arm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>The next steps were to make adjustments to the platter, sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking weight. Additional information on this process is available on my Beogram 4000 page, which includes posts and videos. Before starting, I needed to replace the cabinet guiding washers because they were either damaged or replaced with unsuitable substitutes.
[Image of a missing cabinet guidance washer]
A video demonstrating this process is available in my Beogram 4002 playlist on my YouTube channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going over the chassis and mechanical parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</guid><description>The two circuit boards that needed component updates are finished. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s cabinet and its mechanical parts.
I prefer working on the floating chassis with it removed, which is easier since I&amp;rsquo;ll disassemble most of the tangential arm.
This revealed some hidden issues.
Initially, I believed the three chassis lock bushings were okay because they looked fine. However, examining the locking mechanism showed otherwise.
This was the first indication of the bushings&amp;rsquo; poor condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently arrived from a UK seller for restoration. This report outlines its pre-restoration condition.
Upon arrival, the unit was quite dirty but in good overall shape. The dust cover showed typical scratches from storage, many deep enough to feel with a fingernail. However, it can be polished back to good condition. Positively, the dust cover features an aluminum strip instead of the less durable plastic type, and the hinges appear to be intact...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Michigan - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Michigan for restoration, carefully packaged according to instructions. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, with one minor dent on the platter&amp;rsquo;s surrounding plate. The platter itself, keypads, and small aluminum plate are also in good shape. However, one corner of the plinth is damaged. Fortunately, replacement plinth panels were included, which will be installed.
The hood has noticeable scratches, primarily on the surface, and should polish well...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable arrived in need of repair. The packaging was generally good, but the cartridge was not secured properly for transport. Thankfully, the delicate cantilever was undamaged. The first step was to safely store the cartridge in a specialized MMC cartridge box. These boxes are offered to customers who are shipping their Beograms for restoration and are also available for the MMC1-5 cartridges.
An initial assessment showed that the aluminum panels were in good condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (5503) for restoration. The 5503 is the North American version of the 5501/5502 models, evident in the non-functional voltage switch included to maintain a consistent appearance.
This Beogram is in excellent overall condition, featuring high-quality veneer on the plinth and a dust cover with typical scratches that can be polished to near-original clarity. Internally, it appears largely untouched, though there are indications of prior work, such as loose bolts in the tracking and tonearm mechanisms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Chassis, Platter, Tonearm Limits and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. After adjusting the sub-chassis and platter, I set the tonearm limits and calibrated the tracking force. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to finalize the platter height before adjusting the arm, ensuring the correct arm-to-platter distance. My YouTube channel has videos demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, particularly for the Beogram 4000, but the 4002 process is similar.
Here’s the result:
The platter is now centered and level within the main aluminum plate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>