<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cable Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cable-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Cable Broadband on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cable-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is.</description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs.</description></item><item><title>Shop For DSL and Other Broadband Options Easily</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shop-for-dsl-and-other-broadband-options-easily/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shop-for-dsl-and-other-broadband-options-easily/</guid><description>Frustrated with unreliable internet or sluggish dial-up? Now&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to explore new DSL and broadband choices, thanks to an improved online tool.
Shop for DSL, the innovative search engine, has been enhanced for user-friendliness and comprehensiveness. This real-time tool pinpoints broadband options specific to your location and neatly categorizes them for easy browsing.
What makes this service stand out is its location-based approach. Broadband availability, particularly for DSL and Cable, hinges on your exact location.</description></item><item><title>What’s The Best Business Internet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</guid><description>Is your new business in need of internet service for the first time, or does your existing business require better access? You might suspect you could be getting more for your money, and you&amp;rsquo;d probably be right. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the current business internet service options to determine the best fit for you.
The long-standing favored business internet connection for professionals has been the T1 line, recognized for its high reliability and consistent 1.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Bandwidth vs Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</guid><description>Businesses choose dedicated internet services, like T1 lines and Ethernet over Copper, when they prioritize consistent performance and service guarantees, or when shared options aren&amp;rsquo;t available. Cable broadband, on the other hand, attracts businesses with its high bandwidth for a lower cost. Although cable lacks service guarantees, its proven track record and widespread availability, especially during business hours, make it appealing.
The term &amp;ldquo;dedicated&amp;rdquo; in this context signifies that a specific bandwidth amount is exclusively allocated to the user.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.1 Makes Cable Act Like Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cable broadband has undergone significant technological advancements, making it a strong competitor to fiber optic bandwidth for many businesses. Companies that previously considered cable as a backup option are now finding its blend of high performance and affordability too attractive to disregard. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advancements in cable technology and the options it presents for businesses.
Magic #1: The HFC Cable Plant
Cable television started as a basic system, essentially a collection of large antennas feeding signals to distribution amplifiers, providing an improved version of over-the-air television.</description></item><item><title>Why T1 Is Available Where Other Line Services Aren’t</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:47:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</guid><description>Businesses located outside of city centers may struggle to obtain the same quality of network services as their downtown counterparts. While it may seem like options are limited, a reliable and affordable digital telecom service called T1 is often accessible in these areas.
Contrary to outdated beliefs, T1 lines are no longer prohibitively expensive or geographically restricted. They are widely available for businesses, though they may not be suitable for residential use.</description></item><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest.</description></item><item><title>High Bandwidth Dissimilar Line Bonding From Mushroom Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</guid><description>Want to create your own high-bandwidth internet connection without the exorbitant cost of dedicated services like SONET OC3? Combining consumer-grade options like DSL, cable, or wireless might seem appealing, but achieving a reliable, high-speed connection this way is practically impossible with standard routers.
Instead of another router, consider the Truffles appliance from Mushroom Networks. This innovative device combines multiple internet connections, regardless of type, into a single, high-bandwidth connection.
While traditional &amp;ldquo;T1 bonding&amp;rdquo; offered by carriers has limitations in terms of speed and requiring identical lines from a single provider, Truffles takes a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time.</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item><item><title>Cable vs FTTH Bandwidth Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</guid><description>The competition for superior internet speed is underway. Fiber to the Home (FTTH), is perceived as the frontrunner, while Cable Broadband is the contender. It&amp;rsquo;s still uncertain who will come out on top, but one thing is for sure: users with substantial bandwidth requirements will be the ultimate victors.
This clash is unfolding in Washington state, where Comcast, the Cable behemoth, is introducing a 50 Mbps internet service to rival Verizon, the telecommunications giant, and its 50 Mbps FiOS internet service.</description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements.</description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables.</description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speeds Come to Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</guid><description>Cablevision Systems Corp. is pushing the boundaries of broadband speed by offering internet speeds exceeding 100 Mbps over its existing cable TV infrastructure. This new high-speed internet service, launching on May 11th, provides download speeds up to 101 Mbps and upload speeds up to 15 Mbps for approximately $100 per month.
One might wonder how cable TV lines, which traditionally use coaxial cables, can achieve such high speeds, usually associated with fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably.</description></item><item><title>HFC Broadband For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>Many small businesses don&amp;rsquo;t fit into the &amp;ldquo;residential&amp;rdquo; user category but don&amp;rsquo;t require or can&amp;rsquo;t afford expensive traditional business telecom services like T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper. One solution is HFC, or Hybrid Fiber Coax, broadband services.
You might know this as &amp;ldquo;Cable broadband for business.&amp;rdquo; Many home-based businesses successfully use it to manage websites, access online information, and send and receive emails. However, ordering residential service for a business location usually results in rejection.</description></item><item><title>Redundant Business Internet Connection Using Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Large companies have avoided using consumer-grade broadband services due to concerns about their reliability and performance. While it is prudent to use dedicated circuits with service level agreements for critical business operations, there is a cost-effective solution available for backing up telecom services and enhancing internet speed.
Cable broadband has grown rapidly and seen continuous technological advancements, primarily due to its popularity as a consumer internet service. While alternatives like satellite, wireless, dial-up, and fiber optic exist, they often come with limitations in bandwidth, high installation costs, or limited availability.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.0 Fiberizes Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Cable companies have been envious of Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS fiber optic service because it surpasses the broadband capabilities of coaxial cable. However, a new upgrade to the DOCSIS cable broadband standard might change that. This upgrade boosts digital download speeds to rival those of fiber optic connections, all without needing a fiber optic line to the home.
DOCSIS, which stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification, is the standard for cable modems.</description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs.</description></item><item><title>Unlimited Internet's Days are Numbered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</guid><description>Remember the golden age of air travel? You could stroll into an airport right before your flight, effortlessly purchase a ticket, and enjoy luxurious treatment onboard. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a different story. We endure long lines and cramped seats, a far cry from the preferential treatment of the past. Sadly, this shift from luxury to cattle car is coming soon to the internet.
You might be skeptical. After all, the internet has felt limitless for over a decade.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services.</description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance.</description></item></channel></rss>