<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article 50 TEU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-50-teu/</link><description>Recent content in Article 50 TEU on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:17:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-50-teu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union considered valid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart
Introduction
The Treaty of Lisbon introduced Article 50 to the Treaty on European Union (TEU), establishing the legal framework for exiting the European Union (EU). This article acknowledges the possibility of withdrawal, a concept many legal experts believed existed even before the Treaty of Lisbon. Article 50 TEU outlines the withdrawal procedure. However, some argue that it contradicts the EU&amp;rsquo;s fundamental nature and weakens member states&amp;rsquo; commitment to European integration, raising questions about the ideal withdrawal mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition.</description></item><item><title>Putting an end to Brexit? Explaining the Wightman case on reversing the Article 50 notification independently.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
As the deadline for Brexit approaches and Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s conflicting negotiating goals become clearer, there are increasing demands for transparency regarding the Brexit process.
In late 2017, seven Scottish politicians from different parties and legislative bodies in Scotland (the Scottish Parliament, the UK Parliament, and the European Parliament) initiated a legal case in the Scottish Court of Session.</description></item><item><title>The process of withdrawing from the EU: Examining the uses and abuses of Article 50 TEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</guid><description>If the UK decides to hold a referendum on leaving the EU, also known as &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; Article 50 of the Treaty on the European Union (TEU) will be a focal point. This article outlines the exit process for member states. While some suggest using Article 50 to renegotiate UK membership, its legal and political limitations make this challenging.
The Details of Article 50 Article 50 allows any EU member state to withdraw according to its constitution.</description></item><item><title>The Commencement of Brexit: A Summary of the Legal Matters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commencement-of-brexit-a-summary-of-the-legal-matters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:40:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commencement-of-brexit-a-summary-of-the-legal-matters/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
The UK&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave the European Union has significant consequences for both entities and raises crucial questions about their future relationship. These questions include the potential independence of Scotland and its EU membership, calls for a unified Ireland, the potential spread of Euroscepticism in the EU, and the future of the 27-member bloc.</description></item><item><title>Is this the beginning of the end for citizens' rights in the Brexit 'Sufficient Progress' deal?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent joint report on Brexit negotiations, along with accompanying documents, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of discussions. This phase will center around a transition period and the framework for the future relationship between the UK and the EU.
Although a political rather than legal document, this report holds significant practical relevance for the withdrawal agreement. It outlines agreed-upon details concerning citizens&amp;rsquo; rights, the Irish border, the financial settlement, and concluding rules.</description></item><item><title>Legal Analysis of Article 50(1) TEU: Member States' Right to Decide on Withdrawal from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) outlines the process for a Member State to withdraw from the European Union (EU). While seemingly straightforward, the first paragraph of this article raises questions about its interpretation.
Can a Member State unilaterally decide to withdraw under Article 50(1) TEU?
The primary question surrounding the first paragraph of Article 50 TEU is if it permits a unilateral withdrawal decision.</description></item><item><title>Should the UK continue to vote on its EU membership in an ongoing referendum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-the-uk-continue-to-vote-on-its-eu-membership-in-an-ongoing-referendum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:51:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-the-uk-continue-to-vote-on-its-eu-membership-in-an-ongoing-referendum/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent news report suggested that individuals campaigning for the UK to leave the European Union in the upcoming referendum are prepared to demand a second referendum if the outcome is to remain. On the surface, this appears to indicate that these &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; supporters anticipate defeat and are planning to contest the result. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear if this is a strategic message for them to promote, but offering strategic advice to the &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; campaign is not my objective.</description></item><item><title>The lives of UK nationals living in other EU Member States have been significantly altered by Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah McCloskey and Tamara Hervey, Sheffield Law School
Following a string of significant political shifts, many can relate to the feelings of unease and worry stemming from the resulting instability. Currently, those hit hardest are individuals who have exercised their right to free movement without fear of it being revoked. This is the essence of Brexit: a source of discontent for some, a daily news item for others, but for EU citizens in the UK and UK citizens residing in other Member States, it holds the power to drastically alter their lives.</description></item><item><title>Is the notice to withdraw from the EU being revoked? Wightman's opinion suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
Is initiating the Article 50 withdrawal process from the EU irreversible, like jumping off a cliff? Or is it more like going shopping, where you can change your mind along the way, in the parking lot, or even inside the store? Perhaps this change of heart might be due to discovering the promised sale doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, the management is under investigation, and the supposed extensive international food section is just a couple of dusty packages.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the ECJ to intervene in Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 06:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent High Court decision mandates that the UK government must secure parliamentary approval before initiating Article 50, the process for exiting the European Union. While this post won&amp;rsquo;t delve into the national constitutional law aspects, it will examine the potential involvement of EU courts in Brexit disputes.
Following the government&amp;rsquo;s announced appeal to the Supreme Court, some have suggested a further &amp;ldquo;appeal&amp;rdquo; to the European Court of Justice (ECJ).</description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures.</description></item><item><title>Extension and elections: It is important to discuss Article 50.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</guid><description>Professors Catherine Barnard (University of Cambridge) and Steve Weatherill (University of Oxford) explore the implications of Article 50, the exit clause for leaving the European Union. While brief and seemingly straightforward, Article 50 leaves much open to interpretation.
The authors begin by outlining the process for extending the two-year withdrawal period, noting that an extension would require unanimous agreement from all EU member states. They suggest that an extension is likely to be granted if requested by the UK, as it would provide additional time for the UK to either pass the necessary legislation to implement the Withdrawal Agreement or prepare for a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to unilaterally revoke an Article 50 notice of withdrawal from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 14:31:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Currently, there are no indications that either the UK government or the opposition Labour party are contemplating the reversal of the UK&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal from the EU. Neither party seems interested in initiating another referendum concerning EU membership. Nevertheless, spurred by Nigel Farage&amp;rsquo;s recent attempt to garner attention, the possibility of an additional Brexit referendum, which inherently implies the revocability of the Article 50 notice, remains a topic of public discourse.</description></item></channel></rss>