<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Macau on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/macau/</link><description>Recent content in Macau on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/macau/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Special promotions for the Fireworks Celebration at the Mandarin Oriental, Macau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Macau has special Fireworks Celebration packages perfect for corporate events, team building, or client appreciation. These packages provide a unique opportunity to experience the 26th Macau International Fireworks Display Contest.
Source: Mandarin Oriental Macau website.
Available on September 8th, 13th, 20th, 27th, and October 1st, 2014, the package starts at MOP4,388 and includes:
Overnight accommodations in a room or suite with panoramic fireworks views through expansive windows. A special four-course fireworks-themed dinner for two at the Vida Rica Restaurant, showcasing Chef Dominique Bugnand’s modern take on classic French cuisine.</description></item><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr.</description></item></channel></rss>