<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expansion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expansion/</link><description>Recent content in Expansion on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expansion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor outlines four key pillars for a successful expansion into emerging markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, has published an e-book titled &amp;ldquo;Succeed in Emerging Markets: Selection, Strategy and First Steps&amp;rdquo;. This e-book presents a four-pillar model designed to guide businesses entering emerging markets.
The first pillar, &amp;ldquo;market,&amp;rdquo; examines macroeconomic stability, consumer market size, growth, and openness.
The second pillar, &amp;ldquo;population,&amp;rdquo; delves into demographics to help businesses assess how their products or services align with the competitive landscape.
The third pillar, &amp;ldquo;access,&amp;rdquo; evaluates the ease of market entry.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Budget of Singapore provides support for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Ministry of Finance, Singapore. Infrastructure investments were also announced as part of Budget 2015.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2015, presented by Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Tharman Shanmugaratnam, included several business initiatives. These encompassed increased training assistance, a gradual reduction in business restructuring aid, a freeze on foreign worker levies (excluding manufacturing and construction), and measures to encourage innovation and expansion.
Training and development
Shanmugaratnam emphasized the government&amp;rsquo;s commitment to continuous investment in Singaporeans&amp;rsquo; skills development.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF.</description></item><item><title>The Wanda Reign Wuhan has now opened its doors to guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts debuted its luxury brand, Wanda Reign, with the opening of Wanda Reign Wuhan on March 29th. The brand emphasizes personalized service, exemplified by its &amp;ldquo;Imperial Welcome&amp;rdquo; which includes a Bentley service, and its &amp;ldquo;Reign Butler,&amp;rdquo; offering tailored assistance like schedule management and shopping guidance.
Source: Wanda Reign website
Situated near shopping and attractions in Wuhan&amp;rsquo;s East Lake Scenic Area, the hotel is conveniently located 30 minutes from Wuhan Tianhe airport and 15 minutes from the Wuhan high-speed railway station.</description></item><item><title>CoAssets expands its crowdfunding portfolio by including small and medium-sized enterprise projects and sets its sights on Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</guid><description>CoAssets, a crowdfunding company based in Singapore, is expanding its platform to assist Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs). This expansion allows SMEs to connect with potential investors, addressing the funding challenges many businesses face. CoAssets&amp;rsquo; platform already facilitates real estate crowdfunding and will now provide a space for SMEs to seek funding.
Getty Goh, CEO of CoAssets, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s successful history in real estate crowdfunding and the increasing demand for business loans in Singapore as key drivers for this expansion.</description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains.</description></item><item><title>GoDaddy has expanded its presence to 11 Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a global technology provider for small businesses, has expanded its reach into 11 Asian markets. This expansion brings GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based products and customer support services to millions of small and medium enterprises (SMEs) within the region.
With these 11 new markets, GoDaddy now operates in 14 markets across Asia, encompassing 10 languages. These markets include Hong Kong (English and Traditional Chinese), Indonesia, Japan, Malaysia (English and Malay), Philippines (English and Filipino), Singapore (English and Simplified Chinese), South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, and Vietnam.</description></item></channel></rss>