<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VoMPLS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vompls/</link><description>Recent content in VoMPLS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vompls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service.</description></item><item><title>Managed Voice over MPLS For High Quality Enterprise Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations are realizing the financial and operational benefits of MPLS networks. MPLS VPNs are emerging as the go-to solution for connecting multiple sites nationally and globally. But what about voice services?
Traditionally, voice and data are kept separate. Telephone systems rely on a proven infrastructure of switched circuit analog and digital trunking. Most PBX systems are designed to connect to standard copper-pair analog business lines or ISDN PRI digital trunks, which act as gateways to the global PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) connecting every phone on Earth.</description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers.</description></item></channel></rss>