<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Charter of Fundamental Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Charter of Fundamental Rights on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/charter-of-fundamental-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.</description></item><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>The complex human rights protection system in Europe: facing challenges, embracing opportunities, and managing risks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</guid><description>Lecture at Waseda University Tokyo, 14 March 2016
Jörg Polakiewicz
Professor at the Europainstitut of the University of Saarbrücken and Director of Legal Advice and Public International Law (Legal Adviser), Council of Europe.[1]
Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to be presenting at Waseda University in Tokyo. Thank you to Professor Koji Tonami and Professor Kaoru Obata for making this lecture possible.
I am consistently impressed by the comprehensive understanding of fundamental rights protection within Japan&amp;rsquo;s legal system.</description></item><item><title>A new approach by the Bundesverfassungsgericht regarding constitutional complaints: balancing conflicting rights and applying Union law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</guid><description>Lucia Serena Rossi, Judge at the Court of Justice of the European Union*
* Personal opinions expressed in this article are not representative of the Court&amp;rsquo;s views.
** Originally published in Italian as ‘Il “nuovo corso” del Bundesverfassungsgeright nei ricorsi diretti di constituzionalità: bilanciamento fra diritti confliggenti e applicazione del diritto dell’Unione’ on Federalismi.it, February 5, 2020, ISSN 1826-3534.
Table of contents:
Balancing Competing Fundamental Rights in the EU&amp;rsquo;s Multilevel System.</description></item><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church).</description></item><item><title>Is the EU's Returns Directive beneficial or detrimental to the well-being of undocumented migrants?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at the EU Returns Directive: Five Years On Many EU citizens are worried about the impact of immigration, especially when it comes to unauthorized migrants without legal status. Others, however, prioritize humane treatment for these individuals. To manage this challenge, the EU created the &amp;ldquo;Returns Directive&amp;rdquo; in 2008, outlining procedures for returning unauthorized migrants, including detention rules and procedural rights.
Upon its introduction, the Directive faced criticism from NGOs and academics who felt it was overly harsh.</description></item><item><title>The Bosphorus presumption remains in effect in EU law and the ECHR, as demonstrated in the case of Avotiņš v. Latvia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, a PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*, examines a recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR). On May 23, 2016, the court delivered its judgment in the case of Avotiņš v. Latvia, marking the first detailed analysis of the &amp;ldquo;Bosphorus presumption&amp;rdquo; since the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) rejected a draft agreement for EU accession to the European Convention of Human Rights (ECHR).</description></item><item><title>Advancing Gender-Sensitive EU Asylum Law: Examining the Situation of 'Westernised Women'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand, Assistant Professor, and Salvo Nicolosi, Senior Assistant Professor, University of Utrecht
Photo credit: Mystslav Chernov, via Wikimedia Commons
Recent developments in EU law show a growing recognition of gender-based asylum claims. A notable example is the June 11, 2024, judgment by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of K, L v Staatssecretaris van Justitie en Veiligheid. This case, concerning two Iraqi sisters seeking asylum in the Netherlands, centers around interpreting &amp;ldquo;membership of a particular social group&amp;rdquo; within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, specifically regarding &amp;ldquo;westernized women&amp;rdquo; who fear persecution upon returning to their home countries.</description></item><item><title>Mastering the art of releasing control - the Charter of Fundamental Rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Eduardo Gill-Pedro, Post-Doctoral Researcher, Faculty of Law, Lund University: Eduardo.gill-pedro@jur.lu.se
The UK Government&amp;rsquo;s proposition to exclude the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights (the Charter) from UK law after Brexit (clause 5(4) of the EU Withdrawal Bill) has drawn criticism from opposition parties. The Labour party views this as a non-negotiable issue and refuses to endorse any bill that doesn&amp;rsquo;t integrate the Charter into UK law. Keir Starmer, the Shadow Brexit Secretary, previously stated that Labour would only back a deal that meets its &amp;ldquo;six tests,&amp;rdquo; one being the preservation of &amp;ldquo;rights and protections&amp;rdquo; to avoid a decline in standards.</description></item><item><title>Unexpected turn of events? Case C-128/18 Dorobantu: the conditions of detention and the ECHR's relevance in the EU legal system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</guid><description>Ágoston Mohay, University of Pécs Faculty of Law
Introduction
The EU legal system is often viewed as a distinct entity, separate from both international and national law. Within this system, safeguarding fundamental rights is paramount. Article 6 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) establishes a three-pronged approach to fundamental rights protection: 1) the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union, 2) the EU&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and 3) general principles of EU law derived from the ECHR and shared constitutional values of member states.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Court of Justice reconsidering the European equivalent of the 'fifth amendment'? The CJEU makes a decision on the right to remain silent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</guid><description>Inês Pereira de Sousa, Lecturer and PhD candidate at Porto Faculty of Law, Universidade Católica Portuguesa; Researcher at CEID – Católica Research Centre for the Future of Law; Member of ANESC – Academic Network on the European Social Charter and Social Rights; Member of EUCRIM –European Criminal Law Associations’ Forum - isousa@porto.ucp.pt
On February 2, 2021, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) had the chance to reexamine the right to remain silent and the right against self-incrimination in a case originating from the Italian Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>In support of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK House of Commons European Scrutiny Committee recently suggested that the UK should create a law to nullify the application of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights within the UK. This proposal has three major flaws.
Firstly, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t actually clarify the uncertainty surrounding the Charter&amp;rsquo;s application, as the committee suggests. Instead, it would create more complexity in how human rights are applied in the UK.</description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans).</description></item><item><title>Pilate cleanses his hands. The CJEU's stance on pre-trial detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</guid><description>By Adriano Martufi (Assistant Professor, Leiden University) and Christina Peristeridou (Assistant Professor, Maastricht University)
Introduction
The recent judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of DK (C-653/19 PPU, 28 November 2019) has validated two concerning observations about the state of European criminal law. Firstly, Directive 2016/343 on the presumption of innocence has limited practical application, particularly regarding pre-trial detention. Secondly, pre-trial detention is a contentious subject, with both the CJEU and the EU legislator hesitant to establish common standards despite their absence negatively impacting mutual trust between Member States&amp;rsquo; judicial systems.</description></item><item><title>AGET Iraklis Case: Balancing Economic Freedoms and Labour Rights - Can Governments Regulate Mass Layoffs by Employers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis
DPhil Candidate, University of Oxford; Researcher, Erasmus University of Rotterdam.
The AGET Iraklis case, despite its legal and political importance, has not received adequate attention from scholars or the public. Overshadowed by events like the UK referendum on EU membership and significant court rulings on data retention and trade agreements, the Grand Chamber judgment in this case, delivered on December 21, 2016, highlights the complex interplay between fundamental economic freedoms and collective labor rights.</description></item><item><title>The Dublin system: Balancing Mutual Trust and Human Rights Protection in the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated to the Centre of Interdisciplinary Research in Constitutional Law of Saint-Louis University (USL-B) and the Centre of European Law of the Free University Brussels (ULB). The author wishes to thank the Professors E. Bribosia and S. Van Drooghenbroeck for their valuable advice.
Introduction
On February 16th, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) issued a significant judgment in the case of C.</description></item><item><title>Do national data retention laws fall under the jurisdiction of the Charter?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
After the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidated the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive, a crucial question emerged: do those same rules affect national data retention laws? This post will explain why that&amp;rsquo;s the case.
We begin with Article 51 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights. It states that the Charter applies to EU institutions and bodies, but to Member States &amp;lsquo;only&amp;rsquo; when &amp;lsquo;implementing&amp;rsquo; EU law.</description></item><item><title>Prisoner voting is now a legal issue under EU legislation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 05:28:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Jo Shaw, Salvesen Chair of European Institutions
Article 39(2) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights states:
‘European Parliament members shall be chosen through direct, universal suffrage in a free and secret ballot.’
The Grand Chamber of the Court of Justice, in a concise and understated judgment in Delvigne (Case C-650/13; ECLI:EU:C:2015:648) delivered on October 6, 2015, provided further definition to this provision. It found that national policies determining voter eligibility in European Parliament elections fall under EU law&amp;rsquo;s purview, as they implement EU law according to Article 51(1) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights.</description></item><item><title>The Data Retention Directive's content and implementation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 07:48:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</guid><description>EU Data Retention Directive: A Closer Look By Chris Jones, Statewatch researcher
This article, the second in a series examining the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, dives into the Directive&amp;rsquo;s details and its implementation across EU member states. It builds upon the background information presented in the first post and precedes a final post focusing on legal challenges.
Dissecting the Directive
Article 1 outlines the Directive&amp;rsquo;s goal: harmonizing data retention laws across member states to aid investigations of serious crime, with each country defining &amp;ldquo;serious crime&amp;rdquo; individually.</description></item><item><title>Is the non-refoulement principle in the EU's qualification Directive considered invalid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 14:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</guid><description>By Pieter Boeles, visiting professor migration law, VU University Amsterdam, emeritus professor University Leiden
Introduction
The principle of non-refoulement, which forbids returning individuals to unsafe nations, is generally considered absolute. However, ambiguity persists concerning its application within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, which governs the determination of refugee or subsidiary protection status. The Czech Nejvyšší správní soud inquired with the Court of Justice of the European Union on July 14, 2016, about the potential conflict between Article 14(4) of the Qualification Directive and the principle of non-refoulement (Case C-391/16).</description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations.</description></item><item><title>Feedback on the Commission's latest guidance for Family Reunions for Third-Country Nationals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Family life is essential for everyone living in the EU, regardless of their citizenship. For non-EU citizens (third-country nationals), family reunification is governed by the EU Directive on family reunion, adopted in 2003. Recently, the European Commission released new guidance on this Directive, offering potential for its better implementation and understanding. Although the guidance addresses several issues effectively, there are points that require further improvement or clarification.</description></item><item><title>Brexit has not resulted in any legal changes yet, as the Court of Justice of the European Union continues to rule on the execution of European Arrest Warrants issued by the UK before Brexit Day.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While there are many legal discussions surrounding the impact of Brexit, the ultimate authority on these matters, at least for the EU, is the EU Court of Justice. The Court&amp;rsquo;s first ruling on Brexit, released today, clarifies the legal standing until Brexit Day and potentially influences the approach after that.
The judgment in the case of RO addressed whether Ireland remained obligated to enforce a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) issued by the UK considering its impending withdrawal from the EU after triggering Article 50 TEU.</description></item><item><title>Schrems II and the Transfer of Personal Data: You Were Only Meant to Blow the Bloody Doors Off!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued its highly anticipated decision regarding the legitimacy of standard contractual clauses (SCCs) for transferring personal data outside the European Union. This decision is part of a larger effort to challenge the “surveillance capitalism” model employed by many online businesses. While this case significantly impacts SCCs and Facebook&amp;rsquo;s operations, it also reveals the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s stance against mass surveillance, a recurring theme in European jurisprudence.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on police powers in relation to mobile phone theft and EU eprivacy law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ministerio Fiscal contributes to the understanding of the ePrivacy Directive, specifically Article 15, which allows Member States to make exceptions to the confidentiality of communications for certain purposes. This article played a role in the legal framework surrounding the mass retention of communications data from the Digital Rights Ireland case, where the CJEU established that data retention is justified only in cases of &amp;ldquo;serious crime,&amp;rdquo; as per the Tele2/Watson case.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU upholds the right of asylum seekers to family housing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:41:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This piece examines the housing obligations of EU Member States toward asylum-seeking families. The European Court of Justice (CJEU) recently clarified the minimum standards required of Member States in its ruling on the Saciri case. The judgment is a positive development, confirming that regardless of the challenges Member States face in providing reception services for asylum-seekers, families cannot be left homeless or in extremely poor living conditions by denying them financial aid for housing.</description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood.</description></item><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules.</description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues.</description></item><item><title>Doctor U? The CJEU balances the right to a name with passport security.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many individuals possess a flexible understanding of their personal identity, this concept clashes with the perspective of law enforcement agencies. These organizations aim to establish a fixed identity for each person they gather information on to ensure absolute certainty.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently addressed these contrasting viewpoints in a case involving an individual identified as &amp;lsquo;U.&amp;rsquo; This case was among several during that week where plaintiffs were identified solely by letters, a practice the author suggests moving away from in favor of using pseudonyms for clarity and ease of reference.</description></item><item><title>The potential threat to human rights protection posed by the CJEU and the EU's accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The CJEU’s Opinion on EU Accession to the ECHR: Taking the Football Home Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) finally issued its ruling on the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed accession to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). This intricate judgment brings up numerous legal points. This post will present a concise summary of the ruling, examine its implications, and offer an initial critique of the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning.</description></item><item><title>Restrictions on extradition to countries outside the EU due to EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) is a well-known EU law that streamlined extradition between member states, EU law generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern extradition to non-EU nations. Exceptions exist in cases of pre-existing treaties, like those with the USA and Norway/Iceland, or regarding asylum seekers. The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum laws restrict extraditing asylum-seekers before determining if the requesting country intends to persecute them.
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Petruhhin case has changed this.</description></item><item><title>The Dillon Judgment, Exemption of Laws, and Article 2 of the Northern Ireland Protocol/Windsor Framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD researcher, Queens University Belfast, and Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Aaronward, via Wikicommons media
In a landmark decision, a UK court has disapplied portions of a UK Act of Parliament for the first time since Brexit due to conflicts with the Withdrawal Agreement, specifically highlighting the ongoing connection between UK and EU legal systems. This unexpected development, though previously argued for, underscores the UK government&amp;rsquo;s consistent underestimation of Article 2&amp;rsquo;s impact on rights-related cases.</description></item><item><title>Is it necessary to apply the Charter in reconstructing the hierarchy of employment law norms?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</guid><description>The Uncertain Future of UK Employment Law in a Post-Brexit World Niall O’Connor, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The Charter and Brexit
Boris Johnson famously downplayed the significance of the Charter of Fundamental Rights during the Brexit campaign. He argued in a Telegraph article that the Charter&amp;rsquo;s provisions, such as the right to establish a school or pursue an occupation anywhere in the EU, are not &amp;ldquo;fundamental rights&amp;rdquo; as commonly understood and questioned their enforceability.</description></item><item><title>The EU Data Retention Directive provides the context for the background.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</guid><description>By Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
As the Snowden leaks continue to make waves, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) is set to rule on a case (Digital Rights Ireland, Seitlinger and Others) that could potentially invalidate the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive in its present form. This directive mandates that private companies retain large amounts of their users&amp;rsquo; telecommunications data, just in case law enforcement needs it for criminal or terrorism investigations.</description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition.</description></item><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015.</description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law.</description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration.</description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>Is it an early Christmas gift or a disappointment? Examining data retention and the leaked ePrivacy Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
The leak of a draft ePrivacy Regulation on December 12, 2016, has sparked discussions about its implications for data retention. This post will examine this aspect of the draft regulation.
The Article 29 Data Protection Working Party (A29DPWP) had previously advised against introducing new European data retention requirements. This recommendation, reflecting concerns about the existing ePrivacy Directive&amp;rsquo;s allowance for national data retention regimes, is echoed in the leaked draft Regulation.</description></item><item><title>Could this be a parody? The Advocate-General's viewpoint on the Deckmyn case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-this-be-a-parody-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-on-the-deckmyn-case/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-this-be-a-parody-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-on-the-deckmyn-case/</guid><description>Sabine Jacques, a PhD student at the University of Nottingham&amp;rsquo;s School of Law specializing in parody exceptions, discusses the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s (AG) opinion on the Deckmyn case. The case grapples with the interpretation of copyright exceptions for parodies within EU law, specifically Article 5(3)(k) of the Infosoc Directive, which permits member states to allow exceptions for caricature, parody, or pastiche.
Jacques highlights the timely relevance of the opinion, given the ongoing debate over copyright exceptions and the delayed implementation of a parody exception in the UK.</description></item><item><title>The EU Charter of Rights post Conservative party amendments to UK human rights legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many drivers have encountered the unfortunate experience of hitting a small animal that darted across the road at the wrong moment. Reactions vary from distress to indifference, but some feel a sense of triumph, having removed an obstacle from their path.
This last reaction mirrors the Conservative party&amp;rsquo;s stance on EU law within their UK human rights law reform proposals. They aim to diminish EU law&amp;rsquo;s influence, much like a driver indifferent to roadkill.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on data retention: Mass surveillance is prohibited.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</guid><description>Steve Peers
On July 7, 2005, a relative of mine was on her way to work on a London tube train when terrorists detonated bombs on her train and three others across the city. While my relative was unharmed, dozens of people tragically lost their lives.
This event, along with the prior attacks on 9/11 and in Madrid, understandably fueled public anxiety around terrorism and spurred the EU to introduce additional anti-terrorism measures.</description></item><item><title>National legal challenges to the Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
This article delves into the numerous legal obstacles faced by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, both at national and EU levels. This is the third installment in a series examining this controversial legislation, which has recently been overturned by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The information presented is a result of research conducted by Statewatch as part of the SECILE project, which focuses on the impact, legitimacy, and effectiveness of counter-terrorism measures in securing Europe.</description></item><item><title>After the Steinhoff case, the ECB has an increased responsibility to uphold and advocate for the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Diane Fromage, Maastricht University*
* I am grateful to Menelaos Markakis for his insightful feedback.
On March 12, 2020, the Court of Justice dismissed an appeal concerning the Steinhoff case (T-107/17), previously decided by the General Court in May 2019. This case, though not widely discussed, holds significant weight as it clarifies and broadens the European Central Bank (ECB)&amp;rsquo;s obligation to &amp;lsquo;respect the rights [of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (ECFR)], [to] observe the principles and [to] promote the application thereof&amp;rsquo; as stated in Article 51 ECFR, specifically concerning its advisory role.</description></item><item><title>Guardianship, freedom of movement, and child rights: the SM ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*This blog post expands on research that informed the upcoming revised edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Defining a &amp;ldquo;family member&amp;rdquo; legally can be complex, especially when it comes to immigration law and child welfare. The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment in the SM case highlights these complexities, particularly where EU free movement law intersects with the family law of non-EU nations.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU Grand Chamber "Ilva" judgment: Balancing environmental law and human rights from a Kirchberg perspective.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</guid><description>Jacques Bellezit, University of Strasbourg (France)
Photo credit: mafe de baggis, via Wikimedia Commons
To understand the historical development of European construction, one must acknowledge the European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC). Established following the Schumann Declaration on May 9th, 1950, the ECSC marked the first attempt to create a common market for coal and steel, deemed strategic materials. This initiative aimed to not only bolster post-war reconstruction in Europe but also to curb rearmament efforts on both sides of the Rhine during the nascent Cold War.</description></item><item><title>Disappointing CJEU ruling upholds ban on blood donation by gay and bisexual men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice in Case C-528/13 Léger determined that permanent bans on blood donation by gay and bisexual men solely based on their sexual history with other men might be justified in certain situations to ensure high health protection standards. This piece argues that this ruling is disappointing and could lead to accusations of inadequate LGB rights protection or even ingrained homophobia.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU affirms that data protection authorities are independent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent judgment on data protection, while not as impactful as a prior ruling, is still significant. In Commission v Hungary, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) expanded on earlier decisions in Commission v Germany and Commission v Austria concerning the independent operation of data protection authorities. The judgment&amp;rsquo;s implications, however, reach beyond this specific area.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive mandates that data protection authorities be established to uphold the Directive&amp;rsquo;s regulations, in addition to individual legal action.</description></item><item><title>Further information regarding the horizontal direct impact of the principle of age nondiscrimination can be found in the case of Dansk Industries (DI).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 08:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano The Court of Justice, in the recent DI case, further defined the differences in applying rights derived from Directive 2000/78/EC, which prohibits employment discrimination based on religion, disability, sexual orientation, and age, and the general principle of non-discrimination based on age in employment matters.
This builds upon previous landmark cases like Mangold and Kucukdeveci. In these cases, the Court addressed the obligation to prevent age discrimination in employment when challenged by national laws.</description></item><item><title>Rights for data protection and administrative procedures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the cases of YS and M and S clarified data protection rights for asylum-seekers. This judgment could also have wider implications for accessing documents in administrative procedures.
Two asylum-seekers in the Netherlands wanted to see file notes related to their cases. Instead of relying on the EU’s asylum procedures Directive, which grants access to reasons for negative decisions and interview reports but not all documents, they invoked the data protection Directive.</description></item><item><title>Does repealing the Human Rights Act comply with EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK&amp;rsquo;s new government plans to revoke its Human Rights Act (HRA), a move with legal and political ramifications. While the overlap with EU law is complex, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to examine the potential conflicts and consequences.
Assuming the UK remains part of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and doesn&amp;rsquo;t intend to disapply the EU Charter of Rights domestically, the government&amp;rsquo;s objective seems to be weakening domestic human rights protection and separating it from the ECHR, potentially impacting groups considered undesirable.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on conflicting EU and national law obligations regarding detention time limits. Is this a Prison Break?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD candidate, Utrecht University
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed the conflict between EU and national laws regarding detention periods for individuals subject to a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). Specifically, the case considered whether a longer EU-mandated detention period overrides a shorter national one, and whether unclear national legislation on this matter violates the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</description></item><item><title>Can a person be a member of both a national parliament and the European Parliament at the same time?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recently, Geert Wilders, the leader of the Dutch PVV party and a newly elected Member of the European Parliament (MEP), declared his intent to pursue legal action to maintain his position as both an MEP and a member of the Dutch national parliament. This begs the question: does such a right exist?
The crux of the matter lies in Article 39 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, which states that every EU citizen possesses the right to vote in and stand as a candidate for European Parliament elections.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Appeal ruling in Benkharbouche and Janah: State immunity, remedies, and rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Benkharbouche v Sudan and Janah v Libya delves into significant aspects of public international law, the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, highlighting their interplay within the current British constitutional framework. The cases involved employment law claims brought by two domestic workers against the Sudanese and Libyan embassies, respectively. The embassies invoked state immunity under a UK law based on a Council of Europe Convention.</description></item></channel></rss>