<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bhutan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bhutan/</link><description>Recent content in Bhutan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:13:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bhutan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Six Senses Bhutan experience will be available in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. A view of Bhutan.
Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has created a unique experience by linking five distinct resorts in five separate Bhutanese locations, collectively known as Six Senses Bhutan. Bhutan is notable for its isolation, remaining cut off from the outside world until the 1950s and only welcoming its first international visitors by special invitation in 1974.
With 82 guest suites and villas spread across the five intimate lodges, visitors can immerse themselves in the rich cultural heritage and hospitality of Thimphu, Punakha, Gangtey, Bumthang, and Paro, experiencing the &amp;ldquo;Happiest Place on Earth&amp;rdquo; firsthand.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Bhutan made significant improvements to its business climate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</guid><description>Bhutan has significantly improved its business environment, earning a global ranking of 71st out of 189 countries in the World Bank Group&amp;rsquo;s annual ease of doing business assessment. This achievement places Bhutan at the top spot within the South Asia Region.
The Doing Business 2016: Measuring Regulatory Quality and Efficiency report highlights two key reforms implemented by Bhutan. First, obtaining an electricity connection is now faster, taking only 61 days compared to 93 days five years ago.</description></item></channel></rss>