<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eco on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eco/</link><description>Recent content in Eco on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The RYDE Carpool Challenge will begin in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s carpooling app, RYDE, has teamed up with Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage for the RYDE Carpool Challenge. The grand prize? A Mitsubishi Attrage.
The eight-month campaign, which began on April 1, 2016, aims to have RYDE users complete a collective carpool distance of 1,000,000km, thus reducing carbon emissions by 200,000kg. By encouraging carpooling, RYDE hopes to promote a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.
Each month, RYDE will select two winners: the rider and driver with the highest number of successful carpools.</description></item><item><title>Cachet Hotel Group unveils the fresh appearance of URBN Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</guid><description>The Cachet Hotel Group (CHG) has revamped its stylish URBN Hotel in Shanghai, a former warehouse. Led by CHG&amp;rsquo;s renowned fashion designer, Jay Godfrey, the updated interiors offer guests a modern, zen-like ambiance. The use of recycled and reclaimed wood materials adds a natural touch, further enhanced by the neutral color scheme.
Source: CHG. The Jay Godfrey Courtyard Suite.
Photo - http://photos.prnasia.com/prnh/20140911/0861406560
The URBN Shanghai boasts a unique Jay Godfrey-designed suite.</description></item></channel></rss>