<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contactless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contactless/</link><description>Recent content in Contactless on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contactless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australian consumers are pleased to use contactless cards for payment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard survey highlights the increasing popularity of digital payment methods among Australians. Over 80% of Australians use contactless payments, also known as &amp;ldquo;tap and go,&amp;rdquo; weekly. This preference is so strong that a significant number of consumers get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer this option, with some even choosing to shop elsewhere.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and petrol stations are the most common places where Australians use contactless cards. Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, Garry Duursma, emphasizes that Australians view tap and go as a faster and more convenient payment method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>