<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solutions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Solutions on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I'm not sure if my implementation methodology is working properly.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:59:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</guid><description>Christina and Steve rarely collaborate on blog posts due to the coordination involved, but they decided to team up to address common project failures. They believe that most project issues stem from flawed methodologies rather than individual mistakes. A structured implementation methodology like Sure Step can help avoid these problems.
Steve recounts instances where partners sought his help on troubled projects, needing him to fix integrations or customizations urgently and at discounted rates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>