<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Telephony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephony/</link><description>Recent content in Business Telephony on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments.</description></item><item><title>Telephony In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>When we think about cloud networking, we often picture data networks moving information between locations. However, many businesses are also transitioning their phone systems to the cloud. This shift brings both benefits and hurdles.
The traditional phone network is essentially a large cloud network. This system is designed for reliability and high-quality service, handling countless users at once. Users connect to this cloud through a direct line to their nearest local central office, unconcerned with the complexities of the system.</description></item><item><title>Voice over Internet Protocol Phone Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) suggests it will likely replace traditional phone services, including landlines and ISDN PRI. This shift is primarily driven by the transition from traditional telephone networks to computer-based networks, further complicated by the emergence of wireless voice and data services.
Telephone networks, largely analog during their long history, were initially designed solely for voice communication. While attempts were made to use them for data transfer with analog modems, the limited bandwidth of these networks proved insufficient for anything beyond low-speed data.</description></item><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service.</description></item><item><title>Voice And Data On One Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-on-one-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-on-one-line/</guid><description>Most businesses require phone and internet services, often installed separately, leading to a mix of services. However, technology now allows both services through a single line, saving money. But how does this impact quality?
Combining phone and internet might raise concerns if you&amp;rsquo;ve had negative experiences with residential VoIP, where voice quality suffers due to uncontrolled bandwidth.
Businesses have better options for high-quality, reliable VoIP. The key is ensuring sufficient bandwidth, controlled jitter and latency, and prioritized voice packets.</description></item><item><title>Why Are VoIP and SIP Trunking So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</guid><description>When your outdated PBX system needs an upgrade, consider transitioning to an IP PBX and replacing traditional phone lines with a SIP Trunk. This shift to modern technologies is driven by their ability to deliver new features and cost savings without compromising call quality.
Upgrading doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require replacing existing phones. While VoIP SIP phones offer advantages like network connectivity and simplified management, older phones can connect to the IP PBX via interface cards with FSX ports.</description></item><item><title>T1 Phone Lines Offer More For Less</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-phone-lines-offer-more-for-less/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 09:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-phone-lines-offer-more-for-less/</guid><description>When your business expands and your phone bills become a significant expense, it might be time to consider a service that offers higher volume at a lower cost. This is especially relevant if you&amp;rsquo;ve established a dedicated customer contact center or if your business has grown to require a dozen or more external phone lines.
The service that aligns with this need is a T1 telephone line. Unlike a single phone line, a T1 &amp;ldquo;line&amp;rdquo; is a digital trunk line.</description></item></channel></rss>