<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hainan Airlines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hainan-airlines/</link><description>Recent content in Hainan Airlines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:56:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hainan-airlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hainan Airlines is extending its Change for Good program to additional flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Hainan Airlines flight attendants distributing Change for Good donation bags to passengers.
Hainan Airlines is significantly expanding its successful in-flight donation program, Change for Good, to include 16 more routes. The program, which supports UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s initiatives for children, was initially introduced in September 2013 on the Beijing-Haikou route.
As the first mainland China-based airline to partner with UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s Change for Good alliance, Hainan Airlines aims to raise a minimum of RMB 10 million over five years, starting from September 2013.</description></item><item><title>Used cooking oil fuels 1,000 km flight in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</guid><description>A Hainan Airlines flight recently completed a journey of over 1,000 km from Shanghai to Beijing using a blend of conventional jet fuel and biofuel made from recycled cooking oil. The Boeing 737-800 aircraft, carrying over 100 passengers, was powered by a 50/50 mix of biofuel, produced by Sinopec using waste oil from Chinese restaurants, and standard petroleum fuel.
Sustainable biofuel is gaining traction in the aviation industry for its potential to significantly reduce carbon emissions (by 50-80%) compared to traditional fuels.</description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is now offering flights from China to France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</guid><description>Hainan Airlines has introduced a fifth European route to its network, joining existing services to Moscow, Saint Petersburg, Brussels, and Berlin. The inaugural flight, HU7907, departed Hangzhou International Airport on September 3rd, with a stopover at Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport before continuing to Paris&amp;rsquo; Roissy-Charles de Gaulle Airport.
Source: Hainan Airlines. The ribbon-cutting ceremony for the first flight on September 3.
This new service aims to enhance political, economic, and cultural ties between China and France, especially as 2014 marks the 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between the two nations.</description></item></channel></rss>