<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-service/</link><description>Recent content in Internet Service on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 12:27:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rural Broadband Stimulus Hopes To One-Up Dial-up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 12:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</guid><description>Right before the 4th of July holiday, the much-awaited government funding plan for expanding rural broadband access was officially announced through a &amp;ldquo;Notice of Funds Availability (NOFA)&amp;rdquo; and a call for applications.
The application window is short, running from July 14th to August 14th, 2009, so interested parties need to act fast.
Don&amp;rsquo;t expect to see immediate changes if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to use these new broadband services rather than provide them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Stimulus For The Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 04:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</guid><description>Rural America is on the verge of a major internet transformation thanks to a new broadband stimulus program. This program aims to bridge the digital divide by providing $7.2 billion in funding to states, enabling them to improve internet access significantly.
While South Korea is making strides in providing gigabit internet speeds to its citizens, many Americans struggle with significantly slower connections. This disparity stems from two main issues. Firstly, rural areas often lack the infrastructure and competition found in metropolitan areas, resulting in limited internet options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XOHM, XOHM's Got The Range</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</guid><description>Sprint&amp;rsquo;s XOHM (pronounced &amp;ldquo;zome,&amp;rdquo; like &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;) wireless broadband service has launched in Baltimore, marking the start of the highly anticipated rollout of WiMAX as the next generation of high-speed internet. If Sprint successfully implements its 4G vision, WiFi hotspots could become obsolete. DSL? Cable? Why bother with wires when you can have the freedom of wireless connectivity?
This vision relies on a new wireless technology standardized for global use in both fixed and mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>