<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TW Telecom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tw-telecom/</link><description>Recent content in TW Telecom on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tw-telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance.</description></item><item><title>What Dynamic CoS Means to You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern networks are typically converged, meaning they handle various traffic types like backups, file transfers, cloud access, VoIP calls, streaming, and web services. This begs the question: how can we ensure these networks maintain the integrity of each process with so much going on?
The Need for QoS
When we implement Quality of Service (QoS) controls, a network becomes more than just a passive conduit. But why is this necessary?</description></item><item><title>ENLAN Spans The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</guid><description>The concept of unifying all your company locations under a single extended LAN is gaining momentum. Instead of grappling with the complexities of managing countless connections for numerous branch offices or retail locations, a single managed network can streamline this process.
TW Telecom offers a service called ENLAN, which stands for Extended Native LAN. This service provides users with a high-speed, dependable, and secure network that extends the reach of what is typically considered the WAN or Wide Area Network.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth on Demand Complements Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:50:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
One of the biggest advantages of cloud services over traditional IT infrastructure is their flexibility. With a vast pool of virtual servers and storage, businesses can adjust resources on demand, significantly improving productivity and resource usage.
However, connectivity hasn&amp;rsquo;t quite caught up with this shift. Connecting to the cloud often relies on fixed-capacity connections. Upgrading these connections is typically a complex and time-consuming process, creating a bottleneck in an otherwise agile system.</description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining.</description></item></channel></rss>