<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Right to a Fair Trial on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-a-fair-trial/</link><description>Recent content in Right to a Fair Trial on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-a-fair-trial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the EU here to rescue legal aid, or to put it to rest? Evaluating discussions on the proposed Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</guid><description>by Claire Perinaud (FREE Group Trainee)
Access to legal aid is crucial for individuals facing criminal charges, enabling them to mount a proper defense. The EU is developing legislation to address this right, but its impact remains uncertain.
Progress of the Procedural Rights Roadmap
EU legislation concerning the procedural rights of suspects and accused individuals in criminal cases has been developing gradually since late 2009, following years of unsuccessful attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Has the European Court of Justice shifted from being an offender to a protector of human rights in the context of the European Arrest Warrant?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Since its rushed creation after the 9/11 attacks, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) has become a cornerstone of EU criminal law. It replaces traditional extradition with a streamlined system lacking most of the usual limitations. This has worried critics concerned about potential miscarriages of justice but pleased supporters who appreciate the faster return of more fugitives to face justice.
Despite concerns from some EU countries&amp;rsquo; constitutional courts, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) has long dismissed human rights criticisms of the EAW...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bosphorus presumption remains in effect in EU law and the ECHR, as demonstrated in the case of Avotiņš v. Latvia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, a PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*, examines a recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR). On May 23, 2016, the court delivered its judgment in the case of Avotiņš v. Latvia, marking the first detailed analysis of the &amp;ldquo;Bosphorus presumption&amp;rdquo; since the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) rejected a draft agreement for EU accession to the European Convention of Human Rights (ECHR)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advocating for children? The Directive on procedural safeguards for children suspected or accused in criminal proceedings.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</guid><description>Protecting Young Suspects in the EU: A Look at the New Directive If we don&amp;rsquo;t stand up for children, then we don&amp;rsquo;t stand for much.
Marian Wright Edelman
Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
Ensuring fair treatment within the criminal justice system is crucial, and this fairness necessitates different safeguards based on individual circumstances. Children, being particularly vulnerable, require special protective measures, as recognized by international standards such as the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child and the Council of Europe Guidelines on child-friendly justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pilate cleanses his hands. The CJEU's stance on pre-trial detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</guid><description>By Adriano Martufi (Assistant Professor, Leiden University) and Christina Peristeridou (Assistant Professor, Maastricht University)
Introduction
The recent judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of DK (C-653/19 PPU, 28 November 2019) has validated two concerning observations about the state of European criminal law. Firstly, Directive 2016/343 on the presumption of innocence has limited practical application, particularly regarding pre-trial detention. Secondly, pre-trial detention is a contentious subject, with both the CJEU and the EU legislator hesitant to establish common standards despite their absence negatively impacting mutual trust between Member States&amp;rsquo; judicial systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Public Prosecutor’s Office and Fundamental Rights: A Disquieting Lack of Discussion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</guid><description>Michiel Luchtman, Jannemieke Ouwerkerk, Marloes van Noorloos, Pim Geelhoed, Jorrit Rijpma, and Louis Middelkoop are affiliated with the Meijers Committee (www.commissie-meijers.nl/en).
The EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed European Public Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office (EPPO) has sparked significant debate among Member States. The EPPO&amp;rsquo;s role would be to investigate and prosecute fraudulent use of EU funds, with discussions already underway to expand its jurisdiction to include terrorism and other serious crimes. Current political dialogue centers around the necessity of this supranational entity and the potential impact on national sovereignty, particularly within the sensitive realm of criminal justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the case of Schipani v Italy, under what circumstances is it necessary for national courts to seek guidance from the CJEU as per the ECHR?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo; (ECHR) judgment in the Schipani vs. Italy case, issued on July 21, 2015, revisited a topic of significant interest to EU legal experts: the violation of the ECHR by a national court due to its failure to request a preliminary ruling. This judgment, released just before the summer break, might have slipped under the radar for some...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A.T. v Luxembourg: The Beginning of the EU-ECHR Narrative on Rights to Criminal Defense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 02:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</guid><description>Alex Tinsley, Legal &amp;amp; Policy Officer (Head of EU Office) at Fair Trials, based in Brussels. Twitter: @AlexLouisT In a judgment issued on April 9, 2015, the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruled in the case of A.T. v. Luxembourg. This ruling, which will become final unless reviewed by the Grand Chamber, determined that Luxembourg violated Article 6 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). The judgment expands upon the principles established in Salduz v...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>