<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LAN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lan/</link><description>Recent content in LAN on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple locations often need to share data, traditionally relying on T1 lines for connectivity. While multiple T1 lines can increase bandwidth, this approach might not be the most cost-effective solution, especially in metropolitan areas.
Point-to-point Ethernet offers a compelling alternative, often at a lower cost per Mbps, particularly for higher bandwidth needs. Ethernet streamlines data transmission by maintaining its format throughout the network, potentially allowing locations to function as a single bridged LAN.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Services over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:35:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</guid><description>Connecting networks logically often involves Ethernet, a technology that has recently expanded its reach beyond local boundaries. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) connections are increasing in availability and often come at a lower cost compared to other options.
EoC enables standard Ethernet services to be delivered through existing copper telephone wiring. Unlike typical Cat 5E or Cat 6 wiring, EoC is compatible with older copper infrastructure not initially intended for Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>1,000,000 Miles of Metro Ethernet Fiber And Growing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t assume Metro Ethernet is a small, insignificant service. XO Communications alone has a vast network of metro fiber, connecting thousands of buildings. And that&amp;rsquo;s just one provider, not even counting Ethernet over Copper options.
Metro Ethernet and its long-distance counterpart, Carrier Ethernet, are the future of telecommunications. The world is shifting from traditional circuit-based communication to packet-based IP networks. While your current internet might be a T1 line, your data likely transitions to an IP-based backbone at your provider&amp;rsquo;s location.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth To Support Branch Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</guid><description>Many businesses need multiple locations in a region to stay close to their customers. Connecting these branches seamlessly without breaking the bank is a common challenge. Thankfully, two high-performance networking technologies, Metro Ethernet and MPLS Networks, offer affordable solutions that weren&amp;rsquo;t available even a decade ago.
Carrier Ethernet takes the local networking capabilities of Ethernet and extends them across entire cities. This means easy connection and efficient transmission without needing protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over TDM</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 23:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</guid><description>You might be familiar with Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber, but have you encountered Ethernet over TDM? It&amp;rsquo;s worth understanding this technology and its potential benefits.
](http://www.copperethernet.com/)
TDM, or Time Division Multiplexing, forms the foundation of T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. It became the standard for the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) during its transition from analog to digital in the mid-20th century and remains relevant due to its continued prevalence.</description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards.</description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently.</description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?</description></item><item><title>From LAN to MAN to WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</guid><description>The world is currently experiencing a revolution in network technology. While computer networks have historically relied on various communication protocols, some adapted from the telephone industry, there’s a growing trend towards adopting IP as a universal networking standard. This shift towards IP encompasses all network types, from local area networks (LANs) to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and wide area networks (WANs).
This standardization trend originated in LANs. Today, most LANs utilize Ethernet network interfaces due to economies of scale rather than inherent superiority.</description></item><item><title>IP T1 Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been around for a long time, initially used by phone companies to carry multiple calls between their facilities. Eventually, businesses adopted them for their phone systems. When the Internet became widespread, T1 lines were adapted to serve as dedicated internet connections. This might seem odd given their history, but in today&amp;rsquo;s internet-centric world, T1 lines can indeed function as IP connections.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/) While T1 technology was originally designed for voice calls, the fundamental principle is that digital data is just a series of ones and zeros.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices.</description></item><item><title>Can SIP Trunking Supplant ISDN PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses that require multiple phone lines can benefit from digital trunks. While previously only large companies with numerous lines saw advantages with digital trunks, advancements in technology now make them a viable option for businesses with just a few lines and internet access.
What exactly constitutes a telephone trunk? Essentially, it is a collection of phone lines bundled together. Unlike individual analog lines, which consist of a twisted pair of copper wires, a trunk combines multiple lines.</description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?</description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Take a Bow For The SIP Revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</guid><description>A significant change is happening in businesses of all sizes. It&amp;rsquo;s not related to politics, social issues, or processes. It&amp;rsquo;s a subtle change that most employees aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of, a change that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily noticeable and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require anyone to alter their work methods. It simply provides enhanced capabilities and cost savings. This is the SIP revolution.
What is SIP, and why is it so transformative? Watch this brief introduction to find out&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs.</description></item><item><title>What Becomes Of The Broken Hardware?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</guid><description>_While troubleshooting a LAN for faulty wiring, I&amp;rsquo;m haunted by thoughts of server failures. The concept of uptime seems like a cruel joke, and I&amp;rsquo;m desperate for a solution.
What happens to malfunctioning equipment that dies prematurely? I need to determine the root cause of this outage.
The list of underlying issues is extensive, and the network is collapsing. The pressure mounts daily, becoming unbearable.
I examine server logs, looking for answers while facing the frustrated stares of the staff who demand updates.</description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>Extending Ethernet over MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Ethernet has transitioned from a local network protocol to a preferred choice for metropolitan area networks. Its benefits include easy integration with wired and wireless networks, scalable bandwidth without equipment upgrades, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom options. This begs the question: can Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s success in LAN and MAN be replicated in WAN?
Ethernet WAN is gaining popularity, particularly among businesses with geographically dispersed sites. Dedicated point-to-point Ethernet connections are possible, but Ethernet over MPLS presents a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth Gets Incrementally Finer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet service has been very beneficial for businesses of all sizes. It not only keeps LAN-WAN-LAN connections using the Ethernet protocol, but lease prices are also typically much lower per Mbps than older services like T-Carrier and SONET. But wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have the ideal line speed without settling for a service that&amp;rsquo;s too small or paying too much for unnecessary bandwidth?
Fortunately, XO Communications, a leading Metro Ethernet WAN service provider, now offers a wide range of bandwidth options for businesses with on-net fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages.</description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points.</description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices.</description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks.</description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN to Complement Your LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your company&amp;rsquo;s Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at blazing speeds of 1 Gbps or more, making internal network operations seem almost instantaneous. However, accessing resources outside your physical location can feel painstakingly slow. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be convenient if your LAN could extend across cities or even to remote offices? You might be surprised to learn that this is a possibility.
Yes, The WAN is Ethernet Networks can be broadly categorized as either owned or leased.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive.</description></item><item><title>FastE Is The New DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than their T1 lines can provide have usually upgraded to DS3. However, a faster and more affordable option, Fast Ethernet (FastE), is now available.
While you might not know Fast Ethernet as a Metro or Carrier bandwidth service, the term is likely familiar. Fast Ethernet refers to 100 Mbps Ethernet, one of the standard LAN speeds alongside 10 Mbps and 1,000 Mbps Ethernet (Gigabit Ethernet or GigE).</description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Direct Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The internet provides a wide and affordable way to use cloud services. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer consistently low latency, jitter, or high bandwidth, as it was designed for universal connectivity, not specialized performance. If your cloud-based business processes are slower or less reliable than when they were on-site, a direct cloud connection might be beneficial.
A popular cloud service is Amazon AWS Cloud Computing Platform. This platform lets users utilize Amazon&amp;rsquo;s vast computing resources on a pay-as-you-go basis for various services like application and web hosting, backup, storage, content delivery, enterprise IT applications, and scalable databases.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Will Light Your Building</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</guid><description>Ethernet has become the preferred option for WAN (Wide Area Networking), moving beyond its established role in LAN networks. It makes sense to extend your LAN using the same standards both internally and for connecting to remote locations or the internet.
A key advantage is cost-effectiveness as bandwidth needs grow. While a 1.54 Mbps T1 line might cost around $450 per month ($292.20 per Mbps), a 45 Mbps DS3 connection could cost $5,000 per month ($111.</description></item><item><title>The LAN WAN Connection Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 18:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</guid><description>Local area networks (LANs) are standardized and consistent, making them easy to understand and work with. However, connecting to a wide area network (WAN) introduces a new set of telephone company standards that can be challenging for network professionals familiar with LAN technologies.
In the past, connecting to a WAN required specialized knowledge of complex technologies like DS channels and SONET multiplexing. This often involved significant effort to bridge the gap between LAN and WAN environments.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Copper 50 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</guid><description>Businesses that need to connect numerous employees to the internet or move large files, particularly high-resolution images, require more bandwidth than a standard connection provides. Traditionally, they&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded their T1 lines to DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. Now, there are more choices for around 50 Mbps using both copper and fiber optic connections.
DS3 is often considered a copper wireline service because it connects with coaxial cables and uses BNC connectors.</description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards.</description></item></channel></rss>