<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Custom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/custom/</link><description>Recent content in Custom on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 17:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/custom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can iPhone 3G S Be The Universal Gadget?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-iphone-3g-s-be-the-universal-gadget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 17:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-iphone-3g-s-be-the-universal-gadget/</guid><description>People love electronics but hate carrying a lot of them around. A single, universal gadget would be ideal – one that combines the functions of a cell phone, TV, camera, computer, and more.
Such a device would need to be a phone, TV, DVR, high-quality camera, camcorder, audio recorder, navigation system, gaming console, computer, messaging system, productivity tool, radio, eBook reader, music player, stock trading platform, watch, alarm clock, weather tracker, and shopping service.</description></item><item><title>Customized Samsung Galaxy choices arrive in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 07:38:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</guid><description>Samsung is enhancing the customization options for its Galaxy devices in Singapore.
Customers shopping on the Samsung Online Store can now personalize their Galaxy Z Flip4 5G with the Bespoke Edition. This edition offers 75 combinations of glass colors and frame options, including Black, Silver, or Gold frames, and front and back colors like Yellow, White, Navy, Khaki, or Red. Priced at S$1,548, the custom designs are available for the 256 GB variant only, with delivery taking up to four weeks.</description></item></channel></rss>