<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>50 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/50/</link><description>Recent content in 50 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/50/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amber is the sole Hong Kong restaurant featured in the World's 50 Best Restaurants 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</guid><description>Source: World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants website. Dishes from Amber. Amber, located in The Landmark Mandarin Oriental hotel in Hong Kong, has secured a place on the esteemed World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list for the sixth consecutive year, achieving the ranking of 20th. Notably, Amber is the sole representative from Hong Kong to be featured on this prestigious list. The World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list, likened to the Oscars of fine dining, serves as an annual global celebration of gastronomy, acknowledging restaurants worldwide for their culinary excellence.</description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No.</description></item><item><title>The top food in Asia can be found in China, Japan, Singapore, and Thailand, according to Asia's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>For the best dining experience, consider the top 10 restaurants in Asia, according to Asia&amp;rsquo;s Best 50 Restaurants for 2014.
Most of these top-rated establishments are located in Thailand, Japan, China, or Singapore. The top 10 list features two restaurants from Bangkok, two from Tokyo, three from Hong Kong, and two from Singapore: Nahm, in Bangkok, Thailand, is known for its guinea fowl curry with shampoo ginger and holy basil.</description></item><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments.</description></item><item><title>Air China is providing a 50% discount on excess baggage fees to North America if paid in advance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</guid><description>Air China is the first Chinese airline to offer a prepaid excess baggage fee service for flights to North America. Travelers on Air China flights between Beijing and North America who anticipate exceeding their baggage allowance can now pay a discounted fee in advance. This service can be accessed through Air China ticketing offices globally or by calling their Member Services hotline.
Passengers who prepay for excess baggage will save 50% compared to airport rates, paying RMB 650 per piece or the equivalent in local currency.</description></item><item><title>Japan and Singapore celebrate 50 years of diplomatic relations with the signing of a new Memorandum of Understanding (MoU)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-and-singapore-celebrate-50-years-of-diplomatic-relations-with-the-signing-of-a-new-memorandum-of-understanding-mou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-and-singapore-celebrate-50-years-of-diplomatic-relations-with-the-signing-of-a-new-memorandum-of-understanding-mou/</guid><description>Source: Takasaki City. From left: Shinichi Aoshima, President, Takasaki Seinenkeieisya Kyogikai (seated); HE the Ambassador of Japan Kenji Shinoda (standing); Low Yen Ling, Parliamentary Secretary of Singapore Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Education and Mayor of South West CDC (standing); Douglas Foo, Singapore Manufacturing Federation (seated); Kenji Tomioka, City Mayor, Takasaki (standing).
The 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between Singapore and Japan (SJ50) was commemorated in Singapore on November 18th at the Japan Business Expo - Takasaki Day.</description></item><item><title>Duracell batteries provide six times the power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</guid><description>Source: Duracell. To commemorate five decades of providing portable power, Duracell has partnered with TRANSFORMERS: AGE OF EXTINCTION, the fourth film in director Michael Bay&amp;rsquo;s globally recognized franchise, in a battle of good and evil.
Duracell, the renowned battery manufacturer, is observing 50 years of providing portable power solutions. Although the traditional battery design remains largely unchanged, battery technology advancements have significantly extended battery life.
Duracell&amp;rsquo;s latest CopperTop AA and AAA batteries, equipped with Duralock Power Preserve Technology, are ideal for devices like wireless mice and keyboards.</description></item></channel></rss>