<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Networking Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/networking-services/</link><description>Recent content in Networking Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/networking-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation vs Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:29:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</guid><description>The choice between &amp;ldquo;make&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;buy&amp;rdquo; is about deciding whether to handle tasks internally or outsource them. IT managers frequently face this dilemma when contemplating between managing an on-site data center and opting for a colocation facility. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a third option: the cloud.
While both colocation and cloud services are obtained from external providers, the differences between them are significant from an operational standpoint.
Colocation facilities shine by offering a physical space designed for IT needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>