<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portable on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/portable/</link><description>Recent content in Portable on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/portable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling.</description></item><item><title>The ASUS EeeBook X205 is now available for purchase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</guid><description>ASUS has introduced the EeeBook X205 to the Indian market. This 11.6-inch ultraportable laptop is designed to offer a user experience similar to a smartphone and is well-suited for young professionals.
The EeeBook X205 features &amp;ldquo;connected standby technology,&amp;rdquo; allowing for near-instantaneous wake-up from sleep mode and continuous social connectivity, even in standby. Equipped with a quad-core Intel Atom processor, the laptop comes with Windows 8.1 with Bing and is offered in four colors: dark blue, white, gold, and red.</description></item></channel></rss>