<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1899JKBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1899jkbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 1899JKBG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 12:58:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1899jkbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Choppily Rotating AC Platter Motor - Repair of Wien-Bridge Oscillator Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-choppily-rotating-ac-platter-motor-repair-of-wien-bridge-oscillator-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 12:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-choppily-rotating-ac-platter-motor-repair-of-wien-bridge-oscillator-circuit/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project presented a recurring issue: a malfunctioning oscillator circuit responsible for powering the AC platter motor. This was unusual, as previous 4002 and 4000 models hadn&amp;rsquo;t shown this problem. Although the light bulbs managing the circuit&amp;rsquo;s Automatic Gain Control (AGC) weren&amp;rsquo;t visually illuminated during motor operation, suggesting a longer lifespan compared to indicator bulbs, this unit proved otherwise. It&amp;rsquo;s likely that factors like mechanical vibrations, particularly during transport, could have damaged the bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Exploration of Photocell Function in Sensor Arm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:24:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is going well, but it appears someone attempted repairs before. The sensor arm insert, containing the light bulb and photocell for record detection, was in disarray.
Upon inspection, a photocell wire was disconnected, another was damaged from being forced back into the aluminum profile, and the lens insert had heat damage, likely from improper soldering. Thankfully, the lenses were unharmed.
After reconnecting the wire, replacing the non-standard light bulb with a Beolover LED insert, and adjusting the TR14 bias to 1.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Newly Designed Beolover RIAA Pre-Amplifier Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</guid><description>Due to demand, I designed an internal RIAA pre-amplifier board for the Beogram 4000, adapting the circuit from my recent redesign for the DC motor Beogram 4002 and 4004. I installed this new board in a Beogram 4000 that was in for a warranty repair. This post details the installation process; for technical data, refer to my previous post about the 4002/4 version&amp;rsquo;s performance, as the circuits are identical.
The current prototype board has some features that will be absent in the final version.</description></item></channel></rss>