<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tax on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tax/</link><description>Recent content in Tax on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:57:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tax/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Value Added Tax (VAT) has been implemented in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>In anticipation of the January 1, 2018 Value Added Tax (VAT) launch, the KSA General Authority for Zakat and Tax introduced a mobile app on December 30, 2017. This app provides key information about VAT and helps consumers verify VAT registration status of businesses.
The app&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;check&amp;rdquo; function allows consumers to scan the barcode on a VAT registration certificate or enter the business&amp;rsquo; Commercial Registration Number or 15-digit VAT identification number from an invoice to confirm registration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget provides a significant boost to the commercial sector in various ways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</guid><description>In yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Budget, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized exploring new ideas and diversity to help Hong Kong citizens achieve their goals.
He stated his commitment to utilizing resources generated by the community, supporting those in need, and promoting sustainable development to ensure that people from all sectors of society and future generations can benefit from economic growth.
The Budget outlines measures for the cultural and creative sector:
An extra HK$400 million will be allocated to the CreateSmart Initiative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India no longer accepts high denomination notes in the current series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Reserve Bank (RBI) has decided to discontinue the use of 500 and 1,000 rupee notes. These notes ceased to be legal tender as of November 9, 2016. Consequently, ATMs and other cash transaction machines were shut down on November 9 and 10. However, bank branches and government treasuries remained open on November 10.
This move was prompted by the difficulty in differentiating real banknotes from counterfeit ones. The surge in fake currency was negatively impacting the Indian economy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TINA ERP system is compatible with GCC VAT calculations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</guid><description>Source: dcs plus. Graphic for the TINA travel ERP software.
dcs plus, a Romanian company with a Dubai office, has announced that its TINA web-based travel ERP system now supports value-added tax (VAT) calculations for businesses operating in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) region. This development comes as GCC member states prepare to fully implement VAT based on a framework agreement from 2016.
TINA streamlines business operations by collecting booking details from various sales channels and organizing them into standardized, automated workflows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>