<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extension on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/extension/</link><description>Recent content in Extension on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:55:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/extension/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Life is full of challenges, and then you have to deal with the third extension of EU membership.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This extension was unexpected. Despite the Benn Act, which mandated the Prime Minister to request a three-month extension for EU membership if Parliament failed to approve a withdrawal agreement by October 19, the Prime Minister insisted he would rather resign than comply. Fueled by ambiguous sources within Downing Street, there was persistent speculation that the Benn Act was unconstitutional, riddled with loopholes, would be superseded by emergency powers, or violated EU law.</description></item><item><title>The Legal Implications of Extending EU Membership and Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-implications-of-extending-eu-membership-and-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-implications-of-extending-eu-membership-and-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*This blog post was updated after the official decision extending EU membership was approved.
With the Brexit deadline of March 29th approaching and no approval for the proposed withdrawal agreement, the European Council convened and agreed to extend the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership on March 21st. The UK formally accepted the extension on March 22nd. This raises several legal questions regarding extending EU membership.</description></item><item><title>If the UK remains a member of the EU past May 22nd, it will be necessary for the country to hold European Parliament elections in order to uphold democratic principles.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</guid><description>Professor Eleanor Spaventa, Bocconi University
The UK&amp;rsquo;s political climate surrounding Brexit is highly unstable. Prime Minister May&amp;rsquo;s strategy of delaying a decision may or may not work, but it seems to have created a situation where extending Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union is unavoidable. If Parliament approves the Withdrawal Agreement this week, the UK will need more time to implement the necessary legislation before leaving the EU.</description></item><item><title>Extension and elections: It is important to discuss Article 50.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</guid><description>Professors Catherine Barnard (University of Cambridge) and Steve Weatherill (University of Oxford) explore the implications of Article 50, the exit clause for leaving the European Union. While brief and seemingly straightforward, Article 50 leaves much open to interpretation.
The authors begin by outlining the process for extending the two-year withdrawal period, noting that an extension would require unanimous agreement from all EU member states. They suggest that an extension is likely to be granted if requested by the UK, as it would provide additional time for the UK to either pass the necessary legislation to implement the Withdrawal Agreement or prepare for a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit.</description></item></channel></rss>