<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Noise on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/noise/</link><description>Recent content in Noise on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/noise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75.</description></item><item><title>Bose's sleepbuds are specifically created to improve our sleep quality by masking noise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</guid><description>Bose has introduced noise-masking sleepbuds — wireless earbuds designed to combat common sleep-disrupting noises with a blend of comfortable design and soothing sounds.
Source: Bose. Bose sleepbuds offer noise
masking, not noise cancellation.
These sleepbuds, the most compact product Bose has developed, come equipped with 10 preloaded &amp;ldquo;sleeptracks.&amp;rdquo; These tracks are designed to mimic the frequencies of common noises like snoring, neighbors, dogs, and traffic, effectively masking them with calming audio.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of Beolover Commander MkII Remote and Internal RIAA Pre-Amp Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 09:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</guid><description>The owner of the Beogram 4002 (5513) requested the installation of a 4002 Commander remote control and an internal RIAA pre-amplifier module. The Commander enables complete control of the 4002 using an Apple remote, while the RIAA provides a strong output signal, allowing direct connection to modern amplifiers via CD/DVD/AUX inputs.
The first image displays the RIAA board and its mounting adapter, which elevates it above the output PCB headers.</description></item></channel></rss>