<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-line/</link><description>Recent content in Private Line on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Using T1 Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:54:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</guid><description>T1 lines have diverse applications, including linking offices within a city or across the country. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how this is achieved and the available options.
The fundamental interoffice connection is a point-to-point T1 line, a circuit connecting two specific locations. It runs from one business site to the nearest telecom central office, then between central offices, and finally to the other location.
You might wonder why not directly connect locations with wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Point to Point Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Secure and transparent data transfer is crucial. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some popular methods to achieve this.
What Are Dedicated Private Lines?
Imagine a dedicated private line as a secure connection between two points facilitated by a carrier. It&amp;rsquo;s like having your own wiring, but provided by a third party, spanning across cities or even globally.
T1 Dedicated Lines
T1 lines are the digital version of old-school &amp;ldquo;dry loops&amp;rdquo; used by radio stations and alarm systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>