<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hood on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hood/</link><description>Recent content in Hood on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>My work on restoring the 4002 continues, and today involved polishing the hood – a task that&amp;rsquo;s quite a workout! The plexiglass hood had some noticeable scratches:
I began by using 200 grit sandpaper to create a consistent surface:
Then I gradually polished it using Micromesh polishing cloths:
The final stage involved Micromesh Micro-Gloss:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Hood Mounting Screw Springs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</guid><description>During my quest for the ideal Beogram 4000 turntable, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that none of the early models possess the hood mounting screw springs found on the later Beogram 4002 and 4004. These springs make removing and attaching the hood significantly easier. After consulting the service manuals, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that the Beogram 4000 was not designed with these springs. It seems B&amp;amp;O employed a continuous improvement approach, refining their designs over time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</guid><description>I am currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) and focused on refurbishing its dust cover. As you can see in the first image, the cover had multiple scratches and abrasions common for its age.
My first step was to sand the cover using 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the imperfections.
Following this, I used a Micro-Mesh polishing cloth to restore the cover&amp;rsquo;s clarity. The final result is a clear and revitalized dust cover.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Intermittent "17" Position Switch Causing Immediate Touchdown After Launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</guid><description>I thought I was finished with this Beogram 4000 turntable after refurbishing its dust cover. However, a new problem emerged. After playing a few records, the tonearm would drop next to the platter as soon as I pressed &amp;ldquo;ON.&amp;rdquo; Luckily, the stylus wasn&amp;rsquo;t damaged (thanks to proper arm height adjustment), but I clearly needed to examine the carriage mechanism&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;17&amp;rdquo; position switch. This particular switch is the most troublesome of the position switches because it&amp;rsquo;s the only &amp;ldquo;break switch.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: A New Day, a New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</guid><description>I recently got a new dust cover for a Beogram turntable from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, so they have a seamless look, unlike older reproduction covers that were made by fusing together laser-cut pieces. The result is a cover that&amp;rsquo;s indistinguishable from the original.
This photo shows the new cover:
The hinge for the cover was missing the small plastic pieces that prevent the spring mechanism from rubbing against the hinge&amp;rsquo;s metal parts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Plexiglass Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>The restoration of my Beogram 4000 is nearly complete. The final cosmetic touch was adding a new, reproduction dust cover from Classic Audio in Denmark. They also supplied a matching aluminum trim piece for the back edge. Installing the dust cover was simple.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the process:
This image showcases the original hinge being installed with new stainless steel screws:
The pre-drilled holes in the new cover aligned perfectly, and the screws went in just like the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 02:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>I finally decided to refurbish the dust cover of the Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway, a task that takes me around 3 hours. I had been putting it off because I was enjoying working on a custom transformer for a Beomaster 4000 receiver.
As is common with vintage turntables, the dust cover on this Beogram 4000 was showing its age. It had numerous scratches and blemishes, as you can see here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Brand New Hood Fatally Damaged Due to Bent Hood Hinges! - Straightening Hinges Out and Installation of Another Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) for a Florida-based client and installed a new dust cover purchased from beoparts-shop in Denmark. These dust covers are remarkable replicas, made with the same die-cast process as the originals, resulting in a seamless finish.
However, a problem arose with this particular dust cover. When closing it, there was slight friction on the hinge approximately halfway through its movement. While I initially dismissed it as an insignificant tolerance issue common in older manufacturing, the issue escalated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</guid><description>The final stage of my recent Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project involved reviving the dust cover. Like many Beograms of its era, the cover required attention, particularly the rubber bumpers which needed replacing. The extent of the damage is evident in this photo:
Fortunately, the scratches weren&amp;rsquo;t severe. A 320-grit sanding step effectively leveled the plexiglass, preparing it for polishing to regain its transparency:
After approximately ten stages of polishing, using progressively finer sandpaper and polishing cloths, the cover regained its shine:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Polishing and Exchange of the Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 19:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration project required a hood restoration. I had two hoods: one had a cracked corner, and the other had a good plexiglass body but a corroded hinge.
Corrosion is common on Beogram 4000 hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s fixable with sanding and repainting, but finding a good hinge is preferable. Luckily, the cracked hood had a usable hinge, so I decided to swap them.
Removing the hinge requires care to avoid damaging the aluminum strip on the back of the hood.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Exchange of Trim, Fixing Cracked Hinges, Spray Painting Corroded Metal Parts and Polishing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a damaged dust cover. It was scratched, the metal hinges were corroded, the plexiglass around the hinges was cracked, and it had the typical early-model plastic trim that imitated aluminum.
To start, I removed the plastic trim. It was attached with contact cement, so I warmed the dust cover in the oven at approximately 80 degrees Celsius (wrapped in aluminum foil to prevent hot spots) to soften the adhesive.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Restored Keypad and Plinth, a New Hood and Installation of the Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I finished restoring the functionality of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513), a project detailed in this post. Here&amp;rsquo;s how the unit appeared at that stage:
Although functionally restored, there were two noticeable cosmetic issues: a bleached area on the plinth and typical keypad wear from finger contact. It appears that skin oils negatively affect the keypad coating:
My client opted for a refurbished keypad. Additionally, the RPM panel&amp;rsquo;s plastic securing clamps were cracked, a common issue causing the panel to detach.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a Brand New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</guid><description>Before returning the recently restored Beogram 4002 (5513) to its owner, one final detail needed attention: the original dust cover showed early signs of cracking around the hinges.
The owner opted for a brand new replacement dust cover from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These reproduction dust covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, resulting in a seamless look, unlike previous versions made by fusing laser-cut panels. The result is indistinguishable from the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:11:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>As a final step in restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, the author polished its dust cover. This is a multi-step process that can take several hours, especially since this cover had significant damage.
The author began by protecting the Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen logo with layers of insulation tape to prevent accidental sanding. They then used 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the deep scratches, leaving a surface that resembled wood.
To restore the shine, they progressed through approximately ten grades of sandpaper and micro-mesh polishing cloths, finishing with a polishing liquid.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of a Cracked Hood - Another Process Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on has a cracked hood around the hinge attachments. The left side was entirely detached, and the right side had a crack extending around one of the holes.
The right side had a crack going all the way around one of the attachment holes:
To begin, I glued the broken pieces back together using Weld-On #4 acrylic solvent. This low-viscosity solvent is ideal for injecting into cracks, as capillary action draws it in.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Polishing the Hood and a Strange Hinge Pin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 12:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m completing the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable by addressing the final detail: polishing the dust cover. This one, like many I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered, had scratches from improper storage.
This particular unit had a non-original hinge pin, longer than the original, causing it to protrude. I shortened it, restoring a flush fit. The aluminum trim on the other side had also detached, which I reattached using double-sided tape for easy future removal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</guid><description>During a recent Beogram 4000 restoration, my customer opted for a brand new reproduction hood from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These hoods mark a significant advancement in Beogram 400x restoration. Crafted through injection molding, they perfectly mirror the original hoods, eliminating the seams found in laser-cut and fused alternatives.
Simply put, these hoods are identical in appearance to the originals. Developed by Beoworld&amp;rsquo;s Dillen, their availability has greatly benefited Beogram 400x restorations.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Plexiglass Hood With Laser Cut Patches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</guid><description>The hinge area is the most delicate part of plexiglass hoods found on Beogram turntables. It&amp;rsquo;s subject to significant stress when opened and closed, while the presence of screw holes for the metal hinge makes it structurally vulnerable. I recently worked on a Beogram 4000 with a cracked hood and a broken-off piece.
Inspired by a previous restoration of a Beogram 3000 hinge, I aimed to create a similar solution for the 4000/4002 models.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A Stuck Tonearm and Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously repaired, returned with a tonearm tracking issue. The problem was a misaligned tracking sensor aperture obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. To fix this, I slightly repositioned the aperture after loosening its screw. I replaced the original screw with a more secure flat socket head screw to prevent future misalignment. I then recalibrated the tracking sensor feedback.
While the Beogram was with me, the customer decided to have the dust cover polished.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of Upgrades - Internal RIAA Preamp, Commander Remote Control and a New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</guid><description>Following the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) from Oklahoma, the next step was to add the customer&amp;rsquo;s desired upgrades. These included an internal Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier (designed for AC motor Beogram 4002s), a Beolover Commander remote control system, and a new hood for a pristine appearance.
The first upgrade was preparing the keypad for the Commander remote system. AC motor Beograms primarily use directly soldered wiring harnesses, so Commander installation isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;plug and play&amp;rdquo; like the DC motor version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Restoring the Plexiglass Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I recently restored had a very scratched dust cover.
[Image of scratched dust cover]
If I can feel the scratches with my fingernail, the first restoration step is sanding with 220 grit sandpaper. This creates a smooth surface for polishing. This is what the surface looks like after sanding:
[Image of dust cover after sanding]
It looks a bit like wood at this stage. After approximately 10 polishing steps using progressively finer sandpaper and then micro-mesh polishing cloths, the surface is restored:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Pulley, Hood Bumpers and Shipping Back to Italy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 14:02:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</guid><description>A Beolover always aims for perfection, and I realized my restoration of the Beogram 4000 wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite finished. Working on a Beogram 8000 reminded me of the importance of rubber hood bumpers for a smooth, quiet closing action. I discovered these bumpers were missing on the Beogram 4000, leaving only remnants of degraded rubber.
To fix this, I carefully removed the old rubber with a small drill bit by hand, avoiding any damage to the plexiglass.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The final step in restoring my Beogram 4000 involved replacing the damaged dust cover with one from a donor unit. While the replacement had some typical scratches, it was in good condition overall.
I began by sanding the surface with 320 grit sandpaper to remove the scratches. The next step was to polish it back to its original shine and clarity. Here&amp;rsquo;s the dust cover after polishing with 800 grit:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Installation of a Brand New Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 08:17:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4002 hood hinge from Florida to use in the installation of a new hood. The first photo shows its condition upon arrival.
A closer look revealed the problem:
The mounting holes on the hood had developed a fracture. This is a common issue caused by the original design choices made by B&amp;amp;O. The use of flat head bolts placed lateral stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks and eventual breakage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Polishing of the In- and Outside of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</guid><description>After installing a new remote control and internal pre-amplifier, the final touch on this Beogram 4002 (5523) was polishing its dust cover. While the outside showed typical scratches, the inside had an unusually large scratch as well.
Polishing the inside is more challenging because the polishing tool can hit the corners. However, because this scratch was situated away from the edges, it could be addressed. The technique involved gradually widening the polished area with each step.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:52:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>The final touch in restoring a Beogram turntable is typically polishing its plexiglass cover. This particular Beogram 4002 had noticeable scratches on its cover, including a branded logo above the platter&amp;rsquo;s center.
Deep scratches that can be felt by hand require an initial sanding with 220-grit sandpaper to level the surface, creating a temporarily rough appearance. If the scratches are less pronounced, starting with 320 or 400-grit sandpaper might suffice.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Plexiglass Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 18:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) I recently refurbished had a very scratched lid. Fortunately, the hinges were undamaged, and the inside of the lid was in good condition, with only a few minor cleaning marks. This made it worthwhile to try to restore the lid to an acceptable condition. The photo below shows the condition of the lid when I received the Beogram:
Because some scratches were deep enough to feel with a fingernail, I began by using 400-grit sandpaper to smooth the surface:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 3000 (5228): Restoration of the Plexiglass Hood - Repair of a Cracked Hinge and Installation of 3D Printed Mounting Brackets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 3000 turntable with a damaged plexiglass dust cover. The plastic mounting brackets that held the cover were broken, and one of the plexiglass hinges was also broken.
and one of the plexiglass hinges was broken off:
To address these issues, I created a repair kit. This kit includes 3D-printed replacement mounting brackets, a specialized tool for reinstalling the spring tensioning block, and laser-cut plexiglass pieces for fixing the broken hinge.</description></item></channel></rss>