<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dell on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dell/</link><description>Recent content in Dell on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new laptops and monitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</guid><description>Dell Singapore has launched new laptops and a monitor for consumers.
The XPS 12 is the first 2-in-1 laptop with a 4K Ultra HD display. The Inspiron 11 3000 series offers an affordable and portable laptop option available in three colors. Dell also released their first 4K consumer monitor, the Dell 28 Ultra HD 4K Monitor.
&amp;ldquo;Consumers have increasingly diverse needs. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a student or a professional, size, power, design, and price all matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell presents key features for IT Show 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</guid><description>Dell is featuring special deals on select products at IT Show 2018, happening in Suntec Singapore now through March 18th.
The XPS 13, available in a new rose gold color, starts at S$2,899. This 13&amp;quot; device is touted as the most powerful in its class and the smallest 13&amp;quot; available. It boasts an 8th Gen Intel Quad Core processor, a 4K Ultra HD InfinityEdge display, and introduces Dell Cinema, featuring CinemaColor, CinemaStream with wireless channels, and CinemaSound with Waves MaxxAudio Pro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell has launched backup appliances for midmarket businesses, along with complimentary Windows data recovery software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</guid><description>Dell has introduced new data protection solutions tailored for small and medium-sized businesses to enhance the protection of their crucial systems, applications, and data, both on-site and in cloud environments. These solutions include data deduplication appliance models and the new Dell Data Protection | Endpoint Recovery – Free Edition.
Back up more and store less The latest additions to the Dell DR series of deduplication appliances are the Dell DR4300e, DR4300, and DR6300...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Promotions for Dell at CEE 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</guid><description>Dell is promoting several products at the Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) 2017. These products, equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors, are designed for an excellent visual experience and enhanced gameplay.
Here are some of the featured products:
Inspiron 13 5000 2-in-1
Original Price: Starting from S$1,699 Show Price: Starting from S$1,299 Features:
Latest 7th Gen Intel Core processor 13.3&amp;quot; FHD (1,920 x 1,080) IPS Truelife LED-backlit touchscreen with wide viewing angles and an infrared (IR) camera Four versatile modes: tent, stand, laptop, and tablet XPS 13 2-in-1..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell unveils CES award-winning products at IT Show 2017 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-unveils-ces-award-winning-products-at-it-show-2017-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:19:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-unveils-ces-award-winning-products-at-it-show-2017-in-singapore/</guid><description>Dell unveiled new personal computing products at the IT Show 2017 in Singapore. First shown at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in January 2017, these products are equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors to create an enhanced visual and gaming experience.
[Image of Dell Inspiron 15 Gaming series]
Source: Dell website. The Dell Inspiron 15 Gaming series.
Inspiron 15 Gaming (CES Industry Awards Honoree, Gaming category) Features like strategically placed thermal outlets, dual fans, and large pipes and heat exchangers work together to prevent overheating during extended gaming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-unveils-ces-award-winning-products-at-it-show-2017-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-unveils-ces-award-winning-products-at-it-show-2017-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell: This is the perspective of Singaporean business leaders on the future of human-machine interaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/</guid><description>A significant shift towards human-machine partnerships is underway, but business leaders in the Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) region hold differing views on its implications, according to a global study by Dell Technologies. While 80% of APJ business leaders anticipate humans and machines functioning as integrated teams within five years, their outlook on this future is divided.
While a majority (58%) of Singaporean business leaders believe automation will increase their free time, opinions are split on the broader societal effects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-this-is-the-perspective-of-singaporean-business-leaders-on-the-future-of-human-machine-interaction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell has launched a new Dell Exclusive Store in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-a-new-dell-exclusive-store-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 16:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-a-new-dell-exclusive-store-in-singapore/</guid><description>The store opening was celebrated with a ribbon cutting.
Dell recently launched a new Exclusive Store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Plaza Singapura mall. This location was chosen for its accessibility and retail focus. The store displays Dell&amp;rsquo;s complete line of consumer products, as well as a dedicated virtual reality (VR) experience zone.
The store is set up for customers to try before they buy. It has experience suites featuring Dell&amp;rsquo;s newest XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-a-new-dell-exclusive-store-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-a-new-dell-exclusive-store-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has received the Women Entrepreneur City Blueprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</guid><description>Source: Dell SlideShare. Cover slide for the deck introducing the Dell 2018 Women Entrepreneur Cities Study.
At the 9th annual Dell Women Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN) in Toronto, Canada, Dell introduced new analytical resources for local governments and policymakers. These tools are intended to support the success of female entrepreneurs.
Based on the findings of the 2017 Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, Dell, in partnership with research firm IHS Markit, conducted in-depth analyses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore ranked among the top five in the 2016 WE Cities Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</guid><description>Dell has identified the top 25 cities worldwide that cultivate high-potential women entrepreneurs (HPWE) for 2016 through their Women Entrepreneur Cities Index (WE Cities). This unique index assesses a city&amp;rsquo;s capacity to attract and promote the growth of women-led businesses. The study focused on cities rather than countries to highlight how local policies and initiatives impact women entrepreneurs, in addition to national legislation and norms.
The WE Cities findings will serve as a starting point for discussions at the seventh annual Dell Women’s Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces an improved range of PCs for both consumer and commercial markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</guid><description>Dell debuted groundbreaking personal computing innovations at the annual Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in the US. They also updated their XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware consumer lines. Their OptiPlex, Latitude, and Precision commercial products received upgrades to 7th Gen Intel Core processors, USB-C with Thunderbolt 3 connectivity, and new professional graphics from NVIDIA and AMD. Dell&amp;rsquo;s monitor lineup also saw a refresh. The new Dell PC portfolio is equipped with Windows 10 and 7th Gen Intel Core processors, designed to maximize user productivity and creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell updates tablets, unveils new 5K monitor and smart desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 20:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</guid><description>Dell has improved its PC selection to boost productivity with new tablet functionalities, a 5K Ultra HD monitor, and a futuristic &amp;ldquo;smart desk&amp;rdquo; workspace.
Jeff Clarke, Dell&amp;rsquo;s Vice Chairman of Operations and President of Client Solutions, highlighted Dell&amp;rsquo;s focus on improving productivity and business outcomes at the recent Dell World Executive Summit.
The Dell UltraSharp 27 Monitor, available in December for US$2,499, offers Ultra HD 5K resolution (5,120 x 2,880), seven times sharper than Full HD...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell updates its Inspiron laptop lineup and unveils new business devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-its-inspiron-laptop-lineup-and-unveils-new-business-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 03:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-its-inspiron-laptop-lineup-and-unveils-new-business-devices/</guid><description>Check out the Inspiron 7000 series unveiling on Instagram.
- Dell introduces a new collection of business devices including the Inspiron 7000 series and Alienware&amp;rsquo;s latest gaming accessories at their updated Dell Exclusive Store located in Singapore
- The latest Inspiron 13 7000 2-in-1 packs impressive visuals and robust performance into a compact design - Experience heightened gaming immersion with the Inspiron 15 Gaming Laptop, equipped with NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060 discrete graphics - The award-winning XPS 13 is now up to 44% more potent thanks to the integration of new 8th Generation Intel Core i7 processors..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-its-inspiron-laptop-lineup-and-unveils-new-business-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-its-inspiron-laptop-lineup-and-unveils-new-business-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>80% of employees in Singapore at Dell Technologies are ready to work remotely for an extended period</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-employees-in-singapore-at-dell-technologies-are-ready-to-work-remotely-for-an-extended-period/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 07:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-employees-in-singapore-at-dell-technologies-are-ready-to-work-remotely-for-an-extended-period/</guid><description>A new study by Dell Technologies called the Remote Work Readiness (RWR) Index explores the attitudes and experiences of Singaporean employees regarding long-term remote work. The study found that while a majority of employees feel prepared for this shift, many believe their employers need to provide more support.
The RWR Index surveyed over 7,000 professionals in the Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) region, with 1,030 participants from Singapore. The study revealed that over 80% of Singaporean employees feel ready for long-term remote work, but many are concerned about the blurring lines between their personal and professional lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-employees-in-singapore-at-dell-technologies-are-ready-to-work-remotely-for-an-extended-period/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-employees-in-singapore-at-dell-technologies-are-ready-to-work-remotely-for-an-extended-period/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new network switches designed specifically for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Dell has improved its networking solutions designed for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs). Their new X-series smart managed switches and expanded N-series family provide cost-effective, enterprise-grade network control with user-friendly simplicity.
The Dell Networking X-Series includes web-managed 1 Gigabit Ethernet (GbE) and 10GbE switches with flexible configuration options. SMBs can benefit from advanced network management without specialized IT staff using step-by-step wizards and customizable dashboards. These features allow for quick and accurate configuration, calibration, and troubleshooting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell considers Singapore to be one of the 50 economies worldwide that are prepared for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 10:50:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</guid><description>Dell recognized Singapore as one of 50 economies worldwide prepared to flourish in an evolving, globalized future through technological integration. The _Dell Future-Ready Economies Model*, the foundation for this ranking, assesses large, rapidly growing global metropolitan areas on characteristics that allow individuals and businesses to utilize innovative tools and concepts. These factors contribute to improved connectivity, superior economic performance, and a greater capacity to attract talent.
The ranking evaluated the Global 50 cities based on three key aspects:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>