<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pension on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pension/</link><description>Recent content in Pension on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pension/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TAKAUD will be hosting its first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</guid><description>Source: _Middle East Pensions Conference _website.
With the support of the Central Bank of Bahrain, TAKAUD, a leading provider of savings, investment, and pension solutions in the MENA region, is gathering government officials and financial service leaders to discuss the development of robust pension plans for citizens and foreign workers across the region.
The first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference will occur in Bahrain on October 18, 2016. The conference aims to raise awareness and encourage action towards bringing Middle Eastern pension standards in line with developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's Global Pension Index score has increased</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 12:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/</guid><description>Source: Mercer. Where various countries stand on the MMGPI.
Now in its eighth year, the Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI) urges governments worldwide to act quickly to address aging populations, declining birth rates, and inadequate retirement systems. This year, the MMGPI examined the effects of rapidly aging populations and how prepared countries&amp;rsquo; retirement systems are to handle the significant financial strains this presents.
Dr. David Knox, the report&amp;rsquo;s author and a Senior Partner at Mercer, noted that many governments and communities have underestimated the combined effects of longer lifespans and falling global birth rates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>