<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MegaPath on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/megapath/</link><description>Recent content in MegaPath on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:36:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/megapath/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2x2 Ethernet Takes on T-1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</guid><description>For the past decade, small and medium businesses have relied on T1 lines as their primary commercial telecom solution. However, a new competitor called 2x2 Ethernet, recently introduced by major nationwide carrier MegaPath, is emerging to challenge the long-standing T1. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what 2x2 Ethernet offers.
It might seem surprising that T1 lines would face competition, considering their 50-year history and widespread adoption. As the first widely available broadband digital connection for businesses, T1 emerged from telephone company research...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted PBX Adds Video Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems, also known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, are gaining popularity with businesses of all sizes. This technology offers advanced features without requiring a large upfront investment. Now, these systems are evolving to incorporate video services as well.
MegaPath, a leading network and cloud service provider, is enhancing its hosted PBX offerings by including cloud-based unified communications video services.
A new generation of business phones makes voice and video integration possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Voice Goes Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world: companies are ditching their traditional PBX phone systems for cloud-based communication solutions like hosted PBX or hosted VoIP. This transition also incorporates mobile devices.
For example, Megapath&amp;rsquo;s Hosted Voice Mobile allows you to make and receive calls using a single number across multiple devices – desk phone, computer, and smartphone. Having one consistent number simplifies communication and avoids confusing clients with a business card full of numbers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Security Threat Protection In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 21:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>In the past, castles relied on moats to provide extra security beyond their walls. This stopped attackers from directly reaching the castle. Similarly, today&amp;rsquo;s networks need more than just firewalls.
Firewalls are effective but can be overwhelmed. Cloud-based security acts as a modern moat, providing a barrier outside the network. MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s Unified Threat Management (UTM) uses this approach, offering cloud, on-site, or hybrid security solutions.
MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s UTM is a multi-layered Security as a Service (SaaS) solution that handles simple and complex threats, while also managing security alerts, logs, and compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need A Managed Security Services Provider?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 05:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</guid><description>Cybercrime has evolved from mere mischief into a substantial threat focused on financial gain. If your network holds valuable data, cybercriminals will see it as a target, making network security essential.
Protecting your digital assets isn&amp;rsquo;t optional; the choice lies in managing it yourself or outsourcing it to managed security services, also known as Security as a Service (SaaS).
MegaPath, a prominent carrier, provides comprehensive managed security services, including firewalls, intrusion prevention, malware and virus protection, web filtering, anti-spam measures, application control, data leak prevention, log management, vulnerability assessments, security information management, and file integrity monitoring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Pushes EoC to 400 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services are constantly achieving higher bandwidth capacities, making businesses reconsider the need for fiber optic installations. MegaPath, for example, now offers EoC speeds up to 400 Mbps.
Many companies use EoC as a cost-effective alternative to T1 lines, obtaining double the bandwidth at the same price. Options like 2x2 Mbps and 3x3 Mbps are particularly favored. Others transition to mid-band Ethernet, offering 10 to 20 Mbps, which exceeds bonded T1 capabilities and suits mid-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>