<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flight on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flight/</link><description>Recent content in Flight on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:46:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates has prohibited hoverboards and reminds passengers of the approved items for carry-on luggage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates reminds passengers to check before packing, for hassle-free travel this holiday season.
Emirates Airlines is reminding travelers to review the allowed carry-on and checked baggage items for a smooth and secure journey during this holiday period.
To maintain the safety of everyone onboard, loose lithium batteries used in devices like cameras, cell phones, and laptops are not allowed in checked luggage. This includes &amp;ldquo;hoverboards&amp;rdquo; or self-balancing scooters, whether or not the batteries have been removed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flight Experience Singapore and McGallen &amp; Bolden offer unique leadership workshops that stand out from the rest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</guid><description>Source: McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden.
Flight Experience Singapore, the first flight simulator open to the public in Asia, has partnered with the consulting firm McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden to offer leadership workshops.
Their program, Leadership Secrets at 30,000 Feet, is designed for business leaders and executives. It uses a realistic cockpit setting to teach leadership skills. The customized, four-hour workshop draws on decades of experience from Captain Michael Caston, a pilot with experience flying Boeing 747 and 737 jets for British Airways and Singapore Airlines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flight-experience-singapore-and-mcgallen-bolden-offer-unique-leadership-workshops-that-stand-out-from-the-rest/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will begin flying between Okinawa and Japan in January 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will launch its inaugural charter flights between Singapore and Okinawa, Japan.
Operated in partnership with Okinawa Tourist Service (OTS) and Jumbo Tours Okinawa, these monthly charters will run from September 9, 2014, to January 3, 2015. Utilizing Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both business and economy class seating, these direct flights aim to provide travelers with a convenient option to visit Okinawa.
From September to October 2014, flights will depart Singapore Changi Airport Terminal 2 at 10:00 am and arrive at Okinawa Naha Airport at 4:15 pm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asiana discontinues codeshare agreement with US Airways, impacting flights to Japan and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Asiana Airlines will end its codeshare agreement with US Airways on March 30, 2014. Passengers are advised to review their flight reservations. The affected routes are listed below:
Asiana Airlines flights
Japan
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Fukuoka, Osaka, Nagoya, Okinawa, and Shizuoka
America
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Chicago, New York, and Honolulu
US Airways flights
America
Los Angeles to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia San Francisco to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Seattle to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Chicago to/from Atlanta, Orlando, Indianapolis, Columbus, Cleveland, and Houston...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aeromexico introduces an additional flight connecting Shanghai and Mexico City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Aeromexico will expand its service between Shanghai and Mexico City to include a third weekly flight on Sundays. This increase will bring the total number of seats available on the route to over 1,500 each week. The flights, operated by Boeing 777 aircraft, accommodate 277 passengers with 49 business class seats and 228 economy seats.
Each Aeromexico flight features personal entertainment systems, increased passenger space, and lie-flat seats in Clase Premier, its business class section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Idealo has developed a flight price comparison portal for India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</guid><description>Source: idealo India website.
Idealo, a company specializing in price comparison, has expanded its services to India. With fourteen successful price comparison websites globally, idealo already helps numerous travelers find the best flight deals. The company proudly launched its fifteenth website, flights.idealo.in, in 2015.
Indian customers can now compare prices on thousands of flights from various online travel agencies and airlines, all without any cost. Idealo&amp;rsquo;s platform features offers from both budget-friendly and high-end airlines, encompassing one-way and round-trip journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is extending its Change for Good program to additional flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Hainan Airlines flight attendants distributing Change for Good donation bags to passengers.
Hainan Airlines is significantly expanding its successful in-flight donation program, Change for Good, to include 16 more routes. The program, which supports UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s initiatives for children, was initially introduced in September 2013 on the Beijing-Haikou route.
As the first mainland China-based airline to partner with UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s Change for Good alliance, Hainan Airlines aims to raise a minimum of RMB 10 million over five years, starting from September 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ANA has developed an app to assist passengers in relaxing and diverting their attention away from takeoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</guid><description>Source: App Store.
All Nippon Airways (ANA), a major Japanese airline, developed an app to alleviate stress during the most anxiety-inducing part of air travel. Based on a survey of US airline passengers revealing that takeoff causes the most anxiety (68%), ANA created &amp;ldquo;ANA Takeoff Mode.&amp;rdquo; This mobile app aims to help travelers relax and focus on something other than takeoff.
The app presents a simple puzzle accompanied by calming music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travel to Banwa Private Island with Ascent Flights Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</guid><description>Banwa Private Island, a secluded island in Northeast Palawan known for its pristine beaches, has joined forces with Ascent Flights Global to provide exclusive and secure travel options for its guests. This collaboration aims to create a protected travel environment through personalized on-demand flights using seaplanes, helicopters, or private jets based on individual preferences.
Source: Banwa Private Island. Banwa Private Island has partnered Ascent Flights Global to offer guests safe, private transport to their accommodation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir introduces a new daily flight from Singapore to Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</guid><description>Starting December 12, 2014, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines, will introduce a daily flight service to Denpasar, Indonesia, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, stated, “The increase in flights demonstrates the Singapore Airlines Group&amp;rsquo;s dedication to expanding our service offerings and providing our customers with more choices and convenience. By connecting the networks of both airlines, we can improve connectivity options for our customers through our combined network, reaching 99 cities across 35 countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etiqa has introduced the first-ever complimentary inflight insurance for travelers from Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</guid><description>The first complimentary in-flight insurance plan in Singapore offers up to S$50,000 in personal accident coverage.
For an added S$4, travelers can purchase coverage for flights delayed by three hours or more.
Claims can be paid out instantly through PayNow.
Etiqa, an online insurance provider based in Singapore, has introduced the nation&amp;rsquo;s first complimentary in-flight insurance for travelers. The company also launched a flight delay add-on for S$4, enabling travelers to receive compensation for flights delayed by three consecutive hours, which is a lower threshold compared to the industry average of six to twelve hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates offers passengers complimentary or heavily discounted in-flight Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates provides complimentary* Wi-Fi on a significant portion of its fleet, currently 106 aircraft, and is continuously expanding this service. Passengers on ultra long-haul flights (flights exceeding 14 hours) frequently utilize this service, with over 30% connecting to Wi-Fi.
All 59 Airbus A380s and 47 Boeing 777s in Emirates&amp;rsquo; fleet offer Wi-Fi connectivity. A majority of these aircraft provide the first 10MB of data free of charge, allowing passengers to update social media or use messaging apps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is now offering flights from China to France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</guid><description>Hainan Airlines has introduced a fifth European route to its network, joining existing services to Moscow, Saint Petersburg, Brussels, and Berlin. The inaugural flight, HU7907, departed Hangzhou International Airport on September 3rd, with a stopover at Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport before continuing to Paris&amp;rsquo; Roissy-Charles de Gaulle Airport.
Source: Hainan Airlines. The ribbon-cutting ceremony for the first flight on September 3.
This new service aims to enhance political, economic, and cultural ties between China and France, especially as 2014 marks the 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between the two nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>