<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plinth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plinth/</link><description>Recent content in Plinth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plinth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Germany En Route to California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4000 turntable from Germany, intended for a customer in California. My task is to refurbish the unit and deliver it to its new owner.
The turntable was poorly packaged for shipment, resulting in the keypad plates becoming detached during transit. This led to minor damage to the plates themselves and some cosmetic imperfections on other internal surfaces.
The aluminum surfaces are in surprisingly good shape considering the loose keypad plates.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Stopover From Arizona on the Way to Portugal - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</guid><description>Our company provides a service where we assist customers in buying vintage audio equipment from online marketplaces and other sellers. We arrange shipping to our facility, restore the unit, and then deliver it to the customer. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like taking a trip back in time to buy a brand new unit! This post documents the unboxing of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable purchased on eBay from an Arizona seller for a customer in Portugal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway recently arrived for restoration. The packaging was excellent, using the original styrofoam inserts, and the only issue was two loose control pads, which were prevented from causing damage due to tape and foam inside. This highlights the importance of securing these pads with non-residue tape during shipping.
Fortunately, this is an easy repair. Cosmetically, the Beogram is in excellent condition.
The aluminum panels will gleam like new with a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Very Corroded New Arrival from Sweden</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the Beogram 4000 from Sweden is a mixed bag. Positively, the aluminum surfaces, platter, arm cover lettering, and panels are in good shape, though a thorough cleaning is needed to determine their true condition. The internal components appear original, and the red position indicator is intact. However, there are significant drawbacks.
The black enclosure parts have an unprecedented amount of corrosion, exceeding typical wear and tear. This corrosion is present even on the underside and has also affected the chassis&amp;rsquo;s leaf springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Arrival from Arizona - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) from Arizona. It needed complete functional restoration. The unit arrived without its cover, shipped in a Beolover container, which is a great way to ensure safe transportation.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the unit as it looked when unpacked:
While a little dirty, it&amp;rsquo;s in decent condition except for the worn-out keypad:
Hopefully, these keypads can be professionally refurbished. On a positive note, the base is in good shape, with almost pristine corners:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival From West Virginia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from West Virginia recently arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was in good condition and shipped in a Beolover container.
Initial inspection revealed no significant damage to the dust cover or hinges. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, but the keypad has some wear. This will be addressed by installing a Beolover Commander remote control module, which allows for keypad-free operation.
The plinth is well-preserved, with minimal damage to the front corners, which are prone to wear.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 20:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) AC-motor turntable purchased from eBay. I had sent the seller specific packaging instructions and a sturdy double-boxed container, which they thankfully followed, resulting in the unit arriving undamaged. Initial observations are as follows:
The aluminum surfaces are generally in good shape, just needing a cleaning. The platter, in particular, has remarkably few imperfections.
The keypad shows typical signs of use, with fingerprints visible on the most frequently pressed keys.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Look (What a Packaging Mess!)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</guid><description>I recently purchased a Beogram 4002 (5513) on eBay for a customer. Although the seller described it as being in very good cosmetic condition and included a new Soundsmith SMMC20 EN cartridge, the turntable arrived poorly packaged in a damaged box. Thankfully, the turntable itself was inside a second box with better protective materials.
Upon opening the inner box, I was relieved to find the Beogram 4002 in pristine condition, as advertised.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, which was exciting to receive in its original box and packaging. Upon opening it, I was greeted by a pleasant surprise—a pristine MMC20CL cartridge was mounted on the tonearm. Thankfully, it was protected by a cover and had been gently pressed against the styrofoam, keeping it safe during shipping.
Carefully, I removed the styrofoam and cartridge, relieved to find the cantilever was still centered and undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Missing Leaf Spring on a Plate Lock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</guid><description>During the rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5513), I encountered an issue while adjusting the sub-chassis, platter, and tonearm. The large aluminum plate wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly against the plinth when it was pushed back, making it impossible to align the platter flush with the plate.
The problem originated from one of the locking mechanisms in the back left corner. These locks, equipped with leaf springs, are designed to secure the plate to the frame when the plinth is moved back.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 02:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, known for its unstable RPM, recently arrived for repair. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in excellent cosmetic condition with only minor blemishes.
The keypad appears barely used. However, the hood has some deep scratches, likely from improper storage. Internally, the turntable looks completely original.
Initial testing revealed the arm lowering mechanism is slow, and the automatic RPM switching from 33 to 45 is not functioning, although manual switching works.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>The recent arrival of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable from the UK marks the end of a summer break for one turntable enthusiast. This particular model is unique, showcasing transitional design elements between the Beogram 4000 and the later 4002 models.
ParcelHero, a shipping company offering swift and trackable service between the UK and US, delivered the turntable securely. Its efficient service, comparable in cost to standard international mail, is commendable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Seattle en Route to Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</guid><description>An Australian customer purchased a Beogram 4002 on eBay from the US and sent it to me for restoration. Upon its arrival, I discovered it was in poor condition, likely due to storage in a basement or attic. The dust cover was particularly damaged, with scratches on the aluminum trim and the surface itself.
Despite the dust cover&amp;rsquo;s condition, the internal components appeared undamaged, including the hinges, suggesting a successful restoration is possible.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Restored Keypad and Plinth, a New Hood and Installation of the Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I finished restoring the functionality of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513), a project detailed in this post. Here&amp;rsquo;s how the unit appeared at that stage:
Although functionally restored, there were two noticeable cosmetic issues: a bleached area on the plinth and typical keypad wear from finger contact. It appears that skin oils negatively affect the keypad coating:
My client opted for a refurbished keypad. Additionally, the RPM panel&amp;rsquo;s plastic securing clamps were cracked, a common issue causing the panel to detach.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000, recently acquired in Germany, is about to undergo a complete restoration before being sent to its new home in the UK. A preliminary assessment reveals the aluminum surfaces to be in quite good condition.
The teak plinth is similarly well-preserved, with notably sharp corners.
While the original arm cover shows significant dirt accumulation, thorough cleaning is likely to improve its appearance. Sourcing a replacement would be challenging due to the unique labeling on this model – &amp;ldquo;tracking weight adjusting&amp;rdquo; instead of the &amp;ldquo;tracking force adjustment&amp;rdquo; found on the 4002.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Colorado - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 08:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable arrived from Colorado for restoration, carefully packaged in a specialized box. The outer cover had several scratches but could potentially be polished to an acceptable condition. The hinges seemed fine, and the aluminum underneath the cover appeared to be in good shape. The control keypad showed only minor signs of wear.
The corners of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s base were almost pristine. However, upon inspection, the metal frames attached to the plinth were loosening, a common issue caused by deteriorating glue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Evaluation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable arrived for refurbishment, carefully packaged to prevent damage during shipping. The unit appears to be mostly original and in good cosmetic condition, with the exception of a worn keypad.
The keypad&amp;rsquo;s stamped metal sheet is not scratched, suggesting a straightforward restoration using a specialized technique. Interestingly, the STOP key shows more wear than the START key.
Further inspection revealed minor damage to the plinth corners and non-original screws securing the dust cover.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Another New Arrival - A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable that needs some care. After unboxing it, I was pleased to see the effective packing method, similar to what I demonstrate in my 4002 shipping video. The sturdy metal construction of the 4002 makes it relatively easy to ship safely with proper double boxing and precautions.
My initial assessment is positive. The aluminum surfaces are in great shape and will gleam with a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from California with a Bit of Shipping Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived needing some care, but unfortunately experienced additional damage during shipping. Upon opening the box, it was discovered that the carriage had detached from the pulley, which was stuck to tape residue. Thankfully, the tonearm was secured with tape, preventing it from ejecting through the platter opening and causing more severe damage. However, the tonearm did sustain some impact. This highlights the importance of securing the carriage during transport using foam and tape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Some Final Touches - Replacing Plinth and Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</guid><description>Following the installation of the BeoloverRIAA internal preamplifier and the Commander remote control, this Beogram 4002 (5523) needed a few finishing touches.
The original plinth of the Beogram was damaged. A replacement plinth was sourced, but it also had minor damage, particularly to the corners. Inspired by a previous veneer repair on a Beomaster 8000, a similar approach was taken to address the plinth&amp;rsquo;s corners. Veneer was added and color-matched to the existing finish, significantly improving the appearance, although not completely perfect.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From New York</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 18:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently purchased on eBay was shipped using a specialized container to protect it in transit. Thankfully, the seller mostly followed the provided packing guidelines, resulting in no damage during shipping. Upon opening, the turntable was in good condition, with only minor issues.
While the blue tape used on the aluminum surfaces didn&amp;rsquo;t cause any damage to the lettering, there were a few scratches on the platter. These were likely caused by attempts to remove it improperly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently arrived from a UK seller for restoration. This report outlines its pre-restoration condition.
Upon arrival, the unit was quite dirty but in good overall shape. The dust cover showed typical scratches from storage, many deep enough to feel with a fingernail. However, it can be polished back to good condition. Positively, the dust cover features an aluminum strip instead of the less durable plastic type, and the hinges appear to be intact.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Michigan - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Michigan for restoration, carefully packaged according to instructions. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, with one minor dent on the platter&amp;rsquo;s surrounding plate. The platter itself, keypads, and small aluminum plate are also in good shape. However, one corner of the plinth is damaged. Fortunately, replacement plinth panels were included, which will be installed.
The hood has noticeable scratches, primarily on the surface, and should polish well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable arrived in need of repair. The packaging was generally good, but the cartridge was not secured properly for transport. Thankfully, the delicate cantilever was undamaged. The first step was to safely store the cartridge in a specialized MMC cartridge box. These boxes are offered to customers who are shipping their Beograms for restoration and are also available for the MMC1-5 cartridges.
An initial assessment showed that the aluminum panels were in good condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (5503) for restoration. The 5503 is the North American version of the 5501/5502 models, evident in the non-functional voltage switch included to maintain a consistent appearance.
This Beogram is in excellent overall condition, featuring high-quality veneer on the plinth and a dust cover with typical scratches that can be polished to near-original clarity. Internally, it appears largely untouched, though there are indications of prior work, such as loose bolts in the tracking and tonearm mechanisms.</description></item></channel></rss>