<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Phone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-phone/</link><description>Recent content in Business Phone on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-phone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add a Toll Free Number For Next to Nothing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-a-toll-free-number-for-next-to-nothing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-a-toll-free-number-for-next-to-nothing/</guid><description>Upgrading your business phone system can be pricey, but there&amp;rsquo;s a budget-friendly way to add a toll-free number to any phone, even your cell phone, for a minimal monthly cost.
Toll-free numbers are beneficial for businesses with a public phone number. Local customers can call without long-distance charges, but even calls from nearby areas can become expensive. Out-of-state prospects might hesitate to call due to high long-distance rates.
Offering a toll-free number encourages calls from anywhere, as the business covers the cost.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs ISDN PRI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses have moved past analog phone lines, embracing PBX systems and ISDN PRI for their communication needs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: SIP Trunking. This technology offers potential cost and performance benefits for companies looking to enhance their voice services. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SIP Trunks with ISDN PRI to understand the best choice for your organization.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that both technologies rely on digital telephony, eliminating analog transmission.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone IP Communications offers Polished VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses usually don&amp;rsquo;t spend much effort on their telecommunication systems, often starting with basic necessities like desk phones, internet service, and maybe a simple VoIP system. It&amp;rsquo;s manageable for the owner or an office manager. However, as these businesses grow, their communication needs change. Suddenly, managing communication among numerous employees and locations becomes challenging. Reaching colleagues becomes difficult, and clients experience poor connection quality, leading to apologies. This situation calls for a &amp;ldquo;forklift upgrade.</description></item><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Pick Unlimited Toll Free Numbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pick-unlimited-toll-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pick-unlimited-toll-free-numbers/</guid><description>A toll-free number is undeniably beneficial for any business, often leading to a surge in customer calls once implemented. To manage this influx without incurring excessive costs, consider opting for an unlimited toll-free number service.
For a fixed monthly fee, you receive a comprehensive toll-free service, eliminating unexpected charges on your credit card. This service provides unlimited usage within reasonable bounds.
Beyond cost predictability, this service offers over 30 features typically considered premium add-ons, such as an auto-attendant, voicemail-to-email/text, online faxing, and call forwarding.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Family Plans for Professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-family-plans-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-family-plans-for-professionals/</guid><description>Typically, &amp;ldquo;family plans&amp;rdquo; bring to mind adding lines for children. However, in the current economic climate, a family plan could be the difference between two working individuals each having a dedicated phone and being forced to share. Sharing a phone is impractical for business, so let&amp;rsquo;s explore these family plans further.
You might not have considered this option for professional use due to the name &amp;ldquo;family plan.&amp;rdquo; These plans are more accurately described as shared minutes plans, but the name &amp;ldquo;family plan&amp;rdquo; has stuck, so we&amp;rsquo;ll use it here.</description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider.</description></item><item><title>Low Cost 800 Numbers Are Here</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-800-numbers-are-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-800-numbers-are-here/</guid><description>Considering an 800 number for your business? It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to encourage calls from potential customers, as they won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to reach out if it&amp;rsquo;s toll-free. However, the cost of such a service might be a concern. Fortunately, there are affordable solutions available.
While &amp;ldquo;800 number&amp;rdquo; is a common phrase, various toll-free options exist, including 866, 877, and 888. These numbers function identically, allowing callers to connect without incurring charges, even for long-distance calls.</description></item><item><title>How To Reduce Your Business Wireless Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-reduce-your-business-wireless-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:49:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-reduce-your-business-wireless-costs/</guid><description>Do you suspect your business mobile service expenses are higher than they should be? Your suspicions are likely correct. You could be overspending by 25% to 35%. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you like to find a way to save your company that money?
There&amp;rsquo;s a way to achieve those savings. Gather your wireless bills and examine them thoroughly. Identify plans that are being used efficiently and those with wasted services. Look for billing discrepancies and devices not in use that can be eliminated.</description></item><item><title>Why, Oh Why, PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</guid><description>You might know the terms PRI, T1 PRI, Telephone PRI, PRI Trunk, or ISDN PRI, but what do they actually mean, and why choose this service?
PRI stands for Primary Rate Interface. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN or Integrated Services Digital Network and is a step up from BRI or Basic Rate Interface. Simply put, PRI is a digital line connecting to your PBX phone system. It combines numerous phone lines into a single digital line, leading to cost savings on monthly phone bills.</description></item><item><title>Plain Old Telephone Service For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get a reliable phone service? Surprisingly, it might be POTS – Plain Old Telephone Service.
While the name might sound outdated, POTS offers dependable, high-quality phone service at an affordable price. Why is this the case?
POTS, technically known as analog telephone service over copper wiring, is a direct descendant of the original telephone system. This system, developed and refined over a century by companies like the Bell Telephone System, became incredibly efficient and standardized.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI Offers Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</guid><description>If your company relies heavily on phone communication, using numerous phone lines managed by an internal system, ISDN PRI might be the solution for you. It provides excellent voice quality, quick call transfers, and additional features like Caller ID, all while potentially saving you money.
ISDN PRI, or Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is an advanced form of the traditional T1 digital phone line. While it utilizes the same T1 line infrastructure, making it widely accessible, its channel organization sets it apart.</description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item><item><title>Get a Toll Free Number Instantly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-toll-free-number-instantly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 07:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-toll-free-number-instantly/</guid><description>When starting a new business or expanding an existing one, a toll-free number can significantly enhance sales and customer service. Contrary to common belief, obtaining a toll-free number doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a lengthy waiting period. Services like Kall8 provide an almost instant setup process, allowing businesses to acquire an 800, 855, 866, 877, or 888 number swiftly.
Kall8 simplifies the process through its online system, which houses a vast selection of pre-established toll-free numbers.</description></item><item><title>Sales Lead Generation in a Recession</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sales-lead-generation-in-a-recession/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 01:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sales-lead-generation-in-a-recession/</guid><description>Is your business struggling in the current economic downturn? Are existing customers cutting back, and new leads hard to come by? A virtual assistant from iTeleCenter could be the solution you need to generate more sales leads easily and affordably. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just an answering service or voicemail system; it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool for driving sales growth.
iTeleCenter&amp;rsquo;s virtual phone system operates as a sales system, effectively expanding the reach of your sales team and making a small team seem much larger.</description></item><item><title>Ignore That PBX Behind the Curtain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:31:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</guid><description>Operating a small business doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to sound like it, especially with tools like virtual PBX systems. These systems can give your two-person office the professional edge of a Fortune 500 corporation.
Traditional PBX systems, standard in large companies, offer features such as individual extensions, direct dialing, call transferring, and outside line access. However, they come with a hefty price tag. iTeleCenter, a virtual PBX solution, offers an affordable alternative that transforms your existing phones into a robust communication system.</description></item></channel></rss>