<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP PBX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-pbx/</link><description>Recent content in IP PBX on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:57:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-pbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TelePacific’s SmartVoice Trunking Offers Telephone Smarts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications offers a unique and intelligent solution called SmartVoice for small and medium-sized businesses seeking telephone and internet services. This SIP trunking solution provides both voice and data over a single line. Unlike traditional Integrated T1 lines, SmartVoice stands out by supporting various business telephone systems and offering significantly greater traffic capacity.
SIP trunking uses an IP-based transmission line specifically designed for enterprise VoIP telephone systems. SIP, or Session Initiation Protocol, is the signaling technology employed by numerous IP phone systems.</description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Can You Save 50% With Unified Communications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</guid><description>As your company expands, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely seen a simultaneous increase in your telephone costs. While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this is simply due to having more employees making calls, the reality is that not all phone expenses are unavoidable.
Unified communications technology can help you significantly reduce unnecessary costs. This approach combines your voice, data, and video networks into a single, unified system, leading to cost savings for businesses of all sizes, even those with just one location.</description></item><item><title>CAS vs PRI Voice Channels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</guid><description>T1 telephone trunk lines are commonly used with PBX and IP PBX phone systems because most modern equipment can connect directly to them without a separate CSU/DSU box. There are two main types of T1 lines: CAS and PRI (also called ISDN PRI).
The original T1 line design, T1 CAS, is divided into 24 channels, each carrying a 64 Kbps digitized phone call. This digital conversion process, known as PCM, ensures clear voice quality.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>Private Branch Exchange Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</guid><description>PBX telephone systems are the preferred business phone technology for medium and large businesses, though recent advancements have made them affordable for smaller companies as well, replacing outdated hardwired or key systems. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a new PBX system, reaching out to VAR Network can provide insights into pricing and available options.
Beyond hardware, PBX systems require connectivity, with various options offering different cost and performance benefits. The most basic connection is an FXO, or analog phone line, connecting to a central office.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Why Are VoIP and SIP Trunking So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</guid><description>When your outdated PBX system needs an upgrade, consider transitioning to an IP PBX and replacing traditional phone lines with a SIP Trunk. This shift to modern technologies is driven by their ability to deliver new features and cost savings without compromising call quality.
Upgrading doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require replacing existing phones. While VoIP SIP phones offer advantages like network connectivity and simplified management, older phones can connect to the IP PBX via interface cards with FSX ports.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Trunk Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines often benefit from trunk lines. But with various trunk services available, choosing the right one can be tricky. While VoIP phone systems might make SIP trunking seem like the obvious choice, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to evaluate all options before deciding.
The concept of telephone trunking originated with telephone companies. Initially, individual phone lines connected users to the local phone company. As phone usage surged, businesses adopted switchboards to manage multiple lines, leading to a tangled mess of overhead wires.</description></item><item><title>T1 Phone Lines Offer More For Less</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-phone-lines-offer-more-for-less/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 09:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-phone-lines-offer-more-for-less/</guid><description>When your business expands and your phone bills become a significant expense, it might be time to consider a service that offers higher volume at a lower cost. This is especially relevant if you&amp;rsquo;ve established a dedicated customer contact center or if your business has grown to require a dozen or more external phone lines.
The service that aligns with this need is a T1 telephone line. Unlike a single phone line, a T1 &amp;ldquo;line&amp;rdquo; is a digital trunk line.</description></item><item><title>Toshiba Strata CIX Does SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toshiba-strata-cix-does-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toshiba-strata-cix-does-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Business phone systems have transitioned from analog lines to digital T1 and T1 PRI trunks. With the rise of Enterprise VoIP, SIP Trunking has emerged as a popular all-IP option, supported by a growing number of carriers. SIP trunking eliminates the need for on-site PSTN termination by sending voice and data packets to a service provider, leading to cost savings through economies of scale.
Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s Strata CIX IP Business Communication Systems have integrated SIP trunking, removing the need for a separate VoIP gateway.</description></item><item><title>Is HPBX Your Next PBX?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</guid><description>Businesses across the country are ditching their in-house phone systems and returning to outside phone service providers, mirroring a past era. However, modern telephony has evolved significantly. While maintaining in-house phone systems seemed cost-effective initially, companies are realizing that it comes with unexpected expenses and complexities.
Larger businesses often require numerous phone lines, leading to challenges in internal communication. Having individual lines for each phone necessitates long-distance charges for calls outside the company.</description></item></channel></rss>