<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UK on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk/</link><description>Recent content in UK on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the Prime Minister hinting at a potential shift in Brexit stance with his unexpected mention of competition policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</guid><description>Andreas Stephan, Professor of Competition Law &amp;amp; Head of UEA Law School, University of East Anglia*
In a speech delivered on March 2, 2018, Prime Minister Theresa May aimed to clarify the UK&amp;rsquo;s Brexit objectives. She proposed aligning UK State Aid and Competition rules with those of the EU, while allowing UK courts to consider European Court of Justice (ECJ) judgments. However, she emphasized that the ECJ would not have jurisdiction over the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia, Singapore, and the UAE are among the top 10 destinations on people's relocation wishlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</guid><description>A recent report by Hydrogen Group, a global recruitment firm, reveals a growing trend of professionals seeking international work opportunities. The study found that the number of individuals open to working abroad doubled over a five-year period, rising from 16% in 2010 to 35% in 2014. Furthermore, 40% of respondents believe there are no obstacles to relocating for work.
While the US and UK were the most popular destinations, followed by Australia, Singapore ranked as the most preferred Asian country at seventh place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British lawyers have made a significant impact on EU (migration) law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk, Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen, Netherlands.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) acknowledged the significant contributions of its British members to European integration and legal precedent. This recognition prompts reflection on the impact of British legal professionals on EU law, particularly in the areas of migration and free movement.
British judges and advocates-general, with their common law background, played a key role in shaping the CJEU into a more transparent and adaptable institution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK Automotive industry continues to export to China as its third-largest destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</guid><description>The Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders (SMMT) recently released data revealing that Britain is exporting more cars than ever. The number of British-built cars shipped globally increased by 10.3%, reaching a new record of 1,354,216 units. This marks the second year in a row that this record has been broken.
China, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest car market, maintained its position as the UK&amp;rsquo;s third largest trading partner, after the EU and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LBS and Fudan have collaborated to introduce a new Global Masters in Management program with a double business degree</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</guid><description>London Business School (LBS) and Fudan University&amp;rsquo;s School of Management (FDSM) have partnered to create a dual-degree Global Masters in Management (MiM) program.
Sir Andrew Likierman, Dean of London Business School, emphasized the increasing need for skilled professionals who can navigate the business landscape in both Eastern and Western contexts. He highlighted that this collaboration reflects their dedication to close partnerships with Chinese corporations. The program aims to equip graduates with a global perspective through direct engagement with both China and the West...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guardianship, freedom of movement, and child rights: the SM ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*This blog post expands on research that informed the upcoming revised edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Defining a &amp;ldquo;family member&amp;rdquo; legally can be complex, especially when it comes to immigration law and child welfare. The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment in the SM case highlights these complexities, particularly where EU free movement law intersects with the family law of non-EU nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 3: Is there a lack of democracy in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, Middlesex University
Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The European Union is frequently criticized for being undemocratic or suffering from a &amp;ldquo;democratic deficit.&amp;rdquo; One common assertion is that all EU decisions are made by the unelected bureaucrats of the European Commission. This post will demonstrate why this criticism is fundamentally flawed. It stems from a misunderstanding of both the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s actual powers within the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes and how the European Commission is appointed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>