<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Education on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/education/</link><description>Recent content in Education on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian students are focusing on hospitality management programs at LHE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</guid><description>Asian students make up a significant portion of the student population at the four hospitality schools operated by Laureate Hospitality Education (LHE): Glion Institute of Higher Education, Les Roches International School of Hotel Management, Kendall College, and Blue Mountains International Hotel Management School.
Source: LHE. From left, Hou, Tatar, Williams Knight.
Judy Hou, CEO of Glion Institute of Higher Education, noted a growing demand for LHE&amp;rsquo;s programs (offered in Switzerland, the US, and their branch campuses) throughout the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IndianMoney.com is creating additional financial education content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</guid><description>IndianMoney.com, a leading financial education company in India, partnered with Kannada news channel Suddi TV to create Money Maathu (Money Talk), an educational series about personal finance. The series features short episodes, typically eight to ten minutes long, that cover a wide range of financial topics. With 35 episodes already released, the goal is to empower viewers with the knowledge to make informed financial choices.
CS Sudheer, founder and CEO of IndianMoney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coursera unveils the top courses for learners in Singapore in 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</guid><description>In 2021, Singaporean users on Coursera showed a strong interest in courses teaching in-demand tech and data science skills. This conclusion comes from Coursera&amp;rsquo;s yearly report analyzing course selections made by over 750,000 registered learners in Singapore. The report reveals the skills, abilities, and subjects most sought after by Singaporeans.
Here are the top 10 most popular Coursera courses in Singapore for 2021:
S Course Name Partner Name 1 First Step Korean Yonsei University 2 Machine Learning Stanford University 3 The Science of Well-Being Yale University 4 Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere Google 5 Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) University of Michigan 6 Financial Markets Yale University 7 Introduction to Psychology Yale University 8 _ Chinese for Beginners_ Peking University 9 _ Foundations of Project Management_ Google 10 Learning How to Learn: Powerful mental tools to help you master tough subjects Deep Teaching Solutions Source: Coursera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BenQ interactive flat panel simplifies education and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</guid><description>BenQ, a well-known name in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, introduces the RP750K, a new interactive flat panel (IFP). This innovative IFP offers a comprehensive solution by combining a 4K Ultra HD whiteboard with annotation and collaboration tools.
The RP750K excels in dynamic classroom or corporate training settings. Its Germ-Resistant Screen, infused with a safe and robust nano-ionic silver coating, effectively eliminates most surface germs, reducing cross-infection risks. This antimicrobial protection persists even with regular cleaning and extended use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Soothes The Savage Beasts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/</guid><description>Instead of resorting to strict discipline, a school in Vail, Arizona, found a simple solution to improve student behavior on their buses: providing Wi-Fi access. Surprisingly, once installed, disruptive behavior vanished, and students became more engaged in their homework.
This success story highlights a key point: providing Internet access can effectively address disciplinary issues. While students may engage in various online activities, the core issue of maintaining order is resolved...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-soothes-the-savage-beasts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The skills you possess will be valuable in securing future employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Legrand illustrates how LinkedIn is innovating by connecting existing skills with the needs of emerging jobs.
Olivier Legrand, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at LinkedIn, suggests that many individuals already possess some qualifications for in-demand jobs without realizing it.
During his keynote, &amp;ldquo;Job titles are out, skill sets are in,&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Computer Society&amp;rsquo;s Tech3 Forum, Legrand stated that LinkedIn aims to connect its members not only with employers but also with suitable companies, relevant jobs, and essential skills for future career prospects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GLG increases its presence in Singapore with office expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</guid><description>GLG, a professional learning platform connecting professionals with experts for knowledge sharing, has expanded its presence in Singapore with a new and larger office. The company&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Alexander Saint-Amand, highlighted the rapid growth of GLG&amp;rsquo;s business in Singapore, emphasizing the region&amp;rsquo;s significance for the company&amp;rsquo;s mission to transform professional learning.
The new 6,000-square-foot office, located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, can accommodate 64 employees. GLG&amp;rsquo;s leadership, including Evan Auyang, Head of Asia-Pacific and Managing Director, and David Anderson, Head of GLG Southeast Asia, underscored Singapore&amp;rsquo;s strategic importance as a business hub and its concentration of leading professionals and companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glg-increases-its-presence-in-singapore-with-office-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Textbooks Move To The iPad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/textbooks-move-to-the-ipad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 23:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/textbooks-move-to-the-ipad/</guid><description>College students are familiar with the weight and cost of traditional textbooks. However, eTextbooks offer a significantly cheaper and lighter alternative, available at a 30-50% discount compared to physical books. The future of education is digital, and eTextbooks are leading the way.
Electronic textbooks offer several advantages over print. Firstly, the cost is significantly lower. Physical textbooks are expensive to produce due to their size and durable materials, which aren’t as necessary since students often don’t keep their books long-term...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/textbooks-move-to-the-ipad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/textbooks-move-to-the-ipad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Learn about data science quickly with CEG Digital's online course</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</guid><description>CEG Digital, the flexible learning branch of global education provider Cambridge Education Group (CEG), has teamed up with the Web Science Institute at the University of Southampton (WSI), a top-100 university, to offer short online courses.
Dr. Elena Simperl, WSI Associate Professor and Scientific Director of the European Data Science Academy, emphasized the importance of data science skills, stating, &amp;ldquo;Data science is crucial for our economy. Our new series of short professional courses complement our postgraduate degrees and target decision-makers, business analysts, IT developers, and others interested in cutting-edge data science technologies and applications in fields like digital marketing, finance, and healthcare...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Today is International Women's Day: can you help create the future? #MakeWhatsNext</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft blog. Ada Lovelace was the world&amp;rsquo;s first computer programmer.
In honor of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day, a global celebration of the achievements of women, Microsoft is encouraging girls around the world to pursue careers in STEM fields with their #MakeWhatsNext campaign.
According to the World Economic Forum, the gender gap won&amp;rsquo;t close until 2133. This gap is especially prominent in computer science and STEM fields. Dr. Daiana Beitler, Microsoft Philanthropies Lead for Asia, notes in a blog post that the Asian Development Bank found women in the region are 70% less likely to be employed than men...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AMBA accreditation awarded to India's IIMC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/</guid><description>The Indian Institute of Management Calcutta (IIMC) has received a five-year accreditation from the Association of MBAs (AMBA) for its MBA and MBM programs.
Anindya Sen, Dean of IIMC, stated that the institute aims to secure a distinct global standing. &amp;ldquo;AMBA accreditation will enhance our international visibility and establish us as a global institution, enabling us to attract more international students. We will also receive valuable guidance for continuous improvement,&amp;rdquo; he explained...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amba-accreditation-awarded-to-india-s-iimc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACCA is sponsoring a MOOC on FutureLearn that grants learners an exemption from the F1 paper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) is breaking new ground as the first professional accountancy body to use massive open online courses (MOOCs) for professional recognition. They are partnering with FutureLearn, a UK-based social learning platform, to offer free online courses in accounting, finance, and business.
This partnership aims to reach a global audience, providing valuable supplementary knowledge for professionals and introducing career paths to those new to the field...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singtel Cyber Security Institute aims to enhance the skills of individuals and businesses in the field of cyber security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</guid><description>Singapore Telecommunications established the Singtel Cyber Security Institute (CSI) to bolster the cyber security skills of businesses and governments in the Asia Pacific region. The CSI is the first organization of its kind in the region, merging an advanced cyber range with an educational institute to provide companies with realistic training to handle complex cyber threats.
Bill Chang, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Group Enterprise CEO, highlighted the lack of preparedness among companies, with over 85% lacking robust cyber response plans or realistic training opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-cyber-security-institute-aims-to-enhance-the-skills-of-individuals-and-businesses-in-the-field-of-cyber-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LBS and Fudan have collaborated to introduce a new Global Masters in Management program with a double business degree</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</guid><description>London Business School (LBS) and Fudan University&amp;rsquo;s School of Management (FDSM) have partnered to create a dual-degree Global Masters in Management (MiM) program.
Sir Andrew Likierman, Dean of London Business School, emphasized the increasing need for skilled professionals who can navigate the business landscape in both Eastern and Western contexts. He highlighted that this collaboration reflects their dedication to close partnerships with Chinese corporations. The program aims to equip graduates with a global perspective through direct engagement with both China and the West...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbs-and-fudan-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-global-masters-in-management-program-with-a-double-business-degree/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IBM has raised concerns about the skills gap in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</guid><description>Source: IBM. Cover for the Upskilling India report.
IBM has released a study conducted by the IBM Institute for Business Value (IBV), in partnership with the Economist Intelligence Unit. This study assesses India&amp;rsquo;s increasing skills gap and offers suggestions to address the issue.
The study surveyed Indian executives, and most believe that the Indian workforce&amp;rsquo;s skills are on par with or better than those of other nations. However, only 40% reported that new employees possess the necessary skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing involvement of women in commerce and industry in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) in the Philippines has reported a rise in the number of women participating in skills training programs for traditionally male-dominated fields.
Amelito Cardenas, a supervising specialist at TESDA Pangasinan, mentioned that more women are enrolling in technical-vocational (tech-voc) and private institutions to learn trades such as welding and automotive repair, as reported by the Philippines Information Agency.
Cardenas also shared that TESDA offers a free training program specifically for women who run sari-sari stores and carinderia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia and Pos Malaysia are working together for order fulfillment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</guid><description>Shopee Malaysia has partnered with Pos Malaysia, the national courier service, to offer free shipping to all sellers on its platform.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace with a strong regional presence of over 12 million users, operates as a free online customer-to-customer (C2C) platform. Launched in December 2015, Shopee aims to empower both individual and business entrepreneurs to conduct secure buying and selling transactions on their mobile devices. In Malaysia alone, Shopee&amp;rsquo;s app has been downloaded over a million times within a six-month timeframe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A white paper providing solutions for talent management in the Chinese hospitality industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</guid><description>Florida International University&amp;rsquo;s Chaplin School of Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Management (CSHTM) and its Institute for Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Education &amp;amp; Research (IHTER) have published a new resource for HR professionals and hospitality businesses, particularly those working with Chinese markets. The white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Managing Growing Pains of China’s Relentless Hotel Development Pipeline,&amp;rdquo; examines the significant lack of qualified talent within China&amp;rsquo;s rapidly expanding hotel industry. The paper offers practical solutions such as professional development programs, conflict resolution strategies, and clearly defined career paths to attract and retain skilled employees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SmartUp introduces the Digital Readiness Experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</guid><description>Source: SmartUp website.
Screen capture of the SmartUp
platform.
SmartUp, a mobile-first knowledge-sharing platform, has introduced a Digital Readiness Experience. This offering utilizes microlearning modules to educate the workforce on trending technology topics.
This multi-week Digital Readiness Experience is available for purchase by SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s corporate clients for their employees, as explained by Deborah Tan-Pink, SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s Global Head of Marketing.
&amp;ldquo;The Digital Readiness Experience is a four-to-six-week program designed to shift attitudes and knowledge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The language learning app HelloTalk has reached 1 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</guid><description>Source: HelloTalk app page at the Play Store.
The mobile language learning app HelloTalk has reached over one million registered users globally, according to its developer, HelloTalk.
The HelloTalk app allows users to teach each other their native languages using their mobile devices. Users can communicate in real-time with native speakers through various features, helping them practice their target language.
Over one million HelloTalk users, representing over 200 countries, use the app to learn various languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>