<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bali on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bali/</link><description>Recent content in Bali on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bali/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choose from a variety of MICE packages available in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Three travel companies — Chōsen, The Slate, and Samujana — have designed productivity programs for businesses and workgroups. These programs offer a variety of environments to help teams achieve their best results.
For adventure junkies Source: Chosen website. A view of Bali.
Chōsen provides experiences tailored for teams that thrive on new adventures and challenges:
Activities include cliff jumping, canyoning, surfing, and cooking classes. Accommodation is available at their estate in Bali and other locations, including New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Katamama will be opening its doors to guests in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</guid><description>Source: Katamama. A rooftop suite at dusk.
Katamama, a 58-suite boutique hotel in Seminyak, Bali&amp;rsquo;s prime oceanfront area, is set to open in late March 2016.
The hotel emphasizes &amp;ldquo;handcrafted hospitality,&amp;rdquo; with every detail meticulously designed and executed by skilled Indonesian artisans. Katamama is a project by PTT Family, known for acclaimed restaurants, bars, and the Potato Head Beach Club in Bali. This 20-villa estate is famous for its innovative environmental design and a prominent contemporary Indonesian art gallery.</description></item><item><title>Discover the surrounding areas of Hotel Indigo in the new Neighbourhood 15 campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 02:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</guid><description>Hotel Indigo&amp;rsquo;s new brand campaign, &amp;ldquo;Neighbourhood 15,&amp;rdquo; highlights the unique character of each hotel&amp;rsquo;s surrounding area, specifically within a 15-minute radius. The campaign showcases local businesses and individuals who contribute to the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s vibrant atmosphere.
A two-minute video featuring the Hotel Indigo Bali Seminyak Beach, the brand&amp;rsquo;s first resort location, introduces viewers to nearby attractions like Surf School Bali, Divine Earth restaurant, and Bali Barber. Starting in October, a series of videos will delve deeper into these local businesses, offering insights and personal stories.</description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes.</description></item><item><title>Starting in September, Ulu Cliffhouse will be providing a clifftop beach club playground</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</guid><description>Source: Ulu Cliffhouse.
Opening in September 2017, Ulu Cliffhouse, a &amp;ldquo;clifftop playground&amp;rdquo; created by a group of artists, is ready to change what it means to be a beach club in Bali, Indonesia.
The 50,000 square foot clifftop retreat will provide a stylish area with a 25-meter infinity pool, an on-site spa, a boutique, private beach access, and a variety of food and beverage options, including a terraced restaurant and a cliffside bar, all with breathtaking panoramic views.</description></item><item><title>W Retreat &amp; Spa Bali - Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary with a month-long celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</guid><description>Source: W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali website.
The W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali in Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary on March 5, 2016. The resort will commemorate this milestone with a month-long celebration titled &amp;ldquo;FIVE ON FIVE,&amp;rdquo; showcasing five unique highlights.
WOOBAR will present special edition Paletas Wey popsicles, a Mexican-style frozen treat crafted by the Bali-based company. Meanwhile, W THE STORE will offer an exclusive, limited-edition collection of &amp;ldquo;Wanitas&amp;rdquo; décor.</description></item><item><title>The Tough Mudder Bali event will take place in the green hills of Jimbaran</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Bali. Event poster.
The ultimate test of physical and mental strength, stamina, and teamwork will premiere in Asia on October 1, 2016, at Jimbaran Hijau (Bali International Park), a multifaceted development in South Bali.
Established in 2010 and known as &amp;ldquo;probably the toughest event on the planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder is an obstacle course challenging participants to collaborate and conquer physical and mental hurdles in an extreme endurance event.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Tough Mudder event in Asia will take place in Bali, Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 06:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Indonesia. Chairi Ibrahim, Project Manager at Seroja Partners (left), Gandrasta Bangko, Business Director at Mesa Race (middle), and Ridzki Syahputera, Partner at Seroja Partners (right) at the launch of Tough Mudder Indonesia.
The world-renowned endurance series, Tough Mudder, has officially launched in Indonesia. Known as &amp;ldquo;Probably the Toughest Event on the Planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder has attracted 2.5 million participants across 200 events in six countries. Its Asian debut will take place on October 1st and 2nd, 2016, in Bali, Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>Purify and detoxify on weekends in July and August at REVĪVŌ in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: REVĪVŌ. Throughout July and August, cleansing and detox retreats are offered every weekend.
The luxurious REVĪVŌ wellness resort in Bali, Indonesia, has introduced weekend-long cleansing and detox retreats for July and August.
Guests can choose to participate for one or two days. Kicking off at 10:00 am each Saturday, the program begins with a cold-pressed juice, followed by yoga, Pilates, or meditation. Afterward, attendees enjoy kombucha (a fermented tea beverage) and a detox lunch at the NŪTRIŌ restaurant.</description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir introduces a new daily flight from Singapore to Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</guid><description>Starting December 12, 2014, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines, will introduce a daily flight service to Denpasar, Indonesia, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, stated, “The increase in flights demonstrates the Singapore Airlines Group&amp;rsquo;s dedication to expanding our service offerings and providing our customers with more choices and convenience. By connecting the networks of both airlines, we can improve connectivity options for our customers through our combined network, reaching 99 cities across 35 countries.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Meliá Hotels opened at least 11 new locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</guid><description>Meliá Hotels International is adding at least 11 new hotels to its portfolio in 2015, including the Sol House Kuta Bali in Indonesia.
Source: Meliá Hotels website.
The recently opened 317-room Meliá Doha, which began welcoming guests in January, is the first Spanish hotel in Qatar. Located within Bin Samikh Tower, a prominent skyscraper in Doha&amp;rsquo;s West Bay district, the hotel enjoys a prime position on the Qatari coast.
The urban German brand, Innside by Meliá, is expanding its Middle Eastern presence with the upcoming Innside Dubai, a 125-room hotel.</description></item><item><title>Elite Havens is proud to announce the addition of three new properties in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: Elite Havens. Caption: Elite Havens expands its Bali Collection with three new villas.
Elite Havens, a high-end villa rental and management company in Asia, has expanded its Bali offerings with three new properties:
Sol Y Mar - Uluwatu, Bali, Indonesia
Situated on Nunggalan Beach, Sol y Mar is a four-bedroom villa featuring a private pool.
Villa Dhanika - Badung, Bali, Indonesia
Nestled amidst Balinese rice paddies, Villa Dhanika is a five-bedroom retreat with an Olympic-sized swimming pool and an outdoor jacuzzi.</description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions.</description></item></channel></rss>