<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Municipal WiFi on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/municipal-wifi/</link><description>Recent content in Municipal WiFi on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:32:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/municipal-wifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Municipal WiFi On The Way Out?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</guid><description>While WiFi hotspots are incredibly convenient for travelers in airports, hotels, and restaurants, city-wide WiFi hasn&amp;rsquo;t been as successful as initially hoped. The recent closure of Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s Metro WiFi in Philadelphia raises questions about the future of this technology, even though broadband internet is thriving.
Despite a significant increase in broadband adoption, with dial-up becoming nearly obsolete, city-wide WiFi providers are struggling. Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s experience in Philadelphia, where they only gained a fraction of their projected subscribers, highlights this challenge.</description></item><item><title>Philly Stake With WiFi...Mmm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/philly-stake-with-wifimmm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 19:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/philly-stake-with-wifimmm/</guid><description>Philadelphia&amp;rsquo;s most exciting new venture is citywide WiFi, generating significant buzz after Earthlink abandoned a similar project. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a completely new endeavor, but rather a revival of the existing infrastructure under new management, a group of local investors confident in their ability to succeed.
Their strategy is based on free access for consumers, a welcome change from the $20 monthly fee for the previous unreliable service. Although a discounted plan was offered, even a reduced cost can be prohibitive for low-income residents.</description></item></channel></rss>