<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lohei on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lohei/</link><description>Recent content in Lohei on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lohei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist.</description></item><item><title>Greetings for Chinese New Year in the office and business with a traditional lohei celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/greetings-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-office-and-business-with-a-traditional-lohei-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/greetings-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-office-and-business-with-a-traditional-lohei-celebration/</guid><description>This scroll says 生意興隆/生意兴隆 (sheng yi xing long), which translates to &amp;ldquo;may the business thrive greatly.&amp;rdquo;
The celebratory atmosphere in mainland China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Singapore is palpable this time of year. Everywhere you look, lucky red and gold decorations are for sale, along with symbols of the upcoming year&amp;rsquo;s zodiac animal. Chinese New Year falls on February 8th in 2016, and well-wishes in the form of traditional greetings will be exchanged from the very first day.</description></item><item><title>Quick guide to Chinese New Year for the Year of the Pig</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</guid><description>The Lunar New Year period is a time when Chinese communities are filled with a palpable sense of celebration. Vibrant red decorations, believed to bring good luck, are prominently displayed, and the atmosphere is alive with the melodies of traditional festive music. The Chinese New Year, which falls on February 5th in 2019, is a time when well-wishes are exchanged, particularly during the first fifteen days of the lunar year.</description></item><item><title>Everything is going well at PARKROYAL on Beach Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</guid><description>Beginning January 16, 2017, PARKROYAL on Beach Road will be offering a new take on Lunar New Year celebrations as Executive Chef Ken Ang introduces his culinary perspective to the dishes at Plaza Brasserie, their all-day dining restaurant.
Known for his mastery of traditional Cantonese roasting methods, Executive Chef Ang will be presenting his version of the lucky facai yusheng (发财鱼生, also called lohei), enhanced with additions like crispy salmon and chicken skin.</description></item></channel></rss>