<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Operating System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/operating-system/</link><description>Recent content in Operating System on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 17:12:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/operating-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prepare yourself for the Windows 10 experience on all your devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-windows-10-experience-on-all-your-devices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-windows-10-experience-on-all-your-devices/</guid><description>Microsoft introduced a new, more personalized version of Windows designed to provide a consistent experience across a variety of devices, from Xbox and PCs to phones, tablets, and more.
Windows 10 aims to adapt to different devices and user activities, creating a unified and user-friendly experience. CEO Satya Nadella emphasized the goal of making Windows 10 beloved by current users and attracting billions more.
The company prioritizes a seamless experience across devices, supporting natural interactions like voice, gestures, and gaze.</description></item><item><title>iOS 9 has been released by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple has announced that its latest mobile operating system, iOS 9, will launch on September 16th. This free update for iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch users boasts enhanced search capabilities and improved Siri functionality.
One of the standout features of iOS 9 is its new multitasking capabilities for iPad. Users can now work with two apps concurrently, viewing them side-by-side. A Picture-in-Picture feature also allows for video playback while using other apps.</description></item><item><title>Fishbat provides commentary on the latest developments in iOS8 and the introduction of Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple, the tech giant, recently launched the first beta version of iOS 8.1. This upgrade comes shortly after the release of iOS 8.0.2, which was itself a fix for a bug found in the recently launched iOS 8.0.1.
This new beta version offers several new features:
A redesigned icon for iBooks. An option to enable dictation within the keyboard settings. Updated application permission settings. Larger application icons specifically designed for the new widgets in the notification center.</description></item><item><title>Starting on July 29, upgrades to Windows 10 will be available for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-july-29-upgrades-to-windows-10-will-be-available-for-free/</guid><description>Source: Windows blog.
Microsoft has revealed that Windows 10 will launch on July 29th in 190 countries. The company states that Windows 10 will enhance productivity and offer a more personalized and intuitive user experience across devices. Windows 7 and 8.1 users can upgrade to Windows 10 for free, making it accessible to a majority of current Windows users.
&amp;ldquo;Windows 10 empowers users to achieve remarkable things,&amp;rdquo; says Terry Myerson, Executive VP at Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>The initial significant update is now accessible for Windows 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Microsoft has released its first significant update for Windows 10, available for both PCs and tablets. This update brings enhancements across the platform, improving user experience according to the company&amp;rsquo;s official announcement. The rollout of Windows 10 has also begun for Xbox One and is expected to reach selected mobile phones shortly.
Terry Myerson, Executive VP of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows and Devices Group, expressed confidence in the update, stating that it marks a level of platform maturity suitable for organization-wide deployment.</description></item><item><title>The launch of Windows 10 in Singapore is met with great excitement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-windows-10-in-singapore-is-met-with-great-excitement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-windows-10-in-singapore-is-met-with-great-excitement/</guid><description>The Windows 10 launch event in Singapore was a resounding success, drawing a large crowd.
Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows 10 is now widely accessible, offered as a free upgrade for a limited time or with new computer systems and tablets in 190 countries. This latest version introduces features like Windows Hello, Cortana, an Xbox app, and the Microsoft Edge browser, aiming to deliver a familiar yet enhanced user experience.
Jessica Tan, Managing Director of Microsoft Singapore, highlighted that Windows 10 empowers individuals and groups to achieve remarkable things.</description></item></channel></rss>