<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Penang on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/penang/</link><description>Recent content in Penang on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:51:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/penang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The second edition of Food and Hotel Penang is back!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</guid><description>Source: FHP 2016 website.
The second Food and Hotel Penang (FHP 2016) event is poised to solidify its standing as the premier trade-only platform in Northern Malaysia. This event will host a curated buyer program, offering access to key figures in the food and hospitality sectors within Penang and nearby northern states like Kedah, Perak, and Perlis.
Supported by the Penang state government and the Malaysian Association of Hotels, FHP aims to build upon the achievements of its 2014 edition, which saw participation from 240 companies spanning 30 countries.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces new flights between Penang and Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</guid><description>AirAsia has launched direct flights connecting Penang to Yangon, Myanmar, making it the airline&amp;rsquo;s seventh international destination accessible from its northern hub. Penang also offers direct flights to other international destinations, such as Ho Chi Minh City, Singapore, Medan, Jakarta, Surabaya, and Bangkok.
This new route will operate three times a week, starting on March 22, 2016. The flight schedule for Penang, Malaysia (PEN) – Yangon, Myanmar (RGN) is as follows:</description></item><item><title>Digi is sponsoring customers to participate in the Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</guid><description>Source: Digi Telecommunications.
Digi Telecommunications is sponsoring 200 customers to join the WWF-Malaysia Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk in Penang and Sunway Pyramid. This event coincides with the Earth Hour 2015 celebration on March 28, 2015.
As the Night Walk@Sunway&amp;rsquo;s corporate sponsor, Digi has donated RM35,000 to support WWF-Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s environmental conservation efforts.
Digi is sponsoring 200 walk packs, costing RM60 each, for its customers. 100 packs are designated for Night Walk@Sunway and 100 for Night Walk@Penang.</description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities.</description></item></channel></rss>