<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Review on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/review/</link><description>Recent content in Review on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 20:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing the Targus Geo 15.6" Backpack designed for lasting durability and comfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-targus-geo-15-6-backpack-designed-for-lasting-durability-and-comfort/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 20:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-targus-geo-15-6-backpack-designed-for-lasting-durability-and-comfort/</guid><description>Source: Targus.
Targus, a company known for its business-oriented laptop cases, introduced the Geo lifestyle collection in August. The company states that the collection features a modern style with neutral colors and unique design elements, appealing to both weekend adventurers and daily commuters.
The Geo Collection boasts premium materials, including cross-dyed polyester fabric, patterned lining, soft-touch accents, and soft leather-like details. Targus highlights the signature engineered stripe of the Geo collection, which is individually screen-printed for an artisanal feel.</description></item><item><title>Yahoo has published its 2016 Year in Review for Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 02:37:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</guid><description>Yahoo, a popular online platform, has released its &amp;ldquo;2016 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; (YIR) for Singapore. This yearly recap highlights the major search trends and events that captivated Singaporean internet users, based on their search history and online activity on Yahoo throughout 2016.
Topping the list of &amp;ldquo;Top 10 Singapore Headlines&amp;rdquo; is swimmer Joseph Schooling winning Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first Olympic gold medal. Significant political events like changes to the Elected Presidency and MP David Ong&amp;rsquo;s resignation also feature prominently.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Facebook highlighted the things that caught the world's interest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
Facebook recently unveiled its &amp;ldquo;Year in Review&amp;rdquo; for 2015, featuring a dedicated website and video.
The company highlighted major global conversations, with the US presidential election taking the lead. This was followed by discussions surrounding the November 13 Paris attacks, the Syrian civil war and resulting refugee crisis, the Nepal earthquakes, and the Greek debt crisis.
On the entertainment front, &amp;ldquo;Game of Thrones&amp;rdquo; reigned supreme as the most popular TV show, while &amp;ldquo;Star Wars: The Force Awakens&amp;rdquo; dominated movie discussions globally.</description></item><item><title>Ginvera and Wipro Unza are the top brands on mass-market facial cleanser shelves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ginvera-and-wipro-unza-are-the-top-brands-on-mass-market-facial-cleanser-shelves/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ginvera-and-wipro-unza-are-the-top-brands-on-mass-market-facial-cleanser-shelves/</guid><description>Numerous facial cleansers are available at supermarkets, with prices starting at S$3.85 for a 100g tube. This article compares a selection of these cleansers to the author&amp;rsquo;s usual Eversoft avocado cleanser. While all the cleansers effectively cleaned the skin, none particularly stood out in terms of oil control, hydration, or other advertised benefits. The author prioritizes cleansers that lather well and don&amp;rsquo;t leave residue, and ultimately, ingredients, price, and fragrance are the deciding factors for repeat purchases.</description></item><item><title>IMF approves of Singapore's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its yearly assessment of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy. The IMF noted that while Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy remains strong, it is facing challenges from both global and domestic factors.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economic growth slowed to 2% in 2015, down from 3.3% in 2014, and was 2.2% in the first half of 2016. While unemployment is still low, job creation slowed significantly in 2015, and inflation has remained negative since late 2014.</description></item><item><title>Japan Food Town provides unique dining experiences in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</guid><description>Japan Food Town: An Authentic Taste of Japan in Singapore [Image of Japan Food Town banner in Wisma Atria with a caption suggesting to take the escalators to the fourth floor]
Opening on July 16, 2016, Japan Food Town promises to bring the genuine flavors of Japanese cuisine to Singapore. Located on the 4th level of Isetan Singapore in Wisma Atria mall, this food hall marks the first in a series of planned Japan Food Town locations worldwide.</description></item></channel></rss>