<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Subsidiary Protection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/subsidiary-protection/</link><description>Recent content in Subsidiary Protection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/subsidiary-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion of AG de la Tour in C-621/21: Is it a helpful clarification or an unnecessary hindrance to women seeking international protection from gender-based violence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Grundler, a Lecturer in Law at the Department of Law and Criminology, Royal Holloway, University of London, examines a recent legal opinion concerning refugee and subsidiary protection eligibility for women at risk of violence within their families.
Advocate General (AG) de la Tour&amp;rsquo;s Opinion in case C-621/21 tackles the scope of the refugee definition within Article 2(d) of the Qualification Directive and the definition of subsidiary protection beneficiaries in Article 2(g) concerning women facing potential violence within a family setting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The program in the European Union that allows Syrian refugees in Turkey to seek humanitarian admission.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</guid><description>Laura Robbins-Wright
PhD Candidate in Government, London School of Economics and Political Science
On December 15, 2015, the European Commission put forward a suggestion for a program to offer humanitarian entry to Syrian refugees residing in Turkey. This proposal follows earlier EU initiatives, including a plan to relocate refugees within the EU and a program for resettling refugees from other countries. It also builds upon an action plan from October 2015 and a more recent decision to give €3 billion to a Refugee Facility designed to better coordinate aid for Syrian refugees in Turkey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Strengthening and weakening the legal standing of individuals granted subsidiary protection under European Union law – the ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union in the case of Alo and Osso.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</guid><description>Dr. Louise Halleskov Storgaard, Assistant Professor, Aarhus University
Can a country that offers subsidiary protection (a form of protection similar to refugee status) restrict the movement of those beneficiaries within its borders if they receive social security benefits? This is the central question addressed by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Alo and Osso case on March 1, 2015. The CJEU’s answer is notable, innovative, and potentially contentious as it reinforces the influence of the Geneva Convention on subsidiary protection standards but also raises questions about the applicable non-discrimination standard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>