<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coral on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coral/</link><description>Recent content in Coral on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coral/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New sculptures have been added to the Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi Coralarium</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</guid><description>The Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi resort has added new sculptures to its Coralarium, an underwater art installation that doubles as the Maldives&amp;rsquo; first and only coral regeneration project. This structure, now teeming with marine life, serves as an artificial reef.
The abstract sculptures, conceived by environmentalist and eco-artist Jason deCaires Taylor, draw inspiration from the natural beauty of coral reefs and are designed to resemble coral colonies. These ten partially submerged plinths, reaching heights of up to 5 meters, aim to raise awareness about endangered ecosystems, educate visitors about marine life, and help rehabilitate the reef...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coral Beirut Al Hamra now offers two additional Ambassador Suites as part of its room options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</guid><description>The Coral Beirut Al Hamra Hotel recently introduced a new suite category featuring expansive rooftop terraces with outdoor seating areas. Situated on the 11th floor, the 87 square meter Ambassador Suites offer fully equipped kitchens, large living rooms, and luxurious bathrooms, complete with high-end amenities.
Hartmut Grauel, General Manager of the hotel, stated that these new suites cater to the preferences of discerning travelers. He noted a consistent demand for spacious accommodations akin to full-size apartments, complete with kitchens and living rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>