<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solenoid on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/solenoid/</link><description>Recent content in Solenoid on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/solenoid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523) began, as always, with the arm lowering mechanism. The lubricants in these mechanisms often harden with age, preventing the tonearm from lowering correctly. The mechanism is shown here in its original condition:
Each moving part was removed
for cleaning and re-lubrication before reassembly. Next, I lubricated the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point. This required removing the sensor arm, as pictured below from the back:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Prematurely Activating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is progressing well. Rebuilding the deck led to a successful initial power-up where the carriage moved to the correct position, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower. A visual inspection showed a disconnected thin grey wire from the SK3054 NPN power transistor (0TR4).
Tracing the wiring and consulting the schematic revealed that the grey wire connected to the transistor&amp;rsquo;s emitter, responsible for bypassing a current-limiting resistor (7R1) during the arm&amp;rsquo;s initial descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Arrives From UK! Solenoid Oscillates!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</guid><description>I recently acquired another Beogram 4000 from the UK. The unit is in fair shape; importantly, the MMC cartridge mount is undamaged and the sensor arm insert is present. The control panel for the cueing and tonearm lift detached during shipping, highlighting the wisdom of securing such parts. Thankfully, the seller had protected the turntable with a durable plastic sheet, preventing any damage. Reattaching the panel should be simple.
Internally, all parts appear to be present:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 11:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism/</guid><description>My work began on the recently acquired Beogram 4002 (5513). The arm lowering mechanism, as is common, was the first issue to address. The usual hardened lubricant was present, resulting in sluggish movement. The setup can be seen here:
To address this, I removed the linkages and the damper to clean and lubricate them:
Here, the disassembled damper and linkages are visible:
A detailed video demonstration of this process is available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Strange Solenoid and an Alien 7812 Impostor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</guid><description>As I was testing the restored tonearm carriage on my Beogram 8000 with some recently purchased Genesis reissues (Trespass, Foxtrot, Nursery Crime, etc.), I decided to turn my attention to the Beogram 4000 I had recently acquired from Italy. The most critical issue was its malfunctioning solenoid, which appeared unusual and unlike standard B&amp;amp;O components.
Upon disassembling the damper/solenoid assembly, I discovered a makeshift repair job. The original solenoid had been replaced with a different one, and a nail was used as a plunger to activate the solenoid linkage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Mechanisms, and Installation of a New Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, often problematic due to hardened lubricants, required attention. While the lowering damper section was functional, the damper-to-arm linkage was stuck and only moved because its pin had loosened.
The restoration process involved carefully disassembling the arm lowering mechanism, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubrication. The seized damper-to-arm linkage was removed, requiring a workbench procedure to press out its stuck pin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My work began on the Beogram 4000 turntable that arrived from Germany. As is my practice, the tracking and arm lowering mechanisms were the first to be refurbished. The arm lowering mechanism, controlled by a solenoid and damper arrangement, is pictured here:
After removing components requiring cleaning and lubrication, the area looked like this:
Here are the disassembled parts:
With cleaning and lubrication complete, reassembly followed. Next, I addressed the seized damper-to-arm linkage, accessible only after detaching the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My first step when restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable is to focus on the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. The arm lowering mechanism often requires attention because hardened lubricants can hinder the solenoid and damper assemblies. To address this, I disassemble the mechanism.
Once the solenoid and linkages are removed, I take the parts to my workbench for cleaning and re-lubrication.
Next, I address the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm, as it can cause delays in arm lowering, particularly after storage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 06:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</guid><description>My work began with the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, as is customary for me. My client had already addressed the cleaning and lubrication of the damper and solenoid linkages, so my task was to detach the linkage connecting the damper and tonearm. This required removing the sensor arm assembly, as shown here:
Extracting the sensor arm involved removing two screws at its base:
The linkage could then be detached:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Smoking Solenoid Resistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-smoking-solenoid-resistor/</guid><description>This continues my series &amp;ldquo;A Fun Evening with&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A Beogram 4000 turntable, which I had previously restored, was returned with a malfunctioning arm lowering mechanism and a burning smell.
I removed the turntable from its case and took off the aluminum plates to examine it. When I powered it on, it initially started up as usual, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower at the record&amp;rsquo;s starting point. Instead, there was a strong burning smell and a plume of smoke coming from the circuit board with the carriage switches.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism, and Tracking Sensor Bulb Replacement and Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</guid><description>The initial step for restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable typically involves reconditioning the arm lowering mechanism and calibrating the tracking system. In this instance, hardened lubricants had affected the mechanical operation, and excessive sensitivity in the tracking sensor led to uncontrolled carriage movement after the arm lowered. The solenoid and damper assembly is depicted below:
The restoration began by disassembling the mechanism, cleaning all parts, and applying fresh lubrication:
A video illustrating the tracking sensor adjustment process is available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and the Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I was working on had a completely frozen arm lowering mechanism. The old lubricant had become so hardened that I had to use a screwdriver to pry the linkages off their pivot pins. This is a common issue, easily resolved by cleaning and re-lubricating the mechanism. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the solenoid, damper, and linkages before disassembly:
This image shows the disassembled parts laid out on my workbench:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) began with the arm lowering and tracking systems, as these are essential for any further testing or repair work.
To start, I took out the damper and linkages to clean and lubricate them. Thankfully, all the components were in good condition, so lubrication and reassembly were straightforward. Next, I lubricated the pivot point connecting the damper to the arm linkage. This required removing the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Repair of a Dead H-Bridge and Some Other Updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-dead-h-bridge-and-some-other-updates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:52:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-dead-h-bridge-and-some-other-updates/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, previously restored in 2020, returned for repair. The issue was a familiar one: the carriage wouldn&amp;rsquo;t move towards the platter, suggesting a faulty power transistor in the carriage motor&amp;rsquo;s H-bridge.
This recurring problem has become a pattern, leading to a routine replacement of the H-bridge transistors during restorations. However, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t standard practice in 2020, necessitating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s return for transistor replacement.
Along with the H-bridge transistors, other known problematic components were also updated.</description></item><item><title> Beogram 4004 Type 5526: Platter Motor, Detector Arm Adjustment and Solenoid Repair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-4004-type-5526-platter-motor-detector-arm-adjustment-and-solenoid-repair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-4004-type-5526-platter-motor-detector-arm-adjustment-and-solenoid-repair/</guid><description>During today&amp;rsquo;s work, I installed the Beogram 4004 platter motor, fine-tuned the position sensor&amp;rsquo;s voltage, calibrated the detector arm sensor, and addressed an issue with the arm lowering solenoid.
My previous checks indicated adjustments would be needed after installing new parts, which is typical.
I also observed that the Beogram 4004&amp;rsquo;s arm solenoid, responsible for lowering the tonearm, was not raising it correctly. There was a lag between the signal to raise the tonearm and the solenoid disengaging.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Arrival from Italy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-arrival-from-italy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 20:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-arrival-from-italy/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to be working on another Beogram 4000 restoration. The unit arrived from overseas in just three days and was packaged very well, ensuring its safe arrival.
The exterior looks good overall. The wood veneer is undamaged and the dust cover can be polished back to its original shine.
The aluminum trim on the back of the dust cover needs to be reattached, which should be a simple fix. Inside, the aluminum plates need a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>Following the repair of the MMC cartridge mount on the Beogram 4000, attention shifted to the malfunctioning arm lowering and tracking mechanisms.
The arm lowering system, comprising a solenoid and damper, was examined. The damper and its associated linkages were removed for cleaning and lubrication.
Inspection revealed the absence of a vital rubber washer in the damper unit, substituted with a makeshift transparency foil piece. This modification hindered proper damper function.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Solenoid and the Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-solenoid-and-the-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:44:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-solenoid-and-the-switches/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration I&amp;rsquo;m working on requires some final adjustments. A key part of any complete restoration is calibrating the solenoid and its associated switches. This solenoid is critical as it manages the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s up/down movement and activates three important switches: audio muting, solenoid power control, and carriage transport. The audio muting switches are crucial for silencing the cartridge coils until the stylus makes contact with the record, preventing unwanted noise.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair and Exploration of an Intermittently Oscillating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-and-exploration-of-an-intermittently-oscillating-solenoid/</guid><description>This section details the work done on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s oscillating solenoid, and what was learned about winding solenoid coils and comparing them to the original.
The arm lowering mechanism is shown here:
When the control logic initiates arm lowering, the solenoid pushes the solenoid lever forward. The lever opens the solenoid switch when fully extended, decreasing the current flowing through the solenoid to a level just enough to keep it engaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Arm, Replacement of the Damper Gasket and Re-Glueing of a Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-arm-replacement-of-the-damper-gasket-and-re-glueing-of-a-plinth-corner/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 required a few final adjustments before it could be returned to its owner following a wiring sleeve replacement on the carriage harness and a fix for an intermittent solenoid.
During its initial restoration in 2020, I was unfamiliar with some common problems that these turntables develop. One such issue involves the damper gasket, which tends to harden over time. This hardening can lead to uneven arm lowering due to inconsistent airflow around the gasket.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Linear Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</guid><description>My restoration project of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable started with the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. These mechanisms often require attention because of hardened lubricants and misadjusted tracking sensors.
After taking the mechanism apart for cleaning and lubrication, I addressed the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm, which commonly experiences stiffness due to hardened lubricants.
The sensor arm was then removed for disassembly to further work on the linkage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): When Disaster Strikes! - Replacement of the Solenoid Switch and Restoration of a Melted Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-when-disaster-strikes-replacement-of-the-solenoid-switch-and-restoration-of-a-melted-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 20:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-when-disaster-strikes-replacement-of-the-solenoid-switch-and-restoration-of-a-melted-solenoid/</guid><description>It seems my Beogram 4002 customer in Arizona is having arm lowering issues again, just a short time after my last repair in December 2022. Upon opening the unit, I discovered the solenoid had completely melted down due to a faulty arm extension I had previously installed. This prevented the solenoid switch from deactivating, leading to overheating and ultimately, failure.
To fix this, I crafted a new solenoid coil and replaced the melted one.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of Short Circuited Solenoid Coil and Repair of Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-short-circuited-solenoid-coil-and-repair-of-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-short-circuited-solenoid-coil-and-repair-of-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently received a faulty solenoid coil and the main circuit board from a Beogram 4002 turntable belonging to a customer in Texas. I requested the circuit board be sent along with the coil because there&amp;rsquo;s usually an underlying reason why these coils fail, especially in later models of the Beogram 4002 and 4004 turntables.
The components arrived as shown in the image:
My first step was to measure the coil&amp;rsquo;s resistance to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s diagnosis:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Repair of a Cracked Solenoid Lever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 11:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-repair-of-a-cracked-solenoid-lever/</guid><description>A customer asked for help with a broken part, a solenoid lever, from their Beogram 4002 Type 5503 turntable. The AC-powered versions of this model use a mechanical switch to control the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s current after the arm lowers. To accomplish this, the solenoid arm has a tab that depresses the switch once the arm is down. Some later AC versions use a plastic extension riveted to the lever to achieve this, a design change I observed to be problematic in my experience.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:19:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>The initial phase of the Beogram 4000 restoration involved the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking mechanisms. The solenoid and damper, essential for the arm&amp;rsquo;s smooth and controlled descent onto the record, were revealed.
Each part was carefully removed, cleaned, and lubricated.
Attention then turned to the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm. Located on the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s side, it required the arm&amp;rsquo;s removal to access and lubricate the linkage&amp;rsquo;s pivot point.</description></item></channel></rss>