<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2021 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2021/</link><description>Recent content in 2021 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:48:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In 2021, digitalization will be the driving force behind recruitment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Randstad Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 2021 Market Outlook Report examines the economic and hiring trends anticipated for 2021.
Jaya Dass, Managing Director for Randstad Malaysia and Singapore, emphasizes that digital transformation will be a key driver of talent demand in 2021. She predicts a surge in demand for tech professionals and digitally skilled individuals across various sectors. While acknowledging the cautious optimism of businesses in the wake of the pandemic, Dass highlights the need for agility and innovation to adapt to the evolving landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chocolate is considered the most popular indulgence product in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesians are increasingly understanding the advantages of moderate chocolate consumption, leading to consistent purchases for snacking and special occasions. This trend fueled growth in chocolate confectionery sales in 2016, according to research firm Euromonitor. The company predicts chocolate confectionery will remain the preferred treat for Indonesian consumers of all ages.
Ceres PT, a major player in the Indonesian chocolate market, held a commanding 52% market share in 2016. Euromonitor attributes this success to the company&amp;rsquo;s strong brand reputation, diverse product range, and competitive pricing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coursera unveils the top courses for learners in Singapore in 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</guid><description>In 2021, Singaporean users on Coursera showed a strong interest in courses teaching in-demand tech and data science skills. This conclusion comes from Coursera&amp;rsquo;s yearly report analyzing course selections made by over 750,000 registered learners in Singapore. The report reveals the skills, abilities, and subjects most sought after by Singaporeans.
Here are the top 10 most popular Coursera courses in Singapore for 2021:
S Course Name Partner Name 1 First Step Korean Yonsei University 2 Machine Learning Stanford University 3 The Science of Well-Being Yale University 4 Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere Google 5 Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) University of Michigan 6 Financial Markets Yale University 7 Introduction to Psychology Yale University 8 _ Chinese for Beginners_ Peking University 9 _ Foundations of Project Management_ Google 10 Learning How to Learn: Powerful mental tools to help you master tough subjects Deep Teaching Solutions Source: Coursera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coursera-unveils-the-top-courses-for-learners-in-singapore-in-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to Henley &amp; Partners, APAC passports provide greater international travel opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:41:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</guid><description>The 2021 Henley Passport Index, which ranks global passports based on the number of destinations accessible without a prior visa, places Japan in first place when disregarding temporary restrictions. This is the third year in a row that Japan has achieved the top spot, independently or tied with Singapore. The index, which uses exclusive data from the International Air Transport Association (IATA), demonstrates the Asia Pacific (APAC) region&amp;rsquo;s dominance, a trend experts predict will continue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis highlights the divide between cybersecurity awareness and personal protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-highlights-the-divide-between-cybersecurity-awareness-and-personal-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 23:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-highlights-the-divide-between-cybersecurity-awareness-and-personal-protection/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyber protection company based in Singapore, has discovered a discrepancy between the understanding of the need for data protection and the actions taken to achieve it.
A global survey conducted for World Backup Day on March 31st опросила 4,400 IT users and professionals across 22 countries and 6 continents, including Singapore. The results challenge the assumption that simply using more solutions will address cybersecurity and data protection concerns...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-highlights-the-divide-between-cybersecurity-awareness-and-personal-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-highlights-the-divide-between-cybersecurity-awareness-and-personal-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TechSci Research believes that the organic dairy market has significant potential</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</guid><description>A recent report by TechSci Research, a global management consulting firm, predicts significant growth in the global organic dairy products market. Driven by factors like increased health consciousness, a growing urban population, and rising spending on organic foods, the market is expected to achieve a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of over 11% between 2016 and 2021.
The report, titled Global Organic Dairy Products Market By Product Type, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, identifies expanding product lines, readily available organic dairy products, strong distribution networks, increasing internet access, and proactive marketing strategies from key players as contributing factors to this projected growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-disciplinary conversations are reshaping the service economy at KODW 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Pictured at the KODW 2021 opening ceremony are (from left) Lofai Lo (Director and GM, ViuTV); Dr Lay Lian Ong (Principal, Hong Kong Design Institute &amp;amp; Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education); Victor Tsang (Head of Create Hong Kong); Professor Eric Yim (Chairman of Hong Kong Design Centre); guest of honor The Honourable Edward Yau (Secretary for Commerce and Economic Development); Victor Lo (Chairman, KODW Steering Committee of Hong Kong Design Centre); Professor Kun-Pyo Lee (Dean of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Design), and Dr Edmund Lee (Executive Director of Hong Kong Design Centre)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel celebrates National Day with Olympics film honoring Singapore's resilient spirit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 21:42:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</guid><description>Singtel has chosen an Olympics theme for its annual National Day (August 8) tribute.
Source: Singtel. Sprinter Shanti Pereira is featured in Leading Through Uncertainty, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s National Day tribute for 2021.
This year&amp;rsquo;s film, Leading Through Uncertainty, spotlights several of the nation&amp;rsquo;s top athletes who represented Singapore at the 2020 Olympics in Tokyo. It chronicles the athletes&amp;rsquo; journey to the Games amidst the uncertainty of the COVID-19 pandemic and its impact on the 2020 Games...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2021 Budget of Singapore emphasizes resilience and aims for long-term success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2021-budget-of-singapore-emphasizes-resilience-and-aims-for-long-term-success/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2021-budget-of-singapore-emphasizes-resilience-and-aims-for-long-term-success/</guid><description>Singapore’s Deputy Prime Minister, Coordinating Minister for Economic Policies, and Minister for Finance Heng Swee Keat presented the Budget 2021: Emerging Stronger Together plan, outlining the government’s strategy for addressing current issues and its vision for a stronger Singapore. The goal is a nation that is economically thriving, socially unified, and environmentally sustainable for all.
Source: Singapore Ministry of Finance.
Cover, Budget Booklet.
To fund Singapore’s regular expenses, the government previously announced in Budget 2018 that the goods and services tax (GST) rate would increase between 2021 and 2025...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2021-budget-of-singapore-emphasizes-resilience-and-aims-for-long-term-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2021-budget-of-singapore-emphasizes-resilience-and-aims-for-long-term-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ideal location for candy in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT is a dominant player in the Indonesian confectionery market, particularly recognized for its Mentos brand.
According to a report on the Indonesian confectionery sector by market research firm Euromonitor, the wide array of inexpensive sugary treats, combined with robust marketing campaigns from prominent manufacturers, has propelled sales in this category within Indonesia.
Holding a commanding 23% market share in 2016, Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT remains the leader in the sugar confectionery sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Business of Design Week 2021 is open to participants from all over the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Officiating guests join Business of Design Week 2021’s opening ceremony.
The 19th edition of Business of Design Week (BODW) 2021 has begun. This major Asian design, innovation, and brand event, organized annually by the Hong Kong Design Centre (HKDC) since 2002, will run for a week. The summit showcases a diverse range of speakers and television programs centered around the theme of Global Design Reset.
The event adopts a hybrid format this year, broadcast simultaneously online, on ViuTV, and at various partner venues such as the PMQ in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ascott Star Rewards is marking its second anniversary with special promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 20:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</guid><description>Ascott Star Rewards (ASR), the loyalty program of The Ascott Limited, is marking its second anniversary with a &amp;ldquo;Celebrate The Little Joys&amp;rdquo; campaign. This campaign offers double bonus points and complimentary tier upgrades to show appreciation and reward its members.
Since its 2019 launch, ASR has experienced over 400% membership growth. ASR members are responsible for roughly 90% of Ascott’s direct online bookings, and over 60% are repeat guests. Compared to non-members, ASR members spend 36% more with Ascott...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Submit your entries for the Zayed Sustainability Prize now!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 17:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</guid><description>The Zayed Sustainability Prize, a prominent global sustainability award based in the UAE, is calling for submissions for its 13th annual edition. Winners in each category will receive US$600,000 to further develop their sustainability solutions and create global impact.
Dr. Sultan Ahmed Al Jaber, UAE Minister of State and Director General of the Zayed Sustainability Prize, expressed confidence that the Prize will continue to draw in top innovators worldwide, tackling pressing global sustainability issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>