<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1511PLBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1511plbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 1511PLBG4000 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1511plbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Upgrade of Signal Path with New DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The DIN5 plug on the Beogram 4000 being restored was heavily oxidized and needed replacement. A new, fully metal plug with gold-plated terminals was installed.
To improve the signal output, a switch was added to connect the signal and system grounds. This feature is beneficial when using a DIN5 to RCA adapter, as RCA cables lack a system ground. Connecting the system ground to the signal ground on the Beogram can reduce humming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The final step in restoring my Beogram 4000 involved replacing the damaged dust cover with one from a donor unit. While the replacement had some typical scratches, it was in good condition overall.
I began by sanding the surface with 320 grit sandpaper to remove the scratches. The next step was to polish it back to its original shine and clarity. Here&amp;rsquo;s the dust cover after polishing with 800 grit:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Glueing a Delaminated Platter Back Together and Installation of New Cabined Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on was unfortunately damaged during shipping due to inadequate packaging by the seller. Because the platter wasn&amp;rsquo;t secured, it moved around and ultimately split into two pieces. The images show the separated top and bottom sections of the platter.
Examining the platter&amp;rsquo;s interior reveals interesting details about its construction. The heavier bottom section of each platter was individually balanced, much like car tires. This involved drilling away small amounts of material from the heavier side, as evidenced by the red pen marks near the drill holes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Afternoon Exploring the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem arose with its record detection system. While it functioned correctly at the 12-inch LP position, it frequently failed to detect records at the 7-inch singles position. This malfunction was observed when the turntable, starting without a record on the platter, bypassed the LP position but stopped at the singles position.
An examination of the circuit diagram revealed the signal path of the detection system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Evening Exploring the Differential Stop Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</guid><description>Before returning a refurbished unit to a customer, we put it through rigorous real-world testing. This involves playing music for several weeks to ensure consistent functionality. This listening process is a delightful part of working with Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen equipment, as our workshop is always filled with music! A recent case involving a restored Beogram 4000 turntable highlights the value of this testing phase.
During playback, I noticed the arm occasionally failed to return to its resting position after reaching the record&amp;rsquo;s end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>