<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Insights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insights/</link><description>Recent content in Insights on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in Singapore are increasingly transitioning to cloud services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</guid><description>Parallels, a company specializing in hosting and cloud services, has released an updated report on the Singaporean cloud market for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), called Parallels SMB Cloud Insights. This 2014 report predicts significant growth for the SMB cloud services market in Singapore, projecting it to reach S$916 million by 2017. This represents a strong three-year compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 21%.
Source: Parallels. Zanni.
John Zanni, Chief Marketing Officer for Service Providers at Parallels, observed that the Asia Pacific region is poised to outpace the rest of the world in cloud adoption due to its later start...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The attitudes towards cybercrime and security in Singapore vary across different generations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</guid><description>This past week, I encountered WhatsApp spam shortly after a friend forwarded a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s discount coupon from Sniflr. Upon researching, I discovered Sniflr is a phishing scam that tricks people into sharing the coupon with 10 friends on WhatsApp, adding those numbers to a spam list.
Yesterday, a promoted tweet on my Twitter feed advertised a S$100 discount on a S$120 purchase at NTUC, a popular Singaporean supermarket chain. However, a Google search revealed a months-old news article warning about fake NTUC coupons on Facebook, a claim supported by NTUC&amp;rsquo;s official Twitter account...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>