<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private/</link><description>Recent content in Private on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:03:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring the waters of Indonesia aboard Rascal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-waters-of-indonesia-aboard-rascal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:03:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-waters-of-indonesia-aboard-rascal/</guid><description>Source: Rascal.
Rascal, a refurbished traditional Indonesian Phinisi* yacht outfitted with modern engines, navigation, and entertainment systems, promises the ultimate adventure.
Guests enjoy personalized service on board, experiencing renowned Indonesian hospitality amidst chic tropical decor.
The removal of Rascal&amp;rsquo;s mast and sails allows for five ensuite double cabins across two spacious decks. Both indoor and outdoor areas are designed for relaxation.
The top deck, soaring 21 feet high, doubles as a diving platform.</description></item><item><title>VistaJet has teamed up with Apex Air to provide private jet travel services in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</guid><description>VistaJet, a provider of luxury long-range private jet travel, announced that Apex Air, a business jet operator authorized by the Civil Aviation Administration of China (CAAC), will oversee and operate a fleet of aircraft based in China for VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s Flight Solution Program.
VistaJet is prepared to offer point-to-point service within China as early as the third quarter of 2015 with its first Chinese-registered aircraft, a Bombardier1 Challenger 8501. Chinese customers will also have access to VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s fleet of over 50 large-cabin, long-range Bombardier Challenger and Global aircraft for international flights.</description></item><item><title>Travel to Banwa Private Island with Ascent Flights Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</guid><description>Banwa Private Island, a secluded island in Northeast Palawan known for its pristine beaches, has joined forces with Ascent Flights Global to provide exclusive and secure travel options for its guests. This collaboration aims to create a protected travel environment through personalized on-demand flights using seaplanes, helicopters, or private jets based on individual preferences.
Source: Banwa Private Island. Banwa Private Island has partnered Ascent Flights Global to offer guests safe, private transport to their accommodation.</description></item><item><title>The Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong and Vistajet provide a rare and unique experience called Once in a Blue Moon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</guid><description>VistaJet, a prominent business aviation company, has partnered with the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong to create the &amp;ldquo;Once in a Blue Moon&amp;rdquo; experience. This exclusive offer celebrates the Mid-Autumn Festival with a luxurious private jet journey featuring an in-flight menu designed by Chef Wong, the Executive Chinese Chef of the Michelin-starred Man Wah restaurant at the Mandarin Oriental.
Available from September 15 to October 15, 2020, this unique offering features a customized private jet experience departing from Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Aramex is constructing private parcel lockers to meet the demands of the expanding e-commerce industry in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:04:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Aramex, a leading provider of global logistics and transportation solutions, has partnered with InPost, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest parcel locker network. This collaboration aims to provide consumers in the Middle East with convenient access to private, automated parcel lockers for all their e-commerce needs by the end of 2014.
Aramex attributes the significant growth of the e-commerce sector in the region to several factors. These include a growing affluent urban population, increased interest in and demand for online products and services, and a rise in new online retailers entering the market.</description></item></channel></rss>