<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Personal Data on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/personal-data/</link><description>Recent content in Personal Data on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/personal-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in C-582/14 Breyer establishes IP addresses as personal data.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The opinions presented are solely those of the author and should not be interpreted as representing the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s official stance.
Background
The Breyer case saw the German Supreme Court (Bundesgerichtshof) request clarification from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on whether dynamic IP addresses constitute personal data under the EU Data Protection Directive and to what extent their storage and processing is permissible for maintaining website functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU makes a ruling on data protection laws and home CCTV: Bringing Data Protection to Your Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Law, University of Essex
A recent decision by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ryneš v. Úřad pro ochranuosobníchúdajů addressed whether EU data protection law applies to home CCTV cameras. The CJEU agreed with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s earlier opinion on the matter, though it avoided addressing some of the more complex issues.
This judgment is significant for two reasons. Firstly, its implications extend beyond stationary surveillance systems and could impact how recording devices are used in public areas, even by private citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is EU data protection law violated by Facebook and the USA? The CJEU hearing in Schrems.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</guid><description>Simon McGarr, a solicitor at McGarr Solicitors, provides an overview of the Schrems v Data Protection Commissioner case heard by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The case revolves around Austrian law student Max Schrems&amp;rsquo; legal challenge concerning the transfer of his personal data from Facebook to the United States. Schrems argues that such transfers violate his data privacy rights due to the risk of mass surveillance under US law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>