<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Office Tools on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/office-tools/</link><description>Recent content in Office Tools on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:56:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/office-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FAX On The Run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fax-on-the-run/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fax-on-the-run/</guid><description>Fax machines have long been the go-to for urgent business documents, with large companies utilizing massive machines and smaller offices relying on all-in-one devices. However, these machines share a common limitation: they are tethered to a physical location.
This restriction is eliminated with internet faxing, which allows sending and receiving faxes from any location with internet access, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a cafe, hotel, airport, or even using mobile broadband. This technology is readily accessible at an affordable price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fax-on-the-run/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fax-on-the-run/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Color Printers, Really?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-color-printers-really/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 15:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-color-printers-really/</guid><description>The introduction of television after World War II brought small, black and white images into homes. While basic, it was considered an improvement over radio. However, the arrival of color television quickly overshadowed its predecessor. Suddenly, black and white images seemed inadequate, especially when compared to the vibrant colors offered by the newer technology.
Similarly, early desktop computers displayed images in monochrome, often limited to black and white or basic color combinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-color-printers-really/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-color-printers-really/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>