<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Salary on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/salary/</link><description>Recent content in Salary on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/salary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Think about the possibility of working in the Middle East to increase your savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</guid><description>A new study by Business Name Generator (BNG) reveals salary trends in 28 cities worldwide, focusing on four sectors: marketing, HR, creative, and tech.
Tech
Doha takes the lead as the highest-paying city for tech professionals, boasting an average annual salary of £127,888. Data scientists emerge as top earners, commanding an average yearly salary of £361,877. After factoring in the annual cost of living (£26,382), Doha still provides the highest disposable income for tech workers, reaching £101,506 annually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you have digital or tech skills, chances are your salary is above average</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</guid><description>Source: Willis Towers Watson. Report cover.
The financial sector, particularly in digital roles, is experiencing salary stability due to a high demand for tech professionals. This trend persists despite overall economic weakness in other industries, including banking, according to the global advisory firm Willis Towers Watson.
Businesses across all sectors are becoming progressively reliant on data and technology, and the banking industry is no exception. This shift has resulted in a talent competition where technological expertise is more valuable than financial background...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the Al Rabeh salary account by Kuwait Finance House</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced the Al-Rabeh account, a salary account that offers customers chances to win valuable prizes like Range Rovers and gold each quarter. Al-Rabeh is also designed as an investment savings account, providing customers with annual dividends.
This account caters to individuals who want to transfer their salaries and manage their personal finances while benefiting from savings and investment opportunities. The Al-Rabeh account is available in Kuwaiti Dinars (KD) and requires regular salary transfers to be eligible for prize draws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A study conducted by INSEAD has discovered that when shareholders vote on CEO accountability, it leads to higher company returns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:02:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</guid><description>A new study titled &amp;ldquo;Say Pays! Shareholder Voice and Firm Performance,&amp;rdquo; published in the Review of Finance, suggests that shareholder votes do improve CEO accountability and reduce unnecessary spending within corporations. The study&amp;rsquo;s author, Maria Guadalupe, an Associate Professor at INSEAD, found that previous research on the impact of &amp;ldquo;say-on-pay&amp;rdquo; policies was inconclusive, possibly due to focusing on periods after say-on-pay became law.
Guadalupe&amp;rsquo;s research examined 250 instances where shareholders of S&amp;amp;P 1500 companies proposed to adopt say-on-pay policies between 2006 and 2010, before such votes were mandatory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Salary growth is expected in Southeast Asia as there is a high demand for IT skillsets in key sectors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s IT sector is expected to experience high demand for skilled professionals and contract workers in 2018, particularly in fintech, healthcare, and technology.
Specialized skills will be highly sought after in 2018 across accounting and finance, human resources, sales and marketing, and technology sectors.
According to the 2018 Salary Survey by Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, the economic outlook for the coming year is positive. The survey anticipates that continued digitalization and market expansion in Southeast Asia will fuel salary growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Top-paying technology jobs for 2014 - for those in the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</guid><description>The 2014 Salary Guides published by Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group identify six technology and digital jobs experiencing high demand in the US. This demand may also be reflected in the Asia Pacific region.
Companies are specifically seeking professionals skilled in information and network security, data analysis for business intelligence, and mobile development.
&amp;ldquo;Building a strong online presence and engaging customers through mobile platforms is crucial for businesses today,&amp;rdquo; says John Reed, Senior Executive Director of Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt provides insights on Malaysia's perspective in the Total Compensation Measurement study</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</guid><description>Aon Hewitt, a global human resource consulting firm, has published their Total Compensation Measurement (TCM) 2015 Study. This comprehensive report analyzes compensation data from 25,000 positions in 180 countries.
Salary increase by industry sector in Malaysia
While the global GDP is projected to grow from 3.1% in 2015 to 3.6% in 2016, regional economic conditions play a vital role in employee compensation decisions. In Southeast Asia, the Philippines and Vietnam led in 2015 with 6% and 6...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies are focusing on ensuring that their workforces are prepared for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-are-focusing-on-ensuring-that-their-workforces-are-prepared-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-are-focusing-on-ensuring-that-their-workforces-are-prepared-for-the-future/</guid><description>- The Asia-Pacific region is seeing a high demand for professionals with a mix of skills, especially those with expertise in technology and the ability to adapt to new situations. This trend is driven by the increasing adoption of digital technologies across various sectors.
- To attract and keep skilled workers, companies are refining their hiring strategies to identify individuals who are not only experts in their fields but also adaptable and possess a global perspective...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-are-focusing-on-ensuring-that-their-workforces-are-prepared-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-are-focusing-on-ensuring-that-their-workforces-are-prepared-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>