<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Detection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/detection/</link><description>Recent content in Detection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/detection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Non-Working End Groove Detection - Repair of a Detached Carriage Position Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. One peculiar problem was a detached carriage position sensor, which is housed within a black light shield. This shield was hanging at an angle, but it needs to be positioned vertically. The sensor works by using black sections on a plexiglass strip attached to the carriage to interrupt light from an IR diode. If the sensor is misaligned, stray light can disrupt the carriage&amp;rsquo;s movement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacement of End Groove Detection Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 23:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5501) RPM trimmer panel, the focus shifted to the malfunctioning end groove detection mechanism. This ingenious mechanism utilizes a light bulb, a photoresistor, and an encoder wheel acting as a pulley to detect when the carriage accelerates after the record&amp;rsquo;s final track. By identifying this movement, the mechanism reduces the return time to the home position for records with extended end grooves, such as 12&amp;quot; singles or certain LPs with shorter playtimes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: End Groove Detection Issue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-end-groove-detection-issue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 17:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-end-groove-detection-issue/</guid><description>Following the hood polishing, I believed my work on this Beogram 4000 was complete, but I was mistaken. A final functionality test before packing revealed a peculiar issue. When the ON button was pressed without a record on the platter, the carriage would move inward as expected, but then halt abruptly before reaching the end switch (ES). Pressing FF would release it, but the carriage would instantly retract without contacting the ES...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-end-groove-detection-issue/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-end-groove-detection-issue/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): End Groove Detection Not Working</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</guid><description>Just when I thought I had finished refurbishing a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a problem surfaced during playback. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t return after playing a record, instead getting stuck in the end groove, repeating the sound of the run-out.
Investigating further, I used an oscilloscope to examine the signal from the position sensor, which tells the control system the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s location. The signal was weak specifically in the end groove area, often indicating misalignment between the sensor&amp;rsquo;s IR diode and the light entry slit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Afternoon Exploring the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem arose with its record detection system. While it functioned correctly at the 12-inch LP position, it frequently failed to detect records at the 7-inch singles position. This malfunction was observed when the turntable, starting without a record on the platter, bypassed the LP position but stopped at the singles position.
An examination of the circuit diagram revealed the signal path of the detection system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Random Stop Issue Fixed - Defective Photo Resistor in the Spindle RPM Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, previously restored, began experiencing a problem where the OFF function would randomly activate during playback as if the button was pressed.
Prior to delving into the solution, the circuit diagram is presented for reference.
Transistor TR17, within the &amp;lsquo;Electronic Switch&amp;rsquo; section, is responsible for initiating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s OFF function. When its base is grounded, the collector rises to approximately 18V, causing the arm to lift and return to its resting position...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>