<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NOC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/noc/</link><description>Recent content in NOC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/noc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vocal IP Networx Offers Free SNMP Monitoring</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with the challenges of managing T1 lines and bandwidth, especially keeping track of service availability across different vendors and equipment. While large companies have dedicated IT teams, smaller businesses often handle this responsibility as issues arise.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be beneficial to have affordable network monitoring support? Vocal IP Networx, a leading IP telephony provider, offers a solution: free, continuous SNMP monitoring for all circuits and customer premises equipment (CPE) they provide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>