<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Behaviour on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/behaviour/</link><description>Recent content in Behaviour on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/behaviour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>If apps don't offer speed, simplicity, and security, consumers will not hesitate to abandon them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</guid><description>Source: CA Technologies infographic.
People are pickier than ever about the apps they use, so businesses that don&amp;rsquo;t offer a good app experience could lose a significant portion of their customers. A regional study* sponsored by CA Technologies shows that mobile and desktop applications in the Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) region have become key to earning customer loyalty.
Software: the New Battleground for Brand Loyalty – A survey of 1,449 consumers and 259 business decision-makers across five APJ nations pinpointed three major factors influencing the customer experience: Source: CA Technologies infographic.</description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers.</description></item><item><title>The key to e-commerce success according to Akamai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</guid><description>Akamai, a content delivery network (CDN) provider, emphasizes the importance of speed in e-commerce, stating that slow loading times can lead to customer loss. They suggest two key ways online retailers can improve their businesses: by understanding modern customer behavior and by prioritizing speed, intelligence, and security in their online operations.
Mobile shopping is a growing trend. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s data shows that mobile and tablet shoppers make purchases 20% more often and spend US$500 more than desktop users in the same timeframe, highlighting the need for strong mobile optimization.</description></item></channel></rss>