<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IPBill on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ipbill/</link><description>Recent content in IPBill on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ipbill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it an early Christmas gift or a disappointment? Examining data retention and the leaked ePrivacy Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
The leak of a draft ePrivacy Regulation on December 12, 2016, has sparked discussions about its implications for data retention. This post will examine this aspect of the draft regulation.
The Article 29 Data Protection Working Party (A29DPWP) had previously advised against introducing new European data retention requirements. This recommendation, reflecting concerns about the existing ePrivacy Directive&amp;rsquo;s allowance for national data retention regimes, is echoed in the leaked draft Regulation.</description></item><item><title>Regardless of the CJEU's decision, data retention could potentially continue to exist under national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
A central question regarding internet privacy is whether governments should be allowed to store data about everyone&amp;rsquo;s online and phone activities in the name of fighting terrorism and serious crime. This issue, known as &amp;ldquo;data retention,&amp;rdquo; raises crucial questions about balancing privacy and security, both nationally and within the European Union. Initially, the EU&amp;rsquo;s electronic privacy (e-Privacy) Directive offered member states the choice to implement data retention rules, deviating from the usual rule of communication confidentiality outlined in the directive.</description></item></channel></rss>