<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Freedom of Information on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freedom-of-information/</link><description>Recent content in Freedom of Information on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freedom-of-information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access to documents: The Council may choose not to enforce a significant CJEU ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU is frequently criticized for its lack of transparency, particularly concerning its legislative processes. Ideally, these processes should be as open as those in national legislatures, allowing public access to draft legislation.
However, despite a 2001 regulation on public access to documents, EU transparency in this area remains an issue. Within the Council, some Member States prefer to keep their positions confidential during negotiations. This secrecy undermines the idea that citizens, through their national parliaments, can hold their governments accountable for actions taken within the Council.</description></item><item><title>Is it time for the EU to increase transparency in its legislative process, as condemned by the EU Court?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</guid><description>Massimo Frigo, Senior Legal Adviser of the International Commission of Jurist’s Europe Programme*
Occasionally, cases concerning seemingly insignificant administrative matters evolve into pivotal judgments, shaping the continuous development of our democratic legal frameworks. A prime example in the US is Marbury v. Madison, a case initially garnering limited public interest due to its focus on judicial appointment procedures. Nonetheless, it ultimately established the crucial precedent of constitutional review within the US legal system.</description></item><item><title>A leaked document discloses that the EU is considering suspending the Schengen agreement for a period of two years.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</guid><description>Commentary by Steve Peers
This is Council document 14300/15, from December 1, 2015, called &amp;ldquo;Integrity of the Schengen area,&amp;rdquo; and sent to Coreper (representatives of EU member states) and the Council - likely the Justice and Home Affairs ministers meeting December 3rd and 4th. (An official version of the document is available here).
The first three sections are relatively standard (see here for discussion), but section 4 proposes initiating a process to formally permit the reinstatement of internal border controls within the Schengen zone for a duration of up to two years.</description></item><item><title>Regarding knowledge as power: the transparency of procedures for making EU laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</guid><description>Päivi Leino (University of Helsinki)
A key promise made during the adoption of the Lisbon Treaty was increased transparency in EU law-making. However, this has not yet been realized. Access to documents related to EU legislative processes, especially &amp;ldquo;trilogues&amp;rdquo; (informal meetings between the European Parliament, the Council, and the Commission), has become a significant concern. This issue is highlighted in the new Interinstitutional Agreement (IIA) on Better Regulation, the European Ombudsman&amp;rsquo;s public consultation on trilogue transparency, and a legal appeal by a former LIBE Committee Secretariat head against the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s refusal to grant full access to legislative documents.</description></item></channel></rss>