<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Domestic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/domestic/</link><description>Recent content in Domestic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/domestic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JAL's Japan Explorer Pass simplifies travel in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</guid><description>Japan Airlines (JAL) now offers the Japan Explorer Pass, a convenient and affordable fare option for visitors from outside Japan, as well as Japanese citizens residing abroad, to explore various destinations within the country.
Travelers can easily purchase economy class tickets online, adhering to the following guidelines:
Domestic flights operated by JAL and JTA (Japan Transocean Air) can be booked up to 72 hours before the scheduled departure, even if the traveler is already in Japan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>