<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-network/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Network on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</guid><description>MPLS networks are frequently mentioned as a way to connect multiple business locations. But what exactly is MPLS, and why is it superior to other network architectures?
MPLS, or Multi-Protocol Label Switching, is a technology distinct from traditional circuit-switched or packet-switched networks. While it allows IP traffic transmission, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t rely on IP routing.
The advantage of MPLS networks lies in their ability to handle almost any protocol without requiring conversions to fit the network structure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Lines For MPLS Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</guid><description>Companies needing to link numerous locations are increasingly choosing MPLS networks, often finding T1 lines to be the optimal solution for network access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Consider an MPLS (Multi Protocol Label Switching) network as a private internet. This private ownership allows the MPLS operator to guarantee the bandwidth and service quality needed for your applications&amp;rsquo; reliable operation. Security is also strengthened as access is exclusive to subscribing businesses.
An MPLS network functions as a customized cloud, connecting only your specified locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>