<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>USB on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/usb/</link><description>Recent content in USB on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:13:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/usb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The six-port USB desktop charger solves all your charging problems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</guid><description>Poweradd, a company known for its mobile device accessories, has introduced a new six-port desktop USB charger with a 50W capacity. This charger is designed to meet the growing demand for charging multiple devices simultaneously when outlets are limited.
The compact charger measures 4&amp;quot; x 2.9&amp;quot; x 1&amp;quot; and supports voltages from 100V to 240V, making it suitable for international use. It features two ports that provide 2.4A, two ports with 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: TwistVolt, the innovative power strip designer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/</guid><description>While typical power strips only accommodate standard plugs, the TwistVolt sets itself apart. It features built-in USB outlets and a flexible design that allows for twisting and folding to better suit your power needs.
Source: Kickstarter website
Michael Schroeder, the inventor, explains that their goal was to create a new kind of power strip that prioritizes energy efficiency and provides easy access to all outlets. The result is a product with exceptional energy efficiency, ample USB charging capacity, and a distinctive, patent-pending design that eliminates outlet blockage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check Point warns that free USB devices may be carriers of malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</guid><description>Source: Victoria Police. The unmarked USB drives used are similar to these.
On September 21st, law enforcement in Victoria, Australia, issued a warning to residents of Pakenham, a Melbourne suburb, about unlabeled USB drives found in mailboxes.
According to the Victoria police statement, people have been discovering unmarked USB drives in their mailboxes. When connected to computers, these drives have exposed victims to fraudulent streaming service offers and other serious problems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Concentrating on Kickstarter: Making Solar Power Accessible to Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 10:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</guid><description>Spor Solar Charges aims to make convenient solar-powered battery charging accessible to everyone. Their product, Spor, is a portable battery charger for USB devices that can recharge itself using solar energy. It can also be powered up using a standard AC outlet. The company claims that Spor can charge multiple devices simultaneously and replenish a phone&amp;rsquo;s battery almost as quickly as a wall outlet, according to their Kickstarter page.
Source: Kickstarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>