<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MIMO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mimo/</link><description>Recent content in MIMO on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mimo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit WiFi For Video Streaming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</guid><description>WiFi has become the standard wireless connection due to its widespread availability, outpacing technologies like Bluetooth and WiMax. While cellular data is useful in the absence of WiFi, its limited bandwidth and potential for overage charges make it a secondary choice. In fact, data shows that most tablet users don&amp;rsquo;t even utilize their device&amp;rsquo;s cellular capabilities. WiFi&amp;rsquo;s strength is evident in its ability to not only replace cellular broadband but also wired connections.</description></item><item><title>Increasing Bandwidth By Pair Bonding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</guid><description>When your T1 line starts reaching its bandwidth limit, upgrading to a DS3 line might seem like the next step, but it comes with challenges. DS3 often requires fiber optic cable instead of the copper used for T1, and the cost difference is significant.
A simpler solution for a moderate bandwidth boost is adding another T1 line and using &amp;ldquo;pair bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines two lines into one, effectively doubling your bandwidth to 3 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Over Copper Avoids Fiber Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</guid><description>Businesses desire fiber optic connections for their high bandwidth capabilities, but the installation costs can be prohibitive, ranging from tens of thousands to even hundreds of thousands of dollars. However, there&amp;rsquo;s an alternative solution worth considering: DS3 over Copper.
Although DS3 is often associated with fiber optic lines, it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a 45 Mbps TDM protocol that can operate on various carriers. Originally, DS3 was delivered using T3 coaxial copper lines, waveguides, or microwave transmissions.</description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it.</description></item><item><title>Tripping the LTE Fantastic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</guid><description>Although fiber optic and mobile WiMAX are getting a lot of attention, LTE could become the next major broadband technology. Could gigabit wireless communication be on the horizon?
People struggling with slow 1G connections or the first iPhone might find the idea of 1,000 Mbps speeds on their mobile devices unrealistic. It seems like there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough bandwidth from cell towers. However, emerging technologies may increase wireless bandwidth significantly.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations.</description></item></channel></rss>