<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-line/</link><description>Recent content in E-Line on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple locations often need to share data, traditionally relying on T1 lines for connectivity. While multiple T1 lines can increase bandwidth, this approach might not be the most cost-effective solution, especially in metropolitan areas.
Point-to-point Ethernet offers a compelling alternative, often at a lower cost per Mbps, particularly for higher bandwidth needs. Ethernet streamlines data transmission by maintaining its format throughout the network, potentially allowing locations to function as a single bridged LAN.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Services over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:35:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</guid><description>Connecting networks logically often involves Ethernet, a technology that has recently expanded its reach beyond local boundaries. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) connections are increasing in availability and often come at a lower cost compared to other options.
EoC enables standard Ethernet services to be delivered through existing copper telephone wiring. Unlike typical Cat 5E or Cat 6 wiring, EoC is compatible with older copper infrastructure not initially intended for Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</guid><description>Metropolitan and Wide Area Networks can send your data anywhere you want. To access these networks, you need a connection known as &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connectivity. Ethernet offers advantages for this first mile link.
Several technologies, such as T1 lines, DSL, SONET fiber optic services, and even microwave or 3G/4G wireless, work well for first mile connections. These options connect your building to your service provider or a gateway to their network.</description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Business-grade Carrier Ethernet services are gaining popularity. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about Ethernet and its potential benefits, read on.
Ethernet dominates as a LAN protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable how quickly it outpaced competitors. Switched Ethernet is nearly ubiquitous. A similar shift is happening with telecom services, moving from traditional circuit-switched technologies to packet-switched networks that align better with modern devices. Ethernet is poised to become the standard for both metropolitan and long-distance networks.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>Extending Ethernet over MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Ethernet has transitioned from a local network protocol to a preferred choice for metropolitan area networks. Its benefits include easy integration with wired and wireless networks, scalable bandwidth without equipment upgrades, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom options. This begs the question: can Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s success in LAN and MAN be replicated in WAN?
Ethernet WAN is gaining popularity, particularly among businesses with geographically dispersed sites. Dedicated point-to-point Ethernet connections are possible, but Ethernet over MPLS presents a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices.</description></item><item><title>EtherSphere Spans The World With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Global Crossing, through its EtherSphere solutions, provides standardized Carrier Ethernet services globally, offering a centralized network solution for multinational companies with dispersed operations.
EtherSphere offers various standardized Ethernet services defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). These services include Point-to-Point Ethernet Private Line (EPL) or E-Line, multipoint connections like Ethernet Virtual Private Line (EVPL), Point-to-Multipoint or E-Tree, and Multipoint-to-Multipoint Ethernet Private LAN or VPLS (Virtual Private LAN Service) E-LAN.
This range of Ethernet services caters to diverse connectivity needs for interconnecting multiple locations.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>How To Find Better Metro E Service Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) services are widely available and offer a practical solution for businesses operating within a metropolitan area to connect their various locations. However, securing the most cost-effective Metro E services requires careful consideration.
Metro Ethernet is a type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) designed to meet the local connectivity needs of businesses. Unlike traditional wide-area networks, MANs focus on providing high-speed connections within a specific city or region.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN to Complement Your LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your company&amp;rsquo;s Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at blazing speeds of 1 Gbps or more, making internal network operations seem almost instantaneous. However, accessing resources outside your physical location can feel painstakingly slow. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be convenient if your LAN could extend across cities or even to remote offices? You might be surprised to learn that this is a possibility.
Yes, The WAN is Ethernet Networks can be broadly categorized as either owned or leased.</description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits.</description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth For Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</guid><description>Contrary to popular belief, Ethernet WAN service isn&amp;rsquo;t confined to cities. There are ways to get Ethernet connectivity even in rural areas.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity among small and medium businesses. It uses existing telephone wiring to deliver Ethernet speeds from 3 to 50 Mbps, and even over 100 Mbps in some places. This makes it a cost-effective option for businesses that need high bandwidth. However, EoC has distance limitations.</description></item></channel></rss>