<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accessory on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accessory/</link><description>Recent content in Accessory on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accessory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The handbag app reveals the newest handbag options available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 15:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</guid><description>Source: Google Play Store.
Swipe Boutique has launched a new fashion app for Android devices called &amp;ldquo;handbag swipe.&amp;rdquo;
The app allows users to explore thousands of the latest handbag designs from over a hundred popular brands, including Topshop, New Look, and Michael Kors.
With a browsing experience resembling Tinder, shoppers can swipe through various handbag options. The app enables users to curate personal wish lists, purchase desired products instantly, or save handbag details for future reference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Altec Lansing introduces durable mobile accessories at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</guid><description>Altec Lansing is launching new lines of durable chargers, power banks, cables, and cases for smartphones and tablets. Expected to be available around the second quarter of 2016, these accessories will have rugged features like IP67-rated, military-grade construction for waterproof, dustproof, and shock-resistant functionality and device protection.
The new products will include:
Altec Lansing Everything Proof Power Packs (3,000, 6,000, and 10,000 mAh): These power banks are designed for smartphones, tablets, and MP3 players, offering up to 100 hours of talk time, 75 hours of music, 50 hours of video, or 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Charge your iPhone while also using a 3.5mm jack simultaneously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:25:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/</guid><description>Belkin, a company known for its mobile accessories, has introduced a new adapter called the 3.5 mm Audio + Charge RockStar for iPhone models 8, 8 Plus, X, 7, and 7 Plus. This adapter allows users to charge their iPhones and listen to audio through 3.5 mm headphones simultaneously.
The adapter connects to the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s Lightning connector and supports data syncing, microphone use, and remote control functionality through the headphone jack...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/charge-your-iphone-while-also-using-a-3-5mm-jack-simultaneously/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>