<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carrier Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carrier-ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Carrier Ethernet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carrier-ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Choosing Dark Fiber vs Lit Fiber Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</guid><description>When applications require the bandwidth of fiber optic transmission, businesses face a choice: use existing &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber services or establish their own transport services using purchased or leased &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; fiber.
Deciding between these options involves weighing performance, cost, and installation time. Focusing solely on cost can lead to extended installation delays, potentially impacting operational needs. While a cost-effective solution might be suitable with ample planning time, immediate bandwidth demands may necessitate prioritizing availability over cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circuit Switched vs Packet Switched Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Over the past few decades, two primary network technologies have been vying for dominance. The first is the traditional telephone system, which served us well throughout the industrial age. The second is the computer-based architecture that has driven the information age. You might recognize these as circuit switching and packet switching.
While both technologies will likely coexist for a while longer, we are at a turning point. From now on, packet switching will be the dominant force in every network, from copper lines to fiber optic cables to wireless connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business moves online and companies shift their IT to the cloud, the demand for WAN bandwidth continues to rise. These days, even small businesses frequently require reliable dedicated internet and inter-office network bandwidth in the range of 100 Mbps to 1 Gbps. Larger companies, particularly those dealing with tech-heavy products, services, or medical imaging, can easily saturate Gigabit connections, making a transition to 10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN a worthwhile consideration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP T1 Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been around for a long time, initially used by phone companies to carry multiple calls between their facilities. Eventually, businesses adopted them for their phone systems. When the Internet became widespread, T1 lines were adapted to serve as dedicated internet connections. This might seem odd given their history, but in today&amp;rsquo;s internet-centric world, T1 lines can indeed function as IP connections.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/) While T1 technology was originally designed for voice calls, the fundamental principle is that digital data is just a series of ones and zeros...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Getting Cavalier About Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</guid><description>Is ignoring Ethernet an option for your business&amp;rsquo;s connection to the world? Can you afford to miss out on its benefits?
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about Cavalier Telephone, a competitive telecom provider, whose Ethernet services are now available on the GeoQuote (tm) search tool within our Shop for Ethernet service. While their name might imply a casual approach, Cavalier is serious about providing the bandwidth your growing business requires.
Cavalier Telephone is a regional Competitive Local Exchange Carrier (CLEC) serving 15 states in the Eastern and Southern US, including Washington D...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aktino Sends 90 Mbps Down Copper Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</guid><description>Advancements in technology are challenging the belief that fiber optic cable is necessary for transmitting DS3 or Carrier Ethernet beyond local networks. Aktino, a company based in California, has developed carrier equipment that enhances the performance of traditional unshielded twisted pair copper loops. This technology enables the delivery of DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) or over 90 Mbps of Carrier Ethernet bandwidth over a CSA (Carrier Serving Area) spanning 12,000 feet. Consequently, numerous businesses and cell tower locations, previously limited in terms of connectivity, can now access high bandwidth connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper While Waiting For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</guid><description>Fiber optic connections are the optimal choice for high bandwidth, offering speeds from 10 Mbps to 10 Gbps using either SONET or Carrier Ethernet protocols. However, accessing these options requires &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber service, which can take several months or more due to potential construction delays. So, how do you maintain connectivity in the meantime?
While waiting for fiber activation was once the only option, many carriers now offer a two-stage solution for businesses needing immediate bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GTT Expands Ethernet Footprint With PacketExchange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</guid><description>GTT, a global telecommunications company, is expanding its Ethernet services globally by acquiring PacketExchange, an Ethernet provider. PacketExchange, based in London, boasts a substantial 10 Gigabit fiber optic IP network spanning Europe, the United States, and Asia, largely acquired through its acquisition of MZIMA Networks in 2010. This combined infrastructure offers private line services, MPLS, VPLS networking, and peering capabilities.
This acquisition highlights the growing dominance of Carrier Ethernet in telecommunications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is DS-3 Bandwidth An Endangered Species?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</guid><description>For a long time, businesses needing a moderate amount of bandwidth have relied on DS-3 telecom services for dedicated internet access, file transfers, and video transport. While the price of DS-3 has been steadily decreasing due to increased competition, it might be approaching obsolescence. But why?
The shift began when data packets replaced digitized voice as the dominant traffic on global networks, and now video demands a significant portion of available bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber - Dark, Lit and Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve decided that a fiber optic connection is no longer optional for your business; it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for productivity. The next step is determining which type of fiber to get. You might be surprised to learn there&amp;rsquo;s more than one option.
One Strand, Multiple Options
The foundation of all fiber optic connections is the transmission of information through modulated light waves within a glass strand. The fiber cable entering your building will appear the same regardless of the type...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Covad and ADTRAN Make Everything Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</guid><description>The arrival of Carrier Ethernet is generating considerable excitement around IP core networks and Ethernet access solutions. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean traditional TDM services are obsolete. DS1 and DS3 circuits can be adapted for Ethernet transport with the right equipment, as demonstrated by Carrier Covad and equipment manufacturer ADTRAN.
Covad is expanding its Ethernet service area using ADTRAN&amp;rsquo;s central office and network termination equipment. With a nationwide core network, Covad serves 44 states and 235 major markets, specializing in business DSL, data T1, fixed wireless, bonded T1, and integrated voice and data solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Branching Out With MPLS and VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</guid><description>Is secure communication between multiple locations critical for your business? As businesses increasingly rely on electronic forms and transactions, traditional methods like fax machines, overnight mail, and dial-up connections are no longer sufficient. To stay competitive, businesses need real-time access to sales and inventory data, rapid transfer of large files like medical images and CAD drawings, and instant delivery of important documents. A broadband connection linking all your key locations is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EtherSphere Spans The World With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Global Crossing, through its EtherSphere solutions, provides standardized Carrier Ethernet services globally, offering a centralized network solution for multinational companies with dispersed operations.
EtherSphere offers various standardized Ethernet services defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). These services include Point-to-Point Ethernet Private Line (EPL) or E-Line, multipoint connections like Ethernet Virtual Private Line (EVPL), Point-to-Multipoint or E-Tree, and Multipoint-to-Multipoint Ethernet Private LAN or VPLS (Virtual Private LAN Service) E-LAN.
This range of Ethernet services caters to diverse connectivity needs for interconnecting multiple locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Transparency Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</guid><description>The ideal computer network operates so seamlessly that users don&amp;rsquo;t even realize it&amp;rsquo;s there. They don&amp;rsquo;t think about the technical details, just like they don&amp;rsquo;t think about how electricity works. It&amp;rsquo;s simply a service they can rely on. This is called transparency.
Many local area networks (LANs) already achieve this level of transparency. With most network cards supporting high speeds like Fast Ethernet or Gigabit Ethernet, company LANs can easily handle business needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth on Demand Complements Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:50:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
One of the biggest advantages of cloud services over traditional IT infrastructure is their flexibility. With a vast pool of virtual servers and storage, businesses can adjust resources on demand, significantly improving productivity and resource usage.
However, connectivity hasn&amp;rsquo;t quite caught up with this shift. Connecting to the cloud often relies on fixed-capacity connections. Upgrading these connections is typically a complex and time-consuming process, creating a bottleneck in an otherwise agile system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Fiber Replaces Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 02:23:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T1 lines have been a popular connectivity solution for businesses for many years due to their reliability and flexibility in private lines, dedicated internet access, and telephone trunking. However, with the increasing demands of cloud applications and HD video, the fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps has become a significant limitation.
Solution #1: Bonded T1 Lines
One way to increase bandwidth is to combine multiple T1 lines. This can be achieved using a WAN aggregation device or by ordering bonded T1 lines from a provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How To Find Better Metro E Service Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) services are widely available and offer a practical solution for businesses operating within a metropolitan area to connect their various locations. However, securing the most cost-effective Metro E services requires careful consideration.
Metro Ethernet is a type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) designed to meet the local connectivity needs of businesses. Unlike traditional wide-area networks, MANs focus on providing high-speed connections within a specific city or region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>When your business or applications need more bandwidth than T1 lines can offer, even multiple bonded ones, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider fiber optic solutions. But with various options available, how do you choose?
Traditionally, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was the primary fiber optic bandwidth option, pioneered by phone companies. SONET surpasses T-Carrier technology (T1 and T3 lines). While T1 provides 1.5 Mbps over copper and T3 offers 45 Mbps over coaxial cable, SONET scales up to OC-1, OC-3, OC-12, OC-24, OC-48, OC-192, OC-256, and OC-768...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN to Complement Your LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your company&amp;rsquo;s Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at blazing speeds of 1 Gbps or more, making internal network operations seem almost instantaneous. However, accessing resources outside your physical location can feel painstakingly slow. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be convenient if your LAN could extend across cities or even to remote offices? You might be surprised to learn that this is a possibility.
Yes, The WAN is Ethernet Networks can be broadly categorized as either owned or leased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Now Faster and Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>For a long time, T1 lines have been the top choice for bandwidth for small and medium businesses. They are popular for good reason: they are widely available, reliable, secure, dedicated, adaptable, and relatively affordable.
While T1 services have many advantages, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get even more value: Ethernet, particularly Ethernet over Copper.
Many people are not familiar with Carrier Ethernet services, as they have only become available recently. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is primarily found in large cities, as it has a limited reach and requires businesses to be within a few miles of the provider&amp;rsquo;s office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet From Coast To Coast</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</guid><description>Imagine your current office Ethernet network expanding beyond the building, connecting your locations across the city and the country. This vision of a unified, nationwide network is now a reality with Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet is essentially the same Ethernet used in local networks, but enhanced and standardized for use in metropolitan and long-distance networks.
To get Carrier Ethernet, businesses need to partner with a network provider offering this service. These providers typically have built extensive, nationwide fiber optic networks with service points in major cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Maps At Your Fingertips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</guid><description>You might want to upgrade to a faster internet service, but the cost of installing fiber optic cables might seem scary. How can you figure out if upgrading from copper to fiber is affordable?
The easiest way is to compare quotes from different providers in your area. A telecom broker, like Telarus, Inc., can gather these quotes for you quickly and easily. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a report with pricing from all major providers in your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How To Deal With Sudden Massive Bandwidth Demands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</guid><description>For years, you experience consistent, though gradually increasing, network bandwidth needs. Then, unexpectedly, you&amp;rsquo;re hit with a demand to increase your WAN bandwidth by 10x or even 100x. How does this happen, and how can you handle such unpredictable situations?
It&amp;rsquo;s unlikely everyone in the company suddenly started downloading HD movies, right? While that would certainly max out your bandwidth, it&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic scenario. Bandwidth demands don&amp;rsquo;t surge without reason...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Is Making Obsolescence Obsolete</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</guid><description>Keeping up with technology is a constant struggle, similar to swimming against a strong current. Any pause or delay can cause you to fall behind competitors who are advancing rapidly.
Technology is constantly evolving, becoming outdated quickly. The longer you rely on existing technology, the more outdated it gets, eventually lacking support or functionality. While the physical hardware may remain functional, it struggles to utilize the latest resources and software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will Ethernet Crush DS3?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</guid><description>Companies needing more bandwidth than a 1.5 Mbps T1 line often upgraded to DS3, but its 45 Mbps speed was often more than they needed. A newer option, Carrier Ethernet (also known as Metro Ethernet), offers a more practical solution with scalable bandwidth at a often lower cost.
Ethernet services are significantly less expensive than DS3 in some markets, costing up to 50% less. However, in areas where Ethernet isn&amp;rsquo;t widely available, prices may be comparable to DS3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your 50 Mbps WAN Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The need for 50 Mbps bandwidth has increased due to businesses needing to use cloud services, access remote data centers, transfer large data files, run e-commerce platforms, send high-resolution images, and distribute video content. There are various ways to get 50 Mbps bandwidth connectivity, each with its own benefits and drawbacks.
DS3 &amp;amp; T3
DS3, or T3, is a traditional telecom service designed for transmitting many calls simultaneously between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>