<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fixed Wireless Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fixed-wireless-access/</link><description>Recent content in Fixed Wireless Access on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:28:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fixed-wireless-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit to 10 Gigabit to 100 Gigabit WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business operations transition to the cloud and remote work becomes increasingly common, the demand for robust Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth has surged. Fortunately, providers offer excellent solutions for establishing high-bandwidth connections between locations and to the internet.
Fiber Optic Ethernet WAN
Fiber optic connectivity has become the leading choice for business bandwidth. Businesses still relying on older technologies like T1 lines, ISDN PRI, or DS3 bandwidth may be facing limitations and nearing obsolescence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Obsolete?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you been relying on a T1 line for a long time? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable, given their long history. When the Internet was new, a T1 line provided businesses with a dependable, high-bandwidth connection that made dial-up modems seem incredibly slow. These days, similar bandwidth options are available at comparable prices, making those old T1 lines appear slow in comparison. So, are T1 lines still a viable business solution, or are they outdated?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>