<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Detector Arm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/detector-arm/</link><description>Recent content in Detector Arm on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/detector-arm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Service Manual Adjustments &amp; Preparing for Use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</guid><description>In the previous post, I finished cleaning and deoxidizing the keypad and RPM panel. The keypad is now responsive, but the cueing up and down button is overly sensitive and needs further attention.
The RPM panel re-installation was put on hold because the plastic mounting fixtures were cracked, a common issue with Beogram 4002 turntables. I was fortunate that the cracks weren&amp;rsquo;t severe and the fixtures were still usable. To repair them, I used acrylic repair fluid while pressing the pieces together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Finishing Up The Tangential Arm Position Sensor &amp; The Fixed Arm Platter Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</guid><description>I was pleased to discover that Beolover successfully refurbished the platter motor for my Beogram 4002. During the packing process for the motor&amp;rsquo;s return, I took the opportunity to calibrate the voltage for two newly installed sensor lamps within the Beogram.
The recently added LED replacement light for the tangential arm position sensor was insufficiently bright. While it functioned, even at maximum output (with the 1R88, 25K ohm trimmer at its highest setting), the voltage measured at the 1TR17 base only reached 0.</description></item></channel></rss>