<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VoIP Telephone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voip-telephone/</link><description>Recent content in VoIP Telephone on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voip-telephone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Long Haul Voice, Video and Data via MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses need to transmit voice, video, and data across long distances, whether between cities, across the country, or even internationally. While both the internet and dedicated private lines are viable options, there&amp;rsquo;s another solution you might not be familiar with: MPLS networks. This article will explore why MPLS is a strong option for long-distance data transport and how to decide which solution best suits your needs.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Communications Services To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>A significant shift from traditional phone systems to cloud-based communication is happening right now. XO Communications, a leader in this field, predicts 60% of companies will move almost a third of their voice communications to the cloud in the coming years.
For a free consultation and quotes tailored to your company&amp;rsquo;s communication needs, our partners at Telarus offer fast and reliable service from expert product specialists. Contact them at http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/.</description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity.</description></item><item><title>Filling Coverage Gaps With High Quality Business Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses in big cities have it easy when it comes to internet and phone service. There are so many options! But what if your business isn&amp;rsquo;t in a big city? What if you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with slow internet and outdated phone lines? You&amp;rsquo;re not out of luck!
Look Up for Better Options
Stop looking for internet and phone service on the ground. Look up! Satellite service is a great option for businesses that need fast, reliable service.</description></item><item><title>Maxed Out On Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your business pushing the limits of its WAN bandwidth? Are you facing network congestion during peak hours? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are solutions to improve your situation.
Start by evaluating your network efficiency. Are you using quality of service management, or are you simply hoping for the best? Prioritizing voice packets can resolve issues with VoIP calls without impacting other processes.
Consider the timing of bandwidth-heavy tasks. Running backups to remote sites during peak hours can hinder employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?</description></item><item><title>The Value of Low Latency Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-value-of-low-latency-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 20:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-value-of-low-latency-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow network speeds, particularly when connecting to the internet or other company sites, could point to a latency problem. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how businesses and organizations can achieve faster network connections:
For businesses that rely on high-speed network performance, like high-frequency financial trading, minimizing latency is crucial. Some companies even choose to be in the same building as stock exchanges to be just feet away from servers.
While most applications aren&amp;rsquo;t that demanding, factors like bandwidth, latency, packet loss, and jitter still matter.</description></item><item><title>Triple Play Helps Wireline Fight Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-helps-wireline-fight-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-helps-wireline-fight-satellite/</guid><description>The market for television services is completely saturated. While getting TV used to be simple, viewers now have a wide range of options, including over-the-air, cable, satellite, telco (AT&amp;amp;T), and fiber optic (Verizon).
The recent discontinuation of analog television transmissions was met with indifference by most, except for a small number of consumers who didn&amp;rsquo;t buy a converter or new digital TV. Now, these individuals are rushing to find converter boxes or signing up with cable or satellite providers like DirecTV or Dish Network.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item></channel></rss>