<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Skill on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skill/</link><description>Recent content in Skill on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:25:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CEOs are of the opinion that soft skills will be more important than hard skills in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/</guid><description>Asian CEOs view soft skills as more vital than hard skills for future business success, according to a report by The Economist Corporate Network (ECN), an advisory service for senior executives. The report highlights communication, structural support for skill development, and CEO time constraints as key challenges.
The ECN&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Skills 4.0: How CEOs Shape the Future of Work in Asia&amp;rdquo; report, based on a survey of over 500 clients, reveals that most CEOs acknowledge the impact of major global trends (&amp;ldquo;megatrends&amp;rdquo;) on their companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-are-of-the-opinion-that-soft-skills-will-be-more-important-than-hard-skills-in-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding good people is still a challenge, according to ManpowerGroup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</guid><description>Source: ManpowerGroup infographic.
Around the world, the most difficult positions to fill are in skilled trades (particularly chefs, bakers, butchers, mechanics, and electricians), sales, engineering (mechanical, electrical, and civil), technician roles, and drivers (especially heavy vehicle operators), according to workforce experts ManpowerGroup.
The situation in Singapore is somewhat different. While engineers are among the top five hardest roles to fill, as elsewhere, the other four are accounting and finance professionals, sales representatives, secretaries (including receptionists and administrative assistants), and marketing, public relations, and communications specialists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The skills you possess will be valuable in securing future employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Legrand illustrates how LinkedIn is innovating by connecting existing skills with the needs of emerging jobs.
Olivier Legrand, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at LinkedIn, suggests that many individuals already possess some qualifications for in-demand jobs without realizing it.
During his keynote, &amp;ldquo;Job titles are out, skill sets are in,&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Computer Society&amp;rsquo;s Tech3 Forum, Legrand stated that LinkedIn aims to connect its members not only with employers but also with suitable companies, relevant jobs, and essential skills for future career prospects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is dedicated to developing talent in the infocomm sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, addressed the rising demand for infocomm professionals in the country. This surge is attributed to the growth of the ICT sector and Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation initiatives. Dr. Yaacob emphasized the need to fill 30,000 infocomm positions by 2020.
He acknowledged the challenge of meeting this demand solely with local talent, stating that while relying on non-Singaporeans might be necessary, the focus should be on equipping Singaporeans with highly competitive skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IBM has raised concerns about the skills gap in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</guid><description>Source: IBM. Cover for the Upskilling India report.
IBM has released a study conducted by the IBM Institute for Business Value (IBV), in partnership with the Economist Intelligence Unit. This study assesses India&amp;rsquo;s increasing skills gap and offers suggestions to address the issue.
The study surveyed Indian executives, and most believe that the Indian workforce&amp;rsquo;s skills are on par with or better than those of other nations. However, only 40% reported that new employees possess the necessary skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>