<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Debit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/debit/</link><description>Recent content in Debit on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:56:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/debit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kuwait Finance House introduces Visa Infinite debit card for exclusive VIP clients</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced a new debit card, Visa Infinite, exclusively for its ‘Priority’ private banking customers.
Each customer is assigned a personal relationship manager who oversees the issuance of the new card and serves as their primary point of contact for all KFH services. According to Private Banking General Manager, Matthew Welch, the card offers customers unique benefits and support services.
These benefits include access to over 500 airport lounges globally, special offers and priority reservations at a wide range of upscale restaurants, and a 24/7 international concierge service for reservations, ticket bookings, car rentals, and taxi arrangements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-finance-house-introduces-visa-infinite-debit-card-for-exclusive-vip-clients/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The goal of the BTSE Debit Card is to provide worldwide access to funds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</guid><description>Source: BTSE. The BTSE Debit Card.
There&amp;rsquo;s a new player in the crypto debit card arena. Accepted at over 53 million MasterCard merchants and compatible with over a million ATMs globally, the BTSE Debit Card sets itself apart by allowing users to fund it with various fiat and cryptocurrencies without needing a traditional bank account.
BTSE, a fintech company focused on financial freedom, designed this card to give users more control over their money...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Al Rajhi's initiative to promote card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</guid><description>Al Rajhi Bank has introduced its &amp;ldquo;House, Car and Salary&amp;rdquo; campaign, offering over SR4 million in prizes to encourage the use of its Mada and credit cards within Saudi Arabia and internationally.
The grand prize, exclusively for Saudi citizens, includes a house, a BMW 7 Series car, and a year of monthly SR20,000 payments. Four additional winners will receive a BMW 7 Series car each, while seven others will get a year of monthly SR20,000 payments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UOB creates profiles of the contemporary Singaporean woman and customizes card privileges to suit her needs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 08:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first profiles of the modern Singaporean woman, categorized by their behaviors and spending habits. The UOB Leading Ladies report identifies these women as digital natives, young professionals, and cosmopolitan leaders.
Jacquelyn Tan, UOB&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director and Regional Head of Cards and Payments, highlighted the report&amp;rsquo;s focus on the entrepreneurial spirit and spending trends of contemporary Singaporean women. She emphasized the significant contribution of women to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s GDP, exceeding 40%, and their dedication to both work and family...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>