<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Insurance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insurance/</link><description>Recent content in Insurance on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discover financial products in Malaysia with GoBear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</guid><description>GoBear, a metasearch engine that simplifies financial product comparison, has officially launched in Malaysia. The platform offers unbiased, side-by-side comparisons of products like travel insurance and credit cards, with over 1,000 options currently listed and more to come.
Iskandar Ezzahuddin, GoBear&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, emphasized the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: &amp;ldquo;GoBear stems from the understanding that modern consumers demand convenient access to service information and straightforward product comparisons before making financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and Great Eastern have launched a new home and contents insurance offering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-great-eastern-have-launched-a-new-home-and-contents-insurance-offering/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 03:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-great-eastern-have-launched-a-new-home-and-contents-insurance-offering/</guid><description>Singtel and Great Eastern have partnered to introduce Singtel Home Protect Flexi, a home and contents insurance plan that offers flexibility and convenience. The plan is directly connected to a customer&amp;rsquo;s Singtel broadband subscription, automatically updating with their new address if they move. This feature ensures continuous coverage without any gaps or the need for manual updates. The plan operates on a no-contract basis, allowing customers to cancel at their convenience.</description></item><item><title>ProtectSecure Prime life plan is now available from AmMetLife Insurance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 08:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protectsecure-prime-life-plan-is-now-available-from-ammetlife-insurance/</guid><description>AmMetLife Insurance has introduced ProtectSecure Prime, a whole life insurance plan with guaranteed premiums starting as low as RM150 each month. The plan offers three premium payment term choices: 10 years, 20 years, or until age 60. After the chosen payment period, no further payments are needed to maintain the policy.
Source: AmMetLife website.
Furthermore, policyholders will receive an automatic 10% increase in their initial sum assured annually from the end of the first policy year until the end of the tenth year.</description></item><item><title>UK Motor Insurance Law in the EU: Road Accidents and Off-Road Responsibilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</guid><description>James Marson (Reader in Law, Sheffield Hallam University), Katy Ferris (Assistant Professor in Business Law, Nottingham University Business School) and Neil Fletcher (Senior Lecturer, Sheffield Hallam University)
Introduction
While the UK has seen notable legal victories concerning member state liability for breaches of EU law, the ability to hold the state accountable for individual losses remains limited. Establishing a breach significant enough to warrant damages is often a hurdle, except in motor vehicle insurance law.</description></item><item><title>Receive guidance, then purchase your own life insurance through NTUC Income's online platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/receive-guidance-then-purchase-your-own-life-insurance-through-ntuc-income-s-online-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/receive-guidance-then-purchase-your-own-life-insurance-through-ntuc-income-s-online-platform/</guid><description>NTUC Income recently introduced Online Life, a life insurance portal, and askSage, a digital adviser specifically for life insurance.
Peter Tay, COO of Income and head of the company&amp;rsquo;s Digital Transformation Office, highlighted the significance of these platforms. He emphasized that this is the first time consumers have access to digital tools that allow them to manage their life insurance needs entirely online. This encompasses everything from research and financial analysis to product selection, comparison, and purchase.</description></item><item><title>Customers of AIA Singapore receive complimentary coverage for Covid-19</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-aia-singapore-receive-complimentary-coverage-for-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-aia-singapore-receive-complimentary-coverage-for-covid-19/</guid><description>AIA Singapore is offering complimentary COVID-19 coverage to eligible customers. This additional coverage is automatic and requires no action from the customer.
The company stated that this initiative underscores their commitment to supporting the health and well-being of their customers, particularly during challenging times.
Customers eligible for this benefit will receive it automatically. The coverage will remain active until December 31, 2020, or 30 days after the DORSCON level returns to green, whichever comes first.</description></item><item><title>Online travel insurance offer now available from AIG Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</guid><description>AIG Singapore has introduced a new digital travel insurance product, Travel Guard Direct, designed to improve customer experience from purchase to claim. This innovative product uses data to provide travelers with valuable insights about their destinations.
Travel Guard Direct is the first of its kind in Singapore, offering real-time claims information for popular destinations in Asia Pacific, the US, and the UK. This allows customers to make more informed decisions about their coverage by understanding the risks associated with their travel destinations.</description></item><item><title>Customers who are retrenched will have their bills waived by Singtel Bill Protect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-are-retrenched-will-have-their-bills-waived-by-singtel-bill-protect/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-are-retrenched-will-have-their-bills-waived-by-singtel-bill-protect/</guid><description>Singtel and Etiqa Insurance Singapore have teamed up to introduce Singtel Bill Protect, a free insurance plan designed to help Singaporeans navigate tough economic times and maintain their connectivity even if they encounter financial difficulties. This launch comes as retrenchments in Singapore have increased for three consecutive quarters, according to the Ministry of Manpower&amp;rsquo;s latest labor market reports.
In response to growing economic uncertainty and job insecurity, the Bill Protect plan aims to support Singtel customers experiencing financial strain due to job loss by providing waivers on their upcoming Singtel mobile and fixed broadband bills.</description></item><item><title>Insurance is now available through Singtel's Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash app is launching Dash EasyEarn, a new financial product offering a 2% annual return. This insurance savings plan is available exclusively through the Dash app and is backed by Etiqa Insurance.
Source: Singtel. Dash EasyEarn is a fully digital insurance product, allowing users to manage their plans entirely through the Singtel Dash app.
This innovative addition to the Dash app, which already provides various services like payments and mobile top-ups, aims to make saving simple and accessible.</description></item></channel></rss>