<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SSAE 16 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ssae-16/</link><description>Recent content in SSAE 16 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 20:55:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ssae-16/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scalable Cloud Servers Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 20:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</guid><description>Considering a move to cloud servers but feeling apprehensive about the cost and complexity? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses desire the flexibility and cost-effectiveness of cloud computing without needing excessive processing power.
Scalable cloud servers are a great option for businesses of all sizes, offering pay-as-you-go pricing and easy scalability. Before committing to a major provider, explore options specifically designed for small to medium-sized businesses. These services often provide per-second billing, eliminating wasted expenses, along with free setup and no contractual obligations.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item></channel></rss>