<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hp/</link><description>Recent content in HP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces new storage solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Mid-size businesses need to adapt quickly, but they often don&amp;rsquo;t have the budget for the advanced storage solutions used by larger companies. HP is addressing this issue by offering affordable ways to enhance application performance. This includes a budget-friendly solid-state drive (SSD) read-caching solution from a leading provider, featuring SSD choices for HP MSA Storage.1
For businesses considering hybrid flash storage, HP is introducing a new HP StoreVirtual Storage system. This system boasts 12 times the speed of a similarly priced spinning media array...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eko Nugroho is currently showcasing his street art exhibition through digital prints produced by HP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</guid><description>This image, from HP Inc., showcases embroidered artwork by Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho. It features his signature masked characters and intricate designs reminiscent of Japanese woodcuts.
HP Inc is the Innovation Sponsor for the &amp;ldquo;Art from the Streets&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the ArtScience Museum in Singapore. For the exhibition, HP created nine large-scale prints of significant artworks. They are also using their digital printing technology to showcase the work of Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho in fresh and unexpected ways, demonstrating that street art can be displayed anywhere and on any medium...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP's ElitePOS is specifically designed for the retail industry 2.0</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:36:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</guid><description>HP Inc. is aiming to revolutionize the retail sector with its new HP ElitePOS system, a flexible all-in-one point-of-sale (POS) solution. The company&amp;rsquo;s goal is to enhance the in-store experience by providing a balanced technological approach that boosts sales and simplifies operations.
Research from HP highlights that 69% of customers are more inclined to make purchases in physical stores if they have access to digital self-service resources, such as interactive displays and kiosks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HP 2 in 1 printer is perfect for home offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new PC and printer designed for home offices.
The HP Pavilion x2, available in Singapore starting in October from S$499, offers a stylish and practical solution. This versatile device functions as a 10-inch Windows tablet and easily transforms into a fully functional laptop. It features a detachable magnetic keyboard cover that doubles as both a screen protector and a multi-position stand. Equipped with an Intel Atom processor, the Pavilion x2 boasts front-facing speakers with DTS sound and a battery life of up to 11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has released the HP Helion OpenStack Community Edition for free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 09:24:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</guid><description>As part of its new HP Helion portfolio, HP is launching cloud products and services. These include:
HP Helion OpenStack Community Edition: This commercially available OpenStack product line is delivered, tested, and supported by HP. This free edition, available now, is perfect for proofs of concept, pilot projects, and basic production workloads. HP&amp;rsquo;s OpenStack Technology Indemnification Program: This safeguards eligible customers who use HP Helion OpenStack code from claims of patent, copyright, and trade secret infringement by third parties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-the-hp-helion-openstack-community-edition-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP creates servers specifically for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced new ProLiant Gen9 Tower servers to its Compute portfolio. These servers are designed to give small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) a cost-effective solution with a good mix of performance, efficiency, and manageability.
These servers are designed to handle a variety of general-purpose workloads and critical applications, including IT infrastructure, collaboration, web, and business applications. This support is intended to meet both current and future business needs.
“Small businesses must not only address immediate business challenges but also establish a foundation for rapid business expansion,” stated Peter Schrady, VP and GM of Rack and Tower Servers at HP...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP's Elite business PCs excel in performance, productivity, and security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 22:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</guid><description>HP has introduced its latest Elite business PCs, including the exceptionally thin and light HP EliteBook 705 series, an all-in-one (AiO) model, and a refreshed desktop lineup featuring the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest business-class desktop.
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the demand for high-end Elite notebook innovation to be extended to a wider range of employees and devices. HP&amp;rsquo;s response is the Elite 705 and 800 Series PCs, which bring sleek design, enhanced collaboration features, and robust security to mainstream business devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces the thinnest laptop in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</guid><description>Every Spectre accessory has been designed to provide a luxurious experience.
The CNC machined aluminum body is as sleek as an AAA battery at a mere 10.4mm. Enjoy exceptional performance with Intel Core i5 and i7 processors. Immerse yourself in the vibrant visuals of a full HD 13.3&amp;quot; edge-to-edge display complemented by Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen sound. HP claims to have developed the slimmest laptop globally, meticulously refining every detail to provide an unmatched user experience and peak performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Stream notebooks include a complimentary one-year subscription to Office 365 and OneDrive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new notebook PCs to its HP Stream line of lightweight, cloud-based Windows devices. HP emphasizes affordability, offering these thin and light notebooks at a lower price point than typically seen.
Source: HP. The HP Stream notebooks come in horizon blue and orchid magenta.
“Consumers today want mobile devices that reflect their style and empower them to work and play from anywhere,” says Serena Yong, General Manager for Printing &amp;amp; Personal Systems at HP Singapore and Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-stream-notebooks-include-a-complimentary-one-year-subscription-to-office-365-and-onedrive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP updates Pavilion features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pavilion PCs, including convertibles and notebooks, designed to be stylish and powerful. The company aims to provide customers with a range of options to suit their needs and budgets.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that HP understands customers&amp;rsquo; diverse needs, with some prioritizing portability and others seeking performance. The redesigned Pavilion PCs cater to both, offering affordability and style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LaserJet Enterprise 600 Series from HP offers increased security and versatility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 11:06:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</guid><description>Source: HP. The HP Color LaserJet Managed E87660 MFP.
HP has introduced the HP LaserJet Enterprise 600 Series, a line of printers designed to enhance security and productivity.
These multifunction printers (MFPs) offer a combination of strong performance, energy efficiency, and the ability to produce professional-quality documents. They are built with network security in mind, offering protection against cyberattacks. Additionally, the devices incorporate HP JetIntelligence cartridge technology, which utilizes advancements in toner chemistry to further enhance print quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Office of the Future at HP is filled with cutting-edge innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-of-the-future-at-hp-is-filled-with-cutting-edge-innovation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 12:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-of-the-future-at-hp-is-filled-with-cutting-edge-innovation/</guid><description>HP has introduced new products and services designed to help businesses create a modern and secure &amp;ldquo;Office of the Future.&amp;rdquo; This initiative focuses on empowering employees with technology that boosts productivity and creativity, while also offering flexibility in how and where they work.
This shift is driven by evolving workforce demographics, as over 70% of Asian employees already work remotely and Millennials and Gen Z, who prioritize workplace flexibility, are becoming the majority...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-of-the-future-at-hp-is-filled-with-cutting-edge-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-of-the-future-at-hp-is-filled-with-cutting-edge-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The second season of The Wolf, produced by HP Studios, demonstrates the capabilities of hackers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 22:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</guid><description>Source: HP eDM. Christian Slater stars in The Wolf: The Hunt Continues.
The second season of The Wolf, starring Christian Slater, is out now from HP Studios. This film follows a hacker&amp;rsquo;s exploitation of the healthcare system, revealing how vulnerable endpoints like printers can be compromised, leading to critical data loss.
HP claims that their printers and PCs offer the highest level of security globally.
Want to learn more?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has improved MSA Storage for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP is introducing new features for its MSA Storage solutions to benefit startups, SMBs, and customers with small sites. These enhancements aim to increase competitiveness.
The improved MSA 2040 Storage offers significantly faster application performance, up to 45% faster, without extra costs through firmware updates. Additionally, new MSA 2040 bundles provide cost savings of up to 45% for hybrid flash deployments. Furthermore, the introduction of Serial Attached SCSI (SAS) connectivity to the MSA 1040 Storage positions it as the most budget-friendly shared storage option from a major vendor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For the initial six months, HP Touchpoint Manager is being offered at a discounted rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Touchpoint Manager, a cloud-based IT management solution specifically designed for small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs).
Managing IT systems has become more challenging due to the increasing variety of devices and operating systems used in business, from company-provided equipment to personal devices.
HP Touchpoint Manager simplifies IT management for SMBs, helping them ensure device functionality, data security, and IT staff effectiveness. Its adaptability allows it to manage a wide array of devices and operating systems, including iOS, Android, and Windows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has launched a new mobile broadband service called DataPass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</guid><description>HP has introduced new technology designed for business travelers in the Asia Pacific region called HP DataPass.
&amp;ldquo;In today&amp;rsquo;s constantly connected, fast-moving, and virtual business world, new opportunities are emerging for businesses and individuals,&amp;rdquo; said Nick Lazaridis, Senior VP, Printing and Personal Systems, and Managing Director of HP Asia Pacific and Japan. &amp;ldquo;At HP, our focus is on developing innovations that provide the best possible customer experience while creating opportunities for our customers to transition to the New Style of IT...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-launched-a-new-mobile-broadband-service-called-datapass/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has released a variety of mobile solutions to enhance business productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</guid><description>HP has introduced a suite of commercial mobility solutions aimed at boosting workplace productivity. The offerings include eight new mobile devices and accessories designed to simplify business processes.
Anneliese Olson, HP Asia-Pacific and Japan VP and GM of Personal Computing, highlighted how these products address evolving workplace dynamics, workforce trends, and work styles, ultimately reshaping workflows.
HP has developed a comprehensive mobility solution catering to diverse businesses, including those in specialized sectors like education, field service, healthcare, public safety, and retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces two phablets in the Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 05:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new mobile devices to their collection: the 6-inch HP Slate6 VoiceTab and the 7-inch HP Slate7 VoiceTab. These &amp;ldquo;voice tablets&amp;rdquo; will be released in India this February*.
These devices combine the functions of a phone and a tablet into one portable design. “The voice tablet market is growing because consumers want to combine their phones and tablets into one device,” said Ron Coughlin, Senior VP of HP&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Personal Systems Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Helion offers enterprise-level cloud services tailored for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Helion Managed Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Lean, a service designed to support cloud-based applications for medium and large businesses. This service is suitable for purposes like application development and testing, as well as collaborative work environments.
This managed infrastructure solution allows smaller companies to adopt cloud technology swiftly and scale their usage as needed, all at a lower price point than previous HP Helion managed services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing financial consequences of cybercrime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</guid><description>Source: HP infographic.
HP recently released the findings of their sixth annual study, conducted in partnership with the Ponemon Institute, exploring the financial effects of cyberattacks on both public and private sectors.
The study shows a substantial rise in the total cost of cybercrime, indicating that smaller companies bear a proportionally larger cost than larger ones.
The 2015 Cost of Cyber Crime Study, carried out by the Ponemon Institute and supported by HP Enterprise Security, calculates the yearly cost of cybercrime for businesses across seven countries: the US, UK, Japan, Germany, Australia, Brazil, and Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-financial-consequences-of-cybercrime/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces a limited edition notebook featuring a Star Wars theme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</guid><description>In anticipation of the release of Star Wars: &amp;ldquo;The Force Awakens,&amp;rdquo; HP has launched a special edition notebook.
“As the only PC vendor collaborating with Disney and Lucasfilm, HP is providing an incredible Star Wars experience by creating a truly unique notebook,&amp;quot; shared Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore. &amp;ldquo;This collaboration granted us access to Lucasfilm’s media archives, which we used to create customizable screen savers, desktop backgrounds, and sound profiles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP believes that the digital printing revolution has the potential to make businesses even more agile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</guid><description>Source: HP. High-impact retail graphics, floor covering and corrugated display applications printed using HP Latex and Scitex Digital printing technologies at the new HP Graphics Solutions Centre of Excellence in Singapore.
The way businesses approach printing is being transformed by commercial digital printing presses. Unlike traditional offset printing, which requires large quantities for cost-effectiveness, digital printers can economically personalize any volume of items, from a single piece to thousands, across diverse materials...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>