<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manila on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/manila/</link><description>Recent content in Manila on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 23:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/manila/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cebu Pacific has added Fukuoka to its list of destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</guid><description>Cebu Pacific Air (CEB) initiated flights between Manila and Fukuoka on December 17th, adding a third weekly service to their existing routes in Japan. This marks their fourth destination in Japan, including direct flights from Manila to Osaka, Tokyo (Narita), and Nagoya, as well as flights from Cebu to Tokyo (Narita).
Japan is a top destination for travelers from the Philippines. Data from the Japan National Tourism Organization indicates a 44% increase in Filipino arrivals, reaching over 211,000 between January and October 2015, compared to the same period the previous year.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is increasing the number of weekly flights between Abu Dhabi and Manila</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2016, Etihad Airways will increase its Abu Dhabi to Manila route from 14 to 17 roundtrip flights per week. This provides convenient connections from Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s hub to popular destinations for Philippine travelers, including Bahrain, Kuwait, Dammam, Doha, Jeddah, and Riyadh.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, highlighted the Abu Dhabi-Manila route&amp;rsquo;s high demand and limited capacity in recent years. The added flights will increase capacity by nearly 2,500 seats weekly, improving travel options between the UAE and the Philippines.</description></item></channel></rss>