<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Catering on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/catering/</link><description>Recent content in Catering on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:35:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/catering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rasel offers artisanal catering services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</guid><description>Rasel Catering Singapore, a top-tier halal catering service, has enhanced its offerings to become a leader in the industry.
Alan Tan, Co-Founder and Managing Director of Rasel Catering Singapore, highlighted the company’s focus on meeting the evolving needs of a global clientele. He stated, “Rasel caters to international events and weddings, recognizing the sophisticated tastes of today’s customers and their demand for high-quality halal food. Our service goes beyond just the food itself—we leverage our expertise to elevate the entire experience for our customers.</description></item><item><title>LAVISH is bringing a new standard of high-end catering to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</guid><description>The renowned catering company, LAVISH, celebrated its 18th anniversary with a gala in late January. The event served as a platform for the brand&amp;rsquo;s revitalization and showcased their forward-thinking approach to catering, blending culinary arts with technology and science. LAVISH is well-regarded for its expertise in catering a variety of events, from large-scale conferences and corporate gatherings to intimate private dinners and celebratory functions.
Source: LAVISH. The gala dinner was held</description></item></channel></rss>