<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Phones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-phones/</link><description>Recent content in IP Phones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-phones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted VoIP Solutions Include New Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</guid><description>Cloud services are changing how we think about technology. Just like server racks are moving to the cloud, so are office phone systems. Traditional PBX systems are being replaced by cloud-hosted solutions. But this transition begs the question: what happens to the physical phone lines?
Similar to connecting data servers off-site, a connection called a SIP Trunk links your on-premise network to the hosted PBX. While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to use existing analog phones with adapters, this approach misses out on the advanced features of Voice over IP (VoIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Voice Goes Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world: companies are ditching their traditional PBX phone systems for cloud-based communication solutions like hosted PBX or hosted VoIP. This transition also incorporates mobile devices.
For example, Megapath&amp;rsquo;s Hosted Voice Mobile allows you to make and receive calls using a single number across multiple devices – desk phone, computer, and smartphone. Having one consistent number simplifies communication and avoids confusing clients with a business card full of numbers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefit From The Great CAPEX to OPEX Migration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world, moving away from traditional capital expenditures (CAPEX) towards operational expenses (OPEX). This change, although seemingly subtle, represents a fundamental shift with far-reaching implications for businesses of all sizes.
Businesses incur both capital and operational expenses. Operational expenses are the costs of daily operations, like utilities, supplies, and salaries. Capital expenses, however, are long-term investments, such as purchasing buildings or major equipment. An example of this is an in-house PBX telephone system, which might soon be replaced by an operational expense alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is VoIP For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of talk about the benefits of switching from traditional phone services to VoIP, and for good reason. Businesses can gain a lot from enterprise VoIP solutions. However, there are potential downsides to watch out for to ensure a smooth transition. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what VoIP is and how it compares to your current phone service.
One thing that often causes confusion about VoIP is the name itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>