<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dropbox on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dropbox/</link><description>Recent content in Dropbox on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:28:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dropbox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dropbox is revamping its platform to help users become even more productive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-is-revamping-its-platform-to-help-users-become-even-more-productive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-is-revamping-its-platform-to-help-users-become-even-more-productive/</guid><description>Dropbox, a leading platform for collaboration, has introduced a redesigned workspace. This updated workspace, accessible through the Dropbox desktop app, website, and mobile app, acts as a central hub for files, tools, and teams. A new desktop app, currently available in early access, provides a streamlined entry point to this unified workspace.
“Work is becoming increasingly fragmented—our files are spread across various devices and platforms, and we&amp;rsquo;re using multiple apps that don&amp;rsquo;t communicate with each other, making it challenging for teams to keep up,” said Drew Houston, CEO of Dropbox...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-is-revamping-its-platform-to-help-users-become-even-more-productive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-is-revamping-its-platform-to-help-users-become-even-more-productive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox and Microsoft collaborating more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Dropbox and Microsoft are joining forces to make it easier for their users to work together. This collaboration will allow users to seamlessly work with Dropbox and Microsoft Office on their phones, tablets, and computers. Given that over 1.2 billion people use Microsoft Office and 35 billion Office files are stored in Dropbox, this partnership has the potential to benefit a lot of users.
This integration will enable users to edit their Dropbox documents directly in the relevant Office application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox unveils new tools to enhance productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</guid><description>Source: Dropbox website.
Dropbox aims to simplify content creation, sharing, and teamwork through its new features.
Users can now create new Microsoft Office files, upload photos, or scan documents directly through the Dropbox iPhone app using the plus button.
A Dropbox badge shows who is currently working on the same Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, or Excel files, preventing work duplication or loss. Microsoft co-authoring enables real-time collaboration on Microsoft Office files online, eliminating email exchanges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>