<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>INSEAD on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insead/</link><description>Recent content in INSEAD on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stars at INSEAD drive innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</guid><description>New research from INSEAD suggests that good mentors are incredibly valuable.
The study, titled &amp;ldquo;Where Do Stars Come From? The Role of Star vs. Nonstar Collaborators in Creative Settings,&amp;rdquo; was published in Organization Science. The authors, Manuel Sosa, Jürgen Mihm, and Haibo Liu, examined the skills needed to effectively combine different elements for maximum creativity and innovation, leading to organizational success.
Their research specifically focused on a new aspect of collaborative creativity: the impact of collaborating with high-achievers (&amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo;) versus average performers (&amp;ldquo;non-stars&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Skills and challenges for global citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</guid><description>A new book by an INSEAD professor explores the unique skills and challenges faced by &amp;ldquo;citizens of the world&amp;rdquo; – individuals who hold multiple passports or live outside their home country. These individuals often come from diverse backgrounds, navigating multiple cultures and languages, which has driven their success. Author Linda Brimm, an Emeritus Professor of Organisational Behaviour at INSEAD, emphasizes the importance of a global mindset in international business and problem-solving, stating that these individuals offer valuable insights for addressing today&amp;rsquo;s complex challenges.</description></item><item><title>A study conducted by INSEAD has discovered that when shareholders vote on CEO accountability, it leads to higher company returns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:02:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</guid><description>A new study titled &amp;ldquo;Say Pays! Shareholder Voice and Firm Performance,&amp;rdquo; published in the Review of Finance, suggests that shareholder votes do improve CEO accountability and reduce unnecessary spending within corporations. The study&amp;rsquo;s author, Maria Guadalupe, an Associate Professor at INSEAD, found that previous research on the impact of &amp;ldquo;say-on-pay&amp;rdquo; policies was inconclusive, possibly due to focusing on periods after say-on-pay became law.
Guadalupe&amp;rsquo;s research examined 250 instances where shareholders of S&amp;amp;P 1500 companies proposed to adopt say-on-pay policies between 2006 and 2010, before such votes were mandatory.</description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations.</description></item></channel></rss>