<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WiMAX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wimax/</link><description>Recent content in WiMAX on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wimax/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit WiFi For Video Streaming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wifi-for-video-streaming/</guid><description>WiFi has become the standard wireless connection due to its widespread availability, outpacing technologies like Bluetooth and WiMax. While cellular data is useful in the absence of WiFi, its limited bandwidth and potential for overage charges make it a secondary choice. In fact, data shows that most tablet users don&amp;rsquo;t even utilize their device&amp;rsquo;s cellular capabilities. WiFi&amp;rsquo;s strength is evident in its ability to not only replace cellular broadband but also wired connections.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>The Fiber Gold Rush Is On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</guid><description>The transition from copper wires to fiber optic strands has been recognized as a necessity for some time. This shift is driven by the growing need for bandwidth as technology progresses. Over the past few decades, various sectors, including internet service providers, cable companies, healthcare facilities, and large enterprises, have progressively adopted fiber optic connections. Services like Metro Ethernet have made this transition feasible even for mid-sized businesses. Now, small businesses and individual consumers are poised to benefit from this technology.</description></item><item><title>What is 4G and Why Do You Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re constantly bombarded with ads for 3G phones and wireless aircards, and now 4G is emerging. But what does this new technology mean and why should you care?
2G, 3G, 4G—these &amp;ldquo;Gs&amp;rdquo; represent different generations of wireless broadband. This technology evolves so rapidly that various generations often coexist in the same region. This is intentional. If you&amp;rsquo;re in an area with weak 3G coverage, your device automatically connects to slower 2.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs.</description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part IV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</guid><description>The most desirable wireless frequencies will soon be completely allocated. These prime frequencies, ranging from a few hundred to a few thousand MHz, offer high bandwidth, strong building penetration, and accommodate small antennas. The problem is that the number of these channels is finite. Similar to real estate, once the best spots are taken, expansion continues into less ideal areas.
Finding more bandwidth means moving up or down the electromagnetic spectrum, which presents challenges.</description></item><item><title>Speedier Network For The iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</guid><description>While the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s popularity is a boon for AT&amp;amp;T, which holds the exclusive contract, the device&amp;rsquo;s data demands present a significant hurdle.
Historically, cellular towers primarily handled voice calls, with data as a secondary function. Early data speeds were adequate for text-based services, but the advent of camera phones, web browsers, and video streaming dramatically increased bandwidth requirements. Today&amp;rsquo;s users demand home and work-level speeds, typically between 3 to 10 Mbps, far exceeding the capabilities of older networks.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Plans With Aircards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</guid><description>Wireless modem aircards liberate you from the constraints of WiFi hotspots, transforming your laptop into a truly mobile computer. But how do they work, and what kind of service plans are necessary?
Essentially, an aircard functions as a specialized two-way radio, transmitting and receiving digital computer data instead of voice calls.
While they might resemble them, aircards don&amp;rsquo;t operate on cell phone networks. Currently, the majority adhere to either EVDO (Sprint and Verizon Wireless) or EDGE and HSPA (AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile) standards for cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>What’s the Difference Between WiMAX and WiFi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-difference-between-wimax-and-wifi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 11:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-difference-between-wimax-and-wifi/</guid><description>WiMAX and WiFi sound alike, but are they related? Think of WiMAX as a city-wide hotspot, similar to 3G cellular broadband. It&amp;rsquo;s more than just a powerful WiFi; it&amp;rsquo;s a broadband service covering a much larger area, even inside buildings and vehicles. Watch this video for a closer look at WiMAX.
WiMAX is a robust wireless standard gaining global traction for providing wireless broadband access to stationary and mobile devices. In numerous US cities, WiMAX utilizes old analog TV channels auctioned off recently.</description></item><item><title>HTC ThunderBolt Screams On LTE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:58:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</guid><description>The HTC ThunderBolt, a smartphone with lightning-fast speed, embodies the next generation of mobile connectivity. It operates on Verizon&amp;rsquo;s LTE network with exceptional performance.
Not long ago, having a smartphone with cutting-edge 3G broadband was a status symbol. Technology evolves rapidly, and the speed that impressed us a few years ago seems archaic compared to today&amp;rsquo;s standards.
While 3G seemed remarkably fast at the time, its approximate speed of 1 Mbps pales in comparison to 4G&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Will WiMAX Become WiMedium?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</guid><description>WiMAX, a wireless broadband standard, was envisioned as the key to 4G mobile networks and roaming. However, other technologies are catching up and might become the dominant force in 4G.
WiMAX aimed to broaden WiFi&amp;rsquo;s reach from a few hundred feet to many miles, allowing mobile devices to seamlessly switch between towers for continuous connectivity, similar to cell phone networks. It promised significantly faster speeds compared to existing cellular broadband, suitable for indoor and outdoor use.</description></item><item><title>Covad Lets T1 Lines Go Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 03:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</guid><description>While T1 lines are currently the standard for dedicated internet and business phone service for small and medium businesses, their future might be wireless. Similar to how wireless technology changed phone service, it is now impacting broadband data delivery.
Covad, a national provider of T1 and related services, is at the forefront of this change. While they offer traditional wired T1 service in most areas, they&amp;rsquo;ve deployed &amp;ldquo;T1-class wireless broadband&amp;rdquo; in some major cities using pre-WiMAX technology.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part I</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-i/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 15:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-i/</guid><description>The recent collapse of the AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile merger, while seemingly a win for consumers against a potential monopoly, wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly about market control. Even if the merger succeeded, Verizon and Sprint would still offer competition. The real issue was bandwidth.
The evidence is clear: immediately after the deal failed, AT&amp;amp;T purchased $1.9 billion in spectrum from Qualcomm with FCC approval, while Verizon, after acquiring $3.6 billion worth of spectrum from Comcast and Time Warner Cable, also bought $315 million of spectrum from Cox.</description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Backhaul is Backing Things Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</guid><description>While it may seem like the world operates solely on wireless connections, especially if you rely on cell phones and mobile internet, this is only true for the link between your device and the nearest cell tower or access point. Beyond that point lies the backhaul, a crucial but often overlooked component that bridges the wireless and wired worlds. As wireless connections become faster, the limitations of traditional backhaul solutions are becoming increasingly apparent.</description></item><item><title>Tripping the LTE Fantastic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</guid><description>Although fiber optic and mobile WiMAX are getting a lot of attention, LTE could become the next major broadband technology. Could gigabit wireless communication be on the horizon?
People struggling with slow 1G connections or the first iPhone might find the idea of 1,000 Mbps speeds on their mobile devices unrealistic. It seems like there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough bandwidth from cell towers. However, emerging technologies may increase wireless bandwidth significantly.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Fixed Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fixed-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fixed-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Businesses are discovering the advantages of Metro Ethernet over traditional copper and fiber optic cables. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a lesser-known alternative: Ethernet over Fixed Wireless, offering a fast and budget-friendly way to get the bandwidth you need.
Ethernet over Fixed Wireless (EoFW) is distinct from familiar portable or mobile wireless services like WiFi, WiMAX, or LTE. While these offer broadband within a defined area for general, unencrypted use, their bandwidth is limited and shared, resulting in unpredictable connection speeds.</description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington</description></item><item><title>The Samsung Epic 4G offers Epic Performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 17:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</guid><description>Imagine a smartphone so powerful it surpasses a netbook. Picture yourself declining WiFi because your cellular connection is faster. That&amp;rsquo;s the kind of speed the Samsung Epic 4G offers with its impressive 10+ Mbps download speeds, thanks to the Sprint WiMAX 4G network. You can even share your connection as a mobile hotspot for your other devices.
Beyond speed, the Epic boasts a stunning Super AMOLED touchscreen display with near-HD quality and unmatched contrast.</description></item><item><title>XOHM, XOHM's Got The Range</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</guid><description>Sprint&amp;rsquo;s XOHM (pronounced &amp;ldquo;zome,&amp;rdquo; like &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;) wireless broadband service has launched in Baltimore, marking the start of the highly anticipated rollout of WiMAX as the next generation of high-speed internet. If Sprint successfully implements its 4G vision, WiFi hotspots could become obsolete. DSL? Cable? Why bother with wires when you can have the freedom of wireless connectivity?
This vision relies on a new wireless technology standardized for global use in both fixed and mobile applications.</description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center.</description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable.</description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2.</description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Cell phones today are capable of much more than just voice calls. The mobile networks have evolved to carry both voice and data, offering wireless broadband internet access that rivals DSL and cable connections.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t explored mobile internet recently, you might be surprised by its speed and availability. Currently, two competing systems are widely available, with two even faster networks in their early stages.
AT&amp;amp;T promotes its HSDPA and EDGE networks, notably featuring the Apple iPhone.</description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Lit Towers Improving Rural Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 16:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</guid><description>Living outside the city limits often means limited internet options. While options like 3G and satellite exist, they come with slow speeds and download caps. Businesses might have access to slightly better choices like T1 lines, but high-speed options are generally nonexistent.
Rural areas face a digital disadvantage compared to cities where gigabit and even 10 gigabit ethernet connections are readily available. Fixed wireless and cable options also offer much faster speeds in these areas.</description></item></channel></rss>