<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Status on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/status/</link><description>Recent content in Status on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/status/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vietnam receives report card from World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economy shows resilience due to strong domestic demand and export-focused manufacturing, as highlighted in the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s recent Taking Stock report. The country&amp;rsquo;s mid-term economic outlook appears positive, with GDP projected to grow by 6% in the current year.
The report, a semi-annual assessment of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economic performance, notes that economic growth decelerated to 5.9% in the first nine months of the year. This slowdown is largely attributed to a severe drought that hampered agricultural output, reduced oil production, and weakened external demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Identifying gender through Facebook posts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</guid><description>A 2013 study featured in the research journal Plos One reveals that language use in social media can indicate a user&amp;rsquo;s gender and age. The study, &amp;ldquo;Personality, Gender, and Age in the Language of Social Media: The Open-Vocabulary Approach,&amp;rdquo; found that men and women choose distinct words and phrases online. Location and age also factor into language choices.
Singapore bank DBS&amp;rsquo; lucky red packets
The study&amp;rsquo;s authors, from the University of Pennsylvania and University of Cambridge, noted that women tend to express emotions using words like &amp;ldquo;love,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;wonderful,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;excited...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The acceptance of UnionPay is expanding globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 19:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</guid><description>UnionPay has successfully expanded its network, brand, and products globally, advancing the international use of Chinese financial technology standards. UnionPay International is now present in over 50 markets involved in the Belt and Road Initiative.
Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International, emphasized their strategy of adapting to each local market, fostering personnel exchange between China and other regions, and supporting the globalization of Chinese financial standards.
In Kazakhstan, over 1.3 million UnionPay cards have been issued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>