<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jurisdiction on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jurisdiction/</link><description>Recent content in Jurisdiction on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jurisdiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies.</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Labuan is excited to welcome an increased number of financial services firms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-labuan-is-excited-to-welcome-an-increased-number-of-financial-services-firms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-labuan-is-excited-to-welcome-an-increased-number-of-financial-services-firms/</guid><description>The Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC) has continued to attract financial services companies globally in 2020. Over 800 licensed entities currently operate in this midshore jurisdiction due to a more than 50% increase in licensing application approvals in the first half of the year.
Offshore jurisdictions typically provide advantageous tax rates and other benefits that onshore jurisdictions may not. Midshore jurisdictions like Labuan IBFC provide a balance between client confidentiality, compliance with international standards and best practices, a business-friendly environment, a straightforward and attractive tax system, and a strong, modern, and internationally recognized legal framework enforced by its regulator, Labuan Financial Services Authority (Labuan FSA).</description></item></channel></rss>