<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stress on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stress/</link><description>Recent content in Stress on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Employers in Singapore are struggling with stress and mental health concerns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:23:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/employers-in-singapore-are-struggling-with-stress-and-mental-health-concerns/</guid><description>A large majority (72%) of Singaporean employers view stress and mental health as factors that negatively impact productivity, according to the APAC Benefits Strategy Study 2017 conducted by global professional services firm Aon.
The International Labour Organization has labeled stress a &amp;ldquo;global epidemic&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;silent killer,&amp;rdquo; particularly within many Asian countries experiencing rapid economic growth and adopting Western lifestyles, including Singapore, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and mainland China.
Early physical symptoms of stress can manifest as chronic back pain, fatigue, and headaches.</description></item><item><title>ANA has developed an app to assist passengers in relaxing and diverting their attention away from takeoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</guid><description>Source: App Store.
All Nippon Airways (ANA), a major Japanese airline, developed an app to alleviate stress during the most anxiety-inducing part of air travel. Based on a survey of US airline passengers revealing that takeoff causes the most anxiety (68%), ANA created &amp;ldquo;ANA Takeoff Mode.&amp;rdquo; This mobile app aims to help travelers relax and focus on something other than takeoff.
The app presents a simple puzzle accompanied by calming music.</description></item><item><title>The beauty industry acknowledges the growing demand in Asia for products that promote relaxation and stress relief</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</guid><description>A recent report by market intelligence agency Mintel reveals that the Asia-Pacific region produced one-third of all new beauty and personal care products aimed at relaxation and stress relief in the first nine months of 2018. This represents a significant increase from 2015 when the region accounted for only 26% of similar global product launches.
Sharon Kwek, Senior Innovation and Insights Analyst, Beauty and Personal Care at Mintel, addressed the in-cosmetics Asia event stating that today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, demanding world has normalized stress.</description></item></channel></rss>