<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pullman on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pullman/</link><description>Recent content in Pullman on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pullman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city.</description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel.</description></item><item><title>Luxury hotel to cater to Sydney airport guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</guid><description>Accor, the largest hotel operator in Australia, will be a part of a new multi-use development project in Mascot, near the Sydney Airport. The project will include a hotel, commercial space, and retail areas.
Accor signed an agreement with Goodman to oversee a 5-star hotel, named Pullman Sydney Airport, as part of a new A$100 million development. This project will also include office and retail space. Pullman, the biggest upscale hotel network in the Asia Pacific, has over 45 hotels in the area.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its inaugural five-star international hotel in Vung Tau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The
Pullman Vung Tau.
AccorHotels is introducing the Pullman Vung Tau, the first international five-star hotel in this coastal city just a 90-minute drive from Ho Chi Minh City.
The Pullman Vung Tau offers views of both Back Beach and Front Beach and boasts the largest meeting facilities in Southern Vietnam, making it perfect for business travelers looking for a quick escape from Ho Chi Minh City.</description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers.</description></item><item><title>Experience the enchanting Arabian nights under the stars at the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar until July 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</guid><description>From June 21st to July 16th, 2015, the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar is excited to present a delectable Ramadhan buffet. The culinary team at LINK All Day Dining has crafted a special &amp;ldquo;Starry Arabian Nights&amp;rdquo; themed dinner, featuring a wide selection of traditional Arab and Malay dishes. The restaurant will be adorned with exotic, Arabian-inspired starry lights, and live ‘ghazal’ performances will entertain guests throughout their meal.
Source: Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food.</description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high.</description></item><item><title>Join us at the Pullman Jakarta Indonesia to celebrate the holy month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>The Pullman Jakarta Indonesia hotel has a special offer for corporate groups during Ramadan. For groups of 50 or more, they offer a deluxe Iftar (breaking the fast) package for Rp450,000 per person. This package features a selection of traditional Iftar snacks and drinks, along with an Indonesian buffet.
To make a reservation or get more details, you can contact Ms. Sarat via email at H8491-SM4@accor.com or by phone at +62 21 3192 1111.</description></item></channel></rss>