<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Denmark on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/denmark/</link><description>Recent content in Denmark on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/denmark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a conflict or disagreement between the European Court of Justice and the Danish Constitutional Court? The Danish Supreme Court is questioning the Mangold-principle.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-conflict-or-disagreement-between-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-danish-constitutional-court-the-danish-supreme-court-is-questioning-the-mangold-principle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-conflict-or-disagreement-between-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-danish-constitutional-court-the-danish-supreme-court-is-questioning-the-mangold-principle/</guid><description>Sune Klinge, PhD Fellow, Centre for Comparative and European Consitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
The Danish Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Ajos case, concerning the scope of the EU employment equality Directive and age discrimination. This decision follows a ruling from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) that provided two paths for the Danish court: interpret national law in harmony with the Directive or disapply conflicting national provisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-conflict-or-disagreement-between-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-danish-constitutional-court-the-danish-supreme-court-is-questioning-the-mangold-principle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-conflict-or-disagreement-between-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-danish-constitutional-court-the-danish-supreme-court-is-questioning-the-mangold-principle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can obesity be considered a disability?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</guid><description>By Katharina Ó Cathaoir, PhD Fellow, University of Copenhagen
==============================================================================================
Does being obese qualify as a disability? This complex issue was the focus of Advocate General Jääskinen&amp;rsquo;s opinion on July 17, 2014, in the case of Kaltoft v. Municipality of Billund. The case has drawn significant interest, particularly regarding potential impacts on employment and healthcare. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to note that the Advocate General&amp;rsquo;s opinion is not legally binding and the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will issue its own judgment in the coming months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it permissible for Member States to confiscate the assets of asylum-seekers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk (Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen) and Steve Peers
Recently, several countries within and outside the EU have made headlines for seizing assets from asylum-seekers upon entry. This raises the question of whether this practice aligns with EU law. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine national practices, the development of relevant EU regulations, and finally, draw our conclusions.
Denmark
In November 2015, the Danish government put forward 34 measures aimed at deterring asylum seekers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Details of the upcoming referendum on Denmark's participation in EU Justice and Home Affairs Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Denmark&amp;rsquo;s involvement in international criminal law, exemplified by the TV show &amp;ldquo;The Bridge,&amp;rdquo; is facing uncertainty due to changing EU regulations. This situation will soon lead Denmark to vote on modifying its current near-total opt-out of EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) laws. While the general implications have been discussed, the specifics of this vote are now clearer.
To recap, Denmark negotiated opt-outs from the euro, defense, and parts of JHA law in 1992...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>