<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Telephone System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephone-system/</link><description>Recent content in Business Telephone System on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephone-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX For Features and Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</guid><description>Determining if it&amp;rsquo;s the right moment to transition your business phone system to a cloud-based solution is crucial, especially if your current system struggles with capacity, needs frequent fixes, or lacks vendor support. However, even if your current system functions adequately, you might be overlooking opportunities to enhance productivity and reduce communication expenses with modern hosted PBX solutions.
A prime illustration is AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s updated Cloud Hosted IP PBX, AirePBX version 2.</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>Contact Center On Demand in the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The sophistication of cloud communications services is constantly increasing, representing a logical progression in the cloud computing revolution. With data servers already transitioned to the cloud, numerous businesses are questioning the necessity of maintaining costly and aging PBX phone systems.
Transitioning business phone systems to the cloud is becoming increasingly practical. Beginning with Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, this shift eliminates the need for substantial hardware and traditional phone lines. Instead, handsets connect to the company network and a high-bandwidth WAN connection links to the provider.</description></item></channel></rss>