<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tata Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tata-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Tata Communications on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tata-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tata Communications updates the jamvee unified communications platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-updates-the-jamvee-unified-communications-platform/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications provider, recently launched the newest version of its cloud-based unified communications platform, jamvee.
Source: Jamvee website.
Leveraging Tata Communications&amp;rsquo; robust global network, jamvee consolidates various client software and devices into a single, secure, and versatile platform. This approach streamlines communication and collaboration within and across organizations, allowing employees, suppliers, and customers to connect seamlessly using any combination of audio, video, messaging, and content sharing tools, regardless of their device or browser.</description></item><item><title>WebRTC set to boost business productivity for browsers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably used a web browser like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, or Safari on your phone or computer to visit websites.
Some companies believe browsers can be much more than tools for accessing websites; they think browsers can simplify our lives. Tata Communications suggests that incorporating the right features into browsers could significantly boost employee productivity.
&amp;ldquo;Despite some positive developments, most of us are still dealing with separate, disconnected communication platforms.</description></item><item><title>What Makes High Frequency Trading Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</guid><description>Computerized trading, including high frequency trading, is now the norm in the stock market. As seen on CBS News, algorithms can automatically execute trades when specific conditions are met.
A key challenge of automated trading is ensuring fairness by synchronizing timing for all participants. The New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) addressed this by creating a data center that standardized access time to 65 microseconds for everyone. However, this only applies to trading within the NYSE.</description></item><item><title>Tata Communications announces Global Scrapbook Challenge ahead of upcoming Formula 1 race</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications company, has launched its second technology challenge offering US$50,000 in prizes. This challenge focuses on harnessing innovative connectivity solutions, a key aspect of Formula 1 racing.
Leading up to the FORMULA 1 GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2014, Tata Communications is challenging the public to create a digital scrapbook celebrating the history of the Mercedes-Benz Silver Arrows in Formula 1. This Global Scrapbook Challenge aims to build a virtual museum, a captivating online archive of stories, memories, and intrigue for fans of the sport.</description></item></channel></rss>