<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Trial on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-trial/</link><description>Recent content in Free Trial on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:51:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-trial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Try Internet Fax For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-internet-fax-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-internet-fax-for-free/</guid><description>Even though constantly texting is the norm today, fax machines are still important, especially in business, where they&amp;rsquo;re used for contracts and other key documents. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you need a bunch of fax machines in your office. You can send and receive faxes online, wherever you are, with the right fax plan.
Instead of a clunky fax machine, a fax service plan is much more practical. Fax machines can only send faxes and take up space, while a fax service plan lets you send and receive faxes digitally through email and an online account, using your computer or laptop.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Social Commerce Apps For Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</guid><description>E-commerce is no longer a novelty; it&amp;rsquo;s a cornerstone of modern business. The next big shift, social commerce, is already underway. This evolution utilizes social media platforms, primarily Facebook and Twitter, to connect with customers where they are most active. The question for businesses is how to best harness this power.
While older methods like DIY websites, email campaigns, and blogs still exist, they are becoming outdated. The solution lies in hosted solutions, with Facebook as the foundation.</description></item><item><title>Send Fax From Email On Your Computer or Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</guid><description>Do you recall fax machines with thermal paper rolls? Those messages had a distinct look and tended to fade. To preserve them, you&amp;rsquo;d copy them onto regular paper using a laser printer, then diligently wash the strange residue off your hands.
Fax technology has significantly evolved. Thermal paper is out, and even traditional fax machines are becoming rare. Cloud-based electronic transmission and storage are the modern alternatives.
Sending and receiving faxes via email is the contemporary approach.</description></item><item><title>Secure Any Public WiFi Hotspot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: you&amp;rsquo;re away from your secure office network or home WiFi, relying on public WiFi that makes you uneasy. While convenient, unsecured WiFi hotspots present a security risk. How can you be sure someone isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring your activity with malicious software when you send private emails or sensitive data?
](http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-1726600-11129503)
It&amp;rsquo;s a valid concern. Cybercrime is rampant, and tools for intercepting data on public WiFi are readily available.</description></item><item><title>Put Some Sanity Back In Your Email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/put-some-sanity-back-in-your-email/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/put-some-sanity-back-in-your-email/</guid><description>Are you happy with your email? Do you have a good relationship? All the time you spend together, you&amp;rsquo;d think you&amp;rsquo;d be perfect for each other. Or maybe not.
Email can feel like a burden we can&amp;rsquo;t escape. At first, it was amazing, maybe even love at first sight. But over time, it became overwhelming. Everything seemed important at the beginning, but now it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find what matters in the constant flood of messages.</description></item></channel></rss>