<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Codec on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/codec/</link><description>Recent content in Codec on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/codec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>What is ISDN and Why Do I Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</guid><description>You might have encountered the term ISDN in the context of phone services. What does it mean and how can it benefit you?
ISDN stands for Integrated Services Digital Network, a technical term for a digital phone service that adheres to specific standards.
The concept of ISDN emerged when dial-up modems using analog phone lines were the norm for internet access. ISDN aimed to combine phone and internet services on a single line with three channels.</description></item><item><title>How HD Audio Will Transform VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</guid><description>People who recall the era of analog phones and physical switches often feel nostalgic about the superior audio quality of those systems. The conversations back then possessed a clarity and immediacy that has largely vanished in recent times, though this might be changing soon. A new movement is underway to enhance the fidelity of VoIP calls significantly, aiming to make current phones seem primitive in comparison.
This advancement is known as high-definition audio or HD Voice, a term used by Polycom, a manufacturer of IP phones equipped with this technology.</description></item><item><title>Why Video is Moving to H.264</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</guid><description>Digital video is gaining immense popularity and rapidly consuming internet bandwidth. It&amp;rsquo;s revolutionizing television, expanding its presence on the internet, and being adopted by businesses for cost reduction, productivity gains, and environmental benefits. However, its major drawback is its heavy bandwidth consumption.
H.264, a video coding standard, addresses this issue by offering high-quality video at lower bandwidths through compression. While uncompressed high-quality video demands significant bandwidth, unsuitable for most businesses and consumers, H.</description></item></channel></rss>