<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Waste on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/waste/</link><description>Recent content in Waste on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/waste/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Used cooking oil fuels 1,000 km flight in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</guid><description>A Hainan Airlines flight recently completed a journey of over 1,000 km from Shanghai to Beijing using a blend of conventional jet fuel and biofuel made from recycled cooking oil. The Boeing 737-800 aircraft, carrying over 100 passengers, was powered by a 50/50 mix of biofuel, produced by Sinopec using waste oil from Chinese restaurants, and standard petroleum fuel.
Sustainable biofuel is gaining traction in the aviation industry for its potential to significantly reduce carbon emissions (by 50-80%) compared to traditional fuels.</description></item><item><title>Get Paid To Celebrate National Cell Phone Recycling Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s National Cell Phone Recycling Week, and there&amp;rsquo;s a way to make some money while participating! This initiative, spearheaded by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), highlights the importance of recycling valuable and potentially harmful materials found in cell phones.
Wireless carriers and various retailers are accepting old cell phones to ensure these devices are properly processed and their components are reused in new products. By taking part, you contribute to environmental protection by preventing hazardous materials from ending up in landfills.</description></item></channel></rss>