<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WiFi on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wifi/</link><description>Recent content in WiFi on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:53:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I Know Where You Took Your Pictures Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</guid><description>Eye-Fi, the WiFi-enabled memory card, has introduced a new feature: location tagging. Their latest product, Eye-Fi Explore, automatically adds geotags to photos as you take them.
You might be surprised to learn that they haven&amp;rsquo;t actually included a GPS receiver in the small SD card. Instead, it uses a system that determines location based on known WiFi hotspots. This method covers a significant portion of the U.S. population and major metropolitan areas in Europe.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>China's unicorn company has revealed the top 10 rankings in the Google Play store for its Wi-Fi crowdsourcing app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</guid><description>Source: Play Store.
The free app WiFi Master Key, which helps users find and connect to crowdsourced Wi-Fi hotspots, is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia. It helps people access the internet in a region where connectivity is rapidly expanding.
The app lets users share Wi-Fi hotspot information with the community. While this information allows others to connect for free, the app prioritizes privacy and security by encrypting and storing shared Wi-Fi passwords in its cloud database instead of revealing them directly.</description></item><item><title>What’s the Difference Between WiMAX and WiFi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-difference-between-wimax-and-wifi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 11:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-difference-between-wimax-and-wifi/</guid><description>WiMAX and WiFi sound alike, but are they related? Think of WiMAX as a city-wide hotspot, similar to 3G cellular broadband. It&amp;rsquo;s more than just a powerful WiFi; it&amp;rsquo;s a broadband service covering a much larger area, even inside buildings and vehicles. Watch this video for a closer look at WiMAX.
WiMAX is a robust wireless standard gaining global traction for providing wireless broadband access to stationary and mobile devices. In numerous US cities, WiMAX utilizes old analog TV channels auctioned off recently.</description></item><item><title>Internet to Soothe the Savage Flyer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</guid><description>Is there anything more frustrating than squeezing into the last seat on a long flight, stuck between grumpy passengers with hours to kill? You yearn for the distraction of emails or online games, but alas, internet access in the air seems like a distant dream.
Fear not, weary traveler! The wait for in-flight WiFi is almost over. Major airlines are preparing to offer internet access on their planes, but it comes at a price.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G1 Google Android Phone Gets Vocal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</guid><description>Choosing your next smartphone can be tough. Touchscreen phones like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone, the BlackBerry Bold, and Samsung Delve are appealing, but some prefer a physical QWERTY keyboard. The BlackBerry Pearl&amp;rsquo;s trackball navigation is another option. Connectivity matters too, with 3G being desirable but not always accessible. WiFi capability for fast web browsing is also important.
The HTC-built G1 for T-Mobile might be the solution if you want it all. This &amp;ldquo;Android Phone,&amp;rdquo; marking Google&amp;rsquo;s entry into mobile wireless, operates on T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s network, offering quad-band service and various data features.</description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>I Shall Call It Cellular Mini-Me</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</guid><description>The change from landlines to mobile phones is accelerating as 3G networks expand coverage to suburban and rural areas. Smartphones like the BlackBerry and iPhone are becoming ubiquitous, prompting questions about the necessity of laptops. Wireless technology offers liberation from desktops, allowing users to communicate, browse, and enjoy videos on the move. However, this freedom is often hindered indoors.
Indoor spaces present a significant obstacle to wireless transmission. Walls and other barriers weaken high-frequency radio signals, leading to dropped calls and poor connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes.</description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>Ghost Routers In The Sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wireless internet access on airplanes is becoming a reality. Although it had a slow start, major airlines like American, Delta, Northwest, and Virgin are now embracing in-flight Wi-Fi.
This shift is inevitable in a society increasingly reliant on technology. We might be giving up old habits, but staying connected online is non-negotiable. Just like hotels and restaurants adapted to this need, airlines are following suit. Passengers are willing to endure cramped conditions and forgo traditional amenities, but internet access is a must-have.</description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T HSUPA Aircards Have the Edge Over EDGE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</guid><description>Major wireless carriers, including AT&amp;amp;T, are heavily invested in upgrading their cellular data capabilities to meet the increasing demand for broadband internet access. This demand stems from the desire for constant connectivity, enabling activities like web browsing and mobile video streaming. AT&amp;amp;T is eager to capitalize on this demand and provide the desired connectivity.
Those accustomed to traditional wired broadband connections and basic cell phones may not fully grasp the advancements in mobile broadband technology.</description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?</description></item><item><title>WiFi in a Memory Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wifi-in-a-memory-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 05:41:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wifi-in-a-memory-card/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t often see an SD memory card with an FCC ID, but this one is special. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a 2GB memory card; it&amp;rsquo;s also a WiFi transmitter. Set it up on your computer with the included USB adapter, then put it in your camera. Now, whenever you&amp;rsquo;re within range of your home network, your pictures will automatically upload to your computer or your favorite online photo sharing site. It&amp;rsquo;s like magic!</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington</description></item><item><title>Chumby Kicks the Clock Radio to the Curb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</guid><description>Are traditional alarm clocks and radios truly effective ways to wake up? Imagine a more modern approach: starting your day with your favorite internet radio station, a quick weather and market update, and a glimpse at your online auctions. You could even catch up on news and sports or play a game. All of this is possible with the Chumby.
What exactly is a Chumby? It&amp;rsquo;s a wireless internet device featuring speakers, a touchscreen, and motion sensors.</description></item><item><title>XOHM, XOHM's Got The Range</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</guid><description>Sprint&amp;rsquo;s XOHM (pronounced &amp;ldquo;zome,&amp;rdquo; like &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;) wireless broadband service has launched in Baltimore, marking the start of the highly anticipated rollout of WiMAX as the next generation of high-speed internet. If Sprint successfully implements its 4G vision, WiFi hotspots could become obsolete. DSL? Cable? Why bother with wires when you can have the freedom of wireless connectivity?
This vision relies on a new wireless technology standardized for global use in both fixed and mobile applications.</description></item></channel></rss>