<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellular Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Cellular Broadband on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Maestro Smart Antenna Improves Fixed Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</guid><description>Accel Technologies, a branch of Accel Networks, is launching a groundbreaking product for fixed wireless connections: the Maestro smart antenna system. Maestro aims to make 3G and 4G fixed wireless broadband a more attractive alternative to pricier business connectivity options like T1, MPLS, VSAT, Frame Relay, and point-to-point microwave services.
What makes Maestro so special? Like other smart devices, Maestro utilizes active technology to enhance performance. In this situation, it improves the performance of a typically passive component: the RF antenna...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speedier Network For The iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</guid><description>While the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s popularity is a boon for AT&amp;amp;T, which holds the exclusive contract, the device&amp;rsquo;s data demands present a significant hurdle.
Historically, cellular towers primarily handled voice calls, with data as a secondary function. Early data speeds were adequate for text-based services, but the advent of camera phones, web browsers, and video streaming dramatically increased bandwidth requirements. Today&amp;rsquo;s users demand home and work-level speeds, typically between 3 to 10 Mbps, far exceeding the capabilities of older networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Plans With Aircards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</guid><description>Wireless modem aircards liberate you from the constraints of WiFi hotspots, transforming your laptop into a truly mobile computer. But how do they work, and what kind of service plans are necessary?
Essentially, an aircard functions as a specialized two-way radio, transmitting and receiving digital computer data instead of voice calls.
While they might resemble them, aircards don&amp;rsquo;t operate on cell phone networks. Currently, the majority adhere to either EVDO (Sprint and Verizon Wireless) or EDGE and HSPA (AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile) standards for cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless For Rural Retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</guid><description>Small businesses outside of cities often struggle to obtain affordable and reliable broadband. While some resort to satellite or T1 lines for internet and point-of-sale systems, others have discovered that 3G wireless offers a secure and cost-effective alternative for credit card processing.
](http://www.sheepfort1.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
We associate 3G with mobile phones and laptops, but a lesser-known application exists. This service combines the widespread availability of 3G signals with powerful multi-carrier equipment and a secure VPN network, making it suitable for business needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Caps: What They Are and How to Avoid Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent internet user, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably encountered data caps. This article explains these usage limits and how to navigate them.
OK, What IS a Data Cap? A data cap restricts the amount of data transferred over a connection within a specific timeframe. Usually set monthly, these limits, measured in MB or GB, reset every 30 days. Activities like browsing, file transfers, and cloud backups consume this data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Get To The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing and storage are becoming increasingly popular, and many believe they will soon be the standard for computer use. There are many benefits to using the cloud, such as not needing to buy or maintain software, having data automatically backed up, accessing tools and data from anywhere on any device, and being able to use smaller, more portable computers, like netbooks, cellphones, and tablets. However, one concern remains: reliable access to the cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Aircards Work For Mobile Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 17:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</guid><description>Internet access via broadband has become a standard requirement for almost all businesses and home offices. Individuals can easily find and afford DSL and Cable Internet. Businesses, on the other hand, often opt for T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, and Ethernet connections. However, challenges arise when venturing beyond the confines of a traditional workspace. Without WiFi hotspots, staying connected becomes difficult. How can tasks such as delivering presentations, accessing inventory, or entering orders at a client&amp;rsquo;s office be accomplished if they necessitate a broadband connection?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-aircards-work-for-mobile-computing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tripping the LTE Fantastic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</guid><description>Although fiber optic and mobile WiMAX are getting a lot of attention, LTE could become the next major broadband technology. Could gigabit wireless communication be on the horizon?
People struggling with slow 1G connections or the first iPhone might find the idea of 1,000 Mbps speeds on their mobile devices unrealistic. It seems like there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough bandwidth from cell towers. However, emerging technologies may increase wireless bandwidth significantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Winter Of Our Disconnect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winter-of-our-disconnect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winter-of-our-disconnect/</guid><description>The Challenges of Disconnection in the Digital Age
While we live in an era defined by instant communication, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for businesses to prepare for disruptions. This is similar to the wisdom of anticipating challenges, even during seemingly stable times.
Take, for instance, the recent incident in the Mediterranean where several underwater cables were severed. This caused significant internet outages in Egypt and India, with slower speeds experienced across Europe and Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winter-of-our-disconnect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winter-of-our-disconnect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T HSUPA Aircards Have the Edge Over EDGE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</guid><description>Major wireless carriers, including AT&amp;amp;T, are heavily invested in upgrading their cellular data capabilities to meet the increasing demand for broadband internet access. This demand stems from the desire for constant connectivity, enabling activities like web browsing and mobile video streaming. AT&amp;amp;T is eager to capitalize on this demand and provide the desired connectivity.
Those accustomed to traditional wired broadband connections and basic cell phones may not fully grasp the advancements in mobile broadband technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I'm Not Paying For That Aircard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 07:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</guid><description>Fast and dependable office internet connections are great when you&amp;rsquo;re stationary, but mobile work demands solutions like WiFi hotspots or cellular broadband. While these options are suitable, not all laptops are equipped for cellular broadband.
Aircards, sometimes called wireless modems, bridge this gap. Similar to WiFi access cards, these devices allow laptops to connect to cellular broadband networks. In the past, laptops primarily used built-in modems, requiring separate cards for WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G Fixed Wireless For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</guid><description>The same 3G technology that revolutionized mobile phones is also available as a fixed wireless service, offering a cost-effective solution for businesses in areas with limited internet options. Cellular networks have established a wide infrastructure of base stations, effectively blanketing the country with both voice and data coverage. These familiar cell towers transmit signals using microwave radio equipment.
Essentially, the 3G wireless broadband service functions as a network of interconnected Wi-Fi hotspots with a significantly larger coverage area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Cell phones today are capable of much more than just voice calls. The mobile networks have evolved to carry both voice and data, offering wireless broadband internet access that rivals DSL and cable connections.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t explored mobile internet recently, you might be surprised by its speed and availability. Currently, two competing systems are widely available, with two even faster networks in their early stages.
AT&amp;amp;T promotes its HSDPA and EDGE networks, notably featuring the Apple iPhone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>