<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Connection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-connection/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Connection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-connection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Corporate Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</guid><description>For medium to large businesses, a 100 Mbps connection speed is becoming the new norm. While this might seem excessive and expensive, it&amp;rsquo;s actually neither. In essence, Fast Ethernet is taking over the role of DS3.
A decade ago, a 1.5 Mbps T1 line was considered high bandwidth. Today&amp;rsquo;s need for 100 Mbps reflects the significant evolution of application requirements. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from basic video conferencing to high-definition, two-way video and telepresence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet as a DS3 Upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line provides have historically opted for DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. This high-speed digital connection typically runs on a SONET fiber optic circuit, with the final connection to the customer&amp;rsquo;s location installed and maintained by the local phone company. DS3 is fast, very reliable, and more affordable than ever before. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new contender – Fast Ethernet.
Fast Ethernet is a standard Ethernet LAN speed that delivers 100 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>