<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legal Bases on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/legal-bases/</link><description>Recent content in Legal Bases on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/legal-bases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The European Citizens' Initiative and Greek debt: A surprising pairing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</guid><description>Anastasia Karatzia, Law Lecturer, University of Essex
Introduction
Decisions from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on the European and Monetary Union (EMU) are infrequent. Recent cases on this topic, including landmark judgments like Pringle and Gauweiler, have addressed measures enacted during the Eurozone crisis. Among these decisions is Anagnostakis v Commission, a case challenging the Commission&amp;rsquo;s refusal to register a proposed European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI) titled &amp;ldquo;One million signatures for solidarity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU employment law and irregular migrants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Determining the employment rights of undocumented migrants is complex. On one hand, granting them full access to employment law protections could incentivize unauthorized migration. On the other hand, applying standard employment laws to all workers, regardless of immigration status, could prevent the exploitation of undocumented migrants and deter employers from hiring them to save money.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this issue in the Tumer case, which focused on the application of the EU Directive on insolvent employers to undocumented migrants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beware of the Accountability Gap in the EU's Financial Supervisory Authorities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City Law School
The year 2010 saw the creation of three European Supervisory Authorities: the European Banking Authority, the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority, and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA). These authorities were established by the European Union in response to the then-unprecedented financial crisis. On January 22, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant judgment (Case C-270/12, United Kingdom v Council &amp;amp; Parliament) concerning recent legislation granting ESMA the authority to impose legally binding measures on financial institutions in Member States when the proper functioning of financial markets or the stability of the EU financial system is threatened...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU guarantees the fundamental democratic and judicial oversight of the EU's foreign policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirmed in its recent decision in European Parliament v Council that the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) is subject to a minimum standard of democratic and judicial oversight.
The case involved a challenge by the European Parliament (EP) to the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign and ratify a treaty between the EU and Mauritius. This treaty pertained to the EU&amp;rsquo;s military operations against pirates operating in the Indian Ocean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Poor drivers and European Union legislation: The Court of Justice of the European Union takes the wrong approach.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</guid><description>Steve Peers
There&amp;rsquo;s a humorous anecdote about national stereotypes, where an American, a Canadian, a Brit, and a Frenchman are asked to write about elephants. The punchline highlights their different perspectives: the Frenchman focuses on the elephant&amp;rsquo;s mating habits, the Brit on its colonial significance, the American on its military uses, and the Canadian on whether the elephant falls under federal or provincial jurisdiction. This humorous scenario underscores how jurisdictional issues are central to Canadian identity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Imprisoning bankers: the latest EU Directive on enforcing criminal penalties for market abuse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU politicians likely feel a sense of relief as they&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a group even less popular than themselves: bankers. This unpopularity has only intensified as the global financial crisis and resulting austerity measures continue to impact ordinary citizens across numerous Member States. Politicians understand that targeting disliked groups rarely hurts them in the polls, leading EU institutions to enact legislation that could imprison bankers for specific wrongdoings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>