<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jakarta on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jakarta/</link><description>Recent content in Jakarta on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jakarta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement provides a platform for new entrepreneurs to thrive on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) has been chosen to develop, curate content for, and design the strategy of the Global Entrepreneurship Community (GECommunity) for 2016. The soft launch of this initiative took place at the World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF) in Jakarta, Indonesia. The Finance Ministry, through the National Entrepreneurs Development Office (NEDO) and the Malaysian Global Innovation and Creativity Centre (MaGIC), is hosting GECommunity 2016.
GECommunity aims to establish Malaysia as a global hub for connectivity and innovation.</description></item><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests.</description></item><item><title>The 12th WIEF could provide a boost for Indonesian SMEs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</guid><description>Experts at a public dialogue titled &amp;ldquo;Seizing the Benefits of Disruptive Technology for Manufacturers in Increasing Labor Productivity&amp;rdquo; emphasized that disruptive technology can work alongside traditional, labor-intensive methods. The event was organized by The Habibie Center, in partnership with the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and the World Islamic Economic Forum Foundation, as a precursor to the 12th World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF).
Dr. Zamroni Salim, a Senior Economic Researcher at the Indonesian Institute of Sciences (LIPI), explained that disruptive technologies don&amp;rsquo;t always clash with conventional labor models.</description></item><item><title>Join us at the Pullman Jakarta Indonesia to celebrate the holy month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>The Pullman Jakarta Indonesia hotel has a special offer for corporate groups during Ramadan. For groups of 50 or more, they offer a deluxe Iftar (breaking the fast) package for Rp450,000 per person. This package features a selection of traditional Iftar snacks and drinks, along with an Indonesian buffet.
To make a reservation or get more details, you can contact Ms. Sarat via email at H8491-SM4@accor.com or by phone at +62 21 3192 1111.</description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI.</description></item></channel></rss>