<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Standstill on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/standstill/</link><description>Recent content in Standstill on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/standstill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy.</description></item></channel></rss>