<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cleaning on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cleaning/</link><description>Recent content in Cleaning on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cleaning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning of the Tone Arm Carriage Position Switches and a Non-Returning Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</guid><description>As a preliminary step in the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I chose to verify the functionality of its control system. Prior testing had shown that the arm carriage would not return to its home position when moved across the platter without a record in place. Instead, it would travel to the center of the platter and stop. Ideally, the carriage should trigger the End Switch (ES) at this point and subsequently return to its home position on the right, turning off the turntable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of Bearings, and Repair of a Broken Off Brush and a Disconnected Sensing Coil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-repair-of-a-broken-off-brush-and-a-disconnected-sensing-coil/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-repair-of-a-broken-off-brush-and-a-disconnected-sensing-coil/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor from the Netherlands. The motor was dead on arrival, so I opened it up and discovered a broken commutator spring that had been taped on with electrical tape.
Unsurprisingly, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t turn. I also found a broken lead on one of the sensing coils, which should have a resistance of 22 Ohms between the contact terminals.
This break disabled the motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoring the DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the motor. The motor was noticeably loud, a common issue in DC 4002 models often caused by dried lubricant in the sleeve bearings. Addressing this requires disassembling the motor, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubricant.
The first image highlights the upper sleeve bearing after the rotor was removed.
The next image provides a view of the lower bearing, feedback coils, and brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Oil Infusion of DC Platter Motor Bearings and RPM Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</guid><description>To fully rebuild the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 DC motor, you must relubricate the motor bearings. Many DC motor Beograms have fluctuating RPMs because the oil in their porous brass bearings (called &amp;ldquo;Oilite&amp;rdquo;) depletes over time. These bearings can be &amp;lsquo;refilled&amp;rsquo; by using a vacuum to remove air and allow oil to replenish the pores. The challenge lies in extracting the bearings without causing damage. I documented this process in a recent video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Cleaning the Panels and Installing a 3D Printed Guiding Washer for the Cabinet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:25:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</guid><description>I dedicated some time today to refining the appearance of the Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on. The first step involved adjusting the platter&amp;rsquo;s height and alignment within the aluminum panel. Achieving a centered and flush platter is crucial for the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s visual appeal. The platter was positioned too low upon arrival, even grazing the panel due to misalignment.
Therefore, I made adjustments to the main bearing and the chassis&amp;rsquo;s three suspension points to achieve the correct setup.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors/</guid><description>With 2017 underway and the festivities behind us, it&amp;rsquo;s time to resume the Beocord 9000 restoration. I began by replacing the electrolytic capacitors. As I&amp;rsquo;ve noted before, these Beocord 9000 units often require minimal recapping, if any. This particular unit seems to have been stored for a considerable period, and I already discovered one faulty capacitor, prompting me to replace the others.
My usual practice is to use audio-grade capacitors in the signal path and opt for high-reliability, 105°C rated, long-lasting capacitors elsewhere.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Exciting DC Motor Failure Mode Due to a Shorted Spark Snubber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-exciting-dc-motor-failure-mode-due-to-a-shorted-spark-snubber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 05:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-exciting-dc-motor-failure-mode-due-to-a-shorted-spark-snubber/</guid><description>Another Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor in need of repair recently came to my workbench. During my standard pre-restoration test using a Beogram 4002, this motor was unusually sluggish, only operating with assistance. This contrasted with the typical DC motors I encounter, which generally run powerfully but exhibit RPM fluctuations and often produce high-pitched sounds due to dried-out bearings. This particular motor was noticeably underpowered.
I disassembled the motor and performed my usual bearing oil infusion to ensure the mechanical components were within specifications before addressing the sluggishness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the DC Motor and a Significant Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-dc-motor-and-a-significant-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 02:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-dc-motor-and-a-significant-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>A recently acquired Beogram 4002 turntable exhibited significant speed variations during an initial performance test. The frequent and irregular drops in rotations per minute (RPM) pointed to a need for cleaning and lubrication of the DC motor.
The motor was removed from its housing for servicing.
The motor was then disassembled to allow for cleaning and lubrication of its bearings.
Following reassembly and reinstallation of the motor, a 24-hour RPM test was conducted.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Infusing the DC Motor Oilite Bearings with Fresh Oil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-infusing-the-dc-motor-oilite-bearings-with-fresh-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 16:42:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-infusing-the-dc-motor-oilite-bearings-with-fresh-oil/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5524), the DC motor required attention. The Oilite brass bearings, designed with a &amp;rsquo;lifetime&amp;rsquo; lubricant within their pores, typically need replenishing after approximately four decades. This involves submerging the bearings in motor oil and using a vacuum to extract air from the pores, allowing oil to penetrate. A detailed video demonstrating this process is available here.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse at this specific motor, both extracted from the turntable:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Progress Update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</guid><description>The next stage of the restoration involved removing parts from the Beogram chassis. This was necessary to access the tangential arm for repairs and to thoroughly clean the disintegrated transport bushings.
Fragments of the old bushings were scattered throughout the chassis, even within the tonearm cover.
This image shows the Beogram chassis after a thorough cleaning.
Next, 3D-printed replacement bushings from Beolover were installed.
The new bushings fit perfectly. When reattaching the floating chassis, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to align the top and bottom locking washers on their respective threads.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding DC Motor with Oil Infused Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the RPM relay and trimmers in the Beogram 4002 (5513) with updated parts, the DC motor required attention. The DC motor often proves to be the most challenging aspect of restoring a 4002 and nearly always demands attention. The primary hurdle lies in restoring the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite oil-infused brass sleeve bearings. These bearings are &amp;ldquo;pre-lubricated&amp;rdquo; in a new motor. From a typical consumer perspective, with a lifespan of 10-15 years, these bearings might be considered &amp;ldquo;maintenance-free.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</guid><description>I noticed a knocking sound coming from my Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s AC motor, which meant the Oilite brass bearing needed lubrication. These bearings are designed to release oil onto the motor shaft over time. Eventually, they need to be replaced or re-lubricated. Using a food vacuum sealer and a mason jar, you can replenish the oil. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I did it:
First, I removed the motor.
Next, I removed the two rivets holding the motor together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding a Noisy DC Motor with Oil Infused Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-a-noisy-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 11:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-a-noisy-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-bearings/</guid><description>The majority of Beogram 4002 turntables equipped with a DC motor require motor refurbishment. Indicators of this need include abrupt drops in revolutions per minute (RPM) or audible motor noise during operation. This specific Beogram 4002 (5514) exhibited significant noise during unloaded operation. As part of my restoration process for all 4002 turntables, I comprehensively rebuild the DC motors to preemptively address these common issues.
The primary contributor to these performance issues lies in the brass sleeve bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going over the chassis and mechanical parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</guid><description>The two circuit boards that needed component updates are finished. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s cabinet and its mechanical parts.
I prefer working on the floating chassis with it removed, which is easier since I&amp;rsquo;ll disassemble most of the tangential arm.
This revealed some hidden issues.
Initially, I believed the three chassis lock bushings were okay because they looked fine. However, examining the locking mechanism showed otherwise.
This was the first indication of the bushings&amp;rsquo; poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): DC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently restored a DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The turntable exhibited the common issue of inconsistent RPM, indicating the need to lubricate the motor bearings. I documented this process in detail in a video posted earlier. Here are some observations from the motor restoration.
The first image shows the motor in its initial condition upon arrival:
This image shows the motor after disassembly:
The two small &amp;ldquo;donut&amp;rdquo; shapes in the front right of the photo are the bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Repair of 'Knocking' AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</guid><description>I prefer to thoroughly test restored Beograms to ensure they&amp;rsquo;re free of intermittent issues. It&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for new problems to appear with regular use. This was the case with a recently restored AC motor Beogram 4002 (5501). After playing a few records, I detected a faint knocking sound coming from inside the turntable. Upon removing the aluminum plates, I discovered the knocking synchronized with the AC motor&amp;rsquo;s rotation. Adjusting the motor tilt provided temporary noise reduction, but the knocking always returned, intensifying with each record played until it was noticeable during quieter tracks—an unacceptable issue for a turntable!</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing Capacitors Wrapped Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors-wrapped-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 16:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors-wrapped-up/</guid><description>The capacitor replacement on the Beocord 9000 cassette deck is complete, although it took a bit longer than anticipated. While most capacitors were within specification, a few were not, including two that had completely failed. Notably, a 220uF capacitor (C56) on the Microcomputer/Display board was the culprit behind the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inability to power on. Another failed 220uF capacitor (C7) of the same brand was discovered on the Dolby board. This highlights the importance of checking all electrolytic capacitors in such situations.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Adjustment of AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-adjustment-of-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-adjustment-of-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>After restoring the electronics of a Beogram 4000 turntable, attention turned to the AC platter motor. This model features an older pulley design without built-in belt guards, relying instead on separate guards added to the motor mounting posts. These added guards are not essential, as the pulley&amp;rsquo;s shape effectively secures the belt. Motor tilt allows for adjustments to the belt&amp;rsquo;s vertical positioning.
Like the DC motors in later Beogram models, the AC motors can also suffer from dried-out bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor Bearings with Oil Infusion Under Vacuum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-with-oil-infusion-under-vacuum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 01:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-with-oil-infusion-under-vacuum/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable and decided to address the DC motor while it&amp;rsquo;s open. Previously, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t realized the importance of properly lubricating the motor bearings for long-term stability. Simply applying grease provided a temporary fix, but RPM fluctuations would reappear after a few weeks.
This time, I completely disassembled the motor to access the bearings. To ensure proper lubrication, I used a vacuum method with a mason jar and a FoodSaver pump.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the DC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-dc-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-dc-motor/</guid><description>Following the reconstruction of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, I shifted my focus to the electronics, starting with the motor. While the turntable&amp;rsquo;s RPM stability was excellent, I believe a thorough restoration involves servicing every part, including the motor, to ensure long-term reliability and everyday usability.
The initial step involved extracting the motor from its housing:
Next, I removed the motor from its noise shield:
and proceeded to disassemble it:</description></item></channel></rss>