<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gender Equality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gender-equality/</link><description>Recent content in Gender Equality on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:34:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gender-equality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advancing Gender-Sensitive EU Asylum Law: Examining the Situation of 'Westernised Women'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand, Assistant Professor, and Salvo Nicolosi, Senior Assistant Professor, University of Utrecht
Photo credit: Mystslav Chernov, via Wikimedia Commons
Recent developments in EU law show a growing recognition of gender-based asylum claims. A notable example is the June 11, 2024, judgment by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of K, L v Staatssecretaris van Justitie en Veiligheid. This case, concerning two Iraqi sisters seeking asylum in the Netherlands, centers around interpreting &amp;ldquo;membership of a particular social group&amp;rdquo; within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, specifically regarding &amp;ldquo;westernized women&amp;rdquo; who fear persecution upon returning to their home countries.</description></item><item><title>The Commission's Proposal on gender quotas in corporate boards suggests a 40% representation of Venus and 60% representation of Mars.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-proposal-on-gender-quotas-in-corporate-boards-suggests-a-40-representation-of-venus-and-60-representation-of-mars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 13:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commission-s-proposal-on-gender-quotas-in-corporate-boards-suggests-a-40-representation-of-venus-and-60-representation-of-mars/</guid><description>Juan Carlos Benito Sánchez, LL.M. Candidate at KU Leuven — Twitter @jcbensan
The European Union faces a significant gender diversity challenge in its top corporate leadership positions. Although more than half of European university graduates are women, they remain underrepresented on company boards. Men outnumber women nearly four to one in these positions, with significant disparities among member states, ranging from under five percent female representation to over thirty percent.</description></item></channel></rss>