<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable.</description></item><item><title>Do You Build Wide Area Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:05:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Imagine offering your clients network installations that stretch across the city or even the entire country! You might think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible, but it&amp;rsquo;s more achievable than you think.
You won&amp;rsquo;t need massive spools of wire or heavy equipment. Everything is taken care of, allowing you to focus on expanding your business and profits.
This is possible due to two key advancements: the rise of Metro and Carrier Ethernet services from competitive carriers and a business model that lets you integrate these Ethernet WAN services into your network designs.</description></item><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies.</description></item><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet.</description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives.</description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?</description></item><item><title>I Want Fiber But Not Construction Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has become the top choice for business private lines and internet connections. It offers a practically unlimited capacity with minimal latency, packet loss, and jitter. Prices are now more competitive than before, provided you don&amp;rsquo;t encounter high construction costs.
Why Fiber Can Involve Construction Expenses
Businesses accustomed to T1 lines, Ethernet over Copper, or business cable might be surprised by quotes that include substantial construction costs for installing a fiber line.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Access Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</guid><description>Consumers access the internet in various ways, and businesses have similar options, along with some exclusive ones. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the choices available for companies at their business locations.
Popular consumer broadband choices include DSL and cable for stationary setups, and 3G for mobile use. 4G wireless is emerging, with providers like CLEAR offering it for both fixed and mobile applications. In remote areas, satellite broadband delivers connectivity where wires can&amp;rsquo;t reach.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit to 10 Gigabit to 100 Gigabit WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business operations transition to the cloud and remote work becomes increasingly common, the demand for robust Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth has surged. Fortunately, providers offer excellent solutions for establishing high-bandwidth connections between locations and to the internet.
Fiber Optic Ethernet WAN
Fiber optic connectivity has become the leading choice for business bandwidth. Businesses still relying on older technologies like T1 lines, ISDN PRI, or DS3 bandwidth may be facing limitations and nearing obsolescence.</description></item><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.1 Makes Cable Act Like Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cable broadband has undergone significant technological advancements, making it a strong competitor to fiber optic bandwidth for many businesses. Companies that previously considered cable as a backup option are now finding its blend of high performance and affordability too attractive to disregard. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advancements in cable technology and the options it presents for businesses.
Magic #1: The HFC Cable Plant
Cable television started as a basic system, essentially a collection of large antennas feeding signals to distribution amplifiers, providing an improved version of over-the-air television.</description></item><item><title>Increase Your Bandwidth Beyond T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your trusty T1 line has served you well for years, maybe even decades. You appreciate its reliability, consistent bandwidth, minimal lag, and decreasing contract prices. However, the bandwidth is becoming a constraint. While 1.5 Mbps was sufficient a decade ago, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough. Can you maintain T1&amp;rsquo;s performance with faster speeds? Absolutely!
What Makes a Good T1 Replacement You had good reasons for choosing T1 when you signed your first contract.</description></item><item><title>Business Broadband Options in Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses located in bustling city centers have a wide array of broadband Internet options, unlike their rural counterparts. While the lack of service providers in less populated areas might make it seem like broadband is a luxury they can&amp;rsquo;t afford, there are actually several options available, depending on the location.
Rural businesses might feel limited in their connectivity choices. Unlike their city counterparts, they don&amp;rsquo;t have numerous service providers vying for their business.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>Tech Upheavals in 2009</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</guid><description>The world of technology is about to undergo another major shift, particularly in telecommunications and computing. While these changes have been in motion throughout 2008, 2009 looks to be the year they truly make their mark. Here are a few potential game-changers:
Wireless Broadband Takes the Lead: Traditional DSL and cable internet services are facing stiff competition from wireless providers. Cell towers, now equipped with broadband capabilities, offer comparable speeds to wired connections, often at slightly higher prices.</description></item><item><title>Aktino Sends 90 Mbps Down Copper Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</guid><description>Advancements in technology are challenging the belief that fiber optic cable is necessary for transmitting DS3 or Carrier Ethernet beyond local networks. Aktino, a company based in California, has developed carrier equipment that enhances the performance of traditional unshielded twisted pair copper loops. This technology enables the delivery of DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) or over 90 Mbps of Carrier Ethernet bandwidth over a CSA (Carrier Serving Area) spanning 12,000 feet. Consequently, numerous businesses and cell tower locations, previously limited in terms of connectivity, can now access high bandwidth connections.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals.</description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1.</description></item><item><title>Replace T1 Line With 10 Mbps Fiber at Same Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</guid><description>Are telecommunications companies pushing you to replace your outdated T1 line? See this as a positive change! You might be able to upgrade from a 1.5 Mbps T1 line to a 10 Mbps fiber optic service for about the same price. Moreover, fiber optic allows for easy bandwidth increases as your needs grow.
What&amp;rsquo;s Happening to Traditional Phone Lines?
Bell Labs created T1 lines as the first digital telecommunications service to carry multiple phone calls.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth is Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Business bandwidth solutions are significantly more expensive than residential options like DSL or Cable. While this is partly due to their guaranteed reliability and dedicated lines, another factor is the complex infrastructure involved. Providing business-grade services often requires collaboration between a long-haul carrier and the local phone company for the final connection.
Despite recent price drops in dedicated T1 connections, high-bandwidth services remain costly, potentially hindering smaller companies needing to transmit large amounts of data.</description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time.</description></item><item><title>MAN and MEN - Metropolitan Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are the solution for expanding local networks across different locations within a city. Unlike confined on-site wiring, MANs tackle the challenge of connecting across larger distances.
Traditionally, businesses leased dedicated lines like T1 or DS3 from telecom companies to link their offices. However, this method proved costly and demanded self-management. MANs offer a practical alternative by providing shared fiber optic infrastructure, leading to cost savings and scalability for businesses.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades.</description></item><item><title>Are Your Pipes Fat Enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</guid><description>Higher resolution data demands more bandwidth, and WAN connections can become bottlenecks. Imagine a kink in a garden hose - the data is the water, and bandwidth is the pressure. Just as a kink restricts water flow, limited bandwidth slows data transfer, even with efficient network engineering. A larger pipe is needed for faster flow, just as a fatter data pipe is necessary for faster data transfer.
The increasing size and resolution of electronic business data necessitate these &amp;ldquo;fatter pipes.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic.</description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment.</description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</guid><description>Global telecommunication companies are updating their networks from circuit-based to packet-based systems. With the growth of internet-based networks, Ethernet WAN services have become more accessible and affordable. However, businesses often still rely on older technologies like T1, DS3, or SONET for connecting to these services and cloud networks.
While these older technologies are reliable and getting cheaper, using Ethernet for the initial connection, known as the &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; offers several benefits.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Got a Bandwidth Jones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no limit to how much bandwidth we need, similar to how we always desire more money, health, or chocolate. As we gain more bandwidth, we discover new ways to utilize it. The most sought-after types are wireless, offering flexibility, and fiber optic, providing high capacity. Property owners who provide both to their business tenants might find their properties more appealing than those offering health, wealth, or even delicious chocolate.</description></item><item><title>WiMAX 2 Will Challenge Fiber For Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</guid><description>The idea that copper and wireless technologies are outdated in terms of bandwidth is circulating. While copper has found new life as a last-mile solution for Metro Ethernet services, and wireless stands out for its unmatched mobility, a new wireless technology is emerging that might surpass even fiber optic speeds.
It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to think that wireless could outpace fiber in terms of bandwidth.
While not all fiber optic services offer top speeds of 10 GigE, with many customers receiving 50 to 100 Mbps, especially in the case of Fiber To The Home (FTTH), the prospect of achieving 100 to 300 Mbps wirelessly anywhere in a city is enticing.</description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?</description></item><item><title>Fiber - Dark, Lit and Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve decided that a fiber optic connection is no longer optional for your business; it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for productivity. The next step is determining which type of fiber to get. You might be surprised to learn there&amp;rsquo;s more than one option.
One Strand, Multiple Options
The foundation of all fiber optic connections is the transmission of information through modulated light waves within a glass strand. The fiber cable entering your building will appear the same regardless of the type.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Beefs Up Last Mile Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</guid><description>The main obstacle for companies aiming to boost their WAN (Wide Area Network) bandwidth is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; access problem. Although network bandwidth has become more affordable and easier to access, the final connection between a business and the carrier&amp;rsquo;s network often poses a significant challenge.
Think of it this way: a superhighway might be close to your company, but if the only route to your facility is a rough, narrow road, transportation will be slow and limited.</description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option.</description></item><item><title>Maxed Out On Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your business pushing the limits of its WAN bandwidth? Are you facing network congestion during peak hours? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are solutions to improve your situation.
Start by evaluating your network efficiency. Are you using quality of service management, or are you simply hoping for the best? Prioritizing voice packets can resolve issues with VoIP calls without impacting other processes.
Consider the timing of bandwidth-heavy tasks. Running backups to remote sites during peak hours can hinder employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth Gets Incrementally Finer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet service has been very beneficial for businesses of all sizes. It not only keeps LAN-WAN-LAN connections using the Ethernet protocol, but lease prices are also typically much lower per Mbps than older services like T-Carrier and SONET. But wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have the ideal line speed without settling for a service that&amp;rsquo;s too small or paying too much for unnecessary bandwidth?
Fortunately, XO Communications, a leading Metro Ethernet WAN service provider, now offers a wide range of bandwidth options for businesses with on-net fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient.</description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof.</description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages.</description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs SONET Throw Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SONET and Carrier Ethernet, two contenders for the top spot in high-speed business bandwidth.
SONET, or Synchronous Optical NETwork, is a fiber optic transmission system using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). Primarily used by telephone companies to boost their digital trunk capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s known for its redundant data rings over fiber optic cables, which create an automatic failover mechanism in case of a network disruption. While perfect for carrier-grade digitized phone calls, SONET can also handle packetized data including voice, video, and standard T1 or T3 lines.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?</description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably.</description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond.</description></item><item><title>GigaMAN and Gigabit Ethernet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigaman-and-gigabit-ethernet-services/</guid><description>Organizations in need of truly fast wide area network connections should consider gigabit Ethernet services like GigaMAN. These high-bandwidth circuits are now more affordable than ever.
Ethernet WAN services are a newer option for businesses and organizations, offering end-to-end Ethernet protocol signal maintenance. This eliminates the need for protocol conversion between a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN and traditional TDM telco circuits.
Ethernet speeds range from 10 Mbps (standard) to 100 Mbps (Fast Ethernet) and 1000 Mbps (Gigabit Ethernet).</description></item><item><title>How To Find Better Metro E Service Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) services are widely available and offer a practical solution for businesses operating within a metropolitan area to connect their various locations. However, securing the most cost-effective Metro E services requires careful consideration.
Metro Ethernet is a type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) designed to meet the local connectivity needs of businesses. Unlike traditional wide-area networks, MANs focus on providing high-speed connections within a specific city or region.</description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business.</description></item><item><title>TW Telecom's Extensive Service Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</guid><description>tw telecom is a full-service communications provider with a privately owned, nationwide fiber optic network. They provide service in 75 major markets and over 8,800 commercial buildings. Their network spans more than 26,000 route miles and features a 10 Gbps IP backbone. They offer a wide array of services, from affordable T1 lines to high-speed Carrier Ethernet services ranging from 2 Mbps to 10 Gbps.
You might recognize the name tw telecom from its previous iterations.</description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation.</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.0 Fiberizes Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Cable companies have been envious of Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS fiber optic service because it surpasses the broadband capabilities of coaxial cable. However, a new upgrade to the DOCSIS cable broadband standard might change that. This upgrade boosts digital download speeds to rival those of fiber optic connections, all without needing a fiber optic line to the home.
DOCSIS, which stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification, is the standard for cable modems.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Fiber Optic WAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</guid><description>As your company grows, you might find that your internet connection, cloud services, and connections between offices are slowing down. It might be time to upgrade your bandwidth before things get sluggish. But what should you get? More of what you already have or something new?
Outdated Connections Are Holding You Back When your business was starting out, networking was mostly about connecting computers and printers in the same office, with a basic connection to the outside world.</description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country.</description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 22:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</guid><description>For a long time, the idea of &amp;ldquo;rural broadband&amp;rdquo; seemed contradictory. While cities enjoyed a variety of high-speed internet options, from DSL and cable to fiber optic connections, rural areas remained stuck with slow dial-up or satellite internet. Although high-speed business lines have become more affordable, fiber optic cables in rural areas were deemed too expensive. However, an organization in Vermont is challenging this assumption.
ValleyFiber, led by Dr. Timothy Nulty, is bringing fiber optic broadband to rural homes and businesses in Vermont&amp;rsquo;s Upper Valley.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive.</description></item><item><title>Metro and Long Haul Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies with multiple locations and many employees may find that standard internet and private lines are insufficient for their needs. At a certain point, having complete control over your network becomes desirable, allowing you to establish performance benchmarks and implement upgrades as needed.
This sounds great, but how can you maintain the same level of control over a network that extends beyond your physical premises? Should you become your own network provider and install fiber optic cable to all your locations?</description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs.</description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Will Light Your Building</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</guid><description>Ethernet has become the preferred option for WAN (Wide Area Networking), moving beyond its established role in LAN networks. It makes sense to extend your LAN using the same standards both internally and for connecting to remote locations or the internet.
A key advantage is cost-effectiveness as bandwidth needs grow. While a 1.54 Mbps T1 line might cost around $450 per month ($292.20 per Mbps), a 45 Mbps DS3 connection could cost $5,000 per month ($111.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Speed Challenged By EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</guid><description>When a company needs more bandwidth than its T1 lines can provide, the typical upgrade has been to DS3. However, DS3 is usually delivered through fiber optic SONET connections, which can be costly to install unless a building is already equipped for fiber optic services. A new service called EoC offers a potential solution by providing DS3 speeds over existing copper telephone wiring.
EoC stands for Ethernet over Copper. It delivers high bandwidth services, up to DS3 levels of 45 Mbps, without needing fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Wireline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 23:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</guid><description>In the world of telecommunications, &amp;ldquo;wireline&amp;rdquo; traditionally refers to connections made through copper wires, while &amp;ldquo;wireless&amp;rdquo; implies no physical connections. However, &amp;ldquo;fiber optic&amp;rdquo; technology exists as a distinct category, utilizing physical cables but transmitting data through light rather than electricity. This distinction makes fiber optics a promising successor to the traditional copper wire infrastructure.
Several factors contribute to fiber optic cable&amp;rsquo;s potential to replace copper wire. Interestingly, their structures share similarities.</description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations.</description></item><item><title>The Ethernet Next Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</guid><description>Feeling constrained by your internet speed? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While your business might be struggling with a slow T1 line, your competitors may have a secret weapon: a new, affordable broadband service called Carrier Ethernet.
This service, rapidly being deployed across the nation, is an extension of the familiar Ethernet standard used in local area networks (LANs). Instead of converting data to different protocols for external connections, businesses can now use Ethernet for seamless, high-speed access to the internet and connections with other facilities.</description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades.</description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband.</description></item><item><title>Fiber WAN is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that your business needs the speed of fiber optic WAN service to ensure cloud-based applications are responsive and your team stays productive. However, you may have struggled to find this service in the past. It&amp;rsquo;s time to try again.
Why Is Fiber More Accessible Now?
Fiber optic used to be a rare and costly option limited to large corporations. You had to rely on the telephone company and hope they serviced your area.</description></item></channel></rss>