<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Membership on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/membership/</link><description>Recent content in Membership on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/membership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival.</description></item><item><title>Ascott Star Rewards is marking its second anniversary with special promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 20:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</guid><description>Ascott Star Rewards (ASR), the loyalty program of The Ascott Limited, is marking its second anniversary with a &amp;ldquo;Celebrate The Little Joys&amp;rdquo; campaign. This campaign offers double bonus points and complimentary tier upgrades to show appreciation and reward its members.
Since its 2019 launch, ASR has experienced over 400% membership growth. ASR members are responsible for roughly 90% of Ascott’s direct online bookings, and over 60% are repeat guests. Compared to non-members, ASR members spend 36% more with Ascott.</description></item></channel></rss>