<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access to Benefits on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-benefits/</link><description>Recent content in Access to Benefits on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-benefits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts.</description></item><item><title>Who should have control over the 'emergency brake' on benefits for EU citizens: the Commission or the Council?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
During the UK&amp;rsquo;s negotiations to leave the European Union, a key point of contention arose: the process for enacting an &amp;ldquo;emergency brake&amp;rdquo; to restrict EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to in-work benefits. Should a Member State have the authority to implement this measure independently, perhaps with a requirement to inform the Commission and Council? Or should it be required to submit a request, leaving the decision of authorization to the Commission and/or Council?</description></item><item><title>Is CJEU case law on EU citizenship normatively consistent? Unlikely! - An answer to Davies' 'Has the Court evolved, or have the cases?'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 02:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</guid><description>Alexander Hoogenboom, PhD, MSc. LL.M. Senior Policy Officer at the Dutch Healthcare Authority and associate researcher at the Institute for Transnational and Euregional cross border cooperation and Mobility, Faculty of law, Maastricht University. The opinions presented in this paper are solely those of the author.
Introduction
Some have interpreted recent Court of Justice rulings on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits as a restrictive shift compared to earlier decisions, possibly influenced by rising populism.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening and weakening the legal standing of individuals granted subsidiary protection under European Union law – the ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union in the case of Alo and Osso.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</guid><description>Dr. Louise Halleskov Storgaard, Assistant Professor, Aarhus University
Can a country that offers subsidiary protection (a form of protection similar to refugee status) restrict the movement of those beneficiaries within its borders if they receive social security benefits? This is the central question addressed by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Alo and Osso case on March 1, 2015. The CJEU’s answer is notable, innovative, and potentially contentious as it reinforces the influence of the Geneva Convention on subsidiary protection standards but also raises questions about the applicable non-discrimination standard.</description></item><item><title>Disregard the children! CJEU supports automatic exclusions from family benefits in Case C-308/14 Commission v UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</guid><description>Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School The Court of Justice is increasingly distancing itself from the social welfare systems of Member States. Although the Court once suggested that citizenship is paramount and forms the basis for financial solidarity, guaranteeing some support from a host state for EU citizens facing temporary hardship, this stance is changing.
With the Court moving away from the concept of citizenship, the idea of a reasonable burden may be disappearing.</description></item></channel></rss>