<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PSTN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pstn/</link><description>Recent content in PSTN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pstn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Telephone Systems Hosted VoIP Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes have various choices for their telephone systems. Small businesses can buy systems from local stores, while medium-sized businesses often work with contractors for key telephone systems or small PBXs. Larger companies may have internal teams that handle complex telephone systems. Nowadays, hosted VoIP is a cost-effective option for companies of all sizes.
How can one solution meet the needs of different-sized businesses affordably? It&amp;rsquo;s not a one-size-fits-all solution but a scalable technology adaptable to different demands—hosted VoIP, also known as hosted PBX or cloud telephone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Phone Service Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes might be considering upgrading their phone systems but are unsure of the best approach. Should they stick with their existing Key Telephone or PBX system and upgrade it, or is it time to transition to VoIP? What many businesses may not realize is the wide range of options that VoIP solutions offer.
The key difference between VoIP and traditional phone systems lies in its network-based approach. While even a single-line phone or cell phone operates on a network, known as the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), this network has limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over TDM</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 23:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</guid><description>You might be familiar with Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber, but have you encountered Ethernet over TDM? It&amp;rsquo;s worth understanding this technology and its potential benefits.
](http://www.copperethernet.com/)
TDM, or Time Division Multiplexing, forms the foundation of T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. It became the standard for the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) during its transition from analog to digital in the mid-20th century and remains relevant due to its continued prevalence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circuit Switched vs Packet Switched Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Over the past few decades, two primary network technologies have been vying for dominance. The first is the traditional telephone system, which served us well throughout the industrial age. The second is the computer-based architecture that has driven the information age. You might recognize these as circuit switching and packet switching.
While both technologies will likely coexist for a while longer, we are at a turning point. From now on, packet switching will be the dominant force in every network, from copper lines to fiber optic cables to wireless connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Exchange - The Final Piece For VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</guid><description>The shift from circuit-switched to packet-switched telephone networks is undeniable. While large companies have adopted enterprise VoIP to enhance efficiency, cut expenses, and prepare for the future, small and medium businesses are considering SIP trunking for bundled high-quality telephone and broadband services. Consumers are switching to cable broadband-telephone packages or third-party VoIP options. However, the PSTN remains.
Currently, VoIP systems and services operate in isolation. On-net calls, meaning calls within the same service regardless of location, are often free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Voice Over MPLS The New PSTN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</guid><description>Packet-switched networks are undeniably replacing circuit-switched networks, so much so that the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) might be phased out by the FCC. This signals the potential end of the century-old telephone system, raising the question of what will replace it. VoIP is a strong contender, but not in its current form.
VoIP&amp;rsquo;s strengths lie in its established standards for coding, signaling, and its compatibility with Ethernet data networks. However, its widespread adoption is hampered by incompatible implementations, concerns from wireless carriers about network overload, and inconsistent voice quality on the internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Quality Call Termination With SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Prioritizing voice packets on a network ensures high-quality VoIP calls within an organization. However, connecting to the outside world poses a challenge due to the incompatibility between modern packet-switched networks and the traditional circuit-switched phone system. To bridge this gap, organizations can either manage the conversion internally or outsource it to a third-party provider through SIP trunking.
SIP trunking offers a potentially cost-effective solution by consolidating multiple phone lines into a single &amp;ldquo;trunk&amp;rdquo; line and utilizing the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for call switching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX For Features and Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</guid><description>Determining if it&amp;rsquo;s the right moment to transition your business phone system to a cloud-based solution is crucial, especially if your current system struggles with capacity, needs frequent fixes, or lacks vendor support. However, even if your current system functions adequately, you might be overlooking opportunities to enhance productivity and reduce communication expenses with modern hosted PBX solutions.
A prime illustration is AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s updated Cloud Hosted IP PBX, AirePBX version 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Voice over MPLS For High Quality Enterprise Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations are realizing the financial and operational benefits of MPLS networks. MPLS VPNs are emerging as the go-to solution for connecting multiple sites nationally and globally. But what about voice services?
Traditionally, voice and data are kept separate. Telephone systems rely on a proven infrastructure of switched circuit analog and digital trunking. Most PBX systems are designed to connect to standard copper-pair analog business lines or ISDN PRI digital trunks, which act as gateways to the global PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) connecting every phone on Earth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Save 50% With Unified Communications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</guid><description>As your company expands, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely seen a simultaneous increase in your telephone costs. While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this is simply due to having more employees making calls, the reality is that not all phone expenses are unavoidable.
Unified communications technology can help you significantly reduce unnecessary costs. This approach combines your voice, data, and video networks into a single, unified system, leading to cost savings for businesses of all sizes, even those with just one location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Launches SIP for Multi-Location Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</guid><description>XO Communications, a large telecommunications company, has introduced a new solution that allows businesses with numerous locations to take advantage of enterprise VoIP technology.
Connecting business locations to a phone service provider through SIP trunking is a well-established method for improving network performance and saving money. XO is building on this concept with a multi-site SIP trunking solution. Instead of requiring each location to connect to a remote service provider separately, branch offices, warehouses, and other locations can now use their existing Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect SIP phones back to a central IP-PBX system at the main office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Plain Old Telephone Service For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get a reliable phone service? Surprisingly, it might be POTS – Plain Old Telephone Service.
While the name might sound outdated, POTS offers dependable, high-quality phone service at an affordable price. Why is this the case?
POTS, technically known as analog telephone service over copper wiring, is a direct descendant of the original telephone system. This system, developed and refined over a century by companies like the Bell Telephone System, became incredibly efficient and standardized...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Exchange For Miami, Dallas and Los Angeles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet is emerging as a strong contender to replace the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), as evidenced by the increasing number of Ethernet Exchanges that facilitate traffic sharing among carriers. Telx, a prominent interconnection and colocation provider, recently expanded its Ethernet Exchange services to Miami, Dallas, and Los Angeles. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the significance of Ethernet Exchange and its impact on the future of international wide-area networking.
The PSTN&amp;rsquo;s global reach and interoperability have contributed to its longstanding success, enabling communication between any two phones worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>