<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Integration Manager on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integration-manager/</link><description>Recent content in Integration Manager on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:37:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integration-manager/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The SanScript Library could not be loaded, and Integration Manager is affected.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanscript-library-could-not-be-loaded-and-integration-manager-is-affected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanscript-library-could-not-be-loaded-and-integration-manager-is-affected/</guid><description>Towards the end of the previous month, a client reached out for help with their Dynamics GP year-end update. After resolving that, they described a separate Integration Manager problem that a previous consultant couldn&amp;rsquo;t fix, even after resorting to completely reinstalling the system. Intrigued, I decided to investigate further.
The client demonstrated that when running an integration on a specific machine, it would initially start but then fail with the error message &amp;ldquo;Unable to load SanScript Library.</description></item><item><title>Frustration with Integration Migration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frustration-with-integration-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frustration-with-integration-migration/</guid><description>Around a month ago, I was tasked with evaluating a client&amp;rsquo;s integrations as they prepared to upgrade from GP 8 to GP 10. Their system used four Integration Manager integrations to transfer employee, payroll, and invoice data from their operational system regularly.
My initial assessment of these integrations revealed relatively straightforward processes. They pulled data from a handful of SQL tables within a staging database housed on the GP SQL Server and used a few simple scripts to call stored procedures for data preparation before the IM import.</description></item><item><title>Where could my Integration Manager be hiding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-could-my-integration-manager-be-hiding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-could-my-integration-manager-be-hiding/</guid><description>A user encountering an issue in Microsoft Dynamics GP where the &amp;ldquo;Integration Manager&amp;rdquo; option under Tools &amp;gt; Integrate appears unresponsive, despite having proper security permissions and the application launching correctly from the Start menu, can resolve this problem with a simple fix.
The solution involves navigating to the Microsoft Dynamics GP program directory (typically located at C:\Program Files\Microsoft Dynamics\GP) and locating the &amp;ldquo;Dex.ini&amp;rdquo; file within the Data folder.
Open this file using Notepad and verify that the file paths specified for &amp;ldquo;IntegrationManagerExePath&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;IMWizard&amp;rdquo; are accurate, making any necessary corrections.</description></item></channel></rss>