<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CEO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ceo/</link><description>Recent content in CEO on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ceo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A study conducted by INSEAD has discovered that when shareholders vote on CEO accountability, it leads to higher company returns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:02:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</guid><description>A new study titled &amp;ldquo;Say Pays! Shareholder Voice and Firm Performance,&amp;rdquo; published in the Review of Finance, suggests that shareholder votes do improve CEO accountability and reduce unnecessary spending within corporations. The study&amp;rsquo;s author, Maria Guadalupe, an Associate Professor at INSEAD, found that previous research on the impact of &amp;ldquo;say-on-pay&amp;rdquo; policies was inconclusive, possibly due to focusing on periods after say-on-pay became law.
Guadalupe&amp;rsquo;s research examined 250 instances where shareholders of S&amp;amp;P 1500 companies proposed to adopt say-on-pay policies between 2006 and 2010, before such votes were mandatory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-insead-has-discovered-that-when-shareholders-vote-on-ceo-accountability-it-leads-to-higher-company-returns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CEOs anticipate a deceleration in economic growth in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</guid><description>Global CEOs are expressing unprecedented pessimism regarding the economic outlook for 2020, according to PwC&amp;rsquo;s 23rd Annual Global CEO Survey. 53% of CEOs anticipate a decline in economic growth, a significant increase from 29% in 2019 and a stark contrast to the mere 5% who held this view in 2018. This marks the highest level of pessimism since the survey began in 2012, with only 22% of CEOs predicting economic growth in 2020, down from 42% in 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various approaches to talent management in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: ECN.
Attracting and retaining skilled managers in Asia has become increasingly crucial for business leaders.
A recent survey by the Economist Corporate Network (ECN) of 550 member companies in Asia revealed that 95% of CEOs actively engage in talent management practices. However, their level and type of involvement differ significantly.
The report, Aligned for Success? Strategy, talent management and the role of the CEO in Asia, indicates that CEOs primarily focus on the strategic aspects of human capital, such as forecasting future workforce needs and organizational design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>