<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Instant on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/instant/</link><description>Recent content in Instant on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/instant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new Medium Roast Freeze-Dried instant coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect.
Cafédirect, a British beverage company, has introduced a new premium instant coffee in Singapore. This medium roast, freeze-dried coffee offers a convenient solution for those seeking a flavorful cup on the go, featuring a smooth, vibrant taste with hints of caramel.
Interestingly, a growing number of Singaporean coffee drinkers who typically prefer milk in their coffee are developing a taste for black coffee. This shift is attributed to Cafédirect&amp;rsquo;s master blender, who has crafted a unique blend using sweet and chocolatey Arabica beans from South America, well-rounded beans from Central America, and robust Robusta beans from East Africa (60%).</description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers.</description></item></channel></rss>