<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Epson on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/epson/</link><description>Recent content in Epson on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/epson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park.</description></item><item><title>The L805 photo printer from Epson features a six-colour ink tank system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The L805 ink tank photo printer.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing products, has released its L805 printer. This six-color ink tank photo printer offers wireless printing from mobile devices and boasts the lowest operating expenses on the market. Epson&amp;rsquo;s ink tank printers are unique in that they utilize large ink tanks instead of cartridges.
Building upon the previous L800 model, the L805 incorporates built-in wireless connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces new large format printers designed for small office use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-new-large-format-printers-designed-for-small-office-use/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 08:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-new-large-format-printers-designed-for-small-office-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The Epson SureColor SC-T3130.
Epson has introduced its new line of high-speed SureColor T-series large-format printers, aiming to capture a share of the entry-level and mid-range computer-aided design (CAD) plotter market.
These printers are well-suited for various sectors, including architecture, engineering, CAD, geographical information systems (GIS), education, corporations, and small businesses. Known for their compact size, these wireless plotters are offered in both desktop and floor-standing configurations, boasting a user-friendly design suitable for any office environment.</description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore is sponsoring limited edition prints for The Schooling Effect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-is-sponsoring-limited-edition-prints-for-the-schooling-effect/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. From left: Tan May Lin, Epson Singapore’s GM (Sales, Marketing &amp;amp; Customer Service Division) and Tay Kay Chin, one of the collaborators for the photo book, with one of the prints available for sale as part of the collaboration.
Epson Singapore, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, is supporting The Schooling Effect. This community project is inspired by the victory of Singaporean Olympian Joseph Schooling at the 2016 Olympic Games.</description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore has released the new Moverio Pro smart glasses with augmented reality capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</guid><description>Epson, a global provider of projection technology and visual communication tools, has introduced the Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset. This binocular headset offers an augmented reality experience for applications such as inspections, training, and remote field service support for intricate repairs and troubleshooting.
Source: Epson Singapore. The new
Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset.
Augmented reality smart glasses have the potential to boost worker efficiency across various sectors, including warehousing, logistics, field service, automotive, manufacturing, construction, and retail.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces an affordable WUXGA projector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-an-affordable-wuxga-projector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-an-affordable-wuxga-projector/</guid><description>Epson, a leading manufacturer of projectors, is introducing a new line of affordable Widescreen Ultra Extended Array (WUXGA) projectors. These projectors are designed for business use and offer high-resolution images that surpass Full HD video quality.
Siew Jin Kiat, General Manager of Epson Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s Visual Instruments Division, highlighted the significance of this release. For the first time, businesses can access Epson&amp;rsquo;s renowned high color and brightness projection at competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item><item><title>The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-C869R offers a cost-effective solution for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-workforce-pro-wf-c869r-offers-a-cost-effective-solution-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 12:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-workforce-pro-wf-c869r-offers-a-cost-effective-solution-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. The WF-C869R printer.
Epson recently introduced a new printer with a Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS) that offers both high speed and quality while significantly reducing costs. The WorkForce Pro WF-C869R boasts a high page yield and a low cost per page, which can lead to considerable savings for businesses compared to using laser printers.
The printer&amp;rsquo;s high-capacity ink packs come in two options: standard packs that yield up to 22,500 black and 22,000 color pages, and larger packs that yield up to 86,000 black and 84,000 color pages.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling.</description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore introduces high-brightness projectors designed for large venues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-introduces-high-brightness-projectors-designed-for-large-venues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 20:33:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-introduces-high-brightness-projectors-designed-for-large-venues/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. The white EB-G7000.
Epson Singapore recently introduced the EB-G7000 series, their newest high-brightness projectors designed for large venues. These projectors provide high-quality images with quiet operation, making them suitable for various settings like meeting rooms, lecture halls, and museums.
Featuring the latest 4K enhancements, the projectors produce brighter, more vivid images with up to 8,000 lumens of both color and white brightness. They offer three times the color brightness compared to similar single-chip projector models.</description></item><item><title>Epson's portable projectors are designed for on-the-go presentations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</guid><description>Source: Epson website. The EB-1780W.
Epson has introduced the EB-1700 series, its lightest line of 3LCD projectors yet. This series prioritizes portability without sacrificing image quality or connectivity options, making it ideal for business presentations on the go.
The projectors in the EB-1700 series weigh under 4 pounds and are less than 2 inches thick, making them easy to carry in a laptop bag. Grip lines on the sides add to their portability.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new business printer capable of printing up to 75,000 pages in a single run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</guid><description>Epson helps businesses reduce printing expenses with its Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS). RIPS utilizes high-capacity ink packs that hold significantly more ink than traditional cartridges. This system combines the convenience of cartridges with the high-volume output of ink tanks.
Source: Epson.
The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-R8591 is the first printer in Southeast Asia to offer this technology. Using a complete set of ink packs, the WF-R8591 can print approximately 75,000 pages* before replacements are needed.</description></item><item><title>Epson has launched three business inkjet printers that offer a range of connectivity options and high capacity features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WorkForce WF-2661.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has launched three new inkjet printers for businesses in Singapore. These models are designed for small offices and home offices.
The ultra-compact Epson WorkForce series is designed for small spaces and cost-effective printing. These printers include automatic document feeders (ADFs) and Epson Connect, enabling users to print directly from their mobile devices.
The new WorkForce series offers easy and flexible printing over Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore launches its flagship store on Shopee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-launches-its-flagship-store-on-shopee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-launches-its-flagship-store-on-shopee/</guid><description>Epson Singapore is expanding its online presence to adapt to evolving consumer shopping patterns. The company recently launched a flagship store on Shopee, a major e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia, following the 2018 launch of its flagship Lazada store.
Epson Singapore cites a study indicating that 37% of Singaporean consumers have increased their online shopping due to staying home during the COVID-19 pandemic. Furthermore, over 76% of those surveyed plan to maintain this behavior even after the pandemic stabilizes*.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new family of interactive projectors with 3LCD technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-family-of-interactive-projectors-with-3lcd-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-family-of-interactive-projectors-with-3lcd-technology/</guid><description>Source: Epson website; The EB-696Ui.
Epson recently released the EB-600 series*, a new line of 3LCD projectors with advanced features. These features include ultra short throw projection at resolutions exceeding full HD, PC-free interactivity, and the first-ever seamless dual-screen interactivity.
Designed for classrooms and businesses, the new EB-600 series projectors (EB-696Ui, EB-695Wi2, EB-685Wi, EB-685W3, and EB-680) provide a vibrant viewing experience.
The series boasts WUXGA resolution (1,920 x 1,200), surpassing full HD, and a heightened brightness of 3,800 lumens.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces the latest Moverio smart glasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the third generation of its Moverio smart glasses, designed for augmented reality applications. The Moverio BT-300 utilizes Epson&amp;rsquo;s innovative silicon-based OLED display technology, providing a truly transparent mobile augmented reality (AR) experience for both businesses and consumers.
Epson highlights the Moverio BT-300 as the lightest binocular see-through smart glasses available, boasting a weight reduction of over 20% compared to its predecessor, the Moverio BT-200. These glasses are powered by a quad-core Intel Atom X5 processor and run on Android 5.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean fashion designers are displaying their collections that have been digitally printed by Epson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. Display, Wai Yang.
Epson, a printing technology company, partnered with designers based in Singapore for FashionisTech, a showcase at the recent FUZE Fashion Technology 2017 event in Singapore. The designers used Epson&amp;rsquo;s digital printing technology to create their collections.
Organized by Textile and Fashion Federation (TAFF), the summit was the first of its kind in Singapore. It promoted advancements in materials and highlighted creative uses of technology by Singaporean fashion brands.</description></item><item><title>Haenyeo Singapore visually captures the story of Jeju's female divers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. HAENYO SINGAPORE will be exhibited in Singapore until November 23rd.
Jose Jeuland, a French photographer based in Singapore, is presenting his debut photography exhibition. This exhibition, hosted at The Fullerton Hotel in Singapore, focuses on haenyo (해녀) - female divers from Jeju Island in South Korea. Epson Singapore, the official print sponsor for the exhibition, provided prints produced on one of their commercial and industrial photographic production printers.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new mobile POS printer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 22:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</guid><description>Epson, a company known for its printing and digital imaging solutions, has introduced the TM-m30 point of sale (POS) printer. Created specifically for tablet-based systems, the TM-m30 stands out as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most compact desktop receipt printers, making it a perfect fit for retail and hospitality businesses aiming to transition to a POS system managed by smart devices.
Source: Epson Singapore. The Epson TM-m30 POS printer.
The TM-m30 is engineered for swift and effortless setup on iOS, Android, and Windows mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI.</description></item></channel></rss>