<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Withdrawal Agreement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/withdrawal-agreement/</link><description>Recent content in Withdrawal Agreement on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/withdrawal-agreement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The resolution of disputes and the role of the ECJ in the proposed withdrawal agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A key point of contention in post-Brexit EU/UK relations is the degree to which the UK remains bound to the EU Court of Justice (ECJ). This issue arises first in the withdrawal agreement being negotiated, a draft of which was recently proposed by the EU Commission. While it will eventually affect the future relationship between the two, this post focuses on the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition.</description></item><item><title>'Although you have children together, your marriage is not genuine': Marriages of convenience, UK courts, and EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Aleksandra Jolkina, PhD in Law, Queen Mary University of London
Over the last twenty years, UK authorities have become increasingly wary of marriages within the UK between mobile EU citizens and third-country nationals (TCNs) with uncertain or irregular residence status. In the current climate of Euroscepticism, such marriages are often criticized as &amp;ldquo;marriages of convenience,&amp;rdquo; intended to circumvent British immigration laws. This piece examines how UK courts interpret the concept of marriages of convenience, the potential implications for families of EU citizens residing in the UK, and the anticipated changes after Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Is this the beginning of the end for citizens' rights in the Brexit 'Sufficient Progress' deal?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent joint report on Brexit negotiations, along with accompanying documents, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of discussions. This phase will center around a transition period and the framework for the future relationship between the UK and the EU.
Although a political rather than legal document, this report holds significant practical relevance for the withdrawal agreement. It outlines agreed-upon details concerning citizens&amp;rsquo; rights, the Irish border, the financial settlement, and concluding rules.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 4 of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement focuses on the rights of citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</guid><description>This blog post examines the rights of UK and EU citizens after Brexit, focusing on the revised withdrawal agreement. This agreement aims to protect the rights of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 who moved before the transition period ended (end of 2020, possibly extendable).
The agreement safeguards these individuals better than a &amp;ldquo;no deal&amp;rdquo; scenario, where national law would primarily apply. However, it offers less protection than continued EU membership.</description></item><item><title>The Day the Unicorns Cried: Understanding Phase 1 of the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
The recent joint report on the progress of Brexit negotiations, along with a related paper from the Commission, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of negotiations. Based on this report, the EU27 have agreed that &amp;ldquo;sufficient progress&amp;rdquo; has been made to move forward. This next phase will focus on a transition period and, potentially starting in March 2018, the framework for the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU.</description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement: Analysis 1 Overview</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</guid><description>Analysis of the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement - October 2019 Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction While the approval of the Brexit withdrawal agreement is uncertain at present, the UK Parliament&amp;rsquo;s upcoming vote necessitates an updated analysis of the revised agreement. This updated version includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship.
This post aims to provide a simplified explanation of the agreement for non-lawyers, outlining its structure and key content.</description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement Analysis 2: Transition Period</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Now that a revised Brexit withdrawal agreement is available, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to revisit my prior analyses of the initial agreement. This post, updating my spring 2018 analysis, focuses on the transition period outlined in the agreement. (The revised agreement includes changes to the Irish border protocol and the political declaration on the future relationship.) This post will provide context for the transition period and then break down the text.</description></item><item><title>Part 1 of the European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement text explores the impact on health, focusing on patients and reciprocal healthcare.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Law, University of Sheffield
This article provides an initial examination of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s draft Withdrawal Agreement and its effects on health-related issues, particularly concerning individuals.
The focus here is on patient rights, specifically reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the remaining 27 EU members post-Brexit. Two significant issues are explored:
The future of UK pensioners residing in or planning to retire in other EU countries.</description></item><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration.</description></item><item><title>In what way can the courts enforce Part Two of the Withdrawal Agreement regarding citizens' rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</guid><description>Ensuring the Enforceability of EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Rights in the UK Post-Brexit Professor Tamara Hervey, Natalia Miernik and James C Murphy (UG students), University of Sheffield
Acknowledgement is given to the ESRC for its support of Health Governance after Brexit and UK in a Changing Europe.
1. Introduction
Approximately 3.6 million EU citizens and their families reside in the UK. A significant number, estimated to be over 185,000, contribute to the health and social care sector.</description></item><item><title>Brexit: You have the option to change your mind. The CJEU ruling in Wightman allows for a U-turn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The recent definitive ruling by the Full Court concerning the Wightman case reaffirms the UK&amp;rsquo;s ability to independently revoke its withdrawal notification from the EU under the most flexible terms. This judgment aligns with the non-binding opinion given the previous week by an Advocate-General.
The judgment
The Court dismissed the UK government&amp;rsquo;s claim of the case being hypothetical, emphasizing the imminent involvement of some litigants (who are MPs) in voting on the proposed withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of the revised Withdrawal Agreement: Is Empire 2.0 making a comeback?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</guid><description>Commentary on the Draft Withdrawal Agreement - Version of February 21, 2018 This post provides an updated analysis of the draft Brexit withdrawal agreement, taking into account the UK&amp;rsquo;s response to the EU Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposed text.
The withdrawal agreement, if successfully negotiated, will be the key legal framework for Brexit. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember this agreement will be separate from future treaties governing the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU.</description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA).</description></item><item><title>The Windsor Framework Relaunch receives general acclaim with little said.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: en:User:Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
The opportunity to finalize the Windsor Framework and ensure its acceptance was limited. The challenging task of establishing trade rules for goods moving between Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK had been largely settled almost a year prior. The objective was to minimize trade friction within the UK while upholding the EU Single Market.</description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU.</description></item><item><title>Violating International Law on a Broad Scale: The Northern Ireland Protocol Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Reader in Public Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
In 2020, Brandon Lewis acknowledged that the UK&amp;rsquo;s Internal Market Bill would contravene the Withdrawal Agreement, albeit in a limited capacity. However, regarding the recent Northern Ireland Protocol Bill, Lewis insists that it will not violate international law. This assertion is debatable, as the Bill&amp;rsquo;s implications are vast.
The Protocol and Brexit
The UK government argues that the Protocol lacks cross-community support within Northern Ireland and cannot continue as is.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: The Impact of the Revised European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement on Health - Patients and Reciprocal Healthcare (Updated as of March 18, 2018)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, holding the Jean Monnet Chair in EU Law at the University of Sheffield, has reviewed the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s revised draft legal text on the Withdrawal Agreement (WA) as of March 15, 2018. Her analysis focuses on how the revised text impacts reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the EU-27 post-Brexit, particularly for UK pensioners residing in other EU countries and the use of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) for emergency care.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing and Annotating the Brexit Transition Period: Is it a Bridge Leading to Nowhere?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent weeks have seen significant progress in the Brexit negotiations. The EU27 and the UK reached an agreement on a substantial portion of the withdrawal agreement, including a transition period from March 2019 to the end of 2020, a key concern for the UK. This agreement follows earlier drafts and sets the stage for defining the future relationship between the UK and the EU, to be formalized in separate treaties.</description></item><item><title>New developments in EU case law regarding extradition to non-EU countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A recent European Court of Justice (ECJ) decision in the Pisciotti case concerning the extradition of citizens from one EU Member State to a non-EU country (in this instance, the USA) provides further legal precedent in this domain and carries potential implications for Brexit. This ruling expands on the September 2016 Petruhhin judgment, which dealt with extraditing citizens from one EU Member State to Russia.</description></item><item><title>The Dillon Judgment, Exemption of Laws, and Article 2 of the Northern Ireland Protocol/Windsor Framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD researcher, Queens University Belfast, and Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Aaronward, via Wikicommons media
In a landmark decision, a UK court has disapplied portions of a UK Act of Parliament for the first time since Brexit due to conflicts with the Withdrawal Agreement, specifically highlighting the ongoing connection between UK and EU legal systems. This unexpected development, though previously argued for, underscores the UK government&amp;rsquo;s consistent underestimation of Article 2&amp;rsquo;s impact on rights-related cases.</description></item><item><title>Legal Analysis of the Strasbourg Agreement dated March 11, 2019: A Summary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-the-strasbourg-agreement-dated-march-11-2019-a-summary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 09:53:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-the-strasbourg-agreement-dated-march-11-2019-a-summary/</guid><description>Professor Michael Dougan&amp;rsquo;s Analysis of the March 2019 Brexit Amendments Professor Michael Dougan, University of Liverpool, 12 March 2019
Summary: The legal classification of the “Instrument relating to the Withdrawal Agreement” and the “Joint Statement supplementing the Political Declaration” is insignificant. The crucial factor is whether these new elements meaningfully alter the withdrawal agreement endorsed in November 2018, which awaits Commons approval.
The Instrument primarily reiterates existing Withdrawal Agreement provisions without significant additions or changes.</description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period.</description></item><item><title>Resolving conflicts and the agreement for the UK's exit from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A key point of contention in the Brexit withdrawal agreement is how disputes will be settled. Specifically, there&amp;rsquo;s debate about whether the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) maintains authority over the UK. This post provides an overview of this issue and a detailed analysis of the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s provisions concerning dispute resolution and the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s role.
This post is the third in a series examining the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>Simply Refuse? The latest 'Stormont Brake' within the Windsor Framework (part 2 of the framework analysis)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</guid><description>The Stormont Brake: A Closer Look at its Potential Impact Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons Introduction
This analysis delves into the &amp;lsquo;Stormont Brake&amp;rsquo;, a new mechanism within the Windsor Framework designed to address concerns about how EU law applies to Northern Ireland. This analysis explores the text and interpretation of this &amp;lsquo;brake&amp;rsquo; on changes to EU law under the protocol. While it might never be used, understanding the mechanics of the Stormont Brake is crucial to grasp its potential implications.</description></item><item><title>A Personal Perspective on Citizens' Rights Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
I seldom share personal experiences on this blog or elsewhere. However, I believe it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to approach immigration from a personal angle, not just as an abstract concept. While economic data is valuable for understanding the economic impact, and legal analysis is vital for activists and negotiators, it&amp;rsquo;s equally important to remember that migrants are individuals and families whose lives are impacted by immigration policy changes.</description></item><item><title>Allister: the impact of the EU Withdrawal Act</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-the-impact-of-the-eu-withdrawal-act/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 18:32:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-the-impact-of-the-eu-withdrawal-act/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, a PhD researcher at Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, explores the legal implications of Brexit on Northern Ireland, particularly focusing on the impact of the EU Withdrawal Act 2018 and the subsequent amendments made by the EU Withdrawal Agreement Act 2020. He argues that the 2020 Act didn&amp;rsquo;t simply maintain the legal status quo as one might expect, but instead partially reversed the intended purpose of the 2018 Act.
This reversal is most evident in Section 7A of the 2018 Act, which incorporates the EU Withdrawal Agreement (including the Northern Ireland Protocol) into UK law.</description></item><item><title>Allister Round 2: Exploring the depths of UK constitutional law in the Mariana Trench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD student, Queen’s University Belfast School of Law
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikicommons
Introduction
It&amp;rsquo;s a common observation in UK constitutional law that complex issues rarely have simple solutions. Instead, they often result in multiple, overlapping interpretations. This is certainly the case with the recent Allister and others v Prime Minister and others [2022] NICA 15 ruling from the Northern Ireland Court of Appeal (NICA). It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this case is headed to the UK Supreme Court on appeal, ensuring further analysis and discussion.</description></item><item><title>Putting an end to uncertainty: advocating for the protection of the rights of EU27 and UK citizens post-Brexit - including a suggested draft.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent draft of the Brexit withdrawal agreement might encounter obstacles and potentially fail to gain approval due to conflicting viewpoints on the Irish border or other matters. Should this occur, the question arises: what will happen to the provisions concerning EU27 citizens residing in the UK, and UK citizens residing in the EU27, prior to Brexit?
To provide maximum assurance regarding their immigration status, there is a compelling rationale for separating these provisions from the main withdrawal agreement and ratifying them under a distinct agreement.</description></item><item><title>Preventing the UK from facing another Brexit crisis: Prolonging the Transition Period beyond 1 July 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</guid><description>René Repasi, Associate Professor of EU Law at Erasmus University Rotterdam, Netherlands
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the EU on January 31st, 2020, marked the completion of the initial &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo; phase, focused on resolving the implications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s past membership. This followed the UK general election, which saw Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Conservative Party secure a significant majority in the House of Commons, leading to the swift ratification of the Withdrawal Agreement (WA).</description></item><item><title>A Protocol Proposal for Brexit and the Rights of EU27 Citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</guid><description>Stijn Smismans, Professor of Law, School of Law and Politics, Director of the Centre for European Law and Governance, Cardiff University
While a draft Withdrawal Agreement (WA) between the EU and UK, partially agreed upon in March 2018, aims to address the post-Brexit status of EU27 citizens in the UK and British citizens in the EU, concerns remain about the process of securing residency rights. Although the EU has made efforts to safeguard these rights, the focus has been on the scope rather than the process of obtaining them.</description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the Northern Ireland Protocol in question? Examination of the High Court ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</guid><description>Sarah Kay, human rights lawyer
Brexit has negatively impacted Northern Ireland, as was anticipated. Five years after the Brexit referendum, the High Court in Belfast issued a significant political decision regarding a legal challenge to the Northern Ireland Protocol. This challenge mirrors the Miller 1 case concerning Brexit&amp;rsquo;s constitutionality. Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s fragile political landscape, exacerbated by Brexit, has exposed existing systemic issues.
The legal challenge was brought forward by two main parties: Clifford Peeples, who opposed the Irish Sea border, and unionist members, including former First Minister Arlene Foster, who argued that the Protocol weakens Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s ties with Great Britain.</description></item><item><title>An Unassuming Suggestion: Preventing a Standstill on the Irish Border in the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Brexit withdrawal agreement negotiations are in danger of collapsing due to disagreements on managing the Irish border. The UK government&amp;rsquo;s lack of concrete proposals for customs away from the border is concerning. Additionally, the UK Foreign Secretary&amp;rsquo;s inability to differentiate between a simple congestion charge and the complexities of border control is disappointing.
In anticipation of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s upcoming proposals, I have drafted a text (Annex 1) addressing the Irish border in the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>Gazing into the Void: The Future of Citizens' Rights in the Event of a No Deal Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 03:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
After resisting guarantees for EU27 citizens&amp;rsquo; rights in the UK for over two years, the UK government has finally issued a plan outlining the treatment of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 in a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit scenario. This comes as the UK Parliament prepares to vote on the withdrawal agreement and after the European Commission published its own position on this matter.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 3 of the updated Brexit Withdrawal Agreement focuses on dispute resolution.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
This post examines the dispute settlement mechanisms outlined in the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement, specifically addressing the role of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). It is part of a series analyzing the updated agreement, which includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship. Previous posts have provided an overview of the agreement and examined the transition period.</description></item><item><title>It's finally here - the CJEU has confirmed that UK citizens have officially lost their EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has affirmed that UK citizens lost EU citizenship due to Brexit, as per a recent judgment. This aligns with the earlier Advocate-General’s opinion. While other similar cases exist, the CJEU is unlikely to deviate from this decision.
This judgment is notable for its dismissal of arguments advocating for the retention of EU citizenship for British citizens, marking a significant shift.</description></item><item><title>Perhaps we are drawn to the suffering: The conclusion of the legal battle over the Northern Ireland Protocol.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Law Professor, University of Newcastle
Photo credit: ChrisVTG photography, via Wikicommons media
In October 2019, the UK government, led by Boris Johnson, reached a Withdrawal Agreement with the EU. This agreement encompassed a Northern Ireland Protocol iteration based on closely aligned rules governing goods between Northern Ireland and the EU. Notably, no comparable provisions addressed goods regulations for Great Britain. In January 2020, Westminster passed legislation to enact this agreement.</description></item><item><title>How can the issue of Suella be resolved? Exploring the legal implications of breaching and terminating the withdrawal agreement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent news suggests the UK may plan to violate the Brexit withdrawal agreement, with new Attorney-General Suella Braverman potentially seeking legal justification. This makes examining the repercussions of such a breach crucial. While the dispute resolution mechanisms within the agreement and the UK&amp;rsquo;s Withdrawal Agreement Act have been analyzed separately, this piece aims to provide a comprehensive overview, encompassing international law perspectives. This blog post summarizes the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution clauses and the international law principles concerning treaty termination, exploring their interplay.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of an Advocate-General's opinion reveals that Brexit will result in the end of EU citizenship for UK nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 11:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The question of whether British citizens retained their EU citizenship after Brexit is disputed. While the EU and UK governments assert that they did not, some British individuals disagree.
This issue has been raised before EU courts through various avenues. Three cases directly appealed to the EU General Court, contesting the EU Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to finalize the withdrawal agreement. These appeals argued that the agreement improperly revoked their EU citizenship.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision.</description></item></channel></rss>