<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Drive on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/drive/</link><description>Recent content in Drive on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/drive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): Removing the Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Note: This post documents an outdated method. There&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way to remove the drive that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve lifting the Pre-Amplifier board or disconnecting the solenoid linkage. See my later post for the updated procedure.
Following advice from &amp;lsquo;chartz&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;sonavor&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org (link to thread), I began replacing the belts in my Beocord 5000 (4716), which had become loose and stretched over time.
The first step is removing the drive mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces hard disk drives with high speed and high capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</guid><description>Sony Introduces Speedy and Durable Portable Hard Drives Boasting data transfer speeds up to 138MBps for both reading and writing, Sony&amp;rsquo;s latest portable hard disk drives (HDDs) promise both performance and resilience. Built to withstand the bumps of everyday use, these drives are shock-resistant, splash-resistant (IPX4 rating), and dust-resistant (IP5X rating). They can even tolerate drops from up to 6.5 feet thanks to their robust rubber damper design.
Source: Sony. The new 2TB drive.</description></item><item><title>Google Drive prices have been significantly reduced by Google</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 23:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</guid><description>A blog post published on March 13 revealed that Google significantly reduced prices for cloud storage. The monthly fees have been adjusted to US$1.99 for 100GB (previously US$4.99), US$9.99 for 1TB (previously US$49.99), and US$99.99 for 10TB, with the option to purchase additional terabytes as required.
A 15 GB plan remains free of charge. This storage space can be utilized across Drive, Gmail, and Google+ Photos.
Source: Google
Existing paying users will be automatically transitioned to the corresponding updated plan without incurring additional costs.</description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces complimentary live services for 2017 Garmin Drive models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</guid><description>Garmin International has refreshed its Garmin Drive portable navigation device (PND) lineup with free live services* for the most up-to-date content and driver alerts to improve safety. These upgrades to the Garmin Drive, Garmin DriveSmart, Garmin DriveAssist, and Garmin DriveLuxe models show the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving PNDs.
The base model Garmin Drive 51/61 includes helpful driver alerts. The Garmin DriveSmart 51/61 adds smart features. The camera-equipped Garmin DriveAssist 51 is for recording drives, while the premium Garmin DriveLuxe 51 has an elegant metal design.</description></item><item><title>Uber has expanded its services to Seremban, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 08:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Uber. UberX is arriving in Seremban in December
Uber is expanding its services to Seremban, the eighth city in Malaysia to have Uber. Starting December 1, 2016, residents of Seremban can hail a ride via the UberX service. This launch comes after the successful introduction of UberX in Melaka on October 27, 2016.
Uber also presents earning opportunities for driver-partners using their own vehicles. Drivers have the flexibility to set their own schedules and determine their earnings.</description></item><item><title>Enhance data security by using a Kingston encrypted USB flash drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-data-security-by-using-a-kingston-encrypted-usb-flash-drive/</guid><description>Kingston, a company known for its memory products, has launched the DataTraveler 2000, a new encrypted USB flash drive. This drive provides hardware encryption and requires a PIN entered on a built-in alphanumeric keypad for access.
Created with security in mind, the DataTraveler 2000 is ideal for IT professionals, small and medium businesses, and corporate users who need to keep their electronic data safe. It offers hardware-based, full-disk AES 256-bit encryption in XTS mode without needing any software or drivers.</description></item><item><title>Google is revealing how it plans to increase your productivity in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Google&amp;rsquo;s annual developer conference, I/O, brought a wave of announcements for Apps, Android, Chromebooks, and the Cloud Platform.
As highlighted on the official Google blog, Android now boasts a staggering one billion users who send an estimated 20 billion text messages and 93 million selfies daily. Key introductions include:
Android Wear
Expanding Android&amp;rsquo;s reach to wearable devices, Android Wear allows users to perform tasks or ask questions simply by saying &amp;ldquo;Ok Google.</description></item></channel></rss>