<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DOCSIS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/docsis/</link><description>Recent content in DOCSIS on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/docsis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>