<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Firewall on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/firewall/</link><description>Recent content in Firewall on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/firewall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Here’s Why Companies Actually Want BYOD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The concept of &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) can be a real headache for IT managers. While employees may enjoy the convenience, it poses a significant risk to a company&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data. When personal devices connect to the company network, carefully constructed security protocols are often bypassed. So, what can be done?
Many companies address this issue by drawing a hard line. Recognizing the challenges of managing diverse personal devices, they prohibit their use for business purposes altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Security Threat Protection In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 21:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>In the past, castles relied on moats to provide extra security beyond their walls. This stopped attackers from directly reaching the castle. Similarly, today&amp;rsquo;s networks need more than just firewalls.
Firewalls are effective but can be overwhelmed. Cloud-based security acts as a modern moat, providing a barrier outside the network. MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s Unified Threat Management (UTM) uses this approach, offering cloud, on-site, or hybrid security solutions.
MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s UTM is a multi-layered Security as a Service (SaaS) solution that handles simple and complex threats, while also managing security alerts, logs, and compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaller companies can benefit from Cisco's advanced firewall security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</guid><description>Source: Cisco website. Some members of the Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services family.
Cisco has introduced new Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services models designed for small to mid-sized businesses and branch offices. These models offer the same advanced malware protection and threat detection used by larger organizations.
A recent study by PwC revealed a 64% increase in security breaches among mid-sized organizations in 2014. These organizations face similar security challenges as larger enterprises when safeguarding their network and data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>