<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIP Trunking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-trunking/</link><description>Recent content in SIP Trunking on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-trunking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sipping on the Trunk Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</guid><description>The history of telephone trunks goes back to the early days of telephones. Trunks are lines that carry multiple phone conversations, initially connecting switchboards and switching offices. They&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from wire bundles to analog and now digital circuits, with T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and SONET being common digital trunking services. However, SIP trunking is emerging as a popular alternative.
Telephone trunking saves money by combining multiple phone lines into a single high-bandwidth connection.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Phone Service Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-phone-service-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes might be considering upgrading their phone systems but are unsure of the best approach. Should they stick with their existing Key Telephone or PBX system and upgrade it, or is it time to transition to VoIP? What many businesses may not realize is the wide range of options that VoIP solutions offer.
The key difference between VoIP and traditional phone systems lies in its network-based approach. While even a single-line phone or cell phone operates on a network, known as the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), this network has limitations.</description></item><item><title>2x2 Ethernet Takes on T-1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</guid><description>For the past decade, small and medium businesses have relied on T1 lines as their primary commercial telecom solution. However, a new competitor called 2x2 Ethernet, recently introduced by major nationwide carrier MegaPath, is emerging to challenge the long-standing T1. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what 2x2 Ethernet offers.
It might seem surprising that T1 lines would face competition, considering their 50-year history and widespread adoption. As the first widely available broadband digital connection for businesses, T1 emerged from telephone company research.</description></item><item><title>IP Exchange - The Final Piece For VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</guid><description>The shift from circuit-switched to packet-switched telephone networks is undeniable. While large companies have adopted enterprise VoIP to enhance efficiency, cut expenses, and prepare for the future, small and medium businesses are considering SIP trunking for bundled high-quality telephone and broadband services. Consumers are switching to cable broadband-telephone packages or third-party VoIP options. However, the PSTN remains.
Currently, VoIP systems and services operate in isolation. On-net calls, meaning calls within the same service regardless of location, are often free.</description></item><item><title>Last Mile Connections That Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</guid><description>The US is covered in a network of competing telecom companies, reaching into every major city. Businesses of all sizes are drawn to their advanced IP networks, fiber optic infrastructure, and significantly lower prices. But how can businesses connect to these networks?
The final connection to a customer&amp;rsquo;s location, often called the &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; is frequently the most critical, expensive, and limiting part of a wide area network. It gets its name from the typical distance between a business and the nearest carrier Point of Presence (POP).</description></item><item><title>TelePacific’s SmartVoice Trunking Offers Telephone Smarts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications offers a unique and intelligent solution called SmartVoice for small and medium-sized businesses seeking telephone and internet services. This SIP trunking solution provides both voice and data over a single line. Unlike traditional Integrated T1 lines, SmartVoice stands out by supporting various business telephone systems and offering significantly greater traffic capacity.
SIP trunking uses an IP-based transmission line specifically designed for enterprise VoIP telephone systems. SIP, or Session Initiation Protocol, is the signaling technology employed by numerous IP phone systems.</description></item><item><title>SMB Phone System Needs Only Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</guid><description>The simplicity of traditional phone systems, where plugging in a phone provided immediate dial tone, is making a comeback with cloud-based communication systems.
This modern approach, known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, shifts the responsibility of complex switching equipment to a service provider. This means the provider manages updates, maintenance, and scalability, leaving you with only the phones to handle.
These aren&amp;rsquo;t your typical phones; they are IP phones designed for computer networks, using different electrical signals and connectors.</description></item><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Cost Reduction Ideas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</guid><description>Getting the best price on everything your business buys is crucial for success, and bandwidth is no exception. Telecom expenses can be significant, but there are ways to save without sacrificing productivity.
One surprisingly simple step is to get updated competitive quotes. Bandwidth prices change rapidly, so your current understanding might be outdated.
While gathering quotes used to be time-consuming, online tools like GeoQuote by Telarus have simplified the process. This automated engine collects pricing from various providers, delivering budgetary quotes for services like T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and Ethernet connections almost instantly.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Hosted PBX VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 03:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</guid><description>There are many ways to implement VoIP, with some methods being more effective than others. Your goal with VoIP is likely to reduce expenses and access enhanced features while maintaining high-quality voice communication.
Achieving this balance is possible with the right technology, though proper setup can be challenging. Getting assistance with the installation, specifically by outsourcing complex aspects to a specialized provider, can greatly increase your chances of a smooth implementation.</description></item><item><title>Can SIP Trunking Supplant ISDN PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses that require multiple phone lines can benefit from digital trunks. While previously only large companies with numerous lines saw advantages with digital trunks, advancements in technology now make them a viable option for businesses with just a few lines and internet access.
What exactly constitutes a telephone trunk? Essentially, it is a collection of phone lines bundled together. Unlike individual analog lines, which consist of a twisted pair of copper wires, a trunk combines multiple lines.</description></item><item><title>High Quality Call Termination With SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-quality-call-termination-with-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Prioritizing voice packets on a network ensures high-quality VoIP calls within an organization. However, connecting to the outside world poses a challenge due to the incompatibility between modern packet-switched networks and the traditional circuit-switched phone system. To bridge this gap, organizations can either manage the conversion internally or outsource it to a third-party provider through SIP trunking.
SIP trunking offers a potentially cost-effective solution by consolidating multiple phone lines into a single &amp;ldquo;trunk&amp;rdquo; line and utilizing the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for call switching.</description></item><item><title>Best VoIP Providers For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</guid><description>Thinking about switching from traditional phone lines to VoIP, but unsure about its effectiveness? This guide provides insights and advice for a smooth transition.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, is also known as “network voice” because it operates on computer networks, unlike traditional phone systems. Essentially, voice becomes another service on your network, alongside data, video, and audio streaming. Each service transmits packets routed through the network.
This setup offers significant cost savings for larger businesses by consolidating telephone and data networks.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines might be leaving money on the table if they haven&amp;rsquo;t explored T-1 digital phone lines. Even businesses already using T1 service might be unaware of potential savings from newer options.
Digital telephony emerged in the 1950s as phone companies sought efficient ways to handle large call volumes. Analog phone lines carried a single conversation per wire pair. While analog multiplexing (carrier telephony) allowed multiple calls on a single wire pair, it suffered from quality issues over long distances.</description></item><item><title>XO Nails Down SIP Trunking Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</guid><description>Want to discover how your business could save upwards of $88,000 annually just by switching to SIP trunking service?
Hold on a minute! To achieve this level of savings, your business needs to have a certain volume of operations and spending. This figure comes from XO Communications, a leading voice and data carrier, and their new Enterprise SIP Savings Estimator.
So, what kind of business can expect these substantial savings? In this scenario, a company with 1,000 employees spread across 10 locations, where half of their phone calls are internal.</description></item><item><title>Wireless SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Traditionally, business phone lines and dedicated internet relied on physical wires. However, wireless SIP trunking is emerging as a new option.
](http://www.affordablevpn.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
Airband Communications, a frontrunner in this technology, offers business-class voice services packaged with wireless internet access. This is comparable to a SIP trunk or an integrated voice and data service in the wired world, but Airband&amp;rsquo;s offering presents unique benefits.
Similar to other integrated services, a single connection provides both phone and internet access, only in this case, it&amp;rsquo;s wireless.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Replacement Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-replacement-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-replacement-services/</guid><description>Unhappy with your current VoIP provider? Whether you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing subpar customer service or your provider has gone out of business, our VoIP Service Finder can help you compare options and find a new provider. Businesses have additional alternatives worth exploring.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, has rapidly gained popularity among residential, small business, and enterprise users. Its growth is largely driven by the potential for significant cost savings on phone services.</description></item><item><title>Managed IP Services Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</guid><description>Companies are increasingly interested in cloud services because they can save money and access capabilities that they might not otherwise be able to afford. Cloud services offer a wide range of IP services and can be accessed in-house, privately, or purchased from a provider. While providers offer different services, they all deliver their services over IP networks, leading to the term &amp;ldquo;managed IP services.&amp;rdquo;
Managed services allow carriers or service providers to take responsibility for operations, a task typically handled by on-site IT staff.</description></item><item><title>Local Telephone Service Provider Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</guid><description>All homes and businesses require some form of local phone service. While this was once as simple as calling the phone company, more choices are now available, requiring careful consideration for the best deal.
Traditional analog phone service, or &amp;ldquo;dial tone&amp;rdquo; service, uses century-old technology. With its established infrastructure and widespread availability, customers can still walk into a local phone company for service. However, exploring offers from both traditional and newer competitive carriers can lead to better options.</description></item><item><title>Managed Voice over MPLS For High Quality Enterprise Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations are realizing the financial and operational benefits of MPLS networks. MPLS VPNs are emerging as the go-to solution for connecting multiple sites nationally and globally. But what about voice services?
Traditionally, voice and data are kept separate. Telephone systems rely on a proven infrastructure of switched circuit analog and digital trunking. Most PBX systems are designed to connect to standard copper-pair analog business lines or ISDN PRI digital trunks, which act as gateways to the global PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) connecting every phone on Earth.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Take a Bow For The SIP Revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</guid><description>A significant change is happening in businesses of all sizes. It&amp;rsquo;s not related to politics, social issues, or processes. It&amp;rsquo;s a subtle change that most employees aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of, a change that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily noticeable and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require anyone to alter their work methods. It simply provides enhanced capabilities and cost savings. This is the SIP revolution.
What is SIP, and why is it so transformative? Watch this brief introduction to find out&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Can You Save 50% With Unified Communications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</guid><description>As your company expands, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely seen a simultaneous increase in your telephone costs. While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this is simply due to having more employees making calls, the reality is that not all phone expenses are unavoidable.
Unified communications technology can help you significantly reduce unnecessary costs. This approach combines your voice, data, and video networks into a single, unified system, leading to cost savings for businesses of all sizes, even those with just one location.</description></item><item><title>VoIP is For Smaller Companies Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-is-for-smaller-companies-too/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 10:22:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-is-for-smaller-companies-too/</guid><description>Many people think Enterprise VoIP solutions are too complex and costly for small businesses. While that&amp;rsquo;s often accurate, advanced IP PBX systems can sometimes boost productivity for smaller, sophisticated companies. However, for those seeking quality calls at reasonable prices, SMB (Small and Medium Business) VoIP solutions can be the perfect solution.
VoIP ranges from using your computer as a phone to systems that are virtually identical to standard network-switched technologies. Home-based businesses might prefer VoIP services that utilize their existing Cable or DSL broadband for internet access.</description></item><item><title>PRI Lines For Domestic Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are turning to domestic call centers, whether they are in-house or independent contractors. All call centers rely on telephone service, and PRI lines are the preferred choice. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, belongs to the Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) standard. ISDN aimed to transition all telephone lines from analog to digital. The basic offering, BRI (Basic Rate Interface), provides two phone lines or one phone line with either a 64 Kbps or 128 Kbps data service.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking and Internet On a T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</guid><description>Many smaller companies utilize T1 lines for dedicated internet access, opting for this solution after experiencing unreliable or unavailable consumer-grade broadband options. T1 lines offer these businesses dependable, robust bandwidth at increasingly affordable prices. However, many are unaware that they can bundle their broadband and telephone services onto a single T1 line.
Traditional T1 lines offer various service options. The original format, designed for the telephone industry, provides 24 channels of digitized telephone service over two pairs of twisted copper phone wires.</description></item><item><title>Why NOT to Buy a New PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</guid><description>Traditionally, businesses dealing with outdated or inadequate phone systems have opted for a complete replacement, known as a “forklift upgrade.” While this provided enhanced performance and capacity, like a brand new car, there&amp;rsquo;s a compelling alternative in today&amp;rsquo;s world: hosted PBX solutions.
Rather than investing heavily in another physical PBX system, consider a hosted PBX, also referred to as Hosted VoIP or PBX in the cloud. This service eliminates the need for a physical PBX on your premises.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems.</description></item><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines.</description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings.</description></item><item><title>XO Launches SIP for Multi-Location Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</guid><description>XO Communications, a large telecommunications company, has introduced a new solution that allows businesses with numerous locations to take advantage of enterprise VoIP technology.
Connecting business locations to a phone service provider through SIP trunking is a well-established method for improving network performance and saving money. XO is building on this concept with a multi-site SIP trunking solution. Instead of requiring each location to connect to a remote service provider separately, branch offices, warehouses, and other locations can now use their existing Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect SIP phones back to a central IP-PBX system at the main office.</description></item><item><title>Voice And Data On One Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-on-one-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-on-one-line/</guid><description>Most businesses require phone and internet services, often installed separately, leading to a mix of services. However, technology now allows both services through a single line, saving money. But how does this impact quality?
Combining phone and internet might raise concerns if you&amp;rsquo;ve had negative experiences with residential VoIP, where voice quality suffers due to uncontrolled bandwidth.
Businesses have better options for high-quality, reliable VoIP. The key is ensuring sufficient bandwidth, controlled jitter and latency, and prioritized voice packets.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>T1 vs SIP For Business Telephone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</guid><description>Large businesses with high call volumes require different telecommunications solutions compared to small offices. While T1 lines have been the traditional choice, SIP Trunking is emerging as a strong alternative. This article explores the pros and cons of each technology to help businesses make informed decisions.
T1 lines were initially developed by telephone companies to connect central offices and handle numerous calls simultaneously. This technology, using T-carrier standards (T1 and T3), enabled high-capacity call transportation.</description></item><item><title>What XO’s 1,000,000 VoIP Customers Predicts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</guid><description>XO Communications, a leading competitor in the telecom industry, recently celebrated a significant achievement: reaching one million business VoIP users.
Reaching this milestone in just five years surprised even XO. This rapid adoption might be unexpected for those hesitant about embracing VoIP technology. We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the downsides of poorly implemented VoIP – distortion, dropped calls, and poor sound quality. However, successful implementations demonstrate that these issues are avoidable. After all, a million businesses can&amp;rsquo;t be wrong.</description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>T1 Telephony Has Many Flavors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-telephony-has-many-flavors/</guid><description>Initially designed for high-volume call transfer between telephone exchanges, T1 technology has evolved into a leading digital phone solution for businesses. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering T1, understanding the available options is crucial.
T1 is a digital standard supporting voice, data, video, or a combination thereof. Originally, it carried 24 separate calls on individual channels called DS0s, collectively forming a T1 line or DS1. Each DS0 transmits digitized voice, call control, and signaling information.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item><item><title>Cut Telecom Line Expenses, Not Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</guid><description>During economic downturns, businesses often look to cut costs to stay afloat. While eliminating unnecessary expenses is a good start, managers may soon scrutinize even essential budget items.
Instead of panicking and making rash decisions, it&amp;rsquo;s best to proactively identify reasonable cost reductions. This way, you can present well-thought-out proposals and maintain some control over the process.
The key is to maintain productivity while reducing expenses. Instead of completely cutting essential services, focus on achieving the same functionality for less money.</description></item><item><title>What Is a PRI Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</guid><description>Businesses frequently use PRI lines to obtain multiple phone lines. But what exactly are PRI lines, and what choices are there?
PRI is a component of ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network), a telecommunications standard. Its goal was to replace analog phone lines with digital ones for both residential and commercial customers. When ISDN was first introduced, dial-up connections using 56 Kbps modems were the norm for internet connectivity. Many of these modems only achieved speeds of 30 to 40 Kbps due to phone line limitations.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Why Are VoIP and SIP Trunking So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-are-voip-and-sip-trunking-so-popular/</guid><description>When your outdated PBX system needs an upgrade, consider transitioning to an IP PBX and replacing traditional phone lines with a SIP Trunk. This shift to modern technologies is driven by their ability to deliver new features and cost savings without compromising call quality.
Upgrading doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require replacing existing phones. While VoIP SIP phones offer advantages like network connectivity and simplified management, older phones can connect to the IP PBX via interface cards with FSX ports.</description></item><item><title>Business Broadband and Phone Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses require both internet and phone service. While ordering these services separately remains an option, businesses now have more choices.
Bundled services, offering both phone and internet, often make the most sense for smaller businesses with limited needs and budgets. Two primary bundled options provide cost savings compared to separate services.
The first option, known as Integrated T1 or SIP Trunking, utilizes line sharing but differs in connection methods.</description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient.</description></item><item><title>Signaling for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signaling-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signaling-for-call-centers/</guid><description>Every phone call involves two parts: the conversation itself and the signaling that manages the phone network. While signaling might seem purely technical, its implementation significantly impacts call center efficiency.
Traditional analog phone lines use the same copper wires, called the local loop, for both voice and signaling. Touchtone dialing, handset lifting, and ringing all rely on electrical signals sent over this shared connection. This method, known as in-band signaling, has limitations.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Trunk Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-trunk-service-providers/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines often benefit from trunk lines. But with various trunk services available, choosing the right one can be tricky. While VoIP phone systems might make SIP trunking seem like the obvious choice, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to evaluate all options before deciding.
The concept of telephone trunking originated with telephone companies. Initially, individual phone lines connected users to the local phone company. As phone usage surged, businesses adopted switchboards to manage multiple lines, leading to a tangled mess of overhead wires.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item><item><title>PRI Phone Line Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 18:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</guid><description>Analog business phone lines are suitable for small offices and retail spaces that don&amp;rsquo;t need many outside lines. If you require more than six lines, an option like ISDN PRI might be a better fit.
ISDN PRI, which stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is a standard for transmitting calls digitally over regular phone lines. It&amp;rsquo;s the larger of two primary options, with the smaller being BRI (Basic Rate Interface).</description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate.</description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types.</description></item><item><title>Toshiba Strata CIX Does SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toshiba-strata-cix-does-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toshiba-strata-cix-does-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Business phone systems have transitioned from analog lines to digital T1 and T1 PRI trunks. With the rise of Enterprise VoIP, SIP Trunking has emerged as a popular all-IP option, supported by a growing number of carriers. SIP trunking eliminates the need for on-site PSTN termination by sending voice and data packets to a service provider, leading to cost savings through economies of scale.
Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s Strata CIX IP Business Communication Systems have integrated SIP trunking, removing the need for a separate VoIP gateway.</description></item><item><title>Business VoIP Solution Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about switching your business phone system from the traditional analog or PBX setup to VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), it&amp;rsquo;s wise to explore the various business VoIP options available before making a complete overhaul. The best choice for you depends on your specific needs and, by selecting wisely, you can maximize your telephony investment.
The main reasons to consider VoIP are cost savings, enhanced calling features, or a combination of both.</description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers.</description></item></channel></rss>