<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carriage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carriage/</link><description>Recent content in Carriage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carriage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning of the Tone Arm Carriage Position Switches and a Non-Returning Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</guid><description>As a preliminary step in the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I chose to verify the functionality of its control system. Prior testing had shown that the arm carriage would not return to its home position when moved across the platter without a record in place. Instead, it would travel to the center of the platter and stop. Ideally, the carriage should trigger the End Switch (ES) at this point and subsequently return to its home position on the right, turning off the turntable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Replacement of Carriage Position Sensor Photocell</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</guid><description>Over many years of working with the Beogram 400x, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a wide array of issues, but these turntables never cease to present new challenges. In this instance, a Beogram 4002 exhibited inconsistent behavior when attempting to locate the record&amp;rsquo;s setdown point after pressing start. This pointed to a potential fault in the carriage position sensor.
Initially, I suspected the IR LED, a common culprit in later models like this 5513 Type.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Non-Working End Groove Detection - Repair of a Detached Carriage Position Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. One peculiar problem was a detached carriage position sensor, which is housed within a black light shield. This shield was hanging at an angle, but it needs to be positioned vertically. The sensor works by using black sections on a plexiglass strip attached to the carriage to interrupt light from an IR diode. If the sensor is misaligned, stray light can disrupt the carriage&amp;rsquo;s movement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Gap at the Carriage Servo Pulley Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, significant longitudinal play was discovered in the threaded rod responsible for moving the carriage. This play resulted in a &amp;lsquo;clacking&amp;rsquo; noise whenever the carriage changed direction.
The issue was resolved by removing the servo pulley, damaged locking ring, and worn plastic washer. A new, thick 2-56 nylon washer, which fit snugly on the shaft, replaced the locking ring and washer. The locking ring became unnecessary as the pulley was secured with a setscrew.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of a Wobbly Carriage Pulley with a New Aluminum Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</guid><description>As I was finishing the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5523), I noticed a concerning noise coming from the carriage when it moved quickly, especially when returning to its starting position. This led me to believe there was an issue with the carriage pulley. Upon inspection, I discovered that the pulley was cracked, which is a common problem with this model. It seems the original plastic can&amp;rsquo;t handle the stress from the setscrew over time and eventually cracks.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Wiring Sleeve of Carriage Harness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-wiring-sleeve-of-carriage-harness/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable, previously restored in 2020, was brought in for repairs due to an oscillating solenoid issue. However, upon inspection, a more critical problem was discovered: the wiring harness sleeve was severely damaged, exposing the wires.
This level of damage had never been encountered before. Thankfully, the wires themselves were still intact. The timing of the solenoid problem was fortunate, as further use could have led to wire damage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Tracking Sensor Incandescent Bulb with a Drop-In SMD LED Assembly and a Peek at the Opto-Resistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</guid><description>The tracking sensor bulb in my Beogram 4000 recently burned out. This was the fourth bulb to fail. I decided to use this opportunity to install my new SMD LED replacement assembly. This assembly uses efficient white LEDs at low power for longevity, likely exceeding 50 years. It also reduces the unit&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption by a few watts, lessening the load on the aging transformer. Details about the assembly and adjustments can be found in this video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Restoration of the Carriage Position Sensor - Development of a New Beolover Part</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) being restored had a broken carriage position sensor photo resistor housing with damaged mounting tabs. After removing the housing and extracting the photo resistor, a replacement housing was designed and 3D printed.
The new housing consists of two parts. The photo resistor is placed on the insert part after straightening its leads. The main housing is then slid over the insert, sandwiching the photo resistor. This assembly is then inserted into the existing mounting cutouts and soldered to the PCB.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Gold Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Spring Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring an early model Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, and it&amp;rsquo;s captivating to trace the evolution of its design from the original Beogram 4000. Having already tackled the arm lowering mechanism, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the carriage position switches, a particularly interesting aspect of the 4002&amp;rsquo;s design.
While the design echoes that of the 4000, it features some notable refinements. The 4000&amp;rsquo;s 7&amp;quot; record set-down point switch, for instance, was a break switch prone to issues stemming from oxidation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Slow Slide Transport Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem was encountered where the tonearm carriage would continue moving after attempting to move it in reverse. This issue stemmed from a damaged keypad switch, specifically a bent contact terminal that prevented a clean shut-off connection. This damage was likely caused by a previous repair attempt.
To address this, the control panel and circuit board were removed to access and extract the switch terminals.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control panel (keypad), the next step was to focus on the carriage position switches. These switches are vital for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s digital control system, and even one faulty switch can render the entire device unusable. Similar to the keypad switches, these are prone to oxidation, making gold plating a reliable solution to prevent future contact problems. The image below displays the circuit board with the switches after detaching the carriage position indicator component.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Packaging for Shipping: An Update on How to Secure the Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</guid><description>This article outlines a packaging update for the Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 turntables. Instead of taping the arm cover to the platter, the author now advises using an M3 screw to secure the carriage directly to the chassis.
This change is due to the risk of damaging the arm cover&amp;rsquo;s labeling with tape during shipping. While the author previously suggested using paper to protect the lettering, damage continued to occur.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): End Groove Detection Not Working</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</guid><description>Just when I thought I had finished refurbishing a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a problem surfaced during playback. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t return after playing a record, instead getting stuck in the end groove, repeating the sound of the run-out.
Investigating further, I used an oscilloscope to examine the signal from the position sensor, which tells the control system the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s location. The signal was weak specifically in the end groove area, often indicating misalignment between the sensor&amp;rsquo;s IR diode and the light entry slit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulb of the Tracking Sensor with a Drop-In LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 11:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 400x turntable, it&amp;rsquo;s common to replace the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s incandescent bulb with a more durable LED assembly. A drop-in replacement for the Beogram 4002 and 4004 models has been created and documented, while the Beogram 4000 version incorporates a Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen-specified intensity trimmer for fine-tuning the tracking feedback system&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to recalibrate the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s position after any light source replacement to maintain accurate tracking sensitivity.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Random Stop Issue Fixed - Defective Photo Resistor in the Spindle RPM Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, previously restored, began experiencing a problem where the OFF function would randomly activate during playback as if the button was pressed.
Prior to delving into the solution, the circuit diagram is presented for reference.
Transistor TR17, within the &amp;lsquo;Electronic Switch&amp;rsquo; section, is responsible for initiating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s OFF function. When its base is grounded, the collector rises to approximately 18V, causing the arm to lift and return to its resting position.</description></item></channel></rss>