<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brexit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brexit/</link><description>Recent content in Brexit on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brexit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What impact could Brexit have on the younger generation? EU Referendum Briefing 2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A UK exit from the European Union, or &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; could have significant implications for young people, impacting their education, travel opportunities, and economic prospects.
Education
The EU does not control educational content or matters like tuition costs. Instead, its involvement lies in cross-border educational aspects, including promoting student and teacher mobility through initiatives like the Erasmus program. Established in 1987, this EU law-based program facilitates student exchanges across various educational levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Great Repeal Bill and the Legacy of Henry VIII: Threatening Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</guid><description>Joelle Grogan, Lecturer, Middlesex University
The Great Repeal Bill is ironically named because it won&amp;rsquo;t actually repeal much EU law. Instead, when Brexit concludes, it will initially shift existing EU law into British law. While this maintains some stability during the transition, the bill also includes a concerning element: a Henry VIII clause. This clause, named after the king who gave himself sweeping legislative power, allows the government to alter primary legislation with minimal parliamentary scrutiny...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the Reunification of Ireland from an EU Legal Viewpoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</guid><description>Nikos Skoutaris, Lecturer in EU law at the University of East Anglia; website on Secessions, Constitutions and EU law.
When the UK voted to leave the EU on June 23, 2016, Northern Ireland voted to remain. This result has led Sinn Féin to call for a referendum on Irish unification, which would allow Northern Ireland to stay in the EU. This discussion has gained momentum following the most recent Northern Ireland Assembly election, which saw a significant decrease in the Unionist vote...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union considered valid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart
Introduction
The Treaty of Lisbon introduced Article 50 to the Treaty on European Union (TEU), establishing the legal framework for exiting the European Union (EU). This article acknowledges the possibility of withdrawal, a concept many legal experts believed existed even before the Treaty of Lisbon. Article 50 TEU outlines the withdrawal procedure. However, some argue that it contradicts the EU&amp;rsquo;s fundamental nature and weakens member states&amp;rsquo; commitment to European integration, raising questions about the ideal withdrawal mechanism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-article-50-of-the-treaty-on-european-union-considered-valid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the draft renegotiation deal a legitimate rejection? Tusk's suggestion and the role of national parliaments.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</guid><description>Dr. Katarzyna Granat, Junior Research Fellow &amp;amp; Marie Curie Fellow, Durham Law School Donald Tusk&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A New Settlement for the United Kingdom within the European Union&amp;rdquo; (Draft Decision of the Heads of State or Government), presented on February 2, 2016, provides an initial concrete outline for enhancing the role of national parliaments within the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiation efforts. This note compares the proposed changes with existing mechanisms under the Lisbon Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Brexit Causing the British Mind to Close? The Impact on EU Academics and Government Guidance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Brexit vote is often seen as an attack on both academic expertise and EU citizens in the UK, whether accurate or not. These two issues intersect in a recent dispute involving the Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO) and the London School of Economics (LSE). The FCO allegedly barred EU citizens from advising the government on Brexit, though the details are unclear.
The LSE reportedly informed staff that the FCO no longer sought Brexit advice from EU nationals, sparking a controversy that made its way to social media and prominent news outlets like The Guardian...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-brexit-causing-the-british-mind-to-close-the-impact-on-eu-academics-and-government-guidance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Life is full of challenges, and then you have to deal with the third extension of EU membership.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This extension was unexpected. Despite the Benn Act, which mandated the Prime Minister to request a three-month extension for EU membership if Parliament failed to approve a withdrawal agreement by October 19, the Prime Minister insisted he would rather resign than comply. Fueled by ambiguous sources within Downing Street, there was persistent speculation that the Benn Act was unconstitutional, riddled with loopholes, would be superseded by emergency powers, or violated EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/life-is-full-of-challenges-and-then-you-have-to-deal-with-the-third-extension-of-eu-membership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The resolution of disputes and the role of the ECJ in the proposed withdrawal agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A key point of contention in post-Brexit EU/UK relations is the degree to which the UK remains bound to the EU Court of Justice (ECJ). This issue arises first in the withdrawal agreement being negotiated, a draft of which was recently proposed by the EU Commission. While it will eventually affect the future relationship between the two, this post focuses on the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Divergence in regulations after Brexit: Copyright law as a preview of future changes.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</guid><description>Martin Kretschmer, Professor of Intellectual Property Law (CREATe Centre, University of Glasgow)
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the European Union has resulted in the first instance of regulatory divergence. As the UK exits the single market, existing regulations are starting to show cracks.
In response to a question from MP Jo Stevens, former Intellectual Property Minister Chris Skidmore indicated the UK would not implement the latest EU Copyright Directive, despite the UK&amp;rsquo;s prior support for it in the EU Council...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Prime Minister hinting at a potential shift in Brexit stance with his unexpected mention of competition policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</guid><description>Andreas Stephan, Professor of Competition Law &amp;amp; Head of UEA Law School, University of East Anglia*
In a speech delivered on March 2, 2018, Prime Minister Theresa May aimed to clarify the UK&amp;rsquo;s Brexit objectives. She proposed aligning UK State Aid and Competition rules with those of the EU, while allowing UK courts to consider European Court of Justice (ECJ) judgments. However, she emphasized that the ECJ would not have jurisdiction over the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit Redux: Exploring the legal complexities of retracting the EU departure notification and subsequently re-notifying the intention to leave.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law, University College London
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Wightman case offers valuable insights into the Brexit process. The Court affirmed that the UK could unilaterally withdraw its intention to leave the EU, without needing approval from the remaining 27 EU members.
While this is a significant development that could empower those advocating for a second referendum with the option to remain in the EU, the CJEU ruling is ultimately inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-redux-exploring-the-legal-complexities-of-retracting-the-eu-departure-notification-and-subsequently-re-notifying-the-intention-to-leave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion of the Legal Service of the Council on the Brexit agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</guid><description>This document presents the EU Council legal service&amp;rsquo;s analysis of whether the Brexit deal requires approval from both the EU and its Member States (a &amp;lsquo;mixed agreement&amp;rsquo;), or solely from the EU. It concludes that the EU can act alone due to the deal encompassing a blend of exclusive EU competences and competences shared between the EU and its member states. This aligns with Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law, which allows the EU to enact a treaty encompassing shared competences either independently or jointly with its Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>No Longer Negotiable: The Rights of EU and UK Citizens Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 04:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
This post examines the findings of a British Future inquiry into the post-Brexit status of EU citizens in the UK. It outlines the inquiry&amp;rsquo;s key recommendations concerning EU citizens residing in the UK after Brexit, proposes recommendations for UK citizens in the EU after Brexit, and analyzes the concept of &amp;lsquo;associate citizenship&amp;rsquo; for UK citizens post-Brexit. The latter two points, while outside the inquiry&amp;rsquo;s scope, are addressed in parallel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-longer-negotiable-the-rights-of-eu-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it appropriate to question the credibility of research conducted by academics whose institutions receive funding from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 08:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Some Eurosceptics suggest that research should be disregarded if the academics involved or their institutions have received EU funding, especially if that research contradicts Eurosceptic viewpoints. This tactic has been used against both recent research on the positive impacts of free movement of EU citizens and me personally. While it&amp;rsquo;s tempting to ignore these accusations, they are frequently used to discredit objective evidence supporting pro-European arguments, particularly in the context of a potential referendum on British exit from the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Hard Brexit? Transforming Britain's £24 billion worth of unicorns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The pro-Brexit group &amp;ldquo;Change Britain&amp;rdquo; recently released a statement claiming significant financial benefits for the UK following a &amp;ldquo;hard Brexit,&amp;rdquo; where the UK leaves both the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market and customs union. This claim was widely circulated in the media despite being fundamentally flawed.
While the report attempts to offer a thorough analysis, it highlights the poor quality of the overall Brexit debate. The report&amp;rsquo;s claim of a £24 billion benefit originates from three key areas: ending contributions to the EU budget, potential savings from reduced regulation, and the anticipated benefits of new trade agreements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Entry to the EU's Financial Services Market in the Absence of a Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (Twitter: @KulpaBart)
Introduction
When Boris Johnson became British Prime Minister, a no-deal Brexit appeared increasingly possible. UK-based financial services firms were left wondering if and how they would be able to continue serving clients in the remaining 27 EU countries. These firms currently depend on &amp;ldquo;passporting rights,&amp;rdquo; which allow them to operate across borders. According to The Economist, in 2016, 5,476 British financial services firms used 336,421 European passports to offer their products across the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mastering the art of releasing control - the Charter of Fundamental Rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Eduardo Gill-Pedro, Post-Doctoral Researcher, Faculty of Law, Lund University: Eduardo.gill-pedro@jur.lu.se
The UK Government&amp;rsquo;s proposition to exclude the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights (the Charter) from UK law after Brexit (clause 5(4) of the EU Withdrawal Bill) has drawn criticism from opposition parties. The Labour party views this as a non-negotiable issue and refuses to endorse any bill that doesn&amp;rsquo;t integrate the Charter into UK law. Keir Starmer, the Shadow Brexit Secretary, previously stated that Labour would only back a deal that meets its &amp;ldquo;six tests,&amp;rdquo; one being the preservation of &amp;ldquo;rights and protections&amp;rdquo; to avoid a decline in standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Putting an end to Brexit? Explaining the Wightman case on reversing the Article 50 notification independently.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
As the deadline for Brexit approaches and Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s conflicting negotiating goals become clearer, there are increasing demands for transparency regarding the Brexit process.
In late 2017, seven Scottish politicians from different parties and legislative bodies in Scotland (the Scottish Parliament, the UK Parliament, and the European Parliament) initiated a legal case in the Scottish Court of Session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and Labour Standards during COVID-19: Will they Align or Separate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</guid><description>Jeff Kenner, Professor of European Law, University of Nottingham*
The COVID-19 pandemic has taken center stage, demanding an urgent worldwide response that is yet to materialize. In light of this global crisis, the issue of Brexit, particularly its self-serving nature and political maneuvering, has understandably faded from the minds of both policymakers and the public. However, despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s onset in mid-March 2020, which coincided with the start of negotiations for a new EU-UK partnership and led to widespread lockdowns across Europe, the UK government remains steadfast in its refusal to extend the post-Brexit transition period beyond the December 31, 2020, deadline established in the October 2019 EU-UK Withdrawal Agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>'Although you have children together, your marriage is not genuine': Marriages of convenience, UK courts, and EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Aleksandra Jolkina, PhD in Law, Queen Mary University of London
Over the last twenty years, UK authorities have become increasingly wary of marriages within the UK between mobile EU citizens and third-country nationals (TCNs) with uncertain or irregular residence status. In the current climate of Euroscepticism, such marriages are often criticized as &amp;ldquo;marriages of convenience,&amp;rdquo; intended to circumvent British immigration laws. This piece examines how UK courts interpret the concept of marriages of convenience, the potential implications for families of EU citizens residing in the UK, and the anticipated changes after Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The process of withdrawing from the EU: Examining the uses and abuses of Article 50 TEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</guid><description>If the UK decides to hold a referendum on leaving the EU, also known as &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; Article 50 of the Treaty on the European Union (TEU) will be a focal point. This article outlines the exit process for member states. While some suggest using Article 50 to renegotiate UK membership, its legal and political limitations make this challenging.
The Details of Article 50 Article 50 allows any EU member state to withdraw according to its constitution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who is eligible to vote in the EU Referendum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-eligible-to-vote-in-the-eu-referendum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-eligible-to-vote-in-the-eu-referendum/</guid><description>Jo Shaw, University of Edinburgh
Twitter: @joshaw
Determining who can vote in specific elections is usually a dull topic that doesn&amp;rsquo;t garner much attention. Yet, the UK government&amp;rsquo;s announcement regarding voting eligibility for the EU Referendum unexpectedly became a hot topic in May 2015. This announcement aimed to quell the growing debate on the issue.
The announcement declared that the referendum would utilize a modified Westminster franchise, resembling the UK&amp;rsquo;s national election system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-eligible-to-vote-in-the-eu-referendum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-is-eligible-to-vote-in-the-eu-referendum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Commencement of Brexit: A Summary of the Legal Matters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commencement-of-brexit-a-summary-of-the-legal-matters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:40:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commencement-of-brexit-a-summary-of-the-legal-matters/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
The UK&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave the European Union has significant consequences for both entities and raises crucial questions about their future relationship. These questions include the potential independence of Scotland and its EU membership, calls for a unified Ireland, the potential spread of Euroscepticism in the EU, and the future of the 27-member bloc...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commencement-of-brexit-a-summary-of-the-legal-matters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commencement-of-brexit-a-summary-of-the-legal-matters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Implications of Extending EU Membership and Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-implications-of-extending-eu-membership-and-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-implications-of-extending-eu-membership-and-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*This blog post was updated after the official decision extending EU membership was approved.
With the Brexit deadline of March 29th approaching and no approval for the proposed withdrawal agreement, the European Council convened and agreed to extend the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership on March 21st. The UK formally accepted the extension on March 22nd. This raises several legal questions regarding extending EU membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-implications-of-extending-eu-membership-and-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-implications-of-extending-eu-membership-and-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is this the beginning of the end for citizens' rights in the Brexit 'Sufficient Progress' deal?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent joint report on Brexit negotiations, along with accompanying documents, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of discussions. This phase will center around a transition period and the framework for the future relationship between the UK and the EU.
Although a political rather than legal document, this report holds significant practical relevance for the withdrawal agreement. It outlines agreed-upon details concerning citizens&amp;rsquo; rights, the Irish border, the financial settlement, and concluding rules...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 4 of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement focuses on the rights of citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</guid><description>This blog post examines the rights of UK and EU citizens after Brexit, focusing on the revised withdrawal agreement. This agreement aims to protect the rights of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 who moved before the transition period ended (end of 2020, possibly extendable).
The agreement safeguards these individuals better than a &amp;ldquo;no deal&amp;rdquo; scenario, where national law would primarily apply. However, it offers less protection than continued EU membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Litigation in England involving business and human rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Anil Yilmaz Vastardis, Lecturer in Law, Human Rights Centre, University of Essex
Following the UK&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave the European Union, there is widespread uncertainty about the future. While political questions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit dominate the discussion, the consequences extend far beyond, impacting individuals worldwide, including victims of human rights abuses perpetrated by British corporations. A key concern revolves around the fate of EU laws implemented in the UK, either through legislation or direct application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Day the Unicorns Cried: Understanding Phase 1 of the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
The recent joint report on the progress of Brexit negotiations, along with a related paper from the Commission, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of negotiations. Based on this report, the EU27 have agreed that &amp;ldquo;sufficient progress&amp;rdquo; has been made to move forward. This next phase will focus on a transition period and, potentially starting in March 2018, the framework for the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Questions &amp; Answers about EU Free Movement Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We shouldn&amp;rsquo;t create a misleading impression of the law.&amp;rdquo;
(Measure for Measure, 2.1.1)
Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School, University of York
Laurent Pech, Professor of European Law, Jean Monnet Chair of EU Public Law at Middlesex University London
This article clarifies common misunderstandings about EU free movement rules, often found in British media. We believe much criticism targets a distorted view of the actual system.
The UK shows a desire to restrict EU freedom of movement, yet misinterpretations about these rules persist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Good Friday Agreement: A Personal Reflection on the Value of Peace over Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-good-friday-agreement-a-personal-reflection-on-the-value-of-peace-over-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 11:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-good-friday-agreement-a-personal-reflection-on-the-value-of-peace-over-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah Kay, human rights lawyer
As a teenager in the spring of 1998, I felt frustrated and stuck. I lived in a small house in West Belfast with my grandmother and a rotating group of cousins. My grandfather, an active member of the Republican movement, had died a few years earlier. I was lucky to spend summers traveling with my parents, who had custody of me, experiencing a world beyond our limited opportunities and ongoing conflict...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-good-friday-agreement-a-personal-reflection-on-the-value-of-peace-over-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-good-friday-agreement-a-personal-reflection-on-the-value-of-peace-over-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement: Analysis 1 Overview</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</guid><description>Analysis of the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement - October 2019 Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction While the approval of the Brexit withdrawal agreement is uncertain at present, the UK Parliament&amp;rsquo;s upcoming vote necessitates an updated analysis of the revised agreement. This updated version includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship.
This post aims to provide a simplified explanation of the agreement for non-lawyers, outlining its structure and key content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement Analysis 2: Transition Period</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Now that a revised Brexit withdrawal agreement is available, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to revisit my prior analyses of the initial agreement. This post, updating my spring 2018 analysis, focuses on the transition period outlined in the agreement. (The revised agreement includes changes to the Irish border protocol and the political declaration on the future relationship.) This post will provide context for the transition period and then break down the text...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating Discontent: Questions and Answers about the legal concerns of asylum-seekers crossing the Channel.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 23:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Supported by an ESRC Priority Brexit Grant on &amp;lsquo;Brexit and UK and EU Immigration Policy&amp;rsquo;.
Some politicians are trying to create unnecessary fear and outrage over a relatively small number of people crossing the English Channel. This situation does bring up important legal questions. While the legal aspects have been discussed elsewhere, such as in the Free Movement blog, this post aims to clarify some of these legal issues in a straightforward question-and-answer format...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a 'fast-track' Treaty amendment on the free movement of workers with the Cameron express?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Experts in EU law see Treaty amendments as a monumental event. After the Treaty of Lisbon, significant changes to the Treaty seemed improbable in the near future. However, this prospect is becoming more likely due to David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s push to renegotiate free movement regulations within the EU, a sentiment somewhat shared by the UK Labour party.
This brings us to the crucial question of what form such a Treaty amendment would take...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 1 of the European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement text explores the impact on health, focusing on patients and reciprocal healthcare.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Law, University of Sheffield
This article provides an initial examination of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s draft Withdrawal Agreement and its effects on health-related issues, particularly concerning individuals.
The focus here is on patient rights, specifically reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the remaining 27 EU members post-Brexit. Two significant issues are explored:
The future of UK pensioners residing in or planning to retire in other EU countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Teaching EU law in the UK after Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teaching-eu-law-in-the-uk-after-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 06:43:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teaching-eu-law-in-the-uk-after-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, University of Cambridge
In his final statement concerning the review of Retained EU Law (REUL), Lord Frost indicated a desire to examine the role of EU law in legal education. While acknowledging the potential issues surrounding government influence on university curricula, and setting aside the uncertain future of the REUL review itself, Brexit has undeniably prompted significant questions for EU law academics regarding teaching approaches and content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teaching-eu-law-in-the-uk-after-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teaching-eu-law-in-the-uk-after-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit: You have the option to change your mind. The CJEU ruling in Wightman allows for a U-turn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The recent definitive ruling by the Full Court concerning the Wightman case reaffirms the UK&amp;rsquo;s ability to independently revoke its withdrawal notification from the EU under the most flexible terms. This judgment aligns with the non-binding opinion given the previous week by an Advocate-General.
The judgment
The Court dismissed the UK government&amp;rsquo;s claim of the case being hypothetical, emphasizing the imminent involvement of some litigants (who are MPs) in voting on the proposed withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of the revised Withdrawal Agreement: Is Empire 2.0 making a comeback?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</guid><description>Commentary on the Draft Withdrawal Agreement - Version of February 21, 2018 This post provides an updated analysis of the draft Brexit withdrawal agreement, taking into account the UK&amp;rsquo;s response to the EU Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposed text.
The withdrawal agreement, if successfully negotiated, will be the key legal framework for Brexit. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember this agreement will be separate from future treaties governing the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of the UK government's proposals for cross-border civil litigation post-Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you&amp;rsquo;re a well-known UK politician who spends most of their time speaking on British radio or working in the US, only occasionally attending their primary job in France or Belgium. Imagine this politician is divorcing their German spouse. Which court and legal system would handle the divorce and child custody matters?
This scenario falls under the larger subject of international civil litigation, also known as private international law, which is the focus of the UK government&amp;rsquo;s most recent position paper on Brexit negotiations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK Supreme Court Justices: Defenders Against Anti-democratic Demagogues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-supreme-court-justices-defenders-against-anti-democratic-demagogues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-supreme-court-justices-defenders-against-anti-democratic-demagogues/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The Cherry/Miller case concluded with the significant ruling that Prime Minister Johnson&amp;rsquo;s prorogation of Parliament was unlawful. This decision, delivered unanimously, declared the prorogation legally void, effectively awakening Parliament from an illegal slumber.
This timely judgment allows for the illustration of constitutional law principles through current events. Law students will benefit from the numerous analyses and discussions surrounding this significant case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-supreme-court-justices-defenders-against-anti-democratic-demagogues/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-supreme-court-justices-defenders-against-anti-democratic-demagogues/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial stances on the status of UK and EU citizens in the Brexit negotiations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Introduction
A crucial Brexit issue with potentially significant consequences for many is the fate of UK citizens in the EU and EU citizens in the UK post-Brexit. Addressed early in Brexit negotiations, both sides have established positions: the EU through a Council decision outlining the mandate for Commission negotiators on May 22, and the UK through a government proposal on June 26. Despite claims to the contrary, the UK&amp;rsquo;s proposal didn&amp;rsquo;t precede the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 2: An Overview of the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement on Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/</guid><description>A Summary and Overview of the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
Starting January 1, 2021, the UK-EU relationship transitioned from the Brexit withdrawal agreement to a new framework. This new framework relies partly on the existing withdrawal agreement and partly on the newly established Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). It’s important to note that two additional agreements, concerning security information and Euratom, were also established.
This piece provides a summary of the TCA, drawing from initial observations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Windsor Framework Relaunch receives general acclaim with little said.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: en:User:Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
The opportunity to finalize the Windsor Framework and ensure its acceptance was limited. The challenging task of establishing trade rules for goods moving between Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK had been largely settled almost a year prior. The objective was to minimize trade friction within the UK while upholding the EU Single Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-windsor-framework-relaunch-receives-general-acclaim-with-little-said/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Failed Gamble: Brexit Election aftermath and the future steps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent UK election concluded with an unexpected &amp;lsquo;hung Parliament,&amp;rsquo; where no single party secured a majority in the House of Commons. This raises questions about the future of Brexit.
Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s Conservative party undeniably faced a major setback. The Prime Minister called for this election three years ahead of schedule, seeking a stronger majority to solidify her Brexit plan. Instead, voters reduced her majority, resulting in a minority government...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Violating International Law on a Broad Scale: The Northern Ireland Protocol Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Reader in Public Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons
In 2020, Brandon Lewis acknowledged that the UK&amp;rsquo;s Internal Market Bill would contravene the Withdrawal Agreement, albeit in a limited capacity. However, regarding the recent Northern Ireland Protocol Bill, Lewis insists that it will not violate international law. This assertion is debatable, as the Bill&amp;rsquo;s implications are vast.
The Protocol and Brexit
The UK government argues that the Protocol lacks cross-community support within Northern Ireland and cannot continue as is...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/violating-international-law-on-a-broad-scale-the-northern-ireland-protocol-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit has not resulted in any legal changes yet, as the Court of Justice of the European Union continues to rule on the execution of European Arrest Warrants issued by the UK before Brexit Day.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While there are many legal discussions surrounding the impact of Brexit, the ultimate authority on these matters, at least for the EU, is the EU Court of Justice. The Court&amp;rsquo;s first ruling on Brexit, released today, clarifies the legal standing until Brexit Day and potentially influences the approach after that.
The judgment in the case of RO addressed whether Ireland remained obligated to enforce a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) issued by the UK considering its impending withdrawal from the EU after triggering Article 50 TEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 1: The Impact of the Revised European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement on Health - Patients and Reciprocal Healthcare (Updated as of March 18, 2018)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, holding the Jean Monnet Chair in EU Law at the University of Sheffield, has reviewed the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s revised draft legal text on the Withdrawal Agreement (WA) as of March 15, 2018. Her analysis focuses on how the revised text impacts reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the EU-27 post-Brexit, particularly for UK pensioners residing in other EU countries and the use of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) for emergency care...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the use of "cultural fitness" as an evaluation standard in breach of EU and UK public procurement regulations when purchasing Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-use-of-cultural-fitness-as-an-evaluation-standard-in-breach-of-eu-and-uk-public-procurement-regulations-when-purchasing-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:23:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-use-of-cultural-fitness-as-an-evaluation-standard-in-breach-of-eu-and-uk-public-procurement-regulations-when-purchasing-brexit/</guid><description>Albert Sánchez Graells, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Bristol*
A recent Guardian article by Heather Stewart revealed that the UK Department for International Trade is seeking bids from tech companies that demonstrate the right &amp;lsquo;cultural fit&amp;rsquo;. This requirement, interpreted as a way to determine support for Brexit, raises concerns about potential bias and unfair treatment. This practice, in my view, goes against both EU and UK public procurement regulations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-use-of-cultural-fitness-as-an-evaluation-standard-in-breach-of-eu-and-uk-public-procurement-regulations-when-purchasing-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-use-of-cultural-fitness-as-an-evaluation-standard-in-breach-of-eu-and-uk-public-procurement-regulations-when-purchasing-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Schrems II and the Transfer of Personal Data: You Were Only Meant to Blow the Bloody Doors Off!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued its highly anticipated decision regarding the legitimacy of standard contractual clauses (SCCs) for transferring personal data outside the European Union. This decision is part of a larger effort to challenge the “surveillance capitalism” model employed by many online businesses. While this case significantly impacts SCCs and Facebook&amp;rsquo;s operations, it also reveals the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s stance against mass surveillance, a recurring theme in European jurisprudence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 1: The future of the UK's free movement of people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
*The authors are both at the University of Cambridge and funded by the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe program. They thank their colleagues, Graeme Ross, Steve Peers, Jonathan Portes and Madelaine Sumption.
Introduction
A primary reason many voted to exit the European Union on June 23, 2016, was concern over immigration. Many felt the UK had &amp;ldquo;lost control&amp;rdquo; of its borders and that leaving the EU would allow the UK government to regain control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ ruling in Joined Cases C-203/15 and C-698/15 Tele2 and Watson (Grand Chamber) on data retention and national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent court decision examined the legality of national data retention laws from a human rights standpoint. These laws remained in effect even after the Data Retention Directive was struck down in the Digital Rights Ireland case due to its disproportionate impact on Articles 7 and 8 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (EUCFR). This judgment clarifies the interpretation of Articles 7 and 8 within EU law, particularly in the context of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Directive, and may impact the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Data Protection Bill and UK-EU Data Transfers: A Story of Brexit and Data Protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 13:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Elif Mendos Kuşkonmaz, PhD student at Queen Mary, University of London[*]
Introduction
A Bosnian folk song tells the story of a Pasha who died from a severe illness. When his wife heard about his passing, she died from grief. Similarly, now that the UK has chosen to leave the European Union, will the same fate befall data protection laws once the UK exits the EU?
The UK&amp;rsquo;s current data protection law, the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA), incorporates the EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 Data Protection Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Impact of Brexit on Human Rights Law in the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-brexit-on-human-rights-law-in-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 03:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-brexit-on-human-rights-law-in-the-uk/</guid><description>Steve Peers
*Adapted from comments made at the launch of Conor Gearty’s book On Fantasy Island: Britain, Europe and Human Rights
The future of human rights law in a post-Brexit UK starts with the fate of the Human Rights Act, the subject of Professor Gearty&amp;rsquo;s new book. On Fantasy Island provides a detailed analysis of the Act within its social, political, and historical context. It emphasizes both the legal intricacies and the human impact of human rights cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-brexit-on-human-rights-law-in-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-brexit-on-human-rights-law-in-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit: The Prime Minister chooses the incorrect direction.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-the-prime-minister-chooses-the-incorrect-direction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 17:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-the-prime-minister-chooses-the-incorrect-direction/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Prime Minister Theresa May’s recent speech provided insights into the UK government’s approach to Brexit. While there were some positive takeaways, the speech ultimately presented a flawed vision for the country’s future.
Positive Aspects of the Speech
The speech commendably acknowledges that a successful EU remains in Britain’s best interest, both economically and in terms of security. May’s suggestions for the EU, though unlikely to be well-received, offer some sensible points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-the-prime-minister-chooses-the-incorrect-direction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-the-prime-minister-chooses-the-incorrect-direction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regaining Control: British Travel to the EU Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regaining-control-british-travel-to-the-eu-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:23:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regaining-control-british-travel-to-the-eu-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*linked to research on the upcoming 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Photo credit: John Fielding, via Wikimedia Commons
It&amp;rsquo;s self-evident that the UK leaving the EU has changed travel and residency rules for British citizens within the EU. This change mirrors the altered regulations for EU citizens traveling to and residing in the UK, a specific demand from the Leave campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regaining-control-british-travel-to-the-eu-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regaining-control-british-travel-to-the-eu-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing and Annotating the Brexit Transition Period: Is it a Bridge Leading to Nowhere?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent weeks have seen significant progress in the Brexit negotiations. The EU27 and the UK reached an agreement on a substantial portion of the withdrawal agreement, including a transition period from March 2019 to the end of 2020, a key concern for the UK. This agreement follows earlier drafts and sets the stage for defining the future relationship between the UK and the EU, to be formalized in separate treaties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New developments in EU case law regarding extradition to non-EU countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A recent European Court of Justice (ECJ) decision in the Pisciotti case concerning the extradition of citizens from one EU Member State to a non-EU country (in this instance, the USA) provides further legal precedent in this domain and carries potential implications for Brexit. This ruling expands on the September 2016 Petruhhin judgment, which dealt with extraditing citizens from one EU Member State to Russia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-developments-in-eu-case-law-regarding-extradition-to-non-eu-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 4: Immigration in the EU Referendum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
How does the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the European Union (EU) affect immigration and asylum? This piece examines this complex topic, focusing on migration to the UK by both non-EU and EU citizens.
Non-EU migration
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between non-EU and EU migration in the Brexit referendum discussion for two key reasons. Firstly, while EU migration is inherently linked to the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership, non-EU migration is not...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Analysis of the Strasbourg Agreement dated March 11, 2019: A Summary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-the-strasbourg-agreement-dated-march-11-2019-a-summary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 09:53:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-the-strasbourg-agreement-dated-march-11-2019-a-summary/</guid><description>Professor Michael Dougan&amp;rsquo;s Analysis of the March 2019 Brexit Amendments Professor Michael Dougan, University of Liverpool, 12 March 2019
Summary: The legal classification of the “Instrument relating to the Withdrawal Agreement” and the “Joint Statement supplementing the Political Declaration” is insignificant. The crucial factor is whether these new elements meaningfully alter the withdrawal agreement endorsed in November 2018, which awaits Commons approval.
The Instrument primarily reiterates existing Withdrawal Agreement provisions without significant additions or changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-the-strasbourg-agreement-dated-march-11-2019-a-summary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-the-strasbourg-agreement-dated-march-11-2019-a-summary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The immigration issues in the UK renegotiation deal have been finalized.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
David Cameron has successfully negotiated a deal regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the EU. This post, the first in a series about the deal, focuses on &amp;ldquo;EU immigration&amp;rdquo; or, in terms of EU law, the free movement of EU citizens. I will delve into other important matters (competitiveness, Eurozone relations, sovereignty) and the legal structure of the deal later.
The deal comprises seven legal documents: a Decision by the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government (the &amp;ldquo;Decision&amp;rdquo;); a Statement from the Heads of State and Government (an agreed Council Decision); a Declaration by the European Council (representing the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government); and four declarations by the Commission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Paying tribute to Catalonia: The impact of EU law on movements for independence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:39:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent surge in support for pro-independence parties in Catalonia has revived discussions about the connection between EU law and independence movements within member states. This issue was previously discussed in the context of the Scottish independence referendum, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth revisiting now. There are three interconnected questions: Firstly, what happens if a region within a member state declares independence unilaterally, a potential scenario in Catalonia? Secondly, if a newly independent state, formerly part of an EU member, seeks continued EU membership, what are the implications?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/paying-tribute-to-catalonia-the-impact-of-eu-law-on-movements-for-independence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it necessary to apply the Charter in reconstructing the hierarchy of employment law norms?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</guid><description>The Uncertain Future of UK Employment Law in a Post-Brexit World Niall O’Connor, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The Charter and Brexit
Boris Johnson famously downplayed the significance of the Charter of Fundamental Rights during the Brexit campaign. He argued in a Telegraph article that the Charter&amp;rsquo;s provisions, such as the right to establish a school or pursue an occupation anywhere in the EU, are not &amp;ldquo;fundamental rights&amp;rdquo; as commonly understood and questioned their enforceability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British lawyers have made a significant impact on EU (migration) law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk, Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen, Netherlands.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) acknowledged the significant contributions of its British members to European integration and legal precedent. This recognition prompts reflection on the impact of British legal professionals on EU law, particularly in the areas of migration and free movement.
British judges and advocates-general, with their common law background, played a key role in shaping the CJEU into a more transparent and adaptable institution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Could the EU be considering the formation of a military force, and would the UK have the power to block it?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent discussions have centered around whether the EU is forming an army and if the UK has the power to veto such a move before Brexit. This debate, while heated, often lacks clarity. This piece aims to provide a clear understanding of the situation, concluding that the recent proposals don&amp;rsquo;t constitute an EU army, making a UK veto irrelevant.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy initially avoided defense matters, respecting Irish neutrality and the UK&amp;rsquo;s commitment to NATO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Resolving conflicts and the agreement for the UK's exit from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A key point of contention in the Brexit withdrawal agreement is how disputes will be settled. Specifically, there&amp;rsquo;s debate about whether the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) maintains authority over the UK. This post provides an overview of this issue and a detailed analysis of the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s provisions concerning dispute resolution and the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s role.
This post is the third in a series examining the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simply Refuse? The latest 'Stormont Brake' within the Windsor Framework (part 2 of the framework analysis)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</guid><description>The Stormont Brake: A Closer Look at its Potential Impact Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikimedia Commons Introduction
This analysis delves into the &amp;lsquo;Stormont Brake&amp;rsquo;, a new mechanism within the Windsor Framework designed to address concerns about how EU law applies to Northern Ireland. This analysis explores the text and interpretation of this &amp;lsquo;brake&amp;rsquo; on changes to EU law under the protocol. While it might never be used, understanding the mechanics of the Stormont Brake is crucial to grasp its potential implications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-refuse-the-latest-stormont-brake-within-the-windsor-framework-part-2-of-the-framework-analysis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 4 of the Brexit agreement: Examination of dispute resolution and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement between the EU and UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction and Overview
A crucial element of the &amp;lsquo;Brexit deal&amp;rsquo;, formally called the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA), is dispute resolution. This post provides a thorough analysis of the treaty&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution mechanisms and offers a concise summary upfront. (An update on April 29, 2021, incorporates the final TCA article numbers).
This is the fourth post in a series examining the TCA. It follows an overview of the TCA, an analysis of its social security provisions by Professor Tamara Hervey, and an exploration of the connections between the TCA and human rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Analysis of Article 50(1) TEU: Member States' Right to Decide on Withdrawal from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (London), PhD Candidate (Amsterdam) @KulpaBart Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) outlines the process for a Member State to withdraw from the European Union (EU). While seemingly straightforward, the first paragraph of this article raises questions about its interpretation.
Can a Member State unilaterally decide to withdraw under Article 50(1) TEU?
The primary question surrounding the first paragraph of Article 50 TEU is if it permits a unilateral withdrawal decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-analysis-of-article-50-1-teu-member-states-right-to-decide-on-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the draft UK/EU renegotiation deal considered to be 'legally binding and irreversible'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The draft agreement regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership has sparked significant debate. While some, mostly within the UK, believe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough, others, primarily from the remaining EU member states, argue it grants excessive revisions to EU law for a single member state. These are primarily substantive concerns. While I have previously addressed some immigration-related issues within the draft, I will delve into other substantive matters later...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can the EU be reformed without making changes to the Treaties?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is about to begin renegotiating its European Union membership, a process some call &amp;ldquo;EU reform.&amp;rdquo; However, several member states have already rejected the idea of treaty changes. So, is a renegotiation or reform package even possible?
While amending secondary EU legislation (or convincingly promising to do so) without altering the treaties is possible, there&amp;rsquo;s always a risk that such changes won&amp;rsquo;t happen or could be reversed later...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-eu-be-reformed-without-making-changes-to-the-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will Brexit be unavoidable? The UK's EU membership post-General Election.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Conservative majority win in the UK brings up significant questions regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued membership in the European Union. This piece will initially address concerns surrounding the referendum and the renegotiation process.
The Brexit Referendum
What are the main issues surrounding the approaching referendum?
The new government&amp;rsquo;s plan to renegotiate the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership followed by a referendum (Brexit) based on the renegotiation&amp;rsquo;s results by the end of 2017 is paramount...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit: Explaining the concepts of EFTA and the EEA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/</guid><description>Dr. Michael Sánchez Rydelski and Cath Howdle*
*Respectively Member and Deputy Director of the Legal Service of the EFTA Surveillance Authority. Nothing in the present article binds or necessarily reflects the views of the EFTA Surveillance Authority.
1. Introduction
This article doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer a Brexit solution, leaving that to governments and negotiators. Instead, it provides guidance on key aspects of the European Free Trade Association (&amp;ldquo;EFTA&amp;rdquo;) and European Economic Area (&amp;ldquo;EEA&amp;rdquo;)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Responding to Giles Fraser on family values and Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responding-to-giles-fraser-on-family-values-and-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:27:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responding-to-giles-fraser-on-family-values-and-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Giles Fraser&amp;rsquo;s article, which criticizes &amp;ldquo;Remainers&amp;rdquo; for not considering family issues, is flawed. In reality, many &amp;ldquo;Remainers,&amp;rdquo; including Professor Peers himself, have openly discussed the impact of Brexit on families.
Fraser&amp;rsquo;s central argument is that children should be responsible for the care of their aging parents. He criticizes social mobility, particularly the free movement within the EU, which he believes leads individuals away from their communities and families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responding-to-giles-fraser-on-family-values-and-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responding-to-giles-fraser-on-family-values-and-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Personal Perspective on Citizens' Rights Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
I seldom share personal experiences on this blog or elsewhere. However, I believe it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to approach immigration from a personal angle, not just as an abstract concept. While economic data is valuable for understanding the economic impact, and legal analysis is vital for activists and negotiators, it&amp;rsquo;s equally important to remember that migrants are individuals and families whose lives are impacted by immigration policy changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recognition of Professional Qualifications after Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 23:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</guid><description>Dáire McCormack-George*
*The author, a Ph.D. Candidate in Law and Scholar of Trinity College Dublin, the University of Dublin, based this blog post on his presentation at the third Radboud University Economic Law Conference, ‘Upgrading Trade and Services in EU and International Economic Law’, on June 15, 2018. He thanks the conference participants and attendees for their engaging questions. All errors are his own.
Introduction
The current draft withdrawal agreement between the UK and the EU proposes the temporary application of Directive 2005/36/EC (the Recognition Directive) until the transition period ends, ensuring continued recognition of qualifications recognized beforehand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recognition-of-professional-qualifications-after-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Background information for next week's hearing on the scope of EU external trade policy: Opinion 2/15</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</guid><description>Dr Andrés Delgado Casteleiro
Senior Research Fellow, Max Planck Institute Luxembourg for International, European and Regulatory Procedural Law
Introduction
On September 13th and 14th, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) convened a full court hearing to discuss Opinion 2/15. This opinion focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to establish a new Free Trade Agreement (FTA) with Singapore. This blog post will provide a concise summary of the key issues likely to arise during these hearings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is equal treatment possible in the fair movement of people? (Part Two)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
The authors are both at the University of Cambridge and funded by the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme
Introduction
This blog post proposes a UK/EU migration policy based on &amp;ldquo;fair movement&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;free movement.&amp;rdquo; This system would require work permits for genuine employment or self-employment and a simplified registration process like the one used for Croatian migrants.
The authors suggest limiting the principle of equal treatment for work and benefits, using existing restrictions within the Citizens’ Rights Directive 2004/38 and the Brussels New Settlement Agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to remain in the single market even after exiting the EU? The proposed lawsuit regarding Article 127 of the EEA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</guid><description>Could the UK Remain in the Single Market While Exiting the EU? Steve Peers
A potential legal battle questions whether the UK can remain part of the European Economic Area (EEA) even if it leaves the EU. This situation involves both international and national legal complexities. Let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the EEA itself.
Understanding the EEA
Established in 1994, the EEA treaty aimed to expand the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market to European Free Trade Area (EFTA) nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should the UK continue to vote on its EU membership in an ongoing referendum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-the-uk-continue-to-vote-on-its-eu-membership-in-an-ongoing-referendum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:51:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-the-uk-continue-to-vote-on-its-eu-membership-in-an-ongoing-referendum/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent news report suggested that individuals campaigning for the UK to leave the European Union in the upcoming referendum are prepared to demand a second referendum if the outcome is to remain. On the surface, this appears to indicate that these &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; supporters anticipate defeat and are planning to contest the result. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear if this is a strategic message for them to promote, but offering strategic advice to the &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; campaign is not my objective...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-the-uk-continue-to-vote-on-its-eu-membership-in-an-ongoing-referendum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-the-uk-continue-to-vote-on-its-eu-membership-in-an-ongoing-referendum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 1: Examination of Healthcare Entitlements in the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield examines the healthcare entitlements, if any, provided by the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) that was provisionally agreed upon on December 24, 2020.
Introduction
The TCA includes provisions for social security coordination, similar to EU law but considerably weaker. These provisions are found in Heading Four and are not typical of standard trade agreements like CETA.
Many are interested in the future of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) scheme, as private travel insurance is often expensive or inaccessible, particularly for the elderly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of the Environment and Climate Provisions in the Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Introduction
The start of the new year marked a significant shift in the UK-EU relationship, ending the Brexit transition and ushering in the provisional Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). This post delves into the TCA&amp;rsquo;s environmental and climate change provisions, drawing on prior analyses of the TCA&amp;rsquo;s overview, social security provisions, human rights aspects, and dispute settlement mechanisms. (Updated as of April 28, 2021, to reflect the final TCA article numbering)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The lives of UK nationals living in other EU Member States have been significantly altered by Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah McCloskey and Tamara Hervey, Sheffield Law School
Following a string of significant political shifts, many can relate to the feelings of unease and worry stemming from the resulting instability. Currently, those hit hardest are individuals who have exercised their right to free movement without fear of it being revoked. This is the essence of Brexit: a source of discontent for some, a daily news item for others, but for EU citizens in the UK and UK citizens residing in other Member States, it holds the power to drastically alter their lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's new law on travel authorization for non-EU citizens creating a brave new world?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A new European Union (EU) law regarding travel authorization for non-EU citizens visiting the EU was recently announced. This new law will impact millions of travelers annually, potentially including British citizens post-Brexit. This law, though not immediately applicable, holds significant future implications. This explanation aims to clarify its reach and functionality. (Update: the final law was officially published in September 2018).
Basics of the system..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit must ensure that health is not negatively impacted, which includes ensuring that there are adequate rules in place for medical professional qualifications.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield argues that a Leave.EU tweet claiming EU regulations unnecessarily extend doctor training is misleading.
Hervey presents four key arguments: Firstly, the UK, as a long-standing EU member, significantly shaped EU medical training standards. While these standards do influence UK medical qualifications, their impact is limited, and the UK has the authority to propose changes. The current system, including the duration of training, reflects the UK&amp;rsquo;s active participation in shaping these regulations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-must-ensure-that-health-is-not-negatively-impacted-which-includes-ensuring-that-there-are-adequate-rules-in-place-for-medical-professional-qualifications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for humans to make a legally binding commitment to Treaty change?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British Prime Minister David Cameron has surprised many by securing concessions from the EU, such as a smaller EU budget and a Conservative majority in the House of Commons. However, his goal of renegotiating the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership raises the question: are his demands even achievable?
This question arises from Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recently confirmed intention to secure not immediate Treaty changes, but rather a &amp;ldquo;legally binding&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;irreversible&amp;rdquo; agreement that would commit to future Treaty changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the notice to withdraw from the EU being revoked? Wightman's opinion suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
Is initiating the Article 50 withdrawal process from the EU irreversible, like jumping off a cliff? Or is it more like going shopping, where you can change your mind along the way, in the parking lot, or even inside the store? Perhaps this change of heart might be due to discovering the promised sale doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, the management is under investigation, and the supposed extensive international food section is just a couple of dusty packages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Allister Round 2: Exploring the depths of UK constitutional law in the Mariana Trench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD student, Queen’s University Belfast School of Law
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikicommons
Introduction
It&amp;rsquo;s a common observation in UK constitutional law that complex issues rarely have simple solutions. Instead, they often result in multiple, overlapping interpretations. This is certainly the case with the recent Allister and others v Prime Minister and others [2022] NICA 15 ruling from the Northern Ireland Court of Appeal (NICA). It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this case is headed to the UK Supreme Court on appeal, ensuring further analysis and discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Putting an end to uncertainty: advocating for the protection of the rights of EU27 and UK citizens post-Brexit - including a suggested draft.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent draft of the Brexit withdrawal agreement might encounter obstacles and potentially fail to gain approval due to conflicting viewpoints on the Irish border or other matters. Should this occur, the question arises: what will happen to the provisions concerning EU27 citizens residing in the UK, and UK citizens residing in the EU27, prior to Brexit?
To provide maximum assurance regarding their immigration status, there is a compelling rationale for separating these provisions from the main withdrawal agreement and ratifying them under a distinct agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-uncertainty-advocating-for-the-protection-of-the-rights-of-eu27-and-uk-citizens-post-brexit-including-a-suggested-draft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preventing the UK from facing another Brexit crisis: Prolonging the Transition Period beyond 1 July 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</guid><description>René Repasi, Associate Professor of EU Law at Erasmus University Rotterdam, Netherlands
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the EU on January 31st, 2020, marked the completion of the initial &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo; phase, focused on resolving the implications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s past membership. This followed the UK general election, which saw Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Conservative Party secure a significant majority in the House of Commons, leading to the swift ratification of the Withdrawal Agreement (WA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Scotland and Brexit: Courageous Heart or Fearful Creature?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</guid><description>Steve Peers
During the Scottish National Party (SNP) conference, Scotland&amp;rsquo;s First Minister, Nicola Sturgeon, revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to present a draft bill for a second independence referendum. She also announced their intention to introduce an alternate plan ensuring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the EU single market, even if the rest of the UK chooses to leave. This proposal would involve granting the Scottish Parliament substantial new powers, encompassing all current EU-related powers held by Scotland and additional authority to negotiate international treaties and manage immigration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phase 2 of Brexit negotiations: analysis of the EU27's stance in negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 02:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU Council is anticipated to establish its negotiating directives for the second stage of Brexit discussions on January 29th. These talks will primarily focus on a transition period after Brexit Day, during which existing EU law would still be applicable in the UK. A leaked version of these directives has surfaced, providing an opportunity to analyze them in detail. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is subject to change pending final approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Divergent rulings on Parliament's suspension in England and Scotland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The A-Z of Scots Law: From Avizandum to the Zany Antics of Boris Johnson
Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s recent actions are under scrutiny by the Scottish legal system. In the Cherry case, the Scottish court deemed the decision to suspend Parliament unlawful. Further legal action is anticipated regarding the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s reported refusal to adhere to the European Union (Withdrawal) (No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you are a voter who is undecided or uncertain, here is why you should consider remaining in the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 05:40:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
As the referendum campaign concludes, undecided voters should consider the arguments for remaining in the European Union. This piece outlines the reasons for staying, addressing counter-arguments from the Leave campaign.
Why Remain?
Staying in the EU offers several advantages: economic benefits, security, improved workers&amp;rsquo; rights, and environmental protection. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine each.
Economic Benefits
EU membership grants the UK access to the world&amp;rsquo;s largest market, along with trade deals with 50 additional countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-are-a-voter-who-is-undecided-or-uncertain-here-is-why-you-should-consider-remaining-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The legal status and impact of the UK/EU renegotiation deal.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 14:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</guid><description>Is the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiated EU membership deal legally binding? Steve Peers explores whether the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiated EU membership deal is legally binding and what implications this has. He examines various aspects of the deal, including its legal status, enforceability, and potential for reversibility.
Legal Complexity and Forms The renegotiation deal is comprised of seven legal documents: a Decision by EU Heads of State and Government, a Statement by the same group (including a draft Council Decision), a European Council Declaration, and four Commission declarations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and the Protection of EU Transnational Rights - Part II The Stance of the Supreme Court</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:43:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
This piece expands on a previous one concerning the High Court&amp;rsquo;s stance on protecting EU Law-based transnational rights within the context of the Miller case. It examines the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the High Court&amp;rsquo;s position and the resulting implications for EU law. The significance of transnational rights persists for two primary reasons. Firstly, beyond the immediate impact on EU and UK citizens facing Brexit-related disruptions, it highlights the fundamental nature of individual rights within the EU legal framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-protection-of-eu-transnational-rights-part-ii-the-stance-of-the-supreme-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's upcoming trade policy is beginning to form with the release of the Opinion on the EU/Singapore FTA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s authority regarding trade agreements has been debated for years in the European Court of Justice (ECJ), as it significantly affects the balance of power between the EU and its Member States concerning international economic policies. Treaty revisions, especially the Treaty of Lisbon, have altered these rules, making this issue even more important due to recent controversies surrounding EU trade negotiations (notably with Canada and the USA) and the UK-EU trade talks post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Charter of Rights post Conservative party amendments to UK human rights legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many drivers have encountered the unfortunate experience of hitting a small animal that darted across the road at the wrong moment. Reactions vary from distress to indifference, but some feel a sense of triumph, having removed an obstacle from their path.
This last reaction mirrors the Conservative party&amp;rsquo;s stance on EU law within their UK human rights law reform proposals. They aim to diminish EU law&amp;rsquo;s influence, much like a driver indifferent to roadkill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Protocol Proposal for Brexit and the Rights of EU27 Citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</guid><description>Stijn Smismans, Professor of Law, School of Law and Politics, Director of the Centre for European Law and Governance, Cardiff University
While a draft Withdrawal Agreement (WA) between the EU and UK, partially agreed upon in March 2018, aims to address the post-Brexit status of EU27 citizens in the UK and British citizens in the EU, concerns remain about the process of securing residency rights. Although the EU has made efforts to safeguard these rights, the focus has been on the scope rather than the process of obtaining them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU/Canada free trade deal and investor protection disputes a blessing in disguise or a cause for concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent news suggests the EU/Canada free-trade agreement (CETA) faces obstacles due to the German government&amp;rsquo;s opposition to rules concerning investor/state dispute settlement. This situation carries potential implications for various aspects, including the EU/Canada and EU/USA trade deals, the EU&amp;rsquo;s broader trade and investment policies, and even the UK&amp;rsquo;s potential departure from the EU (&amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;).
Background
After commencing negotiations in 2009, the EU and Canada reached a preliminary agreement in 2013, pending finalization of technical points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Unassuming Suggestion: Preventing a Standstill on the Irish Border in the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Brexit withdrawal agreement negotiations are in danger of collapsing due to disagreements on managing the Irish border. The UK government&amp;rsquo;s lack of concrete proposals for customs away from the border is concerning. Additionally, the UK Foreign Secretary&amp;rsquo;s inability to differentiate between a simple congestion charge and the complexities of border control is disappointing.
In anticipation of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s upcoming proposals, I have drafted a text (Annex 1) addressing the Irish border in the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If the UK remains a member of the EU past May 22nd, it will be necessary for the country to hold European Parliament elections in order to uphold democratic principles.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</guid><description>Professor Eleanor Spaventa, Bocconi University
The UK&amp;rsquo;s political climate surrounding Brexit is highly unstable. Prime Minister May&amp;rsquo;s strategy of delaying a decision may or may not work, but it seems to have created a situation where extending Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union is unavoidable. If Parliament approves the Withdrawal Agreement this week, the UK will need more time to implement the necessary legislation before leaving the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can devolved powers help mitigate the negative effects of Brexit on Scotland?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 07:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The UK&amp;rsquo;s devolution process, implemented with the understanding of continued EU membership, granted legislative and executive autonomy to Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland through specific Acts of Parliament. These Acts, while establishing varying degrees of autonomy, shared a common thread: devolved powers must not contradict UK&amp;rsquo;s international obligations, particularly EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-devolved-powers-help-mitigate-the-negative-effects-of-brexit-on-scotland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guardianship, freedom of movement, and child rights: the SM ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*This blog post expands on research that informed the upcoming revised edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Defining a &amp;ldquo;family member&amp;rdquo; legally can be complex, especially when it comes to immigration law and child welfare. The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment in the SM case highlights these complexities, particularly where EU free movement law intersects with the family law of non-EU nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Issues Surrounding Scotland, the EU, and 'Indyref2'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 08:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Scottish First Minister Nicola Sturgeon recently revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s desire to pursue a second independence referendum. This announcement follows the UK government&amp;rsquo;s dismissal of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s proposed Brexit alternatives. The timing of this potential referendum, contingent on the UK&amp;rsquo;s final Brexit arrangements, brings Scotland&amp;rsquo;s EU membership into focus. While a second referendum would encompass issues beyond EU relations, this analysis will primarily address the legal complexities surrounding Scotland&amp;rsquo;s potential EU membership, particularly the misconception of budget deficits as a barrier to entry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gazing into the Void: The Future of Citizens' Rights in the Event of a No Deal Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 03:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
After resisting guarantees for EU27 citizens&amp;rsquo; rights in the UK for over two years, the UK government has finally issued a plan outlining the treatment of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 in a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit scenario. This comes as the UK Parliament prepares to vote on the withdrawal agreement and after the European Commission published its own position on this matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who should have control over the 'emergency brake' on benefits for EU citizens: the Commission or the Council?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
During the UK&amp;rsquo;s negotiations to leave the European Union, a key point of contention arose: the process for enacting an &amp;ldquo;emergency brake&amp;rdquo; to restrict EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to in-work benefits. Should a Member State have the authority to implement this measure independently, perhaps with a requirement to inform the Commission and Council? Or should it be required to submit a request, leaving the decision of authorization to the Commission and/or Council?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 3 of the updated Brexit Withdrawal Agreement focuses on dispute resolution.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
This post examines the dispute settlement mechanisms outlined in the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement, specifically addressing the role of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). It is part of a series analyzing the updated agreement, which includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship. Previous posts have provided an overview of the agreement and examined the transition period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Irony in Immigration Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:11:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</guid><description>Daniel Thym, Professor of Public, European and International Law at the University of Konstanz
Immigration was a key issue during the Brexit debate, with &amp;ldquo;taking back control&amp;rdquo; becoming a central theme. In her January speech in Lancaster, Theresa May emphasized that controlling immigration was a primary goal of the Brexit negotiations. She stressed the public&amp;rsquo;s message that Brexit must equate to managing the influx of people from Europe to Britain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 3: Is there a lack of democracy in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, Middlesex University
Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The European Union is frequently criticized for being undemocratic or suffering from a &amp;ldquo;democratic deficit.&amp;rdquo; One common assertion is that all EU decisions are made by the unelected bureaucrats of the European Commission. This post will demonstrate why this criticism is fundamentally flawed. It stems from a misunderstanding of both the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s actual powers within the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes and how the European Commission is appointed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's 'emergency brake' preserving or abolishing the free movement of people?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Steve Peers
If British pro-Europeans could travel back in time, their priority should be returning to 2004. They should focus all efforts on persuading the then-British government to reconsider granting immediate free movement of workers from new EU member states. While economically advantageous, this decision has severely damaged public support for EU membership in the UK, as well as for the UK Labour Party.
Today, the free movement of people is often framed as a fundamental flaw within the EU, prompting calls for the UK to either leave or renegotiate its terms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions on Scotland's Position in Europe: Analysis of the Scottish Government's latest suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The Scottish government recently released its anticipated paper exploring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s position within Europe. While acknowledging the government&amp;rsquo;s support for both EU membership and Scottish independence, the paper concentrates on potential outcomes should Brexit occur while Scotland remains part of the UK. Accusations that the paper dismisses referendum results, regarding either Brexit or Scottish independence, or simply rehashes arguments for independence are unfounded.
The paper essentially presents two main options: a UK-wide approach to Brexit that considers the concerns of Scottish voters, or, if that fails, a separate approach specifically for Scotland...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What impact will the Dutch referendum on the EU/Ukraine association agreement have?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Brkan and Alexander Hoogenboom
On April 6, 2016, Dutch voters rejected the EU-Ukraine association agreement. The vote, with 61.1 percent voting against the agreement, was not unexpected based on recent polling. While voter turnout barely passed the 30 percent minimum, the outcome itself delivers a resounding &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;
The EU has established numerous association agreements with countries like Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, Israel, Egypt, Chile, Kosovo, and others. So why was a referendum held specifically for Ukraine?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unemployed EU citizens may benefit from the CJEU's decision, potentially complicating David Cameron's renegotiation strategy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ability of EU citizens to move freely between Member States, often referred to as ‘immigration,’ has sparked significant political debate, particularly in the UK. Access to benefits for these individuals remains a point of contention. The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has an opportunity to provide clarity on key aspects of this issue in the upcoming case of Alimanovic. An Advocate-General recently issued a non-binding opinion on this case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the ECJ to intervene in Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 06:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent High Court decision mandates that the UK government must secure parliamentary approval before initiating Article 50, the process for exiting the European Union. While this post won&amp;rsquo;t delve into the national constitutional law aspects, it will examine the potential involvement of EU courts in Brexit disputes.
Following the government&amp;rsquo;s announced appeal to the Supreme Court, some have suggested a further &amp;ldquo;appeal&amp;rdquo; to the European Court of Justice (ECJ)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The draft adequacy decisions: Data Protection in the UK and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-draft-adequacy-decisions-data-protection-in-the-uk-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-draft-adequacy-decisions-data-protection-in-the-uk-and-the-eu/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Background
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Law Enforcement Directive (LED) have strict rules about transferring personal data outside the EU. Adequacy decisions are the simplest way to ensure these transfers are safe. Currently, twelve countries have received full or partial adequacy decisions, including Japan, which has additional safeguards in place. The US previously held an adequacy status, but the Court of Justice overturned this in the Schrems II case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-draft-adequacy-decisions-data-protection-in-the-uk-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-draft-adequacy-decisions-data-protection-in-the-uk-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Farewell, harsh world: will there be visas for holidays post-Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Previously, I maintained that British citizens needing visas for short trips to the EU after Brexit was highly unlikely. I even disagreed with some &amp;ldquo;Remain&amp;rdquo; supporters who feared this outcome. The EU consistently lifts short-term visa requirements for wealthy nations (like the USA, Canada, and Japan) if they reciprocate for EU citizens. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t envision those on the &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; side supporting short-term visa requirements for EU citizens visiting the UK post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It's finally here - the CJEU has confirmed that UK citizens have officially lost their EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has affirmed that UK citizens lost EU citizenship due to Brexit, as per a recent judgment. This aligns with the earlier Advocate-General’s opinion. While other similar cases exist, the CJEU is unlikely to deviate from this decision.
This judgment is notable for its dismissal of arguments advocating for the retention of EU citizenship for British citizens, marking a significant shift...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Negotiating the future relationship between the UK and EU: the EU's mandate for negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Thanks to Georgina Wright, of the Institute for Government, for a &amp;rsquo;track changes&amp;rsquo; version of the negotiation mandate. The usual disclaimer applies.
This week, the UK-EU future relationship negotiation process progressed. The EU Council approved the negotiation mandate, differing from the initial proposal. This post provides an updated analysis, comparing the final mandate to the political declaration, highlighting differences between the EU and UK&amp;rsquo;s positions that are expected to make negotiations difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reading between the lines of the High Court's Brexit ruling: Protecting EU transnational rights and their safeguards.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 08:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
This piece revisits the recent High Court ruling on the UK government&amp;rsquo;s authority to initiate the process of leaving the EU. It delves deeper into the judgment&amp;rsquo;s EU law implications, going beyond the political turmoil it has caused and potentially extending beyond the immediate consequences of Brexit. The article argues that the judgment, though focused on UK constitutional law, also touches upon the issue of safeguarding transnational rights, such as those of British citizens in other EU countries, during a Member State&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A revival of the Brexit negotiations? Theresa May's address in Florence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s recent speech was largely seen as an effort to jumpstart the Brexit negotiations, which have hit a roadblock, particularly regarding financial matters. The question is whether her speech will be successful, or if its underlying goal of appeasing Leave voters in the UK, especially those in the cabinet and the media, will undermine its effectiveness. Additionally, it prompts questions about the future relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-revival-of-the-brexit-negotiations-theresa-may-s-address-in-florence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Referendum Briefing 6: The Impact on EU Employment and Equality Law Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers suggests that while some claim there would be a &amp;ldquo;bonfire of rights&amp;rdquo; if the UK left the EU, particularly in employment and equality, others argue that the EU has no bearing on these laws in the UK. This post will demonstrate that EU law has significantly improved employment and equality rights in the UK, especially for women in the workplace.
A study of all UK cases reaching the EU court concerning these issues reveals that 60% of cases involving equal treatment for women resulted in findings that UK law was inadequate, leading to improved workplace protections for women...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extension and elections: It is important to discuss Article 50.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</guid><description>Professors Catherine Barnard (University of Cambridge) and Steve Weatherill (University of Oxford) explore the implications of Article 50, the exit clause for leaving the European Union. While brief and seemingly straightforward, Article 50 leaves much open to interpretation.
The authors begin by outlining the process for extending the two-year withdrawal period, noting that an extension would require unanimous agreement from all EU member states. They suggest that an extension is likely to be granted if requested by the UK, as it would provide additional time for the UK to either pass the necessary legislation to implement the Withdrawal Agreement or prepare for a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to unilaterally revoke an Article 50 notice of withdrawal from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 14:31:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Currently, there are no indications that either the UK government or the opposition Labour party are contemplating the reversal of the UK&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal from the EU. Neither party seems interested in initiating another referendum concerning EU membership. Nevertheless, spurred by Nigel Farage&amp;rsquo;s recent attempt to garner attention, the possibility of an additional Brexit referendum, which inherently implies the revocability of the Article 50 notice, remains a topic of public discourse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-unilaterally-revoke-an-article-50-notice-of-withdrawal-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit Negotiations: A Comprehensive Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 05:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK formally initiated the Brexit process by sending the Article 50 withdrawal letter to the EU on March 29th. The EU responded with its draft Brexit negotiating guidelines.
This post offers a thorough analysis of the EU&amp;rsquo;s draft guidelines, comparing them to the UK&amp;rsquo;s stance as articulated in Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s Chatham House speech last January. Although subject to potential modifications before their final adoption on April 29th, significant alterations to the draft guidelines are improbable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-negotiations-a-comprehensive-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dispute resolution between the EU and UK after Brexit in the context of the White Paper.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Emilija Leinarte*
*Professor of EU law, University of Cambridge and PhD student, University of Cambridge. This research has received support from the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme.
A recent publication by UK in a Changing Europe examined various governing structures that could be used to manage the UK-EU relationship following Brexit. The released White Paper offers a glimpse into the institutional structure that the UK envisions for its future dealings with the EU after withdrawal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Commission's new proposal for long-term resident non-EU citizens (part 1)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Marcomob, via Wikimedia commons
The EU has a longstanding interest in regulating the legal status of non-EU citizens residing long-term within its Member States as part of its broader legal migration policy. The current law, a 2003 Directive amended in 2010, focuses on extending rights to those with refugee or subsidiary protection status. A recent Commission proposal aims to further expand the rights of this large group of non-EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Perhaps we are drawn to the suffering: The conclusion of the legal battle over the Northern Ireland Protocol.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</guid><description>Colin Murray, Law Professor, University of Newcastle
Photo credit: ChrisVTG photography, via Wikicommons media
In October 2019, the UK government, led by Boris Johnson, reached a Withdrawal Agreement with the EU. This agreement encompassed a Northern Ireland Protocol iteration based on closely aligned rules governing goods between Northern Ireland and the EU. Notably, no comparable provisions addressed goods regulations for Great Britain. In January 2020, Westminster passed legislation to enact this agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/perhaps-we-are-drawn-to-the-suffering-the-conclusion-of-the-legal-battle-over-the-northern-ireland-protocol/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How can the issue of Suella be resolved? Exploring the legal implications of breaching and terminating the withdrawal agreement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent news suggests the UK may plan to violate the Brexit withdrawal agreement, with new Attorney-General Suella Braverman potentially seeking legal justification. This makes examining the repercussions of such a breach crucial. While the dispute resolution mechanisms within the agreement and the UK&amp;rsquo;s Withdrawal Agreement Act have been analyzed separately, this piece aims to provide a comprehensive overview, encompassing international law perspectives. This blog post summarizes the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution clauses and the international law principles concerning treaty termination, exploring their interplay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Falsehoods, lies, and misleading statements about EU citizens in the context of the 2019 UK election.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/falsehoods-lies-and-misleading-statements-about-eu-citizens-in-the-context-of-the-2019-uk-election/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 23:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/falsehoods-lies-and-misleading-statements-about-eu-citizens-in-the-context-of-the-2019-uk-election/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While political misinformation existed before the internet, online platforms have undoubtedly accelerated its spread. All political parties and sides of a debate engage in spreading false information, though the extent may vary. Recently, several government ministers have made a series of inaccurate or misleading statements regarding EU citizens residing in the UK. This appears to be a calculated tactic to secure votes from individuals with xenophobic sentiments in the upcoming election, making a systematic refutation necessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/falsehoods-lies-and-misleading-statements-about-eu-citizens-in-the-context-of-the-2019-uk-election/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/falsehoods-lies-and-misleading-statements-about-eu-citizens-in-the-context-of-the-2019-uk-election/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the Advantages of Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-advantages-of-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:58:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-advantages-of-brexit/</guid><description>Stephen Weatherill, Jacques Delors Professor of European Law (Emeritus), Faculty of Law and Somerville College, University of Oxford.
Introduction
Two recently released reports, both dated January 31, 2022, promise to shed light on the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s 2016 decision to exit the European Union. After over five years, it seems we can finally move beyond vague slogans like &amp;ldquo;Take back control!&amp;rdquo; and begin to assess the concrete implications of Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-advantages-of-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-advantages-of-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of an Advocate-General's opinion reveals that Brexit will result in the end of EU citizenship for UK nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 11:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The question of whether British citizens retained their EU citizenship after Brexit is disputed. While the EU and UK governments assert that they did not, some British individuals disagree.
This issue has been raised before EU courts through various avenues. Three cases directly appealed to the EU General Court, contesting the EU Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to finalize the withdrawal agreement. These appeals argued that the agreement improperly revoked their EU citizenship...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it *a* Labour Brexit policy or *the* Labour Brexit policy? Thoughts on Jeremy Corbyn's speech on Brexit policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-a-labour-brexit-policy-or-the-labour-brexit-policy-thoughts-on-jeremy-corbyn-s-speech-on-brexit-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 08:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-a-labour-brexit-policy-or-the-labour-brexit-policy-thoughts-on-jeremy-corbyn-s-speech-on-brexit-policy/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
In a recent speech, Labour Party leader Jeremy Corbyn aimed to clarify the party&amp;rsquo;s stance on Brexit, particularly regarding a future customs arrangement with the EU.
Corbyn&amp;rsquo;s speech emphasized unity and collaboration. He condemned the blame placed on immigrants, intergenerational conflicts, and tensions between different parts of the UK. He stressed the importance of the Good Friday Agreement for Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s stability. Corbyn concluded by promoting a global perspective, stating that being a citizen of Britain also means being a citizen of the world...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-a-labour-brexit-policy-or-the-labour-brexit-policy-thoughts-on-jeremy-corbyn-s-speech-on-brexit-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-a-labour-brexit-policy-or-the-labour-brexit-policy-thoughts-on-jeremy-corbyn-s-speech-on-brexit-policy/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>