<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Share on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/share/</link><description>Recent content in Share on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:26:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/share/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore investors who are accredited can transition to digital investing with Jachin Capital</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</guid><description>Jachin Capital, a Singapore-based independent fund manager, is now authorized to offer its digital investment platform, iAdvisor, to accredited investors in Singapore after receiving a Capital Markets Services Licence from the Monetary Authority of Singapore. The company specializes in providing investment management solutions, including discretionary and non-discretionary options, to accredited investors and private family offices throughout the Asia-Pacific region. Jachin Capital uses a transparent, rules-based approach to build and regularly rebalance investment portfolios around specific themes or ideas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-investors-who-are-accredited-can-transition-to-digital-investing-with-jachin-capital/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top 10 global consumer trends for 2015 focus on multitasking and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor.
Market research firm Euromonitor International recently published their findings on the top 10 global consumer trends for 2015.
Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Global Consumer Trends 2015 report states that consumers, pressed for time, are seeking convenience, diverse options, global product availability, and instant satisfaction. They aim to get the most out of their time and money, looking for products and services that meet multiple needs. As an illustration, a Swedish taxi service provides in-car therapists for their stressed and busy clients at a rate of US$165 per hour...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox unveils new tools to enhance productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</guid><description>Source: Dropbox website.
Dropbox aims to simplify content creation, sharing, and teamwork through its new features.
Users can now create new Microsoft Office files, upload photos, or scan documents directly through the Dropbox iPhone app using the plus button.
A Dropbox badge shows who is currently working on the same Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, or Excel files, preventing work duplication or loss. Microsoft co-authoring enables real-time collaboration on Microsoft Office files online, eliminating email exchanges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-unveils-new-tools-to-enhance-productivity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>