<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Minimum Wage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/minimum-wage/</link><description>Recent content in Minimum Wage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 14:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/minimum-wage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Striving for fairness and adequacy: The proposal for minimum wages in the European Union.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 14:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Antwerp
Almost a year after promising an initiative on minimum wages, the European Commission presented its controversial proposal for a directive on this issue on October 28, 2020. This proposal has been met with criticism, particularly regarding the Commission&amp;rsquo;s authority on this matter, potential impacts on the autonomy of social partners and collective bargaining, and concerns about how this might affect the competitive advantage of member states with currently lower wages.</description></item><item><title>Returning from Austerity to Legitimacy: An Overview of the European Pillar of Social Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</guid><description>This piece explores how Juncker can use ‘The European Pillar of Social Rights’ to convey a strong message: that the EU champions dignity, autonomy, and social justice.
Claire Kilpatrick (EUI), Elise Muir (Veni Fellow, Maastricht) and Sacha Garben (College of Europe, Bruges)
The EU has faced skepticism from its citizens about its commitment to prosperity and better living and working conditions, especially since the financial crisis and the subsequent implementation of austerity measures in various countries.</description></item></channel></rss>