<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Consultant Tools on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/consultant-tools/</link><description>Recent content in Consultant Tools on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:27:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/consultant-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Series of tools for consultants: Darkfield Laser Mouse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-darkfield-laser-mouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-darkfield-laser-mouse/</guid><description>Being a roving consultant means you&amp;rsquo;ve likely developed a toolkit of methods and technologies to stay productive in diverse settings. This can involve working from a spare desk at the office, client sites, airports, airplanes, and countless coffee shops. Over the years, this might have included using floppy disks, managing old databases, handling large files, establishing VPN connections from unusual locations, and even resorting to makeshift workstations.
I&amp;rsquo;ve certainly encountered my share of unique challenges, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to share some solutions I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered over time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-darkfield-laser-mouse/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-darkfield-laser-mouse/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tools for Consultants: WinGrep for Windows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-wingrep-for-windows/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-wingrep-for-windows/</guid><description>A client reached out because their Dynamics GP system was displaying duplicate journal entry lines for entries imported from an external system. Recognizing that my integration was likely not the source of the issue, I investigated further and found that only specific journal entries were affected. Upon closer inspection, I noticed that the duplicate journal entries had slightly different descriptions for debit and credit transactions, suggesting the external system might be sending duplicate data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-wingrep-for-windows/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-wingrep-for-windows/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tools for Consultants: 7-Zip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-7-zip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-7-zip/</guid><description>While I try to stay current with technology, I sometimes miss valuable tools, especially in unfamiliar areas.
I&amp;rsquo;ve relied on WinZip for years to email files, even paying for a license! For compressing larger files like SQL Server and VHD backups, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using WinRAR. I believed these two programs covered my compression needs effectively.
However, I recently came across a free, open-source compression utility called 7-Zip, which many of my peers were already familiar with...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-7-zip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-7-zip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tools for Consultants: Coordinating Across Different Time Zones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-coordinating-across-different-time-zones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-coordinating-across-different-time-zones/</guid><description>Calculating times for different time zones often causes me problems. I frequently mix up time zones like Mountain, Central, and Eastern, or I end up adding an hour when I should be subtracting. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple task but prone to errors.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered two helpful tools for managing time zones.
Firstly, there&amp;rsquo;s FoxClocks, a Firefox web browser add-on. This tool is invaluable when I need to collaborate with people across different time zones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-coordinating-across-different-time-zones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-coordinating-across-different-time-zones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Series of tools for consultants: TrueCrypt</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-truecrypt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 04:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-truecrypt/</guid><description>My friends, who aren&amp;rsquo;t tech-savvy, often ask for advice on handling sensitive information. For instance, I have a CPA friend dealing with client data in tax software, another involved in high-stakes business deals requiring secure communication during international travel, and a third managing sensitive employee data for their health insurance and benefits company.
In my work with Dynamics GP, I encounter sensitive client databases containing HR and payroll information, especially during integrations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-truecrypt/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-truecrypt/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Series of tools for consultants: Password Management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-password-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 11:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-password-management/</guid><description>Have you ever stopped to think about how many passwords you need to remember? The number is likely higher than you realize.
Consider all the passwords we use daily: multiple email accounts, website logins, client VPNs and RDP servers, GP logins and system passwords, FTP sites – the list goes on.
Now multiply that by the number of clients or accounts you manage. It quickly becomes impossible to keep track of them all, especially if some are used infrequently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-password-management/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/series-of-tools-for-consultants-password-management/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tools for Consultants: WinDirStat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-windirstat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 04:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-windirstat/</guid><description>Experiencing an unexpectedly full hard drive or needing to free up space can be frustrating. WinDirStat is a free, lightweight application that provides disk usage information and can be incredibly helpful in these situations.
While large, affordable hard drives are becoming the norm, laptop and server drives often have limited space and can fill up with large files. Outdated SQL Server backups and large SQL Server database files are common culprits on servers, while desktops and laptops have their own share of space-hogging files...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-windirstat/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tools-for-consultants-windirstat/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>