<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VARs on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vars/</link><description>Recent content in VARs on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comprehensive Network Services From Telarus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</guid><description>Creating and managing a network can be a significant challenge for businesses of all sizes. Small businesses find it distracting, while larger companies view it as a costly endeavor that can either help or hurt their efficiency. Integrating local and wide area networks seamlessly is a particularly difficult problem.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: Telarus. Regardless of your size or technical expertise, Telarus provides a range of services to address your networking needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Information on PBX Telephone Systems Pricing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 15:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</guid><description>Planning a new office building or hotel? Upgrading your old business phone system? Finding the right PBX system at the right price is essential for a smart decision.
Instead of searching endlessly, utilize an online clearinghouse like the VAR Network. This platform connects businesses with qualified PBX and network equipment vendors.
The VAR Network focuses on these two interconnected technologies. Most businesses rely on both for internal communication and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Painless Way to Find Network Technicians</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</guid><description>Your company might be large and technologically advanced, utilizing an internal data network and a PBX phone system, or even a converged enterprise VoIP system. However, you may lack the resources for a dedicated IT department, let alone a telecom team. Hiring necessary services on an as-needed basis is a reality for your business. But is there a simple solution for finding contractors to handle this work?
Now there is. The solution is called the VAR Network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>