<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:36:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>XO Offering Ethernet to the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</guid><description>Global telecommunications companies now have a unique opportunity: access to 4 million commercial buildings across the U.S. for offering Ethernet services. This is made possible by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; new Ethernet Hub service.
While this might seem irrelevant to businesses unless they&amp;rsquo;re looking to cut costs on voice and data services, the potential savings hidden within XO&amp;rsquo;s recent press release are significant.
XO Communications is a competitive carrier, meaning they weren&amp;rsquo;t part of the traditional Bell Telephone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>