<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Forced Labour on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/forced-labour/</link><description>Recent content in Forced Labour on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 15:08:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/forced-labour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Putting an end to the exploitation of seasonal workers: EU legislation targets the easiest issues.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-the-exploitation-of-seasonal-workers-eu-legislation-targets-the-easiest-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 15:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-the-exploitation-of-seasonal-workers-eu-legislation-targets-the-easiest-issues/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU struggled to create legislation regarding migrant workers from outside the EU. Member States finally agreed on laws focused on higher-income migrants: the Blue Card Directive and the Directive on intra-corporate transferees. The EU also established general rules for admitting labor migrants with the single permit Directive.
In a new development, the EU introduced rules for lower-paid seasonal workers last year. This group is particularly susceptible to exploitation.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to effectively help in the prohibition of forced labor by the ILO?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although often used lightly, the term &amp;ldquo;wage slaves&amp;rdquo; reflects a harsh reality for millions trapped in forced labor globally, a modern form of slavery. This exploitation represents a significant aspect of human trafficking, alongside sexual exploitation.
Key international entities like the United Nations and the Council of Europe have been at the forefront of combating human trafficking. However, the International Labour Organisation (ILO) brings long-standing expertise, particularly concerning labor exploitation.</description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones.</description></item></channel></rss>