<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bonded T1 Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonded-t1-line/</link><description>Recent content in Bonded T1 Line on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 07:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonded-t1-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cheaper DS3 Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</guid><description>Your business needs more bandwidth, but the price of a DS3 connection might seem daunting. While upgrading from a T1 line to a DS3 might have seemed expensive in the past, prices have gone down. Even with the current economic climate, a DS3 connection could now be within your budget.
DS3, or Data Service level 3, is a digital telecommunications standard initially designed for telephone systems. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the T-Carrier system and works seamlessly with SONET fiber optic networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecommunication DS3 Affordable For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</guid><description>Modern businesses need increasing levels of bandwidth to accommodate computer-driven processes that enhance productivity. When a T1 line reaches its capacity, and more bandwidth is necessary, there are options to consider.
A logical next step, if bandwidth needs have gradually increased, is to bond a second T1 line with the first. This doubles the capacity, providing a 3 Mbps WAN connection. Additional T1 lines can be bonded to further multiply the bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>