<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asia Pacific on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asia-pacific/</link><description>Recent content in Asia Pacific on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asia-pacific/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific is dominated by formal severance policies, according to Right Management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-is-dominated-by-formal-severance-policies-according-to-right-management/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 02:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-is-dominated-by-formal-severance-policies-according-to-right-management/</guid><description>Right Management, a global outplacement firm, found that companies in Asia Pacific, especially in Japan (94%) and China (92%), are more likely to have formal severance policies.
According to their global report, &amp;ldquo;Severance Practices Around the World,&amp;rdquo; 75% of surveyed companies globally have formal, written severance policies, while 32% rely on informal, unwritten policies, or general practices.
Source: Right Management. Click here to view the full infographic.
Within Asia Pacific, 82% of companies reported having a formal policy, compared to around 70% in both the Americas and Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-is-dominated-by-formal-severance-policies-according-to-right-management/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-is-dominated-by-formal-severance-policies-according-to-right-management/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Nearly two out of every three firms in the Asia Pacific region will provide outplacement services even when it is not mandated by law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nearly-two-out-of-every-three-firms-in-the-asia-pacific-region-will-provide-outplacement-services-even-when-it-is-not-mandated-by-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nearly-two-out-of-every-three-firms-in-the-asia-pacific-region-will-provide-outplacement-services-even-when-it-is-not-mandated-by-law/</guid><description>Since the announcement of the large merger, rumors have been circulating. It&amp;rsquo;s clear that your department can&amp;rsquo;t absorb everyone from the other company, leading colleagues to compete for the boss&amp;rsquo;s attention, even though their own position is uncertain. Finally, HR schedules the meeting everyone has been anticipating.
US-based HR consultant Nick Corcodilos, in a November 2013 edition of his &amp;ldquo;Ask the Headhunter&amp;rdquo; e-newsletter, states that outplacement is often offered as a consolation prize after termination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nearly-two-out-of-every-three-firms-in-the-asia-pacific-region-will-provide-outplacement-services-even-when-it-is-not-mandated-by-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nearly-two-out-of-every-three-firms-in-the-asia-pacific-region-will-provide-outplacement-services-even-when-it-is-not-mandated-by-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hubspot's new, modern Asia Pacific headquarters in Singapore is designed with Millennials in mind</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot. Pictured at the official opening ceremony, from left: Jeetu Mahtani and JD Sherman.
HubSpot has officially launched its Singapore office and revealed plans to add 150 employees to its Singapore-based team over the next three years. Currently, HubSpot Singapore has 30 employees.
The Singapore office, warmly referred to as SingSpot, joins the Sydney, Australia office as HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s second location in the Asia Pacific region and will serve as the company’s Asia Pacific headquarters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consider pricing and marketing strategies for successful product launches in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Almost 75% of new products launched in the Asia-Pacific region fail. This rate surpasses other global regions, according to a study by strategy consultants Simon Kucher &amp;amp; Partners. The study, Global Pricing Study 2014, was conducted in partnership with the Professional Pricing Society (PPS).
[Image of watches for sale in a shopping district]
Globally, the ability to implement price increases is declining. While companies in 2012 could successfully implement 50% of planned price increases, that number has fallen to about 33% in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There was a significant increase in early-stage M&amp;A activity in the APAC region during the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>The Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor, which forecasts future merger and acquisition (M&amp;amp;A) announcements, anticipates a 6% rise in the total number of global M&amp;amp;A deals announced in the first half of 2017 compared to the same period in 2016. This would establish a new record for global announced deals in the first six months of a year.
The Asia Pacific (APAC) region leads in early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity, demonstrating 44% year-over-year growth in the fourth quarter of 2016, and is positioned to significantly contribute to the projected record deal count in the first half of 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers in the Asia Pacific region are more concerned about the security of their computer data than their mobile payment data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 11:58:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</guid><description>New benchmark data from ACI Worldwide and the Aite Group reveals that consumers in the Asia Pacific region are more worried about the security of their financial and payment information on computers compared to mobile wallets. This conclusion comes from their Global Consumer Survey: Consumer Trust and Security Perceptions report.
The study, which surveyed over 6,000 consumers across 20 countries, found that only 46% of Asia Pacific consumers trust businesses, such as restaurants and retailers, to safeguard their financial data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Club Carlson celebrates reaching one million members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s international hotel rewards program, Club Carlson, celebrated a milestone by awarding its one millionth member in the Asia Pacific region with one million Club Carlson Gold Points.
The lucky recipient, Rong Weiji, is a Sales and Marketing Division Manager at Santen Pharmaceutical. He became the millionth member upon checking in at the Radisson Blu Shanghai New World on August 22, 2014.
When asked about his hotel preferences, Mr. Weiji explained that he values brand recognition, quality, service, and location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotels.com provides exclusive information on transportation options to and from the airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</guid><description>Hotels.com, a website for booking accommodations online, has put together an insider&amp;rsquo;s guide on the top transportation choices from 29 major airports globally. This guide, called the Hotels.com Airport Transportation Insider, compares taxis, private cars, and public transportation in popular international and domestic destinations using data from the recent Hotel Price Index™. Although it&amp;rsquo;s geared towards US travelers, the infographic provides helpful information for cities like Bangkok, Beijing, Singapore, and Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC reveals the preferences of APAC consumers when it comes to mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 05:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</guid><description>The International Data Corporation (IDC) has released an infographic that reveals how consumers in the Asia Pacific region make decisions about mobile devices. Key findings from the Essential Guide to Device Decisions of a Connected Consumer in Asia Pacific report include:
Source: IDC infographic. What consumers like about bigger phone screens.
77% of surveyed consumers reported having a larger smartphone now than their previous device, while only 8% opted for a smaller one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe aims to achieve the highest level of performance in order to increase repeat visits and online sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</guid><description>Source: Adobe.
Recent Adobe research indicates that marketers in the Asia Pacific region who use best practices are significantly outperforming their competitors.
The Adobe Digital Index Best of the Best Benchmark for Asia Pacific analyzed websites across six regions: Australia and New Zealand, Southeast Asia, India, South Korea, Hong Kong, and China, comparing the average website performance with the top 20% based on six key performance indicators: mobile and tablet traffic, stick rate, visits per visitor, time spent, and conversion rate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangkok is the top tourist destination in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Mastercard. Report cover.
Although Bangkok, Thailand remains the top spot for visitors in the Asia Pacific, the latest Mastercard Asia Pacific Destinations Index 2017* shows that Singapore outpaces the Thai capital in total tourist spending.
Singapore experienced an 18% increase in visitor spending between 2015 and 2016. As one of just five destinations in the top 20 for overall expenditure to hit a minimum daily spend of US$200, Singapore drew in the biggest spenders at US$254 per day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verizon enhances e-business capabilities with increased support for private IP services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</guid><description>Verizon Communications is expanding its Private IP services network, offering businesses a secure way to deliver e-business applications and conduct business-to-business e-commerce. The expansion includes 10 additional countries across the Middle East, Africa, and Asia-Pacific regions.
Verizon business and wholesale customers in the Middle East and Asia Pacific now have expanded access to Private IP Multiprotocol Private Label Switching (MPLS) services in Bangladesh, Cambodia, Laos, Nepal, Iraq, Lebanon, and Yemen. Chennai, India, gains an additional location, offering customers enhanced network resiliency and reach through increased access to MPLS services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt reveals top employers for Singapore and the region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 04:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</guid><description>Source: Best Employers website.
Aon Hewitt, a global human resources solutions firm, unveiled its list of top employers in Singapore for 2015 on February 27th. Launched in Asia in 2001, Aon Hewitt’s Best Employers study is currently the most thorough of its kind in the Asia Pacific region. Recognition as an Aon Hewitt Best Employer signifies that a company:
1. Cultivates strong employee commitment and top-tier performance;
2. Achieves strong business results through effective human resources strategies; and, 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The APAC region is strongly featured in Warc's list of the top 100 marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Warc, a provider of marketing intelligence, has introduced the Warc 100, a new ranking of the top marketing campaigns globally based on their effectiveness and strategic impact.
The Asia Pacific region contributed over 30 entries, including one from the UAE, with Australia having the second-highest representation after the US with 11 entries.
Among the top 10 campaigns from the Asia Pacific are: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s More Fun in the Philippines&amp;rdquo; by the Philippines Department of Tourism and BBDO Guerrero (ranked 3rd), &amp;ldquo;Overstay Checkout&amp;rdquo; by Art Series Hotels and Naked Communications (5th), &amp;ldquo;Smoking Kid&amp;rdquo; by Thai Health Promotion Foundation and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (7th), &amp;ldquo;Old Parts for New&amp;rdquo; by ORBIS International and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (8th), and &amp;ldquo;Car Creation&amp;rdquo; by NRMA Insurance and Whybin\TBWA (10th)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers are pleased to engage with hotels on social media</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</guid><description>A 2014 study by Accorhotels called the Social Media Monitor showed that hotels have a significant opportunity to connect with travelers on social media. In the Asia Pacific region, almost half of travelers follow hotel brands, more than airlines or other travel-related businesses. This trend is especially strong among travelers from China and Indonesia, as well as those between 25 and 44 years old.
Interestingly, in countries with prominent airlines such as Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, and Japan, airlines are followed most on social media...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Card-not-present fraud is on the rise, leaving two-thirds of credit card issuers in the Asia-Pacific region vulnerable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 11:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</guid><description>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing a surge in e-commerce, but this growth is accompanied by an increase in online fraud. A survey of fraud professionals in the region, conducted by predictive analytics firm FICO, revealed that card-not-present (CNP) fraud is the fastest-growing type of fraud. Nearly all (94%) of the survey respondents reported an increase in CNP fraud.
eMarketer, a research firm, projects that B2C e-commerce sales in the Asia Pacific region will reach US$525...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies in the Asia Pacific region are allocating funds for security, infrastructure, and business intelligence applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</guid><description>When planning technology budgets for the year, remember to allocate resources for infrastructure software, business intelligence applications, and, most importantly, security. Research firm Forrester states that security software is now the fastest-growing software category in the Asia Pacific region, leading in projected software spending growth for 2014.
In a survey of 3,382 IT executives and technology decision-makers across Asia Pacific organizations, 55% indicated they would increase their security software budget by &amp;lsquo;5% to 10%, or more&amp;rsquo; in 2014 compared to 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>