<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sharjah on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sharjah/</link><description>Recent content in Sharjah on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sharjah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fireworks will be held at Al Majaz Waterfront to celebrate Eid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</guid><description>Al Majaz Waterfront, a popular destination located in Sharjah, UAE, will be hosting a fireworks show to celebrate the beginning of Eid al-Adha.
As reported by the Emirates News Agency (WAM), a three-minute fireworks display will take place at 9pm on the first and second days of Eid. The fireworks will be launched above the Sharjah Musical Fountain, and additional entertainment will be offered.
Source: Al Majaz Waterfront website. Fireworks on Marwa Obaid Al Shamsi, the Manager of Al Majaz Waterfront, emphasized that Eid al-Adha is a joyous celebration for families and especially children.</description></item><item><title>Group discounts are available for the iftar buffet at Coral Beach Resort Sharjah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 12:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</guid><description>Source: Coral Beach Resort Sharjah website.
The Coral Beach Resort Sharjah, having just finished a full update of its rooms and amenities, is offering an iftar buffet at its Al Bahar Restaurant. The buffet will feature a variety of traditional Arabic and international dishes, with options like mixed grills, shawarma, hot and cold mezze, stews and biryani, in addition to soups, salads, snacks, and customary Ramadan beverages.
Jean Pierre Simon, the Regional General Manager for Northern Emirates at Coral Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, highlighted Al Bahar restaurant as the perfect location for gatherings to break the fast, suggesting guests round off their dining experience with classic Ramadan sweets like the ever-popular umm Ali and mouhalabia.</description></item><item><title>The Great Women Connect Series begins with Great Women Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Great Women Malaysia. Puan Nadira Yusoff.
The Great Women Connect Series debuted today in Malaysia. This new program seeks to provide a space for women in business worldwide to connect and exchange ideas and experiences related to trade. It also aims to foster international partnerships, helping women, especially those in Malaysia, build networks and realize their full potential.
Great Women Malaysia (GMW) is an initiative that strives to empower Malaysian women, particularly those in underserved and rural areas.</description></item></channel></rss>