<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reputation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reputation/</link><description>Recent content in Reputation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reputation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FMCG brands are well-regarded in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. Brandindex 2016 rankings for the Philippines are heavy on toiletry brands.
The YouGov BrandIndex rankings from 2016 show that personal care products are very popular in the Philippines. The top 10 includes Colgate dental care, Cream Silk hair products, Dove soaps and hair care, Safeguard soaps and washes, and Olay skin care. Bench, primarily a clothing retailer, also has a presence with their bath and body products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance reveals the top influential brands in Asia for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Brand Alliance. The brand gallery at Marina Bay Sands is open until August 21st.
Brand Alliance, using its brand leadership platform Influential Brands, has announced the 2015 Asia’s Top Influential Brands. This announcement leverages consumer insights gathered from 2013 to 2015.
This year, the Asia’s Top Influential Brands awards expanded to include over 100 categories. These categories span various sectors, ranging from food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) to financial services and property development...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia loves food and communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Top ranked-brands for KSA in 2016.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 illustrate the diverse brands consumers love. Rankings were determined by BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which asks respondents about their recent exposure to a brand through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth and whether their perception was positive or negative.
The Buzz Rankings chart highlights the brands that achieved the highest average Buzz scores from January to December 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is heavily involved in digital communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. This data represents the Brandindex rankings for brands in Thailand in 2016.
According to the YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016, digital brands were highly favored in Thailand. Facebook, Line, and 7-Eleven secured the top three spots, while YouTube and Google were among the top 10. Other notable tech brands included Apple iPhone and the e-commerce platform Lazada.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents whether their exposure to the brand, whether through advertising, news, or word of mouth, in the past two weeks has been positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Singapore welcomed technology and locally-made brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Brand rankings for 2016.
The 2016 YouGov Brandindex rankings show that Singaporeans have a strong preference for both local and digital brands. Singapore Airlines, DBS bank, The Straits Times newspaper, WhatsApp, and the Apple iPhone (in the top three) all made the list. Other popular tech brands included Facebook, Google, e-commerce platform Qoo10, and YouTube.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score, which asks respondents whether their exposure to the brand in the previous two weeks, through advertising, news, or word of mouth, was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>