<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Windstream on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/windstream/</link><description>Recent content in Windstream on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/windstream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>