<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contacts on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contacts/</link><description>Recent content in Contacts on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contacts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning of the Tone Arm Carriage Position Switches and a Non-Returning Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</guid><description>As a preliminary step in the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I chose to verify the functionality of its control system. Prior testing had shown that the arm carriage would not return to its home position when moved across the platter without a record in place. Instead, it would travel to the center of the platter and stop. Ideally, the carriage should trigger the End Switch (ES) at this point and subsequently return to its home position on the right, turning off the turntable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration and Test Drive with Cal Tjader and Claus Ogerman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable for an Australian customer who purchased it on eBay. The turntable arrived in poor condition.
My initial evaluation is documented here.
This post details the unit&amp;rsquo;s restoration, excluding the dust cover, which will be covered separately.
I began with the DC platter motor, as is customary, since the bearing lubrication process requires a few days. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable. Initial assessment of the unit can be found on a separate blog post.
The restoration began with the platter motor, as its bearings require a lengthy oil treatment. The motor was extracted, disassembled, and its bearings were submerged in oil under a vacuum to allow for optimal oil diffusion.
Concurrently, the carriage assembly was cleaned. All &amp;ldquo;motion critical&amp;rdquo; parts, including the arm and its associated mechanisms, were removed, ultrasonically cleaned, and reassembled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration Including a Refurbished Keypad and Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This unit is currently for sale. Please, see here.
This post details the complete restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) from Arizona, which I first inspected as shown here. The unit&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is pictured below:
My first step, as always, was to initiate oil infusion for the platter motor bearings. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:
I took it apart to extract the bearings (two small rings on the black pad):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This blog post details the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a client in Florida. A previous post documented the initial assessment of the unit.
Upon beginning the restoration, the turntable was in relatively original condition. However, the platter motor showed signs of prior work, evidenced by an incorrectly installed pulley.
To address this, the motor was removed and disassembled to extract and lubricate the bearings. This involved immersing them in motor oil under vacuum until air bubbles ceased to appear, indicating the bearings were properly saturated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>Some time ago, a customer in Texas purchased a Beogram 4000 turntable on eBay from a seller in New York. The turntable was in fair condition, as detailed on the blog (see hyperlink). To address a cracked corner on the dust cover, the decision was made to acquire a second Beogram 4000, allowing the creation of one flawless unit from the two. With the arrival of the second turntable, the restoration began...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Full Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 22:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable originating from California. The restoration process commenced with the reconstruction of the carriage and arm lowering mechanisms, encompassing meticulous cleaning and lubrication of components like the solenoid and damper.
Following the mechanism restoration, focus shifted to the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm. This involved addressing a common issue: a detached copper pad on the sensor arm assembly. The pad was reattached using epoxy to ensure smooth operation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This article details the refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5504) turntable. An initial assessment of the unit is documented in a previous post here.
The turntable, stripped of its panels and platter, appeared relatively untouched. However, evidence of previous work emerged later.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly, which was quite dirty. After disassembling and cleaning the parts, the platter motor and capacitors were removed for thorough cleaning. The motor housing, including the bearings, underwent an oil infusion process under vacuum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5501 from Sweden: Full Technical Restoration and Some Interesting Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 turntable (Type 5501 with optical carriage position detection) for a complete technical restoration. The unit arrived without a dust cover. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the Beogram right after unpacking:
Besides a number of loose parts that fell out when I opened the box, I was surprised to see that the cartridge was still mounted on the tonearm:
Fortunately, the MMC4000 cartridge had a small plexiglass guard in place, preventing any damage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>This article details the comprehensive restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The initial evaluation of this unit is detailed in a separate post.
The turntable was first disassembled, revealing the need for bearing lubrication in the platter motor, a common issue in these models. This process typically takes a few days.
While the bearings were being re-lubricated, the intricate carriage mechanism, responsible for raising and lowering the tonearm, was addressed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with Stanley Turrentine and Milt Jackson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Kentucky. The unit, pictured below, was in excellent condition, making it ideal for a complete refurbishment.
As is typical with DC motor Beograms, the platter motor was the starting point. These motors commonly suffer from dried-out bearings, leading to speed instability. The extracted motor is shown here:
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings:
The bearings, visible as two small rings on the black pad, were then submerged in motor oil under a vacuum:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Complete Functional Restoration and a Spin with the Cal Tjader Quartet!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The restoration began with addressing the motor, a common procedure for these models. After removing and disassembling the motor, the Oilite bearings were submerged in oil and placed under a vacuum for several days to replenish lubrication.
Next, the carriage and arm mechanisms were disassembled, cleaned, and re-lubricated. This included taking apart and servicing the damper. The main PCB was removed, and both power transistors were replaced...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Restoration and a Test Spin with Oscar Peterson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable from Sweden in very corroded condition. To address the extensive corrosion, I chose to use another 4000 unit as a donor for parts. The donor unit, while missing some components, was free of corrosion.
My restoration process started with the carriage. I disassembled and cleaned the arm lowering system, damper, carriage rods, and spindle in an ultrasonic bath. Additionally, the sensor arm assembly was removed to lubricate the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with the Bill Evans Trio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable from a Massachusetts customer. The initial evaluation can be found here.
The restoration began by addressing the carriage system. This involved cleaning hardened lubricants from various parts like the arm lowering mechanism, rods, spindle, linkages, and damper, and applying modern synthetic lubricants.
A key aspect of the Beogram 4000 is its solenoid-activated switches, which frequently experience oxidation and require attention. The contact terminals were removed and re-plated with nickel and gold-cobalt alloy for optimal performance and corrosion resistance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>