<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unemployment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unemployment/</link><description>Recent content in Unemployment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unemployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to deport and prohibit unemployed EU citizens from returning?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Germany&amp;rsquo;s recent exploration of expelling unemployed EU citizens has sparked interest among critics of EU free movement in the UK. As this topic gains traction, it&amp;rsquo;s timely to clarify the circumstances under which EU citizens can be expelled.
While the EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive empowers Member States to expel citizens for reasons related to public policy, security, or health, it explicitly prohibits using these grounds for economic reasons. Consequently, the rules for expelling unemployed EU citizens lie elsewhere within the Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Time for Entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-time-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 07:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-time-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>The concept of job security has become almost contradictory in recent times. It&amp;rsquo;s rare to find guaranteed employment, and even the usual promises of job stability for good performance are fading. We&amp;rsquo;ve faced recessions before, but this one is so significant that it might earn a name like &amp;ldquo;The Great Recession,&amp;rdquo; reminiscent of the depression our parents and grandparents endured.
Facing a severe economic downturn is never positive. Job losses without readily available replacements are becoming a harsh reality for many...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-time-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-time-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the Euro's downfall? EU regulations on exiting EMU or defaulting on debts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The stability of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) is once again in question after a period of relative calm. This follows the announcement of early elections in Greece. Should the anti-austerity party, Syriza, gain control of the government, the consequences could be significant.
It is crucial to note that such an outcome is not guaranteed. Syriza holds a small lead in the polls, and even if they become the leading party, they might not secure enough seats to hold a majority...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is CJEU case law on EU citizenship normatively consistent? Unlikely! - An answer to Davies' 'Has the Court evolved, or have the cases?'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 02:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</guid><description>Alexander Hoogenboom, PhD, MSc. LL.M. Senior Policy Officer at the Dutch Healthcare Authority and associate researcher at the Institute for Transnational and Euregional cross border cooperation and Mobility, Faculty of law, Maastricht University. The opinions presented in this paper are solely those of the author.
Introduction
Some have interpreted recent Court of Justice rulings on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits as a restrictive shift compared to earlier decisions, possibly influenced by rising populism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unemployed EU citizens may benefit from the CJEU's decision, potentially complicating David Cameron's renegotiation strategy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ability of EU citizens to move freely between Member States, often referred to as ‘immigration,’ has sparked significant political debate, particularly in the UK. Access to benefits for these individuals remains a point of contention. The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has an opportunity to provide clarity on key aspects of this issue in the upcoming case of Alimanovic. An Advocate-General recently issued a non-binding opinion on this case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Jobs Come Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</guid><description>Although the Great Recession continues, the impact varies across industries. In fact, the technology sector is performing quite well in terms of employment. From November to December of last year, while 85,000 jobs were lost overall, the tech industry actually added 5,200 new positions. This suggests that technology might be a promising field.
However, having technological skills doesn&amp;rsquo;t guarantee employment. Many factory workers, for instance, would likely agree. The manufacturing sector was already moving overseas even before the recession...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>