<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ibis on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ibis/</link><description>Recent content in Ibis on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ibis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations.</description></item><item><title>Accor plans to introduce the ibis Styles brand to Singapore later this year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</guid><description>Source: Accor. The ibis Style in the Macpherson area, Singapore, will be launched this year.
Accor plans to open an ibis Styles hotel in Singapore by the last quarter of 2015, introducing a trendy, lifestyle-focused brand to the country. Situated within the same complex as the MacPherson shopping mall, the hotel is conveniently located at the intersection of MacPherson and Aljunied Roads, a short 20-minute drive from the airport.</description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices.</description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson hosts its first charity event of the year-end</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</guid><description>Source: Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson. The poolside.
Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson will host its first charity event with the Friends of The Disabled Society (FDS) as part of their year-end festivities.
The public can purchase various handicrafts and accessories on November 17, 2016, at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s lounge area and poolside. All proceeds will go to FDS. The hotel will also host a dinner for FDS on December 3, 2016, as part of the holiday celebrations.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Hotels partners with Deezer to create a musical experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
Ibis Hotels, a budget-friendly option within the Accor group, has launched a new campaign in Australia. Through a partnership with Deezer, a global music streaming platform, guests can now immerse themselves in the world of music.
This collaboration gives guests staying at ibis, ibis Styles, and ibis Budget hotels access to ibis PLAY, a dedicated microsite. This platform offers a variety of music-centric content, including regularly updated local concert listings, curated playlists, music news, artist interviews, photo galleries, exclusive ibis content, and a spotlight on Australian live acts.</description></item></channel></rss>