<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Environmental Protection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environmental-protection/</link><description>Recent content in Environmental Protection on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environmental-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Even If There Is No Global Warming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-if-there-is-no-global-warming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 23:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-if-there-is-no-global-warming/</guid><description>The debate surrounding climate change is heating up, with strong opinions on both sides. Whether or not human activity is the primary driver of global warming, shifting towards green energy makes sense for a multitude of reasons. We need to change our approach to energy consumption or face serious consequences, potentially even sooner than anticipated.
The current economic downturn has provided a temporary reprieve in energy consumption, but as the economy recovers, the demand for oil will surge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-if-there-is-no-global-warming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-if-there-is-no-global-warming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Paid To Celebrate National Cell Phone Recycling Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s National Cell Phone Recycling Week, and there&amp;rsquo;s a way to make some money while participating! This initiative, spearheaded by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), highlights the importance of recycling valuable and potentially harmful materials found in cell phones.
Wireless carriers and various retailers are accepting old cell phones to ensure these devices are properly processed and their components are reused in new products. By taking part, you contribute to environmental protection by preventing hazardous materials from ending up in landfills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>