<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Management Reporter on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/management-reporter/</link><description>Recent content in Management Reporter on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/management-reporter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Deep Dive Now Accessible: Management Reporter!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</guid><description>I previously shared information about the &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s New Deep Dives&amp;rdquo; series for Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010. We recently released another installment focused on Management Reporter. Access it here! Craig Anderson from MSX Group, an expert in Management Reporter, developed and presented this topic. MSX Group and Craig are leading authorities on Management Reporter, and we were thrilled to leverage their expertise for this installment!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Returned from Convergence 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</guid><description>Looking forward to Convergence 2013 in New Orleans! I enjoyed New Orleans, though San Diego remains my top pick. It was a successful event, even though it seemed to fly by. As always, the hands-on labs were a highlight, and I appreciated connecting with attendees, partners, and familiar faces. We had better access to the product teams this year, which provided valuable opportunities to interact with those who consistently support us...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Limitation of Management Reporter Size</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limitation-of-management-reporter-size/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limitation-of-management-reporter-size/</guid><description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been helping a client with some unusual Management Reporter (MR) problems. The first issue involved trees in MR. When adding a branch and defining dimension codes for it, the codes wouldn&amp;rsquo;t save for some branches, leaving the dimension field empty.
We investigated the cause of the disappearing dimensions, but it seemed random. After consulting Microsoft, we learned there&amp;rsquo;s a 512-character limit for the dimension field in a tree. Adding multiple dimensions, including their names, can quickly reach this limit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limitation-of-management-reporter-size/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limitation-of-management-reporter-size/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A brief post on my love for Management Reporter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-brief-post-on-my-love-for-management-reporter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-brief-post-on-my-love-for-management-reporter/</guid><description>Stuck in an airport with a four-hour delay on my way to our yearly customer event in Denver, I decided to share some quick thoughts on Management Reporter. I&amp;rsquo;ve been increasingly impressed with it. While some features are still in development, I&amp;rsquo;m confident they will be available soon. In the meantime, here are a few things that make it incredibly useful:
Adding dimensions like account categories or analytical accounting details is incredibly simple...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-brief-post-on-my-love-for-management-reporter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-brief-post-on-my-love-for-management-reporter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Management Reporter Dimension Sets and AX Update The latest information on Management Reporter Dimension Sets and AX.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax-update-the-latest-information-on-management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 16:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax-update-the-latest-information-on-management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax/</guid><description>In an update to a previous post about Dimension Sets not functioning with Management Reporter in AX2012, it has been officially recognized as a quality report. The issue is expected to be addressed in the March release of MR2012.
The current limitations within Management Reporter, including the inability to utilize Dimension Sets and a 512 character restriction for dimension strings in rows, columns, or trees, creates challenges for report design. Particularly when working with extensive or intricate charts of accounts, users are encountering workarounds like creating numerous individual rows followed by a total row...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax-update-the-latest-information-on-management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax-update-the-latest-information-on-management-reporter-dimension-sets-and-ax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Management Reporter is experiencing alignment issues with zero columns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-is-experiencing-alignment-issues-with-zero-columns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-is-experiencing-alignment-issues-with-zero-columns/</guid><description>A minor but bothersome formatting issue was encountered in Management Reporter, where a calculated column rounded to one decimal place displayed a misaligned 0.0 value. This misalignment stems from the value being rounded from a slightly negative number (e.g., -0.02), while other values in the column consistently round to one decimal place.
While seemingly insignificant, this inconsistency can impact the visual appeal of financial reports. A straightforward solution involves adjusting the Print Control setting for the affected column to &amp;ldquo;NP&amp;rdquo; and introducing a new calculated column...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-is-experiencing-alignment-issues-with-zero-columns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/management-reporter-is-experiencing-alignment-issues-with-zero-columns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Learning Management Reporter Lessons the Hard Way Learning from the mistakes made in managing a reporter.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learning-management-reporter-lessons-the-hard-way-learning-from-the-mistakes-made-in-managing-a-reporter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 20:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learning-management-reporter-lessons-the-hard-way-learning-from-the-mistakes-made-in-managing-a-reporter/</guid><description>Today, I encountered an interesting problem in Management Reporter related to consolidated multi-company reporting. It turns out that for this type of reporting, having identical account segment names across all involved companies is crucial.
Let me illustrate with an example. Imagine two companies, A and B. Both use a 4-2 account structure. However, Company A labels its account segments (accessible via Microsoft Dynamics GP &amp;gt; Tools &amp;gt; Setup &amp;gt; Company &amp;gt; Account Format) as &amp;ldquo;Main Account&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Department...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learning-management-reporter-lessons-the-hard-way-learning-from-the-mistakes-made-in-managing-a-reporter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learning-management-reporter-lessons-the-hard-way-learning-from-the-mistakes-made-in-managing-a-reporter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lessons learned from Management Reporter report distribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-learned-from-management-reporter-report-distribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-learned-from-management-reporter-report-distribution/</guid><description>Here are some helpful tips for using Management Reporter, especially for distributing reports:
Utilize Security Groups in the Report Viewer for folder security whenever possible. You can create these groups on the Security page in Management Reporter. When setting up a folder in the Reports Library, grant access to the group (right-click on the folder and choose Report Library Permissions). Now, any user added to this group will automatically have access to these folders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-learned-from-management-reporter-report-distribution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-learned-from-management-reporter-report-distribution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking for innovative management reporter solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-innovative-management-reporter-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-innovative-management-reporter-solutions/</guid><description>While I vaguely remember the show &amp;ldquo;In Search Of,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m currently focused on finding solutions to Management Reporter challenges rather than Bigfoot or the Bermuda Triangle.
I&amp;rsquo;m seeking creative solutions, even if they&amp;rsquo;re unconventional, for two specific Management Reporter issues:
Implementing Management Reporter in environments without a domain or Active Directory. Managing high-volume reporting, including generating reports for online viewing in the library and printing them for physical distribution. Although I know these aren&amp;rsquo;t currently supported, I&amp;rsquo;m interested in hearing from anyone who has developed workarounds or alternative approaches for their clients...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-innovative-management-reporter-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-innovative-management-reporter-solutions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>