<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Printer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/printer/</link><description>Recent content in Printer on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/printer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park.</description></item><item><title>The L805 photo printer from Epson features a six-colour ink tank system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The L805 ink tank photo printer.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing products, has released its L805 printer. This six-color ink tank photo printer offers wireless printing from mobile devices and boasts the lowest operating expenses on the market. Epson&amp;rsquo;s ink tank printers are unique in that they utilize large ink tanks instead of cartridges.
Building upon the previous L800 model, the L805 incorporates built-in wireless connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Lexmark introduces seven innovative laser multifunction models with groundbreaking features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</guid><description>Lexmark has introduced seven new A4 color laser and smart multifunction printers (MFPs). These MFPs feature Kofax TotalAgility from Lexmark to improve omnichannel capture strategies and boost business efficiency.
Amy Machado, Research Manager at IDC, highlighted the strong growth of the A4 color MFP market, projecting a 10.5% increase throughout the forecast period, according to the Worldwide Hardcopy Peripherals Format Forecast from Q3 2015.
These new models, powered by a quad-core processor, boast leading print and copy speeds for their class.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces new large format printers designed for small office use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-new-large-format-printers-designed-for-small-office-use/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 08:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-new-large-format-printers-designed-for-small-office-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The Epson SureColor SC-T3130.
Epson has introduced its new line of high-speed SureColor T-series large-format printers, aiming to capture a share of the entry-level and mid-range computer-aided design (CAD) plotter market.
These printers are well-suited for various sectors, including architecture, engineering, CAD, geographical information systems (GIS), education, corporations, and small businesses. Known for their compact size, these wireless plotters are offered in both desktop and floor-standing configurations, boasting a user-friendly design suitable for any office environment.</description></item><item><title>Compact prints on-the-go with the Canon Mini Photo Printer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compact-prints-on-the-go-with-the-canon-mini-photo-printer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 20:39:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compact-prints-on-the-go-with-the-canon-mini-photo-printer/</guid><description>Canon has unveiled its most compact photo printer to date. Weighing a mere 160 grams, this pocket-sized device employs inkless printing technology, enabling instant printing and sharing of smartphone photos.
Source: Canon. The Canon Mini Photo Printer.
&amp;ldquo;Nowadays, photos of meaningful events often remain confined to our social media feeds. We at Canon aim to change this by encouraging spontaneity through the ultra-portable Canon Mini Photo Printer. Now, sharing printed photos with loved ones can be instantaneous,&amp;rdquo; stated Edwin Teoh, Head of Marketing, Singapore Operations, Canon Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Eko Nugroho is currently showcasing his street art exhibition through digital prints produced by HP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</guid><description>This image, from HP Inc., showcases embroidered artwork by Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho. It features his signature masked characters and intricate designs reminiscent of Japanese woodcuts.
HP Inc is the Innovation Sponsor for the &amp;ldquo;Art from the Streets&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the ArtScience Museum in Singapore. For the exhibition, HP created nine large-scale prints of significant artworks. They are also using their digital printing technology to showcase the work of Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho in fresh and unexpected ways, demonstrating that street art can be displayed anywhere and on any medium.</description></item><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item><item><title>The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-C869R offers a cost-effective solution for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-workforce-pro-wf-c869r-offers-a-cost-effective-solution-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 12:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-workforce-pro-wf-c869r-offers-a-cost-effective-solution-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. The WF-C869R printer.
Epson recently introduced a new printer with a Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS) that offers both high speed and quality while significantly reducing costs. The WorkForce Pro WF-C869R boasts a high page yield and a low cost per page, which can lead to considerable savings for businesses compared to using laser printers.
The printer&amp;rsquo;s high-capacity ink packs come in two options: standard packs that yield up to 22,500 black and 22,000 color pages, and larger packs that yield up to 86,000 black and 84,000 color pages.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling.</description></item><item><title>Fuji Xerox provides an introduction to 3D printing in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fuji-xerox-provides-an-introduction-to-3d-printing-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fuji-xerox-provides-an-introduction-to-3d-printing-in-singapore/</guid><description>Eugene Ying inquired about the audience&amp;rsquo;s understanding of additive manufacturing.
Singapore offers ample resources for those interested in 3D printing, according to Eugene Ying, 3D Sales Manager for Fuji Xerox Asia Pacific. He made this statement during the Fuji Xerox DocuWorld event in Singapore.
Ying emphasized the rapid commercialization of 3D printing, citing Airbus as a prime example. As of September 2017, Airbus incorporated a 3D-printed titanium bracket into the production of their A350 XWB aircraft.</description></item><item><title>The HP 2 in 1 printer is perfect for home offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new PC and printer designed for home offices.
The HP Pavilion x2, available in Singapore starting in October from S$499, offers a stylish and practical solution. This versatile device functions as a 10-inch Windows tablet and easily transforms into a fully functional laptop. It features a detachable magnetic keyboard cover that doubles as both a screen protector and a multi-position stand. Equipped with an Intel Atom processor, the Pavilion x2 boasts front-facing speakers with DTS sound and a battery life of up to 11.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new business printer capable of printing up to 75,000 pages in a single run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</guid><description>Epson helps businesses reduce printing expenses with its Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS). RIPS utilizes high-capacity ink packs that hold significantly more ink than traditional cartridges. This system combines the convenience of cartridges with the high-volume output of ink tanks.
Source: Epson.
The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-R8591 is the first printer in Southeast Asia to offer this technology. Using a complete set of ink packs, the WF-R8591 can print approximately 75,000 pages* before replacements are needed.</description></item><item><title>For the fourth year in a row, Konica Minolta has been awarded the prestigious BLI 'Line of the Year' award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-fourth-year-in-a-row-konica-minolta-has-been-awarded-the-prestigious-bli-line-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-fourth-year-in-a-row-konica-minolta-has-been-awarded-the-prestigious-bli-line-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>Buyers Laboratory (BLI), a recognized independent evaluator for the imaging industry, has given Konica Minolta&amp;rsquo;s A3 multifunction printer (MFP) family its &amp;ldquo;Line of the Year&amp;rdquo; award for an unprecedented fourth consecutive year.
The &amp;ldquo;Line of the Year&amp;rdquo; award is presented annually to companies whose products demonstrate exceptional performance in BLI&amp;rsquo;s rigorous two-month laboratory assessments.
&amp;ldquo;Konica Minolta&amp;rsquo;s success comes down to consistency,&amp;rdquo; said George Mikolay, BLI&amp;rsquo;s Senior Product Editor for A3/Copier MFPs.</description></item><item><title>The LaserJet Enterprise 600 Series from HP offers increased security and versatility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 11:06:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</guid><description>Source: HP. The HP Color LaserJet Managed E87660 MFP.
HP has introduced the HP LaserJet Enterprise 600 Series, a line of printers designed to enhance security and productivity.
These multifunction printers (MFPs) offer a combination of strong performance, energy efficiency, and the ability to produce professional-quality documents. They are built with network security in mind, offering protection against cyberattacks. Additionally, the devices incorporate HP JetIntelligence cartridge technology, which utilizes advancements in toner chemistry to further enhance print quality.</description></item><item><title>The second season of The Wolf, produced by HP Studios, demonstrates the capabilities of hackers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 22:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-season-of-the-wolf-produced-by-hp-studios-demonstrates-the-capabilities-of-hackers/</guid><description>Source: HP eDM. Christian Slater stars in The Wolf: The Hunt Continues.
The second season of The Wolf, starring Christian Slater, is out now from HP Studios. This film follows a hacker&amp;rsquo;s exploitation of the healthcare system, revealing how vulnerable endpoints like printers can be compromised, leading to critical data loss.
HP claims that their printers and PCs offer the highest level of security globally.
Want to learn more?</description></item><item><title>Epson has launched three business inkjet printers that offer a range of connectivity options and high capacity features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WorkForce WF-2661.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has launched three new inkjet printers for businesses in Singapore. These models are designed for small offices and home offices.
The ultra-compact Epson WorkForce series is designed for small spaces and cost-effective printing. These printers include automatic document feeders (ADFs) and Epson Connect, enabling users to print directly from their mobile devices.
The new WorkForce series offers easy and flexible printing over Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>New Canon PIXMA all-in-one printers have been released in vibrant colors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-canon-pixma-all-in-one-printers-have-been-released-in-vibrant-colors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 22:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-canon-pixma-all-in-one-printers-have-been-released-in-vibrant-colors/</guid><description>Canon is releasing three new PIXMA all-in-one printers in stylish colors like Millennial Pink, Brilliant Green, and Navy Blue, offering options for everyone.
These PIXMA TS8370, TS6370, and TS5370 all-in-one printers blend design and functionality. They offer various connectivity choices and productivity tools, making them perfect for home offices and small businesses.
PIXMA TS8370 Photo All-in-One - A Compact Six-Ink Photo Printer
This printer, available in red, white, and black, has top-tier features and photo print quality.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean fashion designers are displaying their collections that have been digitally printed by Epson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. Display, Wai Yang.
Epson, a printing technology company, partnered with designers based in Singapore for FashionisTech, a showcase at the recent FUZE Fashion Technology 2017 event in Singapore. The designers used Epson&amp;rsquo;s digital printing technology to create their collections.
Organized by Textile and Fashion Federation (TAFF), the summit was the first of its kind in Singapore. It promoted advancements in materials and highlighted creative uses of technology by Singaporean fashion brands.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new mobile POS printer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 22:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</guid><description>Epson, a company known for its printing and digital imaging solutions, has introduced the TM-m30 point of sale (POS) printer. Created specifically for tablet-based systems, the TM-m30 stands out as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most compact desktop receipt printers, making it a perfect fit for retail and hospitality businesses aiming to transition to a POS system managed by smart devices.
Source: Epson Singapore. The Epson TM-m30 POS printer.
The TM-m30 is engineered for swift and effortless setup on iOS, Android, and Windows mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights.</description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI.</description></item><item><title>HP believes that the digital printing revolution has the potential to make businesses even more agile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</guid><description>Source: HP. High-impact retail graphics, floor covering and corrugated display applications printed using HP Latex and Scitex Digital printing technologies at the new HP Graphics Solutions Centre of Excellence in Singapore.
The way businesses approach printing is being transformed by commercial digital printing presses. Unlike traditional offset printing, which requires large quantities for cost-effectiveness, digital printers can economically personalize any volume of items, from a single piece to thousands, across diverse materials.</description></item></channel></rss>