<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automotive on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/automotive/</link><description>Recent content in Automotive on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:05:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/automotive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Carly users now have the ability to post on Carousell as well</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</guid><description>Carousell, a popular online classifieds platform, has acquired Caarly, a Singapore-based startup, as part of its strategy to dominate the classifieds market.
Caarly is a mobile-first tool designed to simplify inventory management for used car dealerships. Since launching in Singapore in 2014, Caarly has partnered with over 200 car dealerships, representing a large portion of the market in Singapore. Existing Caarly partners can continue managing their inventory on the Caarly platform and seamlessly cross-post their listings to the cars category on Carousell with just one click.</description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has seen the launch of four new BMW models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</guid><description>BMW Group Asia is launching four new car models simultaneously for the first time in Singapore.
The First-Ever BMW i8 Roadster The BMW i8 Roadster features upward-opening doors.
This groundbreaking convertible plug-in hybrid, dubbed a &amp;ldquo;gentleman&amp;rsquo;s racer,&amp;rdquo; can accelerate from 0 to 100 km/h in 4.6 seconds. CS Liew, a director at an agricultural science company, owns the first edition in Singapore, which is already on the road. Initially preferring hardtop convertibles, Liew was captivated by the i8 Roadster&amp;rsquo;s design.</description></item><item><title>Lexus has launched the new NX luxury crossover, accompanied by video advertisements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</guid><description>Source: Lexus. The Lexus NX.
Lexus has launched the NX, a luxury crossover. The 2015 NX marketing campaign highlights how the vehicle surpasses typical SUVs to provide urban drivers with a stylish option that suits their dynamic lifestyles.
“This is Lexus&amp;rsquo; first venture into the entry luxury crossover market. The NX is a dynamic vehicle that combines high-end design with practicality,” said Brian Smith, Lexus&amp;rsquo; VP of marketing. “This campaign showcases the fun driving experience and adventurous spirit of this vehicle, which boasts a bold, angular design and a powerful turbocharged engine.</description></item></channel></rss>