<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>121EMBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/121embg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 121EMBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/121embg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Non-Working End Groove Detection - Repair of a Detached Carriage Position Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. One peculiar problem was a detached carriage position sensor, which is housed within a black light shield. This shield was hanging at an angle, but it needs to be positioned vertically. The sensor works by using black sections on a plexiglass strip attached to the carriage to interrupt light from an IR diode. If the sensor is misaligned, stray light can disrupt the carriage&amp;rsquo;s movement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, which was exciting to receive in its original box and packaging. Upon opening it, I was greeted by a pleasant surprise—a pristine MMC20CL cartridge was mounted on the tonearm. Thankfully, it was protected by a cover and had been gently pressed against the styrofoam, keeping it safe during shipping.
Carefully, I removed the styrofoam and cartridge, relieved to find the cantilever was still centered and undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</guid><description>The final stage of my recent Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project involved reviving the dust cover. Like many Beograms of its era, the cover required attention, particularly the rubber bumpers which needed replacing. The extent of the damage is evident in this photo:
Fortunately, the scratches weren&amp;rsquo;t severe. A 320-grit sanding step effectively leveled the plexiglass, preparing it for polishing to regain its transparency:
After approximately ten stages of polishing, using progressively finer sandpaper and polishing cloths, the cover regained its shine:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Transport Lock Bushings and cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>Many Beogram 4002 (5513) turntables, including the one I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring, require replacement of the transport lock bushings and cabinet guidance washers. These components are crucial for proper platter and arm alignment. Without them, alignment is unreliable and won&amp;rsquo;t hold during transport.
This image shows the front transport lock missing its bushing:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the disassembled mechanism with the lower part of the new bushings installed:
The top part of the bushing is added next:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) began with the arm lowering and tracking systems, as these are essential for any further testing or repair work.
To start, I took out the damper and linkages to clean and lubricate them. Thankfully, all the components were in good condition, so lubrication and reassembly were straightforward. Next, I lubricated the pivot point connecting the damper to the arm linkage. This required removing the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Idris Muhammad (KU-17) After Platter and Tonearm Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day at the shop, where another Beogram 4002 (5513) is looking and sounding fantastic! The finishing touches involved adjusting the sub-chassis and platter to ensure they float freely and sit flush with the deck&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface. My YouTube channel features two videos demonstrating these adjustments for a Beogram 4000, which are very similar to the 4002 model.
Afterward, the tonearm lowering limit was adjusted, a crucial procedure given the 4002&amp;rsquo;s control system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent photosensor malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding DC Motor with Oil Infused Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the RPM relay and trimmers in the Beogram 4002 (5513) with updated parts, the DC motor required attention. The DC motor often proves to be the most challenging aspect of restoring a 4002 and nearly always demands attention. The primary hurdle lies in restoring the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite oil-infused brass sleeve bearings. These bearings are &amp;ldquo;pre-lubricated&amp;rdquo; in a new motor. From a typical consumer perspective, with a lifespan of 10-15 years, these bearings might be considered &amp;ldquo;maintenance-free.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Pins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</guid><description>A gold-plated plug is the finishing touch for a fully restored signal path. Here&amp;rsquo;s the process on a Beogram 4002(5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on:
Above is the original plug in rough shape due to oxidation.
The new Rean plug offers a neat and tidy internal layout.
Placing the metal enclosure back results in an even more visually appealing look. That&amp;rsquo;s the Beolove!</description></item></channel></rss>