<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Identity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/identity/</link><description>Recent content in Identity on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA.</description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM.</description></item></channel></rss>