<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PageUp People on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pageup-people/</link><description>Recent content in PageUp People on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:13:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pageup-people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The practice of recruiting and retaining skilled individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-practice-of-recruiting-and-retaining-skilled-individuals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-practice-of-recruiting-and-retaining-skilled-individuals/</guid><description>Innovative talent acquisition strategies are helping some companies secure the best possible candidates.
Mei-lynn Chan, Head of Organizational Development, Group Human Capital at Maybank, emphasizes the need for HR departments to approach hiring from a business perspective. This involves quantifying HR activities into tangible business metrics.
She argues that while budget constraints may have traditionally limited HR&amp;rsquo;s hiring choices, a new perspective allows for hiring the right talent if the business can absorb the cost until the hire generates a return on investment.</description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia's unique focus on talent management sets it apart as a hub for talented individuals in the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-s-unique-focus-on-talent-management-sets-it-apart-as-a-hub-for-talented-individuals-in-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:51:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-s-unique-focus-on-talent-management-sets-it-apart-as-a-hub-for-talented-individuals-in-the-region/</guid><description>PageUp People, a global talent management solutions company, has introduced &amp;ldquo;Talented Southeast Asia,&amp;rdquo; a publication dedicated to talent management in Southeast Asia. The book tackles significant challenges and future trends for employers, drawing from insights gathered from over 100 interviews with business and HR leaders over a year.
Sylvia Vorhauser-Smith, PageUp People’s Senior Vice President of Global Research and co-author, highlights the region&amp;rsquo;s distinct characteristics and the varying approaches to talent management.</description></item></channel></rss>