<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cost Savings on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cost-savings/</link><description>Recent content in Cost Savings on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cost-savings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Strategies For The Hunkered Down Economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</guid><description>While the new year has arrived, the economic situation remains challenging. Unemployment is still high, companies are focusing on cost-cutting over revenue growth, and uncertainty about the future persists. Consumers are tightening their belts and spending less, leaving businesses with little choice but to do the same. It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to hesitate before making significant moves when the path ahead is unclear.
Does this mean your business is stuck or in irreversible decline?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center Telecom Service Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</guid><description>Contact centers manage various communication methods like phone calls, faxes, emails, and mail for businesses and organizations. These centers often use a lot of telecommunications technology, making them a significant expense for the company. A typical center might have analog phone lines, digital phone lines (T1 or DS3), SIP trunking for VoIP, dedicated internet, and private lines for specific needs.
Contact center managers need voice and data services that reduce costs without sacrificing performance or reliability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Nails Down SIP Trunking Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</guid><description>Want to discover how your business could save upwards of $88,000 annually just by switching to SIP trunking service?
Hold on a minute! To achieve this level of savings, your business needs to have a certain volume of operations and spending. This figure comes from XO Communications, a leading voice and data carrier, and their new Enterprise SIP Savings Estimator.
So, what kind of business can expect these substantial savings? In this scenario, a company with 1,000 employees spread across 10 locations, where half of their phone calls are internal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom Cost Savings Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-cost-savings-strategies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 09:06:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-cost-savings-strategies/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, businesses are looking everywhere to save money. Have you considered your telecom costs? There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you could be saving money there.
Start by gathering your monthly bills and reviewing them. Begin with last month&amp;rsquo;s bill and identify each line item and its purpose.
Larger organizations often have extensive long-distance bills. Instead of getting bogged down in the details, look for anything unusual. Are there any users with significantly higher bills than others?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-cost-savings-strategies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-cost-savings-strategies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick Way to Cut the Corporate Phone Bill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 03:33:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/</guid><description>As the cost of goods and fuel continues to rise, many businesses find themselves caught between escalating expenses and a limited ability to increase prices. The situation is changing so rapidly that overhauling or even reconsidering business strategies is challenging. The most practical solution for maintaining profits becomes straightforward cost reduction.
At this juncture, attention often turns to the phone bill. Are all those calls truly essential?
Reviewing telecommunications invoices is a wise practice, even when business operations are running smoothly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-way-to-cut-the-corporate-phone-bill/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>