<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transformation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transformation/</link><description>Recent content in Transformation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is leading the way in digital transformation and digital leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</guid><description>Source: SAP. Agree or disagree? Management and staff in Southeast Asia and globally share their thoughts in the Leaders 2020 study.
Almost 25% of Southeast Asian companies are considered digital leaders, according to a recent study by SAP and Oxford Economics. This figure surpasses the global average of 16% reported in the Leaders 2020 study.
This new category of high-achieving companies reports greater profit increases, improved employee engagement, and more inclusive workplace environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The implementation of smart technologies is increasing revenues by up to 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</guid><description>A global Avanade study, involving Australian executives, business unit leaders, and IT decision-makers, reveals that a majority of business leaders are already investing in and seeing positive results from incorporating smart technologies in their workplaces. A key motivator is the potential for increased revenue, with business and IT leaders projecting up to a 33% revenue boost from these technologies within the next five years. Furthermore, companies anticipate retraining existing employees, generating new roles, and restructuring their organizations as they predict the repurposing of up to 20% of current roles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are now blending their physical and digital experiences. How should companies respond?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</guid><description>A new study emphasizes the importance of personalization in merging online and offline shopping experiences for &amp;ldquo;phy-gital&amp;rdquo; consumers. The study found that while companies are embracing digital technologies, they are lagging in implementing personalization strategies that consumers desire.
The study revealed that personalized promotions significantly influence purchasing decisions, encouraging consumers to buy familiar products and explore new ones. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between consumer expectations and company investments. While consumers value enhanced search and comparison features, companies prioritize features like shopping lists and social elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kampong Glam introduces new digital initiatives with the participation of 150 merchants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:03:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</guid><description>Haji Lane in Kampong Glam.
Kampong Glam, the first neighborhood in Singapore to embrace digital technology, has introduced five initial projects to help its traditional businesses thrive in the digital world.
This neighborhood revitalization project, spearheaded by the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), involves collaboration with Enterprise Singapore, One Kampong Gelam (OKG) association, and the Singapore Malay Chambers of Commerce and Industry (SMCCI). Its objective is to make the neighborhood more attractive to tech-savvy shoppers and tourists seeking immersive retail experiences, while enabling businesses to increase their productivity through technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kampong-glam-introduces-new-digital-initiatives-with-the-participation-of-150-merchants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial business transformation program in Malaysia has achieved notable success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</guid><description>UOB Malaysia and The FinLab have reported that the small- and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) participating in the _Jom Transform Programme_1 could experience productivity gains of up to 30% through digitalization.
Jom Transform is the first program in Malaysia dedicated to helping local businesses digitize their operations, aiming to increase productivity and revenue growth.
Over the three-month program, the 16 participating SMEs acquired digital transformation expertise in areas such as business re-engineering and digital marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating the digital landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</guid><description>Business leaders from major telecommunications and media companies recently met to talk about how to thrive in a digital world. IBM iX, the consulting firm that organized the gathering, emphasizes that these challenges are relevant to every industry.
A key takeaway was the urgent need for companies to disrupt themselves before someone else does. This involves understanding emerging digital trends and investing in ways that increase market share and profits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Brunei boot camp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in transitioning to digital platforms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</guid><description>DHgate, the APEC Business Advisory Council (ABAC) China, and ABAC Brunei have initiated the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation Cross-Border E-commerce Training (APEC CBET) boot camp in Brunei. This program aims to develop more skilled professionals within the cross-border e-commerce sector and elevate industry training standards.
E-commerce exporters see a greater first-year survival rate (60-80%) than traditional businesses (30-50%), according to the APEC CBET website. E-commerce also allows exporters to reach around 40 different economies compared to just three to four for traditional exporters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>