<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Michelin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/michelin/</link><description>Recent content in Michelin on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/michelin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has welcomed three new celebrity chefs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. From left: Costa, Joinie-Maurin, Kurdahl, Semblat and Silva.
The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has added three new chefs to its roster of acclaimed restaurants, aiming to elevate the dining experience for their guests.
Jose Silva, CEO of Jumeirah Group, stated that the addition of these culinary experts to their flagship Dubai hotel signifies the beginning of a more diverse and innovative culinary program. He emphasized their dedication to guest experiences as a crucial aspect of luxury hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Art Basel at the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong offers menus that are inspired by art</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong, the official hotel partner of Art Basel Hong Kong for the third consecutive year, will offer guests a range of special services this March. These include art-themed menus at the Michelin-starred restaurants Mandarin Grill + Bar and Pierre, as well as an exclusive accommodation package.
From March 11th to 17th, 2015, Chef Pierre Gagnaire of the two-Michelin-starred restaurant Pierre will present unique menus entitled &amp;ldquo;The Art of Pierre Gagnaire.</description></item><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef.</description></item><item><title>The restaurants at InterContinental Hong Kong have been awarded a combined total of three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>The 2018 Michelin Guide recognized two restaurants at the InterContinental Hong Kong, awarding a total of three Michelin stars. Yan Toh Heen, their Cantonese restaurant, earned two stars, while Rech by Alain Ducasse, a recent addition opened in March 2017, received one. Rech by Alain Ducasse is not only the hotel&amp;rsquo;s newest culinary venture but also marks the first international location of the acclaimed Parisian seafood restaurant.
Claus Pedersen, General Manager of the InterContinental Hong Kong, expressed his pride, stating that achieving these stars is a testament to the dedication and effort of their entire team.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon, the Korean fine-dining restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, has been awarded three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. Nine delicacies at La Yeon.
During the first-ever Michelin Guide Seoul launch in 2017, held at The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Dynasty Hall, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s traditional Korean fine-dining establishment, La Yeon, was granted a coveted three-star Michelin rating. Recognized for its authentic flavors, exceptional service, inviting atmosphere, and well-paired drinks, La Yeon stands as the sole Seoul restaurant within a hospitality group to achieve this three-star distinction.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds.</description></item><item><title>SJM Resorts will be hosting the inaugural MICHELIN Star Table event in mid-September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</guid><description>Source: SJM resorts. Palace Garden Head Chef Ken Chong will introduce the authentic elegance of fine Cantonese cuisine with his signature dish, crystal king tiger prawn.
SJM Resorts, an official MICHELIN Guide partner in Macao, has introduced its inaugural MICHELIN Star Table experience.
The debut event will be held at the Palace Garden within the Grand Lisboa Palace Resort Macau on September 15th and 16th. It will showcase a six-course menu representing the best of Chinese cuisine through a collaborative effort between two renowned chefs.</description></item></channel></rss>