<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ireland on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ireland/</link><description>Recent content in Ireland on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ireland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the Reunification of Ireland from an EU Legal Viewpoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</guid><description>Nikos Skoutaris, Lecturer in EU law at the University of East Anglia; website on Secessions, Constitutions and EU law.
When the UK voted to leave the EU on June 23, 2016, Northern Ireland voted to remain. This result has led Sinn Féin to call for a referendum on Irish unification, which would allow Northern Ireland to stay in the EU. This discussion has gained momentum following the most recent Northern Ireland Assembly election, which saw a significant decrease in the Unionist vote...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-reunification-of-ireland-from-an-eu-legal-viewpoint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The alignment of Ireland's Public Health (Alcohol) Bill with EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Ollie Bartlett, Maynooth University
After nearly three years of discussion, the Irish Public Health (Alcohol) Bill has been passed by the Irish Parliament. The Bill aims to address Ireland&amp;rsquo;s significant alcohol-related harm through five key measures: minimum alcohol pricing; stricter labeling; advertising restrictions; separating alcohol from other retail products; and limitations on alcohol sales and supply.
While lauded as &amp;ldquo;groundbreaking&amp;rdquo; by Health Minister Simon Harris, some argue that elements of the Bill, particularly those related to the free trade of alcohol within the European Union, might not be legal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alignment-of-ireland-s-public-health-alcohol-bill-with-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finally free? Detention, the European Arrest Warrant, and Julian Assange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Lanigan case, which deals with prolonged pre-trial detention and the European Arrest Warrant (EAW), is especially noteworthy given the UN&amp;rsquo;s recent statement regarding Julian Assange&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;arbitrary detention.&amp;rdquo; Assange, who is also facing an EAW, presents a unique situation. What can we learn from each of these cases about the intersection of detention length and the EAW?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Day the Unicorns Cried: Understanding Phase 1 of the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
The recent joint report on the progress of Brexit negotiations, along with a related paper from the Commission, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of negotiations. Based on this report, the EU27 have agreed that &amp;ldquo;sufficient progress&amp;rdquo; has been made to move forward. This next phase will focus on a transition period and, potentially starting in March 2018, the framework for the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions of the Attorney General on recent CJEU cases regarding national data retention laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
Advocate General Campos Sanchez-Bordana has presented his opinions on three cases concerning data retention: SpaceNet and Telekom Deutschland, GD v Commissioner of the Garda Síochána, and VD and SR. These opinions are the latest development in a series of legal challenges related to data retention that began with an Irish challenge to the Data Retention Directive.
The Data Retention Directive, which allowed for the retention of communications data under certain exceptions to privacy principles, was invalidated in the Digital Rights Ireland case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Compliance of Alcohol Health Warning Labelling in Member States with EU Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Nikhil Gokani, a lecturer specializing in consumer protection and public health law at the University of Essex, holds key positions in several organizations: Chair of the Alcohol Labelling and Health Warning International Expert Group at the European Alcohol Policy Alliance, Vice President of the Law Section at the European Public Health Association, and a member of the Technical Advisory Group on Alcohol Labelling at the World Health Organization (WHO)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Arrest Warrants and the autonomy of public prosecutors as ruled by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Julia Burchett, PhD candidate at the Université libre de Bruxelles and the University of Grenoble
Introduction
Widely recognized as a cornerstone of EU criminal law, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as one of the most, if not the most, utilized tools for judicial cooperation in criminal matters among EU member states. This streamlined cross-border surrender procedure, designed for prosecution or execution of custodial sentences and detention orders, has replaced traditional systems relying on political involvement from individual member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Commentary on the EU/Canada free trade agreement and its implications on the Irish constitution: Costello v The Government of Ireland and Ors [2022] IESC 44</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-the-eu-canada-free-trade-agreement-and-its-implications-on-the-irish-constitution-costello-v-the-government-of-ireland-and-ors-2022-iesc-44/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-the-eu-canada-free-trade-agreement-and-its-implications-on-the-irish-constitution-costello-v-the-government-of-ireland-and-ors-2022-iesc-44/</guid><description>Dr John Cotter, Lecturer in Law, Keele University, UK
Photo credit: Guiseppe Milo, via wikicommons media
Background
The EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA), signed in 2016 after five years of talks, came at a critical point in EU trade policy. While trade wasn&amp;rsquo;t central to the Brexit vote earlier that year, prominent Brexit supporters used the EU&amp;rsquo;s slow trade deal progress to argue for a more agile UK that could ratify deals faster...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-the-eu-canada-free-trade-agreement-and-its-implications-on-the-irish-constitution-costello-v-the-government-of-ireland-and-ors-2022-iesc-44/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-the-eu-canada-free-trade-agreement-and-its-implications-on-the-irish-constitution-costello-v-the-government-of-ireland-and-ors-2022-iesc-44/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dr. David L. Parris v. Trinity College Dublin and Others represents yet another missed chance to effectively protect LGB rights under EU law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>By Dr. Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Introduction
The recent ruling in the Parris case represents a missed chance for the European Court of Justice (ECJ) to provide meaningful protection to LGB individuals and same-sex couples under EU law. While recent cases like Asociaţia Accept and Hay suggested a shift towards stronger protection of LGB rights, the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s judgment in Parris, similar to the Léger case preceding it, reveals a hesitancy to address matters considered sensitive by Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Unassuming Suggestion: Preventing a Standstill on the Irish Border in the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Brexit withdrawal agreement negotiations are in danger of collapsing due to disagreements on managing the Irish border. The UK government&amp;rsquo;s lack of concrete proposals for customs away from the border is concerning. Additionally, the UK Foreign Secretary&amp;rsquo;s inability to differentiate between a simple congestion charge and the complexities of border control is disappointing.
In anticipation of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s upcoming proposals, I have drafted a text (Annex 1) addressing the Irish border in the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>