<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FTTH on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ftth/</link><description>Recent content in FTTH on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ftth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas.</description></item><item><title>Cable vs FTTH Bandwidth Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</guid><description>The competition for superior internet speed is underway. Fiber to the Home (FTTH), is perceived as the frontrunner, while Cable Broadband is the contender. It&amp;rsquo;s still uncertain who will come out on top, but one thing is for sure: users with substantial bandwidth requirements will be the ultimate victors.
This clash is unfolding in Washington state, where Comcast, the Cable behemoth, is introducing a 50 Mbps internet service to rival Verizon, the telecommunications giant, and its 50 Mbps FiOS internet service.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speeds Come to Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</guid><description>Cablevision Systems Corp. is pushing the boundaries of broadband speed by offering internet speeds exceeding 100 Mbps over its existing cable TV infrastructure. This new high-speed internet service, launching on May 11th, provides download speeds up to 101 Mbps and upload speeds up to 15 Mbps for approximately $100 per month.
One might wonder how cable TV lines, which traditionally use coaxial cables, can achieve such high speeds, usually associated with fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology.</description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades.</description></item></channel></rss>