<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SME on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sme/</link><description>Recent content in SME on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:08:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Swag employment superapp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises as well as job seekers in Singapore and Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</guid><description>Employment Hero, a company specializing in HR, payroll, and employee engagement, is launching Swag, an employment superapp designed to modernize the employer-employee relationship.
Building on its existing platform that streamlines HR and payroll processes for SMEs, Employment Hero is shifting its focus to enhance the job hunting experience for both employers and job seekers. Swag utilizes AI-powered recruitment tools to simplify and expedite the process of finding, onboarding, and rewarding talent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai World Central is pleased to welcome partnerships between the UAE and Japan through the Japan Trade Centre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</guid><description>Source: Dubai World Central. Khalid Abdulla, Vice President, Licensing, Registration &amp;amp; Permits Approval, Dubai World Central, Usama Saleh, Vice President, Land Planning and Development, Dubai World Central, with Shogo Ishida, Director, JTC DWC LLC, during the inauguration of the Japan Trade Centre at Dubai World Central in January 2015.
The Japan Trade Centre (JTC), a private business-to-business platform promoting Japanese small and medium enterprises (SMEs) internationally, is now operational at Dubai World Central (DWC)&amp;rsquo;s Business Park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</a></p></description></item><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Canon has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Canon Singapore has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution providing businesses with real-time delivery tracking and automated scheduling. Designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) that rely on scheduling, delivery, and documentation for their core operations, FleetnexG offers a way to optimize resources and boost efficiency.
Vincent Low, Director &amp;amp; General Manager of Business Imaging Solutions at Canon Singapore, highlights the need for SMEs to go beyond timely order fulfillment. He emphasizes that optimizing resources for greater efficiency and productivity is crucial for success in today&amp;rsquo;s business landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ITFC and Catalyst Group collaborate to enhance trade for small and medium enterprises in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>The International Islamic Trade Finance Corporation (ITFC) and Catalyst Group, a Jeddah-based real estate company, have partnered to support small and medium-sized enterprise (SME) trade development in Saudi Arabia. This collaboration will launch ITFC’s KSA SME Program, starting with a pilot SME Trade Development Program (TDP) in Saudi Arabia, with the intention of expanding to other countries.
This agreement aligns with Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Vision 2030 SMEs Trade Development Program, which focuses on supporting businesses&amp;rsquo; export capabilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Golden Equator Consulting assists small and medium-sized enterprises and startups in advancing towards success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 02:34:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</guid><description>Golden Equator Consulting (GE Consulting), a business consultancy firm, has established a presence in Singapore to serve small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups in the region. Sharon Chong, CEO of GE Consulting, noted that these businesses need strategic and operational support to streamline their growth and focus on core business functions.
GE Consulting offers comprehensive business consultancy services, covering areas such as business strategy, sales positioning, financial support, marketing, technology, human resources, and legal compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-equator-consulting-assists-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-startups-in-advancing-towards-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LBC 360 provides comprehensive business services in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 20:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: LBC YouTube channel.
In November 2014, LBC Express, the top cargo and logistics company in the Philippines, introduced a unique, fully integrated payment and logistics solution for the country. This platform, called LBC 360, aims to assist Filipino businesses of all types and sizes in overcoming supply chain obstacles.
“LBC 360 is intentionally crafted to be advantageous for all business models, from physical stores to online marketplaces,” explained Miguel Camahort, LBC President and Chief Operating Officer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lbc-360-provides-comprehensive-business-services-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces new storage solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Mid-size businesses need to adapt quickly, but they often don&amp;rsquo;t have the budget for the advanced storage solutions used by larger companies. HP is addressing this issue by offering affordable ways to enhance application performance. This includes a budget-friendly solid-state drive (SSD) read-caching solution from a leading provider, featuring SSD choices for HP MSA Storage.1
For businesses considering hybrid flash storage, HP is introducing a new HP StoreVirtual Storage system. This system boasts 12 times the speed of a similarly priced spinning media array...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-new-storage-solutions-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, Singaporean small and medium-sized businesses are leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</guid><description>Source: Cisco ebook. This Cisco report, the APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, evaluates digital maturity based on four key aspects.
· Singaporean SMBs achieved the highest ranking on the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index.
· Cybersecurity is the primary technology that Singaporean SMBs are investing in, followed by cloud computing and analytics.
· The most significant challenges cited by SMBs across Singapore are a shortage of digital skills and talent within their organizations and a lack of understanding of operational and customer data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aptugo develops customized web software without requiring any training</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 03:31:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</guid><description>Aptugo, a software tool designed to help individuals without coding experience build websites, is currently in beta testing. Developed by the company Aptugo, the software is expected to launch in 2015.
&amp;ldquo;Aptugo has the potential to bridge the gap between large and small businesses. Users don&amp;rsquo;t need any programming knowledge to use it,&amp;rdquo; stated Gaston Gorosterrazu, Head of Aptugo. &amp;ldquo;However, those with coding experience can further enhance what Aptugo can do, as it is designed to empower users and expand their capabilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UOB discovers misunderstandings about financing options for small and medium businesses in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 03:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: UOB infographic. Statistics gathered from the Financing for Startups and Small Businesses Survey.
A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB) revealed that a significant number of startups and small businesses in Singapore lack a comprehensive understanding of the alternative funding options available to them for early expansion. These businesses are also uncertain about how to effectively utilize options such as venture capital, venture debt, and debt and equity crowdfunding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-discovers-misunderstandings-about-financing-options-for-small-and-medium-businesses-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhancing financial inclusion has the potential to boost economic growth in the Arab region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) is advocating for the development of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and greater financial inclusion in the Arab world.
During the World Government Summit in Dubai, UAE, IMF Managing Director Christine Lagarde emphasized the need for Arab countries to prioritize growth and job creation. She highlighted the significant role of SMEs in generating employment, diversifying economies, and driving overall economic growth.
Lagarde pointed out that while SMEs make up 96% of registered companies and employ half of the workforce in the Arab region, they face significant challenges in accessing finance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore businesses can access cybersecurity and financing services from Acronis and Minterest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyberprotection company, has partnered with Minterest, a Singaporean online financial services provider, to offer financing to Singaporean businesses. This collaboration, called Acronis #CyberFit Financing, Powered by Minterest, aims to help businesses in Singapore stay resilient and #CyberFit during the COVID-19 pandemic.
Acronis and Minterest want to empower businesses by providing easily accessible, customized financing solutions. This will help businesses navigate challenging times while also strengthening their cybersecurity defenses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-businesses-can-access-cybersecurity-and-financing-services-from-acronis-and-minterest/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell has launched backup appliances for midmarket businesses, along with complimentary Windows data recovery software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</guid><description>Dell has introduced new data protection solutions tailored for small and medium-sized businesses to enhance the protection of their crucial systems, applications, and data, both on-site and in cloud environments. These solutions include data deduplication appliance models and the new Dell Data Protection | Endpoint Recovery – Free Edition.
Back up more and store less The latest additions to the Dell DR series of deduplication appliances are the Dell DR4300e, DR4300, and DR6300...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-has-launched-backup-appliances-for-midmarket-businesses-along-with-complimentary-windows-data-recovery-software/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Singapore polytechnics on initiatives for small and medium enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Singtel is partnering with Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) and Singapore Polytechnic (SP) to equip small and medium enterprises (SMEs) with digital skills, as part of the 99% SME initiative. This partnership aims to help SMEs in the retail and food and beverage industries thrive in the digital world.
The collaboration with NYP&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Institute of Retail Studies (SIRS) will connect SMEs with re-skilled professionals who can guide them in e-commerce, data analysis, and digital marketing strategies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-singapore-polytechnics-on-initiatives-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BCM Institute offers Business Continuity Management courses specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</guid><description>The BCM Institute, in collaboration with the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC), is offering a free two-day Business Continuity Management (BCM) course designed to enhance the resilience of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) against disruptions.
Taking place on October 28-29, 2014, at the Singapore Productivity Centre, this course is presented with support from the Singapore Business Federation and SPRING Singapore. Participants will engage with the following topics:
APEC-endorsed step-by-step BCM implementation guidelines Complimentary, ready-to-use BCM templates Guidance on utilizing BCM templates Insights into BCM trends affecting SMEs, shared by an APEC ASEAN BCM Working Group Committee member SMEs meeting the criteria of an annual sales turnover not exceeding S$100 million or employing 200 or fewer staff are eligible to participate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IIJ Global Solutions Singapore is now providing cloud monitoring services using CA Nimsoft Monitor for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 15:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>IIJ Global Solutions Singapore, a subsidiary of a major Japanese internet and network solutions company, Internet Initiative Japan (IIJ) Group, has incorporated CA Nimsoft Monitor from CA Technologies into its cloud solutions for small and medium-sized businesses.
This addition allows IIJ Global Solutions Singapore to offer its clients extensive 24/7 monitoring and reporting services. Using this unified monitoring platform from CA Nimsoft Monitor, users can optimize resources, improve planning and investments, and reduce time spent on troubleshooting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iij-global-solutions-singapore-is-now-providing-cloud-monitoring-services-using-ca-nimsoft-monitor-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget provides a significant boost to the commercial sector in various ways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</guid><description>In yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Budget, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized exploring new ideas and diversity to help Hong Kong citizens achieve their goals.
He stated his commitment to utilizing resources generated by the community, supporting those in need, and promoting sustainable development to ensure that people from all sectors of society and future generations can benefit from economic growth.
The Budget outlines measures for the cultural and creative sector:
An extra HK$400 million will be allocated to the CreateSmart Initiative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP creates servers specifically for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced new ProLiant Gen9 Tower servers to its Compute portfolio. These servers are designed to give small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) a cost-effective solution with a good mix of performance, efficiency, and manageability.
These servers are designed to handle a variety of general-purpose workloads and critical applications, including IT infrastructure, collaboration, web, and business applications. This support is intended to meet both current and future business needs.
“Small businesses must not only address immediate business challenges but also establish a foundation for rapid business expansion,” stated Peter Schrady, VP and GM of Rack and Tower Servers at HP...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xero collaborates with UOB to assist small businesses in handling their cash flow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 07:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/</guid><description>Xero announced today that its platform will now integrate with UOB. This partnership will allow small businesses in Singapore who bank with UOB to connect their bank accounts to their Xero subscription.
Both Xero and UOB are dedicated to helping small businesses in Singapore succeed. This integration is a significant step toward solving a major challenge these businesses face: managing cash flow.
Small business customers banking with UOB can now opt to have their transactions sent directly from UOB to Xero daily through a secure connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India will receive the India Inclusive Innovation Fund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</guid><description>The Indian Cabinet has approved a proposal from the Ministry of Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSME) to establish a dedicated fund. This fund will focus on promoting grassroots innovations that generate social benefits alongside reasonable economic returns. Union Minister Shri Kalraj Mishra shared this information in a written response to a question in Lok Sabha.
The fund, named &amp;ldquo;India Inclusive Innovation Fund,&amp;rdquo; aims to support businesses developing solutions for citizens at the lower end of India&amp;rsquo;s economic spectrum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Seller University has been launched by Amazon in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 05:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</guid><description>Amazon has introduced Seller University, an online platform designed to assist small and medium businesses (SMBs) in Singapore, at its inaugural Amazon Singapore Online Seller Summit 2020. Seller University offers interactive e-learning materials, practical exercises, and customized support to equip sellers on Amazon.sg with the skills to thrive.
Bernard Tay, Country Leader of Amazon.sg Seller Services and Head of Amazon Global Selling Southeast Asia, Australia and New Zealand, emphasized Amazon&amp;rsquo;s commitment to empowering local businesses through initiatives like Seller University...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protect your Office 365 emails with the latest Dropsuite cloud solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</guid><description>Smaller businesses can access Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s email backup and archiving tool for Microsoft Office 365 through intermediary companies like Ozhosting in Australia and ICONZ-Webvisions in Singapore.
Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Charif Elansari, emphasized their commitment to developing user-friendly solutions that are easy for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to buy and use.
Ozhosting CEO, Doug Endersbee, expressed satisfaction in offering Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive email archiving service, which meets legal requirements for retaining records, to their customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SPRING Singapore reviews its accomplishments in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</guid><description>Despite a slowing economy in 2016, SPRING Singapore, a government agency supporting business growth, reported that over 16,000 companies enhanced their capabilities.
These companies participated in projects backed by the Capability Development Grant (CDG) and Innovation &amp;amp; Capability Voucher (ICV) programs. SPRING estimates these projects will generate S$7.8 billion and create approximately 21,400 skilled jobs upon completion, representing a 13% and 43% increase from 2015 respectively.
A record-breaking 2,400 projects received CDG support, almost double the previous year and the highest in five years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>du offers corporate mobile plans for SMEs in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Du offers five corporate mobile plans designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These plans include data and free calls to colleagues within the business.
Ranging from AED 50 to AED 450 per month, the plans provide data, national calling minutes, national text messages, and free calls to numbers within a designated &amp;lsquo;business calling circle&amp;rsquo;. Three of the plans also include free international minutes and texts. Businesses can purchase additional &amp;lsquo;packs&amp;rsquo; to add more minutes, texts, or members to their calling circle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa introduces Visa Business Hub to assist small and medium-sized businesses with technology and strategic planning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</guid><description>Visa has launched the Visa Business Hub, a platform designed to assist small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in navigating technology and improving their management practices. The hub, initially launched in Singapore and Malaysia, offers software-as-a-service (SaaS) solutions that can potentially reduce IT costs by up to 25% through a pay-as-you-use model. This approach minimizes upfront expenses and implementation time.
Research indicates that a significant number of businesses in Singapore (80%) view SaaS/cloud adoption as a strategic move rather than a passing trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SAP reported that small and medium-sized enterprises in the Asia-Pacific region have adopted remote work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</guid><description>A recent study titled &amp;ldquo;Digital, Resilient, and Experience-driven: How Small and Midsize Organisations Can Prepare for the New Economy,&amp;rdquo; conducted by SAP in conjunction with Oxford Economics, reveals that small and mid-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the Asia-Pacific region are well-situated to flourish in the evolving business landscape following the COVID-19 pandemic.
The study, which surveyed 2,000 senior executives globally, including 832 from APAC countries like Singapore, Australia, and Japan, examined the priorities and digital readiness of SMEs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lessons for small and medium-sized enterprises from successful viral campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 07:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</guid><description>4imprint, a company that sells promotional products, has created a new infographic called &amp;ldquo;Going Viral.&amp;rdquo; This infographic explains how small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) can learn from viral marketing campaigns.
One suggestion is to connect a campaign with something already trending, like a popular TV show or book. This can effectively help a marketing effort gain traction with a specific audience.
The infographic also encourages businesses to consider product trials and giveaways...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-from-successful-viral-campaigns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Blue paper designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in developing effective Pinterest strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blue-paper-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-developing-effective-pinterest-strategies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blue-paper-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-developing-effective-pinterest-strategies/</guid><description>4imprint, a company selling promotional products, has published a guide to help small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) utilize Pinterest for business growth. This guide showcases the success stories of established brands on Pinterest and explores its role in a comprehensive marketing strategy.
[Image]
Source: Pinterest.
The guide emphasizes the platform&amp;rsquo;s visual nature, making it especially well-suited for industries like food, interior design, and fashion. With a user base of 70 million, &amp;ldquo;Grow your Business with Pinterest&amp;rdquo; suggests significant potential for businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blue-paper-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-developing-effective-pinterest-strategies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blue-paper-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-developing-effective-pinterest-strategies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CoAssets expands its crowdfunding portfolio by including small and medium-sized enterprise projects and sets its sights on Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</guid><description>CoAssets, a crowdfunding company based in Singapore, is expanding its platform to assist Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs). This expansion allows SMEs to connect with potential investors, addressing the funding challenges many businesses face. CoAssets&amp;rsquo; platform already facilitates real estate crowdfunding and will now provide a space for SMEs to seek funding.
Getty Goh, CEO of CoAssets, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s successful history in real estate crowdfunding and the increasing demand for business loans in Singapore as key drivers for this expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's International Enterprise (IE) and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to collaborate on connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</guid><description>International Enterprise (IE) Singapore, a government agency promoting international trade, and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have established a partnership to boost trade and international expansion for Singaporean companies. This agreement, solidified in a memorandum of understanding (MoU), marks IE Singapore’s first strategic partnership with a Singaporean bank.
The collaboration between IE Singapore and UOB aims to support 200 Singaporean companies in expanding overseas within the next three years. Their focus is primarily on Southeast Asia, China, Japan, and Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET advocates for the use of two-factor authentication to enhance security for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, cautions that small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) are frequently targeted by cybercriminals due to the vulnerability of their data. Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research&amp;rsquo;s study reveals that stolen personal data fuels a multi-billion dollar industry.
Lukas Raska, COO of ESET Asia, emphasizes the evolution of cybercrime from viruses to the current threat of identity theft, highlighting its potential to cripple businesses and compromise customer trust.
Parvinder Walia, Director at ESET APAC, explains that SMBs are attractive targets because they often lack the robust cybersecurity budgets and dedicated personnel of larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has improved MSA Storage for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 07:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP is introducing new features for its MSA Storage solutions to benefit startups, SMBs, and customers with small sites. These enhancements aim to increase competitiveness.
The improved MSA 2040 Storage offers significantly faster application performance, up to 45% faster, without extra costs through firmware updates. Additionally, new MSA 2040 bundles provide cost savings of up to 45% for hybrid flash deployments. Furthermore, the introduction of Serial Attached SCSI (SAS) connectivity to the MSA 1040 Storage positions it as the most budget-friendly shared storage option from a major vendor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-improved-msa-storage-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 12th WIEF could provide a boost for Indonesian SMEs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</guid><description>Experts at a public dialogue titled &amp;ldquo;Seizing the Benefits of Disruptive Technology for Manufacturers in Increasing Labor Productivity&amp;rdquo; emphasized that disruptive technology can work alongside traditional, labor-intensive methods. The event was organized by The Habibie Center, in partnership with the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and the World Islamic Economic Forum Foundation, as a precursor to the 12th World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF).
Dr. Zamroni Salim, a Senior Economic Researcher at the Indonesian Institute of Sciences (LIPI), explained that disruptive technologies don&amp;rsquo;t always clash with conventional labor models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaller companies can benefit from Cisco's advanced firewall security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</guid><description>Source: Cisco website. Some members of the Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services family.
Cisco has introduced new Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services models designed for small to mid-sized businesses and branch offices. These models offer the same advanced malware protection and threat detection used by larger organizations.
A recent study by PwC revealed a 64% increase in security breaches among mid-sized organizations in 2014. These organizations face similar security challenges as larger enterprises when safeguarding their network and data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial business transformation program in Malaysia has achieved notable success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</guid><description>UOB Malaysia and The FinLab have reported that the small- and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) participating in the _Jom Transform Programme_1 could experience productivity gains of up to 30% through digitalization.
Jom Transform is the first program in Malaysia dedicated to helping local businesses digitize their operations, aiming to increase productivity and revenue growth.
Over the three-month program, the 16 participating SMEs acquired digital transformation expertise in areas such as business re-engineering and digital marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-business-transformation-program-in-malaysia-has-achieved-notable-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trend Micro cautions that hackers are focusing on small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Trend Micro website.
Trend Micro warns that hackers are shifting tactics, moving away from mass spamming and towards sending personalized emails containing harmful attachments to compromise businesses. This method, the company cautions, could become the standard attack strategy in the Asia Pacific region.
A Trend Micro report titled &amp;ldquo;Piercing the HawkEye: Nigerian Cybercriminals Use a Simple Keylogger to Prey on SMBs Worldwide&amp;rdquo; reveals that two Nigerian hackers, known as &amp;ldquo;Uche&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Okiki,&amp;rdquo; are using inexpensive keylogging software called Hawkeye to target small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-cautions-that-hackers-are-focusing-on-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropmysite has undergone a rebranding and is now known as Dropsuite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</guid><description>Dropmysite, a cloud-based backup provider for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), has been renamed Dropsuite. This rebranding reflects a new global vision, business strategy, and ambition focused on business continuity, data recovery, and protection.
Dropsuite now offers a comprehensive suite of backup, recovery, and archiving solutions, consolidating its previous standalone brands: Dropmysite (website and database backup), Dropmyemail (email backup), and Dropmymobile (mobile data backup).
Furthermore, Dropsuite has introduced DSE Server Backup, a new file-based server backup solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</a></p></description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Facebook introduces a user-friendly, streamlined video advertising format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</guid><description>Over one-third of mobile internet users in Saudi Arabia are receptive to video advertisements, exceeding the global average of 22%.
Facebook is introducing &amp;ldquo;Slideshow,&amp;rdquo; a new, user-friendly video ad format designed to increase reach across various devices and connection speeds.
In a blog post announcing Slideshow, Facebook highlights a recent report indicating that people in regions like the Philippines, where connectivity can be slow, costly, or both, and where feature phones are common, are even more receptive to video ads...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy is dedicated to creating impressive and impactful business identities for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>GoDaddy: Expanding Beyond Domains to Empower Small Businesses While GoDaddy is known for domain names, it has evolved into much more. CEO Blake Irving emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s focus on supporting small businesses, a demographic often overlooked despite representing a significant portion of most economies.
Irving highlights that small businesses, even those with a single employee, present a vast untapped market. Traditional solutions often cater to either large enterprises or individual consumers, leaving small businesses underserved...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has revealed a budget for 2016 that is favorable to small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: Budget in Brief document on Singapore Budget website.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Heng Swee Keat, introduced a new program to bolster businesses and industries while stimulating growth through innovation. Building on the Quality Growth Programme from Budget 2013, this initiative, called the Industry Transformation Programme (ITP), seeks to foster innovation and productivity. The goal is to empower Singaporean companies to become more resilient and capitalize on the anticipated global economic upswing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Excelity Global will be providing HR and payroll services in Indonesia through Cekindo Bisnis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 07:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</guid><description>Excelity Global Solutions, the largest payroll service provider in Asia, has partnered with Cekindo Bisnis Grup to offer its services in Indonesia. Excelity Global, which operates in 19 countries across Asia Pacific, provides payroll outsourcing and human capital management cloud services.
Indonesia, with a large SME market, presents a significant opportunity for Excelity. SMEs make up over 98% of companies in Indonesia and contribute significantly to the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP.
By collaborating with Cekindo, a provider of market-entry and corporate secretarial services, Excelity aims to simplify HR and payroll processes for businesses in Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Helion offers enterprise-level cloud services tailored for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Helion Managed Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Lean, a service designed to support cloud-based applications for medium and large businesses. This service is suitable for purposes like application development and testing, as well as collaborative work environments.
This managed infrastructure solution allows smaller companies to adopt cloud technology swiftly and scale their usage as needed, all at a lower price point than previous HP Helion managed services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACCA advises small and medium-sized enterprises to focus on innovation, resource optimization, and compliance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-advises-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-to-focus-on-innovation-resource-optimization-and-compliance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-advises-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-to-focus-on-innovation-resource-optimization-and-compliance/</guid><description>A recent global study by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), titled SMEs: Business challenges and strategic innovation opportunities, reveals key challenges and opportunities for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). The study, which gathered insights from the Asia Pacific region, highlights three major challenges: increasing costs, workforce and talent management, and the evolving landscape of environmental, social, and governance (ESG) reporting.
Aleksandra Zaronina-Kirillova, ACCA&amp;rsquo;s head of SME, emphasizes that while SMEs face a variety of challenges, the study&amp;rsquo;s findings present a chance for these businesses to adopt strategic innovation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-advises-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-to-focus-on-innovation-resource-optimization-and-compliance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-advises-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-to-focus-on-innovation-resource-optimization-and-compliance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The enhanced Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB from ALE simplifies collaboration and boosts productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</guid><description>Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise, operating under the Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise brand, helps small and medium businesses provide a streamlined user experience and enhanced onsite mobility for their employees, while ensuring business continuity. This is achieved through the latest update of their product, Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB.
The latest improvements to OpenTouch Suite for SMB focus on increasing productivity and efficiency. This is achieved through expanded communication and collaborative tools, as well as enabling employees to access the company environment from any location, at any time, using mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy has expanded its presence to 11 Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a global technology provider for small businesses, has expanded its reach into 11 Asian markets. This expansion brings GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based products and customer support services to millions of small and medium enterprises (SMEs) within the region.
With these 11 new markets, GoDaddy now operates in 14 markets across Asia, encompassing 10 languages. These markets include Hong Kong (English and Traditional Chinese), Indonesia, Japan, Malaysia (English and Malay), Philippines (English and Filipino), Singapore (English and Simplified Chinese), South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, and Vietnam...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai welcomes the opening of a new Chinese Business Hub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 23:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</guid><description>Source: CBH. Pictured at the Business Centre opening ceremony are (from left to right) Justin Wilshaw, SVP Commercial, Dubai South; Shoaib Alrahimi, VP, Business Park, Dubai South; Mohsen Ahmad, VP, Logistics District, Dubai South; alongside other senior officials and association representatives. The UAE&amp;rsquo;s first dedicated business center specifically designed for new and expanding Chinese startups and SMEs, known as the Chinese Business Hub (CBH), has officially opened its main office in Dubai South Business Park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xero thoroughly examines the effects of COVID-19 on small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 17:55:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</guid><description>Xero, a global platform for small businesses, has published two reports examining the economic and emotional effects of the COVID-19 pandemic on small businesses worldwide.
Source: Xero&amp;rsquo;s Emotional metrics: small business mindsets during the pandemic report. From January to August 2020, small business owners experienced a range of emotions, from feeling &amp;ldquo;worn down&amp;rdquo; to a sense of loss.
The Xero Small Business Insights (SBI) Special Report, Pandemic Insights: Small Business Experience, was created in collaboration with AlphaBeta (part of Accenture) and utilizes anonymized and aggregated data from over 300,000 Xero subscribers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accounting solution in the cloud specifically created for individuals without accounting expertise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 03:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</guid><description>Asian Business Software Solutions (ABSS) has introduced Financio, a cloud-based accounting software designed for micro and small businesses in Singapore. This secure solution simplifies financial tracking without requiring accounting expertise.
Developed by ABSS and utilizing Microsoft Azure, Financio allows users to easily monitor sales, purchases, and other transactions through a user-friendly dashboard. It automates tasks like generating financial reports, tax records, and sending invoices, and enables seamless collaboration and document sharing through Financio Connect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new network switches designed specifically for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Dell has improved its networking solutions designed for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs). Their new X-series smart managed switches and expanded N-series family provide cost-effective, enterprise-grade network control with user-friendly simplicity.
The Dell Networking X-Series includes web-managed 1 Gigabit Ethernet (GbE) and 10GbE switches with flexible configuration options. SMBs can benefit from advanced network management without specialized IT staff using step-by-step wizards and customizable dashboards. These features allow for quick and accurate configuration, calibration, and troubleshooting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean financial technology company is striving to provide improved lending terms for business-to-business transactions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</guid><description>A Singapore-based fintech startup, Cash-IN-Asia, has introduced a new business-to-business (B2B) lending platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s fully digital approach lets business owners secure financing directly from their mobile devices.
Cash-IN-Asia aims to support micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in Singapore. The company offers products designed to meet current needs and help these businesses thrive even after the current economic challenges.
Their ISO27001-certified platform leverages artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics to deliver a comprehensive solution for MSMEs seeking transparent and flexible financing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kaspersky provides solutions to combat ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</guid><description>Ransomware is increasingly targeting businesses, encrypting files and demanding payment for decryption keys.
A Kaspersky Lab report reveals a six-fold increase in ransomware attacks against businesses from 2015 to 2016, affecting one in ten business users.
Cybercriminals are focusing on businesses, particularly small and medium-sized companies. A Kaspersky Lab and B2B International study found that 42% of respondents from these businesses considered ransomware a major threat.
Even brief data unavailability can severely impact small businesses, potentially halting operations entirely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of the SME Exporter of the Month award were honored by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently acknowledged member companies for their exceptional export achievements during the first nine months of 2016.
Nine trading companies received recognition at the &amp;ldquo;SME Exporter of the Month&amp;rdquo; ceremony: Universal International, Moon Flor General Trading, Signature Snacks, Al Khoud Trading, Raheeq Alasal Trading, Rais Hassan Saadi Logistics, Orient Links Co, Mohamed Abdulrahman Al Bahar, and Rayhan Al Sharq General Trading.
These companies were celebrated for excelling in categories such as highest export value, most export markets served, highest number of certificates of origin issued, and highest export value achieved by a start-up within a specific month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Brunei boot camp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in transitioning to digital platforms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</guid><description>DHgate, the APEC Business Advisory Council (ABAC) China, and ABAC Brunei have initiated the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation Cross-Border E-commerce Training (APEC CBET) boot camp in Brunei. This program aims to develop more skilled professionals within the cross-border e-commerce sector and elevate industry training standards.
E-commerce exporters see a greater first-year survival rate (60-80%) than traditional businesses (30-50%), according to the APEC CBET website. E-commerce also allows exporters to reach around 40 different economies compared to just three to four for traditional exporters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>