<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephony Solutions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephony-solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Telephony Solutions on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephony-solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 vs SIP For Business Telephone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</guid><description>Large businesses with high call volumes require different telecommunications solutions compared to small offices. While T1 lines have been the traditional choice, SIP Trunking is emerging as a strong alternative. This article explores the pros and cons of each technology to help businesses make informed decisions.
T1 lines were initially developed by telephone companies to connect central offices and handle numerous calls simultaneously. This technology, using T-carrier standards (T1 and T3), enabled high-capacity call transportation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>