<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ISP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/isp/</link><description>Recent content in ISP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/isp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dial-Up is Alive and Kicking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world of high-speed internet, it might seem strange to talk about dial-up. Many people consider it outdated technology.
However, dial-up internet access is still relevant. Millions of people still use and appreciate it for browsing the internet and checking emails. This &amp;ldquo;outdated&amp;rdquo; technology remains profitable.
One of the main advantages of dial-up is its affordability. Unlimited access is available for a low monthly cost, making it a budget-friendly option compared to DSL or cable internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Exchange Email Service Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</guid><description>POP3 email, while widely used by both businesses and individuals, has limitations that might make you reconsider your email service. While convenient, its client-server model, where emails are downloaded to your device, poses risks such as data loss and limited accessibility.
What exactly is POP3? It stands for Post Office Protocol, an internet standard for retrieving emails from a server to a client, like Microsoft Outlook or Mac Mail, installed on your computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Choose Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet has transitioned from a novelty to a necessity, as indispensable as electricity or heat. However, its unreliability can be a source of frustration, especially given its immense potential for businesses. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to enhance Internet stability and dependability.
Internet vs Internet
Internet experiences are not universal, despite discussions about net neutrality claiming otherwise. While some enjoy superior performance, others face limitations. How is this possible?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Service Without The Outages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</guid><description>The internet has become an essential tool for accessing information, connecting with others, and conducting business. It offers a vast repository of knowledge, real-time services, and entertainment options. However, internet outages can occur, causing frustration and disruption.
While complete internet blackouts are rare, local outages can still happen. These outages can be planned maintenance, accidental disruptions, or natural disasters. For businesses and individuals who rely heavily on the internet, these outages can be costly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom Providers Build Their Own Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</guid><description>As cloud computing companies start to establish themselves, internet service providers and similar carriers are developing their own cloud services. This creates a challenge for IT professionals and business owners who need to choose the best option.
It’s important to recognize that cloud computing is still in its early stages. Like any new technology, it will take time for it to fully develop. As the technology progresses, we will see a lot of activity from many different companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dude, Where's My Site?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 04:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</guid><description>Ever feel like the internet is taking a break, but you&amp;rsquo;re not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s just you? Sometimes, websites refuse to load, leaving you wondering if the problem is on your end. A new tool called DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com provides a simple solution. Just enter the website address, and it will tell you if the site is truly down or if it&amp;rsquo;s just your connection.
Created by a Twitter engineer, DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com addresses the common question of whether a website is offline or if it&amp;rsquo;s a personal issue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Symmetrical Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</guid><description>The majority of internet users consume content rather than create it. While content has shifted from primarily text to images and video, broadband internet access remains asymmetrical, favoring downloads over uploads.
Why is this the case? Consider how you browse the internet: you click or type to select content, which uses minimal bandwidth. However, receiving the content, like web pages with text, images, and videos, requires significant bandwidth for timely delivery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why You Need Dedicated Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume all high-speed internet connections are equal, but this isn&amp;rsquo;t true. Unfortunately, businesses may only discover this reality after missing out on sales and losing valuable customers.
While the core of the internet is quite reliable, with issues like packet loss, latency, and bandwidth rarely impacting crucial applications, the most significant difference between internet services lies in the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection – the link between your router and the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Is a Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</guid><description>Internet access has evolved from slow modems, but connecting still requires converting between protocols and Ethernet used in offices. Now, direct Ethernet internet is possible.
Ethernet for internet access is popular in cities, mainly due to cost savings and simpler networking. Called Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet, it extends your network using Ethernet across cities, countries, or to the internet.
Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) is the top choice for businesses, providing exclusive bandwidth unlike shared services like DSL, WiFi, and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic ISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</guid><description>Internet service used to rely on dial-up connections, but it has advanced significantly since then. Today, medium-sized businesses are now transitioning to fiber optic internet service providers, a technology already embraced by larger corporations.
Residential fiber optic internet, like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS, offers high speeds, with Google soon to introduce even faster Gigabit service. Business broadband connections, however, have already surpassed Gigabit speeds, with 10 Gbps becoming increasingly common. The technology is well-established, leaving businesses to determine their bandwidth needs and locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tired of Flaky Internet Connections?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</guid><description>Running a business is challenging when your tools are unreliable. You would think technology would make things easier, but it often has the opposite effect. As processes become more complex and interconnected, they seem to become less dependable. A simple cash transaction can turn into an e-commerce nightmare. Why can&amp;rsquo;t things just work flawlessly all the time?
While expecting perfection might be unrealistic, your business systems should function seamlessly most of the time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>