<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PAETEC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/paetec/</link><description>Recent content in PAETEC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/paetec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Rush To Cloud Service Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are moving away from managing their own servers and rapidly shifting towards public data centers. This article explores the reasons behind this trend and its potential future.
Cost savings have always been a major driver for companies considering data center colocation. Instead of investing in their own data centers, companies can move their equipment to a colocation facility. These facilities provide economies of scale by housing servers and network devices from multiple companies, sharing the costs of cooling, power, security, and bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>