<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Databases on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/databases/</link><description>Recent content in Databases on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible that there are multiple companies with multiple databases?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-there-are-multiple-companies-with-multiple-databases/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-there-are-multiple-companies-with-multiple-databases/</guid><description>When a customer has multiple companies, it seems logical to assume they would need separate Dynamics GP databases for each. While this is often true, there are exceptions. Determining the best approach requires careful consideration.
There are several factors to analyze when deciding whether to create a dedicated database per company or consolidate them within a single database. Combining companies into one database is less common but can be the ideal solution in certain situations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-there-are-multiple-companies-with-multiple-databases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-there-are-multiple-companies-with-multiple-databases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking at Article 43 of the EU Data Act through a Research Lens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-at-article-43-of-the-eu-data-act-through-a-research-lens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 08:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-at-article-43-of-the-eu-data-act-through-a-research-lens/</guid><description>Author: Maryna Manteghi, PhD researcher, University of Turku, Finland.
Photo credit: rjcastillo, via Wikimedia commons
Introduction
The EU&amp;rsquo;s new Data Act, a cornerstone of its data strategy, took effect on January 11, 2024, and will be implemented in September 2025. This regulation seeks to break down barriers hindering data access for individuals and companies, promoting a balanced and fair data distribution within society. It emphasizes easier access to and utilization of extensive digital datasets, particularly those originating from sensors and machines within the Internet of Things (IoT)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-at-article-43-of-the-eu-data-act-through-a-research-lens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-at-article-43-of-the-eu-data-act-through-a-research-lens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK is now part of the Schengen Information System, bringing the Panopticon Home.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The idea of a &amp;ldquo;Panopticon,&amp;rdquo; a prison where guards could potentially see any inmate at any point, was conceived over two centuries ago by British philosopher Jeremy Bentham. He believed that the constant threat of observation would motivate prisoners to act appropriately. This concept is now often used to illustrate contemporary patterns in widespread monitoring and societal control.
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) initial move in this direction was the establishment of the Schengen Information System (SIS) during the 1990s...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>