<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digitisation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digitisation/</link><description>Recent content in Digitisation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:50:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digitisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KODAK CapturePro Software v5.0 has been released by Kodak Alaris</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</guid><description>Large businesses are constantly looking for ways to manage information more efficiently and productively. Extracting data from documents for business processes and getting information into digital storage can slow things down, impacting expenses and customer happiness.
Source: Kodak Alaris.
&amp;ldquo;As organizations rely more on online platforms for profit, it&amp;rsquo;s critical to manage remaining paper documents effectively,&amp;rdquo; says Harvey Spencer, President of leading capture software analyst firm Harvey Spencer Associates. &amp;ldquo;The best approach is quickly converting paper into usable electronic data.</description></item><item><title>The demand for jobs in Singapore is being driven by digitization, according to Robert Walters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</guid><description>Source: Robert Walters. Click on the
image to view a larger version.
According to the international recruitment firm Robert Walters, the increasing presence of digital technology was the main driver of recruitment in Singapore during the second quarter of 2015. These insights were published in the company’s Asia Job Index for Q2 2015.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, acknowledged the anticipated decrease in job advertisements during this quarter.</description></item></channel></rss>