<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pairing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pairing/</link><description>Recent content in Pairing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pairing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Installation Video</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 &amp;ldquo;Commander&amp;rdquo; remote control system has recently seen a surge in popularity, with multiple orders coming in over a short time. This could be linked to the Commander&amp;rsquo;s new compatibility with a specific Apple TV remote, allowing it to integrate with Apple devices in the same space. Designed for later models of the 4002 turntable with the keypad connector on the main circuit board (types 551x and 552x), I recently built three receivers over the weekend and shipped them out today, each packaged with a compatible Apple remote:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of the Latest Version of the Beogram Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>While restoring my Beogram 4002 (5513), I decided to improve the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control I had previously designed. I added a &amp;ldquo;pairing&amp;rdquo; feature to prevent conflicts with Apple TVs and other devices that use Apple remotes. To completely eliminate the need to touch the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s delicate keypad, I also included remote switching between 33 and 45 RPM. A detailed video about the latest version explains the functions and demonstrates the remote and its pairing process:</description></item></channel></rss>