<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AirAsia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airasia/</link><description>Recent content in AirAsia on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airasia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces three new exclusive routes with a 20% discount on all flights until February 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</guid><description>AirAsia is the sole airline offering flights for three new routes: Johor Bahru to Tawau, Singapore to Kota Bharu, and Singapore to Terengganu. The airline is currently promoting these routes with fares as low as RM69* for travel between Johor Bahru and Tawau. This offer is valid for bookings made before February 16th, 2014, for travel dates between April 18th, 2014 and January 31st, 2015.
Welcome banners at Changi Airport</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces new flights between Penang and Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</guid><description>AirAsia has launched direct flights connecting Penang to Yangon, Myanmar, making it the airline&amp;rsquo;s seventh international destination accessible from its northern hub. Penang also offers direct flights to other international destinations, such as Ho Chi Minh City, Singapore, Medan, Jakarta, Surabaya, and Bangkok.
This new route will operate three times a week, starting on March 22, 2016. The flight schedule for Penang, Malaysia (PEN) – Yangon, Myanmar (RGN) is as follows:</description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service.</description></item><item><title>Starting on January 26, 2015, AirAsia will no longer impose fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 02:27:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Starting January 26, 2015, AirAsia, along with its long-haul affiliates AirAsia X, Thai AirAsia X, and Indonesia AirAsia X, will eliminate fuel surcharges on all flights. This decision aligns with the current downward trend in global oil prices.
Source: AirAsia eDM.
This marks a return to AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s previous policy from 2008, where fuel surcharges were eliminated on all domestic and international flights. However, due to surging fuel prices, surcharges were reinstated in 2011.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia has relocated its Surabaya operations to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 04:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</guid><description>AirAsia has relocated its operations from Terminal 1 to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport.
All AirAsia domestic and international flights to and from Surabaya will keep their original schedules and operate as usual.
Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport opened on February 14th. The terminal is designed to be environmentally friendly and can accommodate 6 million passengers annually. It features 40 check-in counters, an updated baggage handling system, six gates for domestic use, three gates for international flights, 12 avirobridges, and 14 parking stands for both narrow and wide-bodied aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities.</description></item><item><title>The AirAsia Foundation is investigating the concept of social enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia Foundation website.
The AirAsia Foundation is hosting a conference and marketplace focused on social enterprise on November 7th at Nexus Bangsar South in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. This event, Destination: Good – ASEAN Social Enterprise 2015, is the first public event organized by the AirAsia Foundation, the philanthropic branch of the AirAsia Group. Its goal is to initiate a discussion on the role large companies and social enterprises can play in fostering fair, sustainable, and inclusive economies.</description></item></channel></rss>