<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marriages of Convenience on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marriages-of-convenience/</link><description>Recent content in Marriages of Convenience on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marriages-of-convenience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Although you have children together, your marriage is not genuine': Marriages of convenience, UK courts, and EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Aleksandra Jolkina, PhD in Law, Queen Mary University of London
Over the last twenty years, UK authorities have become increasingly wary of marriages within the UK between mobile EU citizens and third-country nationals (TCNs) with uncertain or irregular residence status. In the current climate of Euroscepticism, such marriages are often criticized as &amp;ldquo;marriages of convenience,&amp;rdquo; intended to circumvent British immigration laws. This piece examines how UK courts interpret the concept of marriages of convenience, the potential implications for families of EU citizens residing in the UK, and the anticipated changes after Brexit.</description></item><item><title>The Handbook on Marriages of Convenience by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
In September 2014, the Commission introduced a Handbook designed to guide Member States in addressing marriages of convenience between EU citizens and non-EU nationals. The goal is to combat these marriages without unduly restricting the free movement rights of EU citizens. The Commission emphasizes that the guidelines, developed in collaboration with Member States, are not legally binding and don&amp;rsquo;t supersede existing EU law or its future interpretations.</description></item></channel></rss>