<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Korea on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/korea/</link><description>Recent content in Korea on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/korea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two JW Marriott hotels have been ranked in the top 10 TripAdvisor Travelers' Choices for Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Lotte Hotel Seoul.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for hotels in Korea ranked the following as the top ten:
Lotte Hotel Seoul, with a rating of 4.5 out of 5 from 1,849 reviews. The Plaza Conrad Seoul JW Marriott Dongdaemun Square Seoul Park Hyatt Seoul The Shilla Seoul Sheraton Seoul D Cube City Hotel The Westin Chosun Seoul The Ritz-Carlton, Seoul The JW Marriott Seoul Curious?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In January, StarHub will be featuring high-definition Korean movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</guid><description>StarHub TV customers will be the first in Asia to enjoy the latest and greatest Korean films in high definition (HD), 24 hours a day. The company announced that tvN Movies HD, Asia’s first channel dedicated to Korean films, will launch on StarHub TV (channel 818) on January 11, 2017. For added convenience, the channel will also be available on demand as tvN Movies VOD HD. Customers can watch it anytime on StarHub TV Channel 819, or stream it via StarHub Go, StarHub&amp;rsquo;s online streaming service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Business Plan package at The Shilla Seoul includes access to The Executive Lounge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. The Executive Lounge.
Through June 30, 2019, The Shilla Seoul is offering its Business Plan package, which gives guests the opportunity to experience The Executive Lounge.
Guests selecting the Executive Business Deluxe option receive exclusive access to The Executive Lounge, complimentary breakfast at The Parkview, and access to both the gym and indoor swimming pool.
The Executive Lounge at The Shilla Seoul, situated on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s top floor, is designed as a luxurious penthouse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jin Jiang International Hotels and Hanwha Hotels &amp; Resorts have officially merged their loyalty programs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</guid><description>Jin Jiang International Hotels from China and Hanwha Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts from Korea have joined their loyalty programs.
Starting September 1st, members of Jin Jiang&amp;rsquo;s J-Club and Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s THE PLUS will share membership benefits. This includes perks like discounts on rooms, food, and beverages, as well as late check-outs and room upgrades at both hotel groups. J-Club&amp;rsquo;s over 14 million members will also have access to Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s resorts and golf courses across Korea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asiana discontinues codeshare agreement with US Airways, impacting flights to Japan and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Asiana Airlines will end its codeshare agreement with US Airways on March 30, 2014. Passengers are advised to review their flight reservations. The affected routes are listed below:
Asiana Airlines flights
Japan
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Fukuoka, Osaka, Nagoya, Okinawa, and Shizuoka
America
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Chicago, New York, and Honolulu
US Airways flights
America
Los Angeles to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia San Francisco to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Seattle to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Chicago to/from Atlanta, Orlando, Indianapolis, Columbus, Cleveland, and Houston...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Le Meridien Seoul combines traditional Korean elements with French sophistication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 07:40:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</guid><description>Source: Le Meridien, Seoul website. Hub lobby.
The Le Meridien, Seoul, the first of its brand in Korea, introduces the renowned London-based David Collins Studio to the country. Conveniently located in the upscale Gangnam district, the hotel is a short walk from the Sinnonhyeon and Gangnam subway stations and easily accessible from both Gimpo (GMP) and Incheon (ICN) International Airports.
Tasked with designing the hotel&amp;rsquo;s public spaces and rooms, the studio has crafted a sophisticated blend of Parisian elegance with mid-century modern influences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A South Korean workwear brand is planning to grow its presence globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-south-korean-workwear-brand-is-planning-to-grow-its-presence-globally/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-south-korean-workwear-brand-is-planning-to-grow-its-presence-globally/</guid><description>Source: a.mont website.
A South Korean workwear company, a.mont, is expanding its reach internationally. Their online store currently operates in Korean and English, with plans to launch Japanese and Chinese versions soon.
A.mont offers uniforms and workwear designed by industry professionals, catering to diverse businesses including restaurants, cafes, hotels, corporations, and cosmetics companies.
Kim Hyuk, President of a.mont, highlights the changing perception of workwear: &amp;ldquo;While uniforms were once primarily about neatness, today&amp;rsquo;s trend emphasizes reflecting a company&amp;rsquo;s culture and values...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-south-korean-workwear-brand-is-planning-to-grow-its-presence-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-south-korean-workwear-brand-is-planning-to-grow-its-presence-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Urban Island promotion has been introduced by The Shilla Seoul</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</guid><description>With the arrival of summer, The Shilla Seoul presents Urban Island, a luxurious outdoor escape for guests. This all-inclusive retreat offers relaxation, a connection with nature, and delightful poolside service.
Reopened for the season, Urban Island welcomes guests to heated outdoor pools, a jacuzzi, and a rooftop garden against a scenic backdrop of Namsan Mountain and the Seoul skyline. Intimate cabanas nestled among lush greenery provide secluded havens.
The Urban Days room rate, available until June 30, 2019, starts from KRW 320,000 per night, excluding taxes and service charges, based on double occupancy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Viu introduces exclusive Korean content: Song Ji Hyo's Beauty Views</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 16:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</guid><description>Song Ji Hyo’s Beauty Views is a partnership between Viu and the famous Korean actress from the variety show Running Man.
Viu, a pan-Asian streaming platform owned by PCCW Media, has made investments in Viu Originals to boost user engagement. Viu Originals features Korean, Chinese, Indian, and Southeast Asian content for viewers across Asia.
Given the significant popularity of Korean content in the region, Viu Originals aims to increase user engagement by offering captivating and locally relevant original programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AIN has added English and Chinese websites for those interested in fashion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</guid><description>Source: AIN English website.
A Korean women&amp;rsquo;s fashion brand is aiming to become a global name, focusing particularly on mainland China, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
AIN has seen positive results selling on international e-commerce platforms. To further expand its reach, the company has launched English and Chinese websites through cafe24, a leading Korean e-commerce platform. AIN&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Park A-In, shared that customers appreciate the brand&amp;rsquo;s distinct, contemporary designs and overall aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>16% of the top 100 MBAs from the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Business schools in Asia may be overlooking the potential of online MBAs. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s first ever Online MBA Rankings for 2014, which came out in March, contained no Asian business schools in its list of the top 15 programs.
However, the region performs better in the traditional MBA format. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s Global MBA Rankings for 2014, published in January 2014, features a number of Asian schools within its top 50...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>La Yeon, the Korean fine-dining restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, has been awarded three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. Nine delicacies at La Yeon.
During the first-ever Michelin Guide Seoul launch in 2017, held at The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Dynasty Hall, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s traditional Korean fine-dining establishment, La Yeon, was granted a coveted three-star Michelin rating. Recognized for its authentic flavors, exceptional service, inviting atmosphere, and well-paired drinks, La Yeon stands as the sole Seoul restaurant within a hospitality group to achieve this three-star distinction...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG has introduced the G3 Beat, a mid-tier model of the G3, in Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG Electronics (LG) introduced the LG G3 Beat in Korea on July 18th. This mid-range version of their flagship G3 smartphone provides a comparable high-quality experience, incorporating the Floating Arc design and rapid Laser Auto Focus technology in a smaller form factor with a 5-inch thin-bezel display.
Dr. Jong-seok Park, President and CEO of LG Electronics Mobile Communications Company, emphasized the growing consumer demand for a balanced mix of aesthetics, functionality, performance, and affordability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google prefers websites that are optimized for mobile devices. Have you taken any steps to ensure your site is mobile-friendly?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</guid><description>World Markets Korea, a Seoul-based online marketing firm, has outlined some of the factors Google now considers when evaluating websites for mobile friendliness. These include text size, spacing between links, and whether the content fits comfortably on a mobile screen. Google uses these criteria to determine if a website is &amp;ldquo;Mobile Friendly.&amp;rdquo;
The company recommends that businesses engage their web designers to update their sites accordingly. World Markets Korea also provides services to optimize websites for mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enjoy delicious autumn treats at The Shilla Seoul and The Shilla Jeju</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-delicious-autumn-treats-at-the-shilla-seoul-and-the-shilla-jeju/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 19:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-delicious-autumn-treats-at-the-shilla-seoul-and-the-shilla-jeju/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul.
Both the Shilla Seoul and Shilla Jeju hotels are celebrating autumn with a variety of special promotions and activities.
The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s upscale Korean restaurant, La Yeon, will offer a special autumn menu featuring seasonal ingredients like pine nuts, sweet potatoes, and seafood in keeping with traditional culinary practices. La Yeon made its debut on the list of Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants in 2015 at position 38 and received the coveted One To Watch award...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-delicious-autumn-treats-at-the-shilla-seoul-and-the-shilla-jeju/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-delicious-autumn-treats-at-the-shilla-seoul-and-the-shilla-jeju/</a></p></description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Haenyeo Singapore visually captures the story of Jeju's female divers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. HAENYO SINGAPORE will be exhibited in Singapore until November 23rd.
Jose Jeuland, a French photographer based in Singapore, is presenting his debut photography exhibition. This exhibition, hosted at The Fullerton Hotel in Singapore, focuses on haenyo (해녀) - female divers from Jeju Island in South Korea. Epson Singapore, the official print sponsor for the exhibition, provided prints produced on one of their commercial and industrial photographic production printers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines expands its presence in the United States with a new codeshare agreement with Asiana Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines has broadened its codeshare partnership with Asiana Airlines, expanding its network beyond Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon International Airport to include Honolulu, Seattle, and Los Angeles.
These Star Alliance members have been codesharing on flights between Singapore and Seoul-Incheon since September 2005. Singapore Airlines currently offers four daily flights on this route, with one continuing to San Francisco, while Asiana operates daily flights.
Asiana also places its code on Singapore Airlines-operated flights extending beyond Singapore to Jakarta, Indonesia; Perth, Australia; Auckland, New Zealand; and Cape Town, South Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AC Works introduces Korean versions of free stock image websites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</guid><description>Source: AC works. Screen capture of illustAC.
AC works, a company with over 2.3 million users in Japan, is expanding globally. They recently introduced Korean versions of their popular stock image platforms: photoAC, illustAC, and silhouetteAC.
The stock image industry has historically been restrictive, often imposing fees for various uses of a single image. Costs are common for both the stock images themselves and their vector files. Purchased images typically come with limited usage rights, like a single use within a specific advertising campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An innovative social media project, fueled by the power of crowdsourcing, is revolutionizing Korean brand marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 01:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Bitter, Sweet, Seoul,&amp;rdquo; a feature-length film directed by Park Chan-wook, is the culmination of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s first international crowdsourced film project.
Source: PR Newswire
The Seoul Metropolitan Government, as part of a global brand marketing campaign to showcase the diverse experiences and emotions Seoul has to offer, invited individuals worldwide to submit short video clips about the city through YouTube and a dedicated microsite.
The initiative generated almost 12,000 submissions, totaling an impressive 159 hours, 35 minutes, and 4 seconds of footage from around the globe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>