<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Euratom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/euratom/</link><description>Recent content in Euratom on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/euratom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options.</description></item><item><title>The Day the Unicorns Cried: Understanding Phase 1 of the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
The recent joint report on the progress of Brexit negotiations, along with a related paper from the Commission, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of negotiations. Based on this report, the EU27 have agreed that &amp;ldquo;sufficient progress&amp;rdquo; has been made to move forward. This next phase will focus on a transition period and, potentially starting in March 2018, the framework for the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU.</description></item></channel></rss>