<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bespoke on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bespoke/</link><description>Recent content in Bespoke on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bespoke/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people.</description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces</description></item><item><title>Customized Samsung Galaxy choices arrive in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 07:38:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customized-samsung-galaxy-choices-arrive-in-singapore/</guid><description>Samsung is enhancing the customization options for its Galaxy devices in Singapore.
Customers shopping on the Samsung Online Store can now personalize their Galaxy Z Flip4 5G with the Bespoke Edition. This edition offers 75 combinations of glass colors and frame options, including Black, Silver, or Gold frames, and front and back colors like Yellow, White, Navy, Khaki, or Red. Priced at S$1,548, the custom designs are available for the 256 GB variant only, with delivery taking up to four weeks.</description></item></channel></rss>