<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Metro Area Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metro-area-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Metro Area Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metro-area-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>