<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alpheus Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/alpheus-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Alpheus Communications on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/alpheus-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps).</description></item></channel></rss>