<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asylum Procedures on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asylum-procedures/</link><description>Recent content in Asylum Procedures on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asylum-procedures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What potential issues could arise with the EU, Turkey, and the Refugee Crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers* and Emanuela Roman, University of Palermo and Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam**
*Emanuela Roman wrote the sections on ‘safe third country’, ‘super-safe third country’ and ‘first country of asylum’. Steve Peers wrote the rest of the main text and the annexes.
Turkey plays a pivotal role in the EU&amp;rsquo;s current refugee crisis, hosting over two million Syrian refugees and serving as a transit point for many asylum seekers. A growing number of these individuals travel from Turkey to the Greek islands, contributing to a notable increase in asylum seekers within the EU in recent times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three main points about the EU's New Pact on Migration and Asylum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</guid><description>Lilian Tsourdi, Assistant Professor, University of Maastricht
*Photo credit: Délmagyarország/Schmidt Andrea
The EU&amp;rsquo;s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, along with its accompanying legislative proposals, represents the latest policy framework for asylum, migration, and border management. Its stated goal is to create streamlined migration procedures and stronger governance. Since September 2020, negotiations on the Pact&amp;rsquo;s legislative components have been underway.
Recently, both the European Parliament (April 2023) and the Council of the European Union (June 2023) have adopted negotiating positions on two significant instruments: the Asylum Procedures Regulation (APR), which updates regulations on determining asylum and related rights, and the Asylum and Migration Management Regulation (AMMR), which reforms the EU&amp;rsquo;s system for allocating responsibility for processing asylum requests and establishing a solidarity framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the draft EU/Turkey agreement on migration and refugees legally sound?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent legal debates have arisen concerning the proposed EU/Turkey agreement on refugees. While general points were discussed last month, a leaked draft of the final deal necessitates a closer examination before the finalizing summit.
The agreement, framed as an EU-Turkey statement, builds upon the March 7, 2016, statement with added elements. It is crucial to note that as a statement, it won&amp;rsquo;t be legally binding, requiring no formal EU or national approval beyond the summit&amp;rsquo;s endorsement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Childhood Coming to an End? The Court of Justice Affirms the Right of Unaccompanied Child Refugees to Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Reaching the age of 18 is a major milestone, signifying a transition to adulthood. While it may not bring immediate changes to family dynamics, it holds significant legal implications.
However, in immigration and asylum law, turning 18 can mean reduced legal rights, especially for vulnerable unaccompanied minors. Given lengthy legal processes, a key question arises: When an applicant starts as a minor but turns 18 before the process concludes, do they keep the protections afforded to children?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Could a third phase of the Common European Asylum System bring wisdom and goodness to those who are considered vile?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 05:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
The EU is looking to overhaul its Common European Asylum Policy, and the Commission has laid out its suggestions in a new discussion paper. These proposals, which are expected to lead to further legislation, aim to address the flaws in the current system. This blog post will break down these proposals and analyze their potential impact.
The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum policy has been developed in phases, with the initial legislation implemented between 2003 and 2005 and the second phase between 2011 and 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Assessing the Legal Implications of the EU/Turkey Refugee Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</guid><description>Steve Peers analyzes the legal and political implications of the recent EU-Turkey agreement on refugees. The agreement, while legally controversial, aims to address the refugee crisis and restore order.
A key point of contention is the return of migrants arriving in Greece to Turkey. While the agreement states this will be done in accordance with international law, returning all migrants without considering individual circumstances raises concerns about collective expulsion, a violation of EU and international law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rights for data protection and administrative procedures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the cases of YS and M and S clarified data protection rights for asylum-seekers. This judgment could also have wider implications for accessing documents in administrative procedures.
Two asylum-seekers in the Netherlands wanted to see file notes related to their cases. Instead of relying on the EU’s asylum procedures Directive, which grants access to reasons for negative decisions and interview reports but not all documents, they invoked the data protection Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evaluating the new proposal on "Safe countries of origin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission recently introduced several new immigration and asylum initiatives. Three proposals, in particular, suggest binding measures: a temporary relocation measure for asylum-seekers, a permanent relocation system for asylum-seekers, and a regulation establishing a common list of &amp;ldquo;safe countries of origin.&amp;rdquo; This list would include Western Balkan countries and Turkey. This article will focus on the &amp;ldquo;safe country of origin&amp;rdquo; rules.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the UK, Ireland, and Denmark are not subject to these measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>