<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project Accounting on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/project-accounting/</link><description>Recent content in Project Accounting on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 10:42:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/project-accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 2 of the Project Accounting Timesheet Recalc has been released.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/version-2-of-the-project-accounting-timesheet-recalc-has-been-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 10:42:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/version-2-of-the-project-accounting-timesheet-recalc-has-been-released/</guid><description>A new version of the Project Accounting Timesheet Recalc Utility (Version 2.0) has been released to address a customer&amp;rsquo;s need.
This utility is designed for Dynamics GP users who utilize Project Accounting Timesheets to track salaried employees&amp;rsquo; time.
Salaried employees receive fixed payroll costs. However, when their worked hours fluctuate from the standard hours within a pay period, the general ledger project timesheet costs don&amp;rsquo;t align with their actual payroll expenses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/version-2-of-the-project-accounting-timesheet-recalc-has-been-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/version-2-of-the-project-accounting-timesheet-recalc-has-been-released/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dance with the one who brought you - Fixing transactions in Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dance-with-the-one-who-brought-you-fixing-transactions-in-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dance-with-the-one-who-brought-you-fixing-transactions-in-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>It seems many questions on Dynamics GP forums revolve around fixing transactions, or even worse, how fixing one transaction created more problems. When I train, I emphasize &amp;ldquo;Dance with the one who brung &amp;lsquo;ya,&amp;rdquo; meaning corrections should happen where the transaction originated. During my support shifts, I get asked &amp;ldquo;how do I fix this?&amp;rdquo; a lot. I always start with these questions:
What&amp;rsquo;s been tried already? Often, attempts to fix the issue made it worse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dance-with-the-one-who-brought-you-fixing-transactions-in-dynamics-gp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dance-with-the-one-who-brought-you-fixing-transactions-in-dynamics-gp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Inventory Transfer Entry: Dual Personality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inventory-transfer-entry-dual-personality/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 09:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inventory-transfer-entry-dual-personality/</guid><description>When people hear &amp;ldquo;Inventory Transfer Entry,&amp;rdquo; they usually think of moving an item between locations. However, this function (found in Transactions&amp;raquo;Project) is actually a project accounting tool with multiple uses.
If you use Project Accounting with Inventory, you probably recognize this as the step after receiving a project-related item. Here&amp;rsquo;s a typical project accounting purchase and inventory workflow:
A purchase order for an inventory item is recorded and linked to a project and cost category, increasing the committed cost on the project budget...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inventory-transfer-entry-dual-personality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inventory-transfer-entry-dual-personality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sourcing default accounts for project accounting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sourcing-default-accounts-for-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:50:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sourcing-default-accounts-for-project-accounting/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently managing multiple project accounting implementations. When dealing with several similar projects simultaneously, I concentrate on common aspects. Recently, my focus has been on the default project account configuration in Dynamics GP (Tools&amp;raquo;Setup&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;Accounts). Explaining this to clients who inquire about how the project determines account usage is interesting. The answer usually depends on their setup.
Default posting accounts in Dynamics GP&amp;rsquo;s core modules are straightforward. The system prioritizes the master record for account specifications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sourcing-default-accounts-for-project-accounting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sourcing-default-accounts-for-project-accounting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Have you heard about Project Macros?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-heard-about-project-macros/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-heard-about-project-macros/</guid><description>Have you ever been surprised after adding project accounting to Dynamics GP, only to find that users are constantly asked if they want to include project details when entering purchase orders?
You might already know that GP support offers macros for both customers and vendors. These tools automatically set default project settings, eliminating the need for manual entry or repetitive prompts.
For additional information, please reach out to me at christinap@theknastergroup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-heard-about-project-macros/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-heard-about-project-macros/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alternative uses for existing products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-uses-for-existing-products/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-uses-for-existing-products/</guid><description>A client needed a system to track expenses online. They were looking for a basic solution and found the popular options too expensive. While searching for alternatives, I realized they already owned a software called Project Accounting, but weren&amp;rsquo;t using its expense features.
We decided to implement the Time and Expense portion of their existing software to meet their needs. This was a much more affordable option, especially since they didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full functionality of the software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-uses-for-existing-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-uses-for-existing-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Allocating project costs by unit for accounting purposes.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allocating-project-costs-by-unit-for-accounting-purposes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allocating-project-costs-by-unit-for-accounting-purposes/</guid><description>While stuck in a Denver hotel room during a snowstorm, I finally had a chance to unravel a feature in our project management software.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been curious about the Project Allocation feature since its release last summer but haven&amp;rsquo;t had a project that required it. My initial exploration didn&amp;rsquo;t help me grasp its capabilities compared to the Unit allocation method at the Cost Category level. However, last night&amp;rsquo;s testing session brought some clarity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allocating-project-costs-by-unit-for-accounting-purposes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allocating-project-costs-by-unit-for-accounting-purposes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Issue with upgrading Project Accounting and Purchase Order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 03:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</guid><description>A recent upgrade from GP9 to GP10 resulted in an unexpected issue: purchase order line items were missing account numbers. This was perplexing because previous upgrades, even those involving project accounting, had gone smoothly.
The problem became evident when a user discovered that upon receiving purchase orders, no Cost of Goods Sold account defaulted. This was because the purchase order line items lacked account numbers. Database examination confirmed that the INVINDX field, which stores account indexes for purchase order lines in the POP10110 table, was empty for all 7500 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Frustration with integrating project accounting: Customer project information</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frustration-with-integrating-project-accounting-customer-project-information/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frustration-with-integrating-project-accounting-customer-project-information/</guid><description>Steve Endow wrote this two-part blog post about managing unique numbering for records, using an example from his project accounting integration with eConnect.
Endow&amp;rsquo;s integration pulls four columns of data from an Excel file to create records in GP, setting up projects from the customer level to the budget. However, he encountered an unexpected problem with the PA Customer Options window, which, though simple, isn&amp;rsquo;t automatically set up by eConnect. This window has a &amp;ldquo;Customer Alias&amp;rdquo; field, limited to five characters, which becomes problematic when dealing with many sequentially numbered customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frustration-with-integrating-project-accounting-customer-project-information/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frustration-with-integrating-project-accounting-customer-project-information/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Issue with Project Accounting Cost Category and Fee ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 01:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</guid><description>Last week, a client contacted me with a peculiar problem in Project Accounting. While their actual billings and payments/receipts matched in summary and detail, running the Cash Apply reconciliation (Tools&amp;raquo;Routines&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;PA Reconcile) incorrectly recalculated the payments/receipts as less than the actual billings. This discrepancy, equal to the &amp;ldquo;FREIGHT&amp;rdquo; fee charged on projects, was especially noticeable on projects with a single invoice and payment.
We investigated the database, comparing the &amp;ldquo;FREIGHT&amp;rdquo; fee setup to other fees, but found no differences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tracking assets for project accounting.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-assets-for-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-assets-for-project-accounting/</guid><description>Many clients are using Microsoft Dynamics GP&amp;rsquo;s Project Accounting module in unconventional ways, often because it&amp;rsquo;s included in their software suite. One example is using it to track capital expenditures, effectively managing the various costs associated with a capital project, such as labor, materials, and overhead.
A common question is how to manage asset &amp;ldquo;recognition&amp;rdquo; when a project reaches a certain completion stage and construction in progress (CIP) becomes capitalized. We can address this by utilizing the Work in Progress (WIP) function within Project Accounting, employing a time and materials project to simulate the transfer of expenses from a CIP account to an asset account...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-assets-for-project-accounting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-assets-for-project-accounting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Costs for timesheets in project accounting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/costs-for-timesheets-in-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/costs-for-timesheets-in-project-accounting/</guid><description>Lately, Steve and I have been collaborating on a customization to tackle a recurring obstacle I encounter with project accounting timesheets for salaried employees. It&amp;rsquo;s a problem that bothers me enough that I frequently seek reassurance from others in the field, such as project accounting consultants, trainers, and Microsoft support.
What exactly is the issue? Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate with a scenario:
Employee 1 earns a salary of $1000 per week, resulting in an hourly rate of $25 based on a 2080-hour work year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/costs-for-timesheets-in-project-accounting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/costs-for-timesheets-in-project-accounting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ramblings on Project Accounting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ramblings-on-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ramblings-on-project-accounting/</guid><description>It can be lonely being a Microsoft Dynamics GP Project Accounting trainer because there aren&amp;rsquo;t many of us, and clients seem to use the module differently. This highlights a contradiction: Project Accounting is specialized yet serves diverse purposes. Through my experience, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that thorough discovery, including pre-purchase discussions about realistic expectations and software fit, is crucial for successful implementation.
While Project Accounting fulfills many requirements and boosts productivity, it&amp;rsquo;s vital to understand its limitations, which can be addressed proactively during implementation:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ramblings-on-project-accounting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ramblings-on-project-accounting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A straightforward approach: Managing the ego</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-straightforward-approach-managing-the-ego/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:54:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-straightforward-approach-managing-the-ego/</guid><description>I like to think of myself as a creative problem-solver. Finding ingenious solutions to complex issues is something I take pride in. With enough time and focus, my logic and reasoning skills (and a healthy dose of sarcasm) can usually crack the code.
However, today I encountered a real head-scratcher, a problem that genuinely stumped me (cue the sarcastic surprise). Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of the situation:
The client has been using project accounting since January 1, 2009, with no changes to their fiscal period setup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-straightforward-approach-managing-the-ego/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-straightforward-approach-managing-the-ego/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>