<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ransomware/</link><description>Recent content in Ransomware on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:24:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ransomware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Acronis True Image 2018 features AI technology that can detect ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</guid><description>Acronis Integrates AI into True Image 2018 for Enhanced Data Protection Image: Beloussov introducing Acronis ahead of the launch of Acronis True Image 2018.
Beloussov speaking at the Acronis True Image 2018 launch event.
Acronis, a global leader in hybrid cloud data protection, is incorporating artificial intelligence (AI) into its entire product line. Serguei Beloussov, co-founder and CEO of Acronis, emphasized their commitment to AI integration across all products. This announcement was made during the launch of their flagship product, Acronis True Image 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces the latest version of its software, Acronis True Image 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 19:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</guid><description>Acronis introduces the Acronis Survival Kit, a comprehensive system recovery solution.
New active disk cloning functionality for Mac enables data migration to other devices.
Acronis Active Protection, powered by AI, effectively combats ransomware threats.
Acronis Notary and ASign leverage blockchain technology to guarantee data integrity through notarization and e-signatures.
Enhanced backup solutions now extend protection to social media profiles.
Acronis, a leading provider of cyber protection and hybrid cloud solutions, has unveiled the 15th-anniversary edition of its renowned personal backup software, Acronis True Image 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia is included in global ransomware attacks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 20:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</guid><description>WannaCrypt, also referred to as WannaCry or WCry, holds data files hostage and demands a $300 USD ransom in Bitcoin. The ransom message warns that the payment will double after three days. If payment isn&amp;rsquo;t received within seven days, the encrypted files are permanently deleted.
A key feature of WannaCrypt is its ability to self-propagate within company networks without any user intervention. This is achieved by exploiting a known weakness in the Microsoft Windows operating system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Veritas presents a concise overview of ransomware in just five minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veritas-presents-a-concise-overview-of-ransomware-in-just-five-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 08:41:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veritas-presents-a-concise-overview-of-ransomware-in-just-five-minutes/</guid><description>Justin Loh, Singapore Country Director at Veritas, points out that the shift to remote work, using various often unsecured personal devices and networks, has made businesses more vulnerable to attacks. This creates opportunities for malicious actors to steal sensitive information and hold it for ransom.
Here’s a concise overview of ransomware:
What is ransomware?
Ransomware is a type of malicious software that blocks access to computer systems or data until a ransom is paid...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veritas-presents-a-concise-overview-of-ransomware-in-just-five-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veritas-presents-a-concise-overview-of-ransomware-in-just-five-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kaspersky provides solutions to combat ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</guid><description>Ransomware is increasingly targeting businesses, encrypting files and demanding payment for decryption keys.
A Kaspersky Lab report reveals a six-fold increase in ransomware attacks against businesses from 2015 to 2016, affecting one in ten business users.
Cybercriminals are focusing on businesses, particularly small and medium-sized companies. A Kaspersky Lab and B2B International study found that 42% of respondents from these businesses considered ransomware a major threat.
Even brief data unavailability can severely impact small businesses, potentially halting operations entirely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>