<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Private Lines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar.</description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions.</description></item><item><title>DS1 Bandwidth vs Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</guid><description>DS1, commonly called T1, is a popular choice for business internet. This article will explain DS1 and compare it to another popular option: Ethernet over Copper.
While the terms are often used synonymously, DS1 and T1 are slightly different. They both come from a set of technical standards created by Bell Labs called the T-carrier system, which was originally a digital replacement for analog phone lines. Though designed for telephones, DS1 and T1 are now widely used for dedicated internet connections and private lines.</description></item><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections.</description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion.</description></item><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Attributes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-attributes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 13:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-attributes/</guid><description>T1 lines have become the standard connectivity solution for small and medium-sized businesses. They support various uses like dedicated internet connections, private lines, network access, and business phone lines. What makes T1 lines so popular?
A T1 line uses one or two twisted pairs of copper telephone wiring installed between a business and the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. While the local telephone company owns this copper wiring, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t have to buy T1 service directly from them.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind.</description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit and 10 Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you ever wanted to expand your Local Area Network (LAN) to reach locations across a city or even further? A Metro Fiber Ethernet connection can help. This type of connection acts as an extension of your existing LAN, linking multiple locations seamlessly.
The Challenge of Connecting Multiple LANs
Private networks, typically Ethernet LANs, give you complete control within your own space. You manage the cabling, switches, routers, user devices, and overall network operations.</description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines, a technology dating back to the telegraph, have evolved to offer businesses speeds ranging from 1.5 Mbps to 100 Gbps. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the characteristics of leased lines and how they stand apart from conventional broadband.
What is a Leased Line?
Similar to leasing a property, leased lines involve an agreement and regular payments that grant you exclusive access to a dedicated communication line.
In its simplest form, a leased line consists of a pair of copper wires, linking your location to your provider, often through a local telephone company (ILEC).</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price.</description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Can Improve Telephone Reliability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</guid><description>Many businesses, even large ones, hold onto their own phone systems believing it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to guarantee reliable communication. But is this true, or is it time to reconsider this assumption?
The phone service industry has experienced a significant shift with the emergence of hosted PBX (HPBX), also called hosted VoIP or cloud communications. Like other cloud-based technologies, this is a game-changer. In the future, we&amp;rsquo;ll wonder why we didn&amp;rsquo;t switch sooner.</description></item></channel></rss>