<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Foreign on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/foreign/</link><description>Recent content in Foreign on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/foreign/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Compass Offices has launched a new business center at Oberoi Centre in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</guid><description>Compass Offices, a leading provider of serviced offices in the Asia Pacific region, is expanding its presence to the United Arab Emirates with the inauguration of its first business center in Dubai in July 2014. This strategic move comes on the heels of the company&amp;rsquo;s recent expansion into Australia and Kazakhstan, as well as the establishment of new business centers in Hong Kong.
Alexander Passler, Vice President of Business Development at Compass Offices, highlighted Dubai&amp;rsquo;s growing appeal for businesses, stating, &amp;ldquo;Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation for economic stability and its thriving financial hub status are attracting a growing number of companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawksford has released the latest data on new business formations in Singapore for the fourth quarter of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 09:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</guid><description>Source: Hawksford report. Data represents the shareholder&amp;rsquo;s country of origin. Although the final quarter of 2015 saw a decrease in new Singaporean company formations compared to the previous quarter and the same period last year, international investors continue to set up companies and subsidiaries in Singapore, according to Hawksford, a provider of corporate, private client, and fund administration services.
Hawksford notes this decline is typical for the fourth quarter. Private limited companies made up the largest portion of new formations at 48...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, ASEAN received the highest amount of foreign direct investment (FDI) among developing countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The latest ASEAN Investment Report examines the growth of foreign direct investment (FDI) into the ASEAN region, particularly the influence of corporations on infrastructure expansion and regional integration.
In 2014, ASEAN emerged as the top recipient of FDI among developing nations. FDI inflows to the region experienced a third consecutive year of growth, reaching US$136.2 billion, a rise from US$117.7 billion in 2013. This achievement occurred despite a 16% global decline in FDI and inconsistent global economic progress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>