<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Christmas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/christmas/</link><description>Recent content in Christmas on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:27:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel has released its annual festive film about a lost phone just before Christmas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest holiday film centers around the importance of family connection during the Christmas season, particularly in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s tech-savvy environment.
The film, titled The Gift, portrays a teenager excessively focused on her digital life and how this affects her family&amp;rsquo;s Christmas traditions. The creators were inspired by research indicating that people of all ages, across demographics, are spending a significant amount of time on their phones, even more so than quality time with their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-released-its-annual-festive-film-about-a-lost-phone-just-before-christmas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2015 Singapore Christmas Gift Guide: The Joyful Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</guid><description>The holiday season is here, and with it comes the need for corporate gift ideas. Fortunately, there are many options to choose from this year.
Source: Kaizer Leather website.
Kaizer Leather offers a variety of leather business gifts, ranging from handcrafted luggage to smaller leather accessories. One notable option is the Cavalry Business Bag (shown above), crafted from high-quality Italian calf leather and featuring a detachable, adjustable shoulder strap.
~ o ~..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Orchard Road in Singapore is adorned with Christmas lights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road is aglow with Disney magic this holiday season. The &amp;ldquo;Disney Magical Moments — Christmas on A Great Street!&amp;rdquo; celebration features illuminated displays of beloved characters. The lights were officially switched on the evening of November 10.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the Toy Story-themed lights outside Plaza Singapura from the opening night.
The lights are arranged in four color-themed zones:
- Orange: Pixar’s Toy Story characters, including Woody, Buzz Lightyear, and their friends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sony Singapore's year-end promotions are valid until the beginning of January 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</guid><description>Are you looking for some of Sony&amp;rsquo;s top products from 2019? Here are a few:
Digital imaging
Sony A7 III
Source: Sony. The α7 III.
The A7 III boasts five-axis stabilization, 4D Focus for reliable focusing in low light (down to EV-3), and the capability to record 4K HDR videos.
Promotional price: S$2,699 (usual price S$2,899)
Sony α7 III with 35mm full-frame image sensor (ILCE7M3K) Sony RX100 VII
The compact RX100 VII features an extensive zoom range and remarkable speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazon has introduced exclusive holiday offers for Prime Now members</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</guid><description>This holiday season, Amazon Prime members in Singapore can enjoy thousands of deals on local and international products through the Prime Now app. These deals cover a wide range of categories, from toys and electronics to beauty products and holiday essentials.
Since its launch, Prime Now has expanded its offerings to include new brands like Yakult, Dell, Tefal, Sambucol, Bausch &amp;amp; Lomb, and Pinkfong. New categories such as fresh flowers, organic fruits (including durians), and international foods have also been added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Last Minute Online Gifts For Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</guid><description>_On Christmas Eve, instead of the typical peaceful house,
your home is filled with stress as you realize you forgot a gift.
Despite your best efforts, you overlooked someone on your list.
The pressure is on to find a solution quickly.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that can save your holiday!
Search online and find the K.I.N.D site for the perfect gift.
You&amp;rsquo;ll not only deliver a thoughtful present but also make a difference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Hong Kong offers a plethora of high-end gift options. Make a lasting impression with these distinctive incentive or corporate gift suggestions:
For the Fashionable
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjTOBGQGtqMhlt_i0m3XHwBn1QjO906znU9xMy97VBPqWBHVy80nBxjOKm1Lgg1I_v5sIp6sxy7HGCTZRC2xSpXTAGFdVOIKDSwZQes3MFguk5NpzGOVFh1lp4vHGEYKbE_CzRPC6l2PblW/s1600/chandelier+earrings.JPG)
Source: The 5th C. My 5-Ways chandelier earrings.
The 5th C, a Hong Kong-based diamond consultancy and jewelry brand, presents My 5-Ways, a completely customizable pair of diamond earrings. At their core, My 5-Ways are elegant stud earrings. However, with a few simple adjustments, they transform into studs with drops, elegant dangle earrings, or eye-catching chandelier earrings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a unique twist on French-inspired dining this holiday season at Sofitel So Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel So Singapore. Paulo.
At Sofitel So Singapore, Xperience restaurant&amp;rsquo;s head chef, Trevor Paulo, is celebrating his first Christmas season at the hotel with a special four-course Christmas Eve dinner.
The dinner starts with a small bite of blinis topped with dill yogurt and herring roe. The first course is a visually appealing dish of house-cured Salmon Gravlax arranged to look like a miniature garden with edible truffle &amp;ldquo;soil&amp;rdquo; and pickled shallots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the end of the year with eco-friendly festivities at East, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</guid><description>The environmentally conscious EAST, Hong Kong hotel is ready to celebrate the holiday season this year with special decorations and exciting events.
Continuing a tradition that began in 2014, EAST&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Village highlights creative recycling. This year, the EAST team gathered fallen logs left behind by Typhoon Mangkhut from the city streets to create unique Christmas decorations. Students from Jockey Club Sarah Roe School (JCSRS), the only school in Hong Kong offering an English curriculum for students with additional learning needs, collaborated with the EAST team on this project...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Immerse yourself in the holiday spirit with the Holiday fragrance by House of Sillage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</guid><description>Source: House of Sillage.
House of Sillage, a high-end perfume maker, introduces its Holiday fragrance for the Christmas season. The perfume features a blend of mandarin, peach, and vetiver, creating a festive aroma.
The design of the fragrance bottle draws inspiration from the illuminated Rockefeller Center Christmas tree in New York City. Its snow globe cap, crafted from 18-karat gold and white gold, depicts a scene of falling snow. The floral and citrus perfume is housed in a hand-polished glass bottle with an ombre lacquer finish...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It’s Free Phones Time For The Holidays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 15:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>The holiday season is about to start, and many people will rush to buy things like new smartphones. But before you spend a lot of money, consider getting a free phone.
You can find free phones by using a special search engine that focuses on phones offered for free when you sign up for a new service contract. You can find this search engine at Cell Phone Plan Finder.
You might think these free phones are outdated models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indulge in these food-themed gifts and enjoy!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 03:45:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</guid><description>As the holiday season approaches, businesses are looking for unique and thoughtful gifts for clients and employees. Here are a few distinctive gift ideas:
Source: Cafédirect.
For coffee lovers, Cafédirect, a British beverage company, introduced a premium freeze-dried instant coffee in Singaporean supermarkets this year. This meticulously crafted blend combines the sweetness and chocolate notes of South American Arabica beans with the well-rounded flavor of Central American beans and the boldness of East African Robusta beans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in celebrating at Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong and Macau are celebrating this December with special holiday menus.
An American feast at Grand Central
Source: Eclipse Hospitality Group. Cardamom spiced snapper fillet combined with winter squash, asparagus and lemongrass broth.
Grand Central, situated on the roof of the Elements shopping mall, is offering three-course dinners for HK$368 and four-course dinners for HK$398. Start with roasted sweet potato soup or roasted beets with blue cheese mousse, poached pears, and pistachios...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During the festive season, you can find exclusive Ferrero Rocher pralines at Pasticceria Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 03:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>Celebrities Qi Yu Wu and Joanne Peh are pictured at the event.
Ferrero Rocher has opened its first Southeast Asia store, Pasticceria Ferrero, at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Wisma Atria on Orchard Road. This unique boutique is the only one in the world and will be open for the holiday season.
A sneak peek before the official opening.
The shop offers a unique experience, allowing customers to personalize chocolate boxes with limited-edition Ferrero pralines available only during this special time of year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Festive takeaways and buffets at Hotel Jen Tanglin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 06:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</guid><description>Hotel Jen Tanglin&amp;rsquo;s popular &amp;ldquo;Fully-Loaded&amp;rdquo; holiday takeaway meal is back. This offering features a whole roasted turkey, accompanied by all the fixings, conveniently packaged in a thermal bag. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to easily serve 10 to 12 guests.
According to Vathsala Subramaniam, General Manager of Hotel Jen Tanglin Singapore, they&amp;rsquo;ve crafted a special Asian roasted turkey using the &amp;ldquo;percik&amp;rdquo; style. This approach aims to blend tradition with a distinct Asian flavor. For those with bigger parties, ordering both the Western and Asian style turkeys ensures a diverse culinary experience for everyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2020 Christmas Gift Guide: Must-Have Gadgets for the Holiday Season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:34:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>As the year ends, it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to treat yourself. Check out these gadgets for relaxation and maybe even work:
OPPO Find X2 Pro smartphone
The OPPO Find X2 Pro blends technology and elegant design. Marketed as &amp;ldquo;a cinema in your hand,&amp;rdquo; it boasts a 120 Hz QHD+ Ultra Vision screen with exceptional resolution, color, refresh rate, and brightness. Enjoy immersive audio and video with its powerful dual speakers and Dolby Atmos...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarke Quay is shimmering with holiday spirit this Christmas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-is-shimmering-with-holiday-spirit-this-christmas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:44:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-is-shimmering-with-holiday-spirit-this-christmas/</guid><description>This Christmas season at Clarke Quay is all about celebrating and enjoying the festivities. Visitors can delight in the luminous displays along the river or snap photos with Christmas characters every Friday and Saturday from 8 pm to 10 pm until December 30th around Clarke Quay and Read Bridge.
From December 5th to 7th, between 5 pm and 11 pm, shoppers can explore a wide selection of handcrafted goods at the Artisan Pop Up Christmas Market located in Central Fountain Square...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-is-shimmering-with-holiday-spirit-this-christmas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarke-quay-is-shimmering-with-holiday-spirit-this-christmas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cirque de Cuisine: The Festive Edition returns to Atlantis, The Palm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</guid><description>Source: Atlantis, The Palm. Cirque de Cuisine.
The Cirque de Cuisine event will launch Dubai&amp;rsquo;s holiday season with a Winter Wonderland theme. Held on December 6th at The Avenues in Atlantis, The Palm, this all-you-can-eat-and-drink event offers early bird tickets starting at AED495 for four hours of holiday festivities.
Cirque de Cuisine gives diners the opportunity to sample signature dishes, live cooking stations, buffets, drinks, and live entertainment at a variety of restaurants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong offers a winter wonderland experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:08:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</guid><description>Source: HKTB website.
With temperatures dipping below 15°C, December is an ideal time for a winter escape to Hong Kong. The ongoing 2015 Hong Kong WinterFest offers a variety of attractions and experiences for visitors.
A short walk from the Observation Wheel, where visitors can enjoy a 15-minute ride with panoramic views of Victoria Harbour and the Hong Kong skyline from luxurious gondolas, stands a dazzling, jewellery-inspired Serpenti light art installation in Statue Square, Central...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Watsons stores in Singapore are offering a variety of Christmas gift sets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watsons-stores-in-singapore-are-offering-a-variety-of-christmas-gift-sets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watsons-stores-in-singapore-are-offering-a-variety-of-christmas-gift-sets/</guid><description>Watsons Singapore offers a variety of boxed Christmas gift sets, ideal for office Secret Santa gift exchanges. These sets include toiletries, travel accessories, and even a coffee mug.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjuFQqRo_4KdJEEAt15qa83slFSXiCLkOhVqNapfI1b4jkE6ukFQPhs1wRGbVAowuWpJ4UwAN_fCdEHchVu3DPtpFMtEedEO6vXFbR06xUcMG0stNQ2hbT_c0NaucfCCoJVqEoT4RiWifek/s1600/watsons+spaa+reviving+collection.JPG)
Source: Watsons. The Spaa Reviving Collection.
The Spaa Reviving Collection (S$15.90) allows you to create a spa experience at home. It includes aloe vera extract and pro vitamin B5 to calm both your senses and skin. The set contains a 150ml body wash, 100ml body lotion, 100ml body scrub, 50g bath fizzer, and a body puff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watsons-stores-in-singapore-are-offering-a-variety-of-christmas-gift-sets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watsons-stores-in-singapore-are-offering-a-variety-of-christmas-gift-sets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Be cautious of malware with a Christmas theme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</guid><description>Christmas tree, Marina Bay Sands.
_&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;On the twelfth day of Christmas
my true love gave me:
Twelve pieces of malware
Eleven malfunctioning firewalls
Ten ransomware dangers
Nine account breaches
Eight adware websites
Seven deceitful emails
Six compromised PDFs
Five warning signs
Four spyware-infected games
Three junk text messages
Two Trojan horses
And a phishing email!&amp;quot;_
Holiday greetings can carry hidden cyber threats, even if sent from loved ones. Yeo Siang Tiong, Southeast Asia General Manager at Kaspersky Lab, emphasizes the importance of robust computer and mobile device protection before engaging in holiday activities like downloading festive content, sending emails, or online shopping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazon is sharing the best-selling Christmas items from Prime Now Singapore orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</guid><description>Amazon has revealed the top-selling items purchased by Prime Now users in Singapore during a record-breaking holiday season worldwide. Customers took advantage of Prime Now&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ultra-Fast Delivery&amp;rdquo; option throughout the holiday period, with tens of thousands of products delivered, even in the final hours. The last Prime Now order was delivered at 10:23 p.m. on December 24th.
&amp;ldquo;The volume of shoppers in Singapore using Prime Now leading up to Christmas was remarkable, as was the number who signed up for a free Prime trial or initiated a paid membership,&amp;rdquo; shared Kourosh Kaghazian, Country Manager for Amazon Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks' festive beverages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/</guid><description>An advertisement for Starbucks&amp;rsquo; holiday beverages at a train station in Singapore.
Starbucks has launched its holiday drink menu in participating stores globally. Some of the drinks available in the Asia Pacific region include:
Teavana Apple Joyful Medley Tea
This new Christmas beverage features a blend of black, oolong, and jasmine green teas, combined with apple juice and topped with cinnamon foam. It&amp;rsquo;s available hot or iced.
Christmas Panettone Latte..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-festive-beverages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sydney's Christmas programme has been officially launched by the City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</guid><description>Source: City of Sydney. Lord Mayor Clover Moore launched the Sydney Christmas program at Martin Place.
Sydney has officially begun its Christmas celebrations, featuring an array of decorations, carols, light displays, concerts, Christmas trees, and special retail events.
Lord Mayor Clover Moore expressed her enthusiasm for the festivities, stating, &amp;ldquo;Each year, we warmly welcome thousands of people from all over Sydney to the city center for our Christmas celebrations. With live concerts, vibrant light projections, excellent shopping opportunities, and the chance for kids to meet Santa, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone - visitors, shoppers, and locals alike...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During the holiday season, Transamerica Life Bermuda and the World Wide Fund for Nature are advocating for the conservation of forests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 08:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/</guid><description>Source: TLB/WWF. A booth for the Rewrap Project.
Transamerica Life Bermuda (TLB), a life insurance provider for high-net-worth individuals, has teamed up with the World Wide Fund for Nature (WWF) in Singapore to launch the Rewrap Project.
The campaign, which will run until December 24, 2019, aims to raise awareness about the dangers of deforestation and the importance of forest conservation. All proceeds will support WWF&amp;rsquo;s conservation initiatives.
In 2018 alone, Singapore generated about 1 million tonnes of paper waste...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-holiday-season-transamerica-life-bermuda-and-the-world-wide-fund-for-nature-are-advocating-for-the-conservation-of-forests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Giftano improves the experience of giving gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</guid><description>Giftano, a Singapore-based online gifting platform, has expanded its offerings to include a complete online gifting solution. In addition to their existing digital gift card selection, Giftano now features &amp;ldquo;Giftano Gifts,&amp;rdquo; a curated marketplace for physical presents.
Giftano aims to provide a seamless and personalized online gifting experience, especially with the holiday season approaching. The company has improved its platform by adding a user-friendly search engine and features that allow for custom gift cards and various delivery choices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Office Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 22:04:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</guid><description>Stationery The Scenic Route 2021 calendar
Victoria McGrane, an illustrator and textile designer, collaborated with Rainforest Rescue, an organization dedicated to rainforest protection and restoration since 1999, to create a 2021 calendar. McGrane, the talent behind The Scenic Route brand, is known for her hand-illustrated designs and stationery that showcase the beauty of Australian nature. Her work has garnered attention and partnerships with prominent brands.
“Protecting and restoring Australia&amp;rsquo;s valuable rainforests is incredibly important to me, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that my illustrations and travel inspiration can contribute to safeguarding these ancient forests and their wildlife,” shared McGrane...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vacationing at Black Sheep Restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Elevate your holiday celebrations with the Black Sheep Restaurants group in Hong Kong:
Carbone
This New York-Italian establishment will be serving up generous portions of classics, like their 40oz Prime Porterhouse with a rosemary infusion. For a luxurious New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, enjoy an early dinner (6pm-8:45pm) or partake in The Fiasco, a mobster-themed dinner theater experience from 9pm-1am (HK$1,500).
Details:
Carbone is located at 9/F, LKF Tower, 33 Wyndham St, Central, Hong Kong..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/</guid><description>As the holiday season approaches, it&amp;rsquo;s time to search for unique gifts for employees or clients. Here are a few ideas:
Facials
Kew Organics&amp;rsquo; Red Carpet Organic Facial presents a natural, non-surgical method for achieving a more youthful appearance. This facial utilizes non-invasive skin-firming methods to deliver a lifted, firmer, and more radiant look.
Kew Organics states that this facial, which incorporates organic botanicals from their serum line, rejuvenates the skin and firms all 57 facial muscles, resulting in revitalized, youthful skin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an unexpected Christmas at Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel in Singapore has designed a Christmas menu featuring new versions of classic dishes, playful food presentations, and delightful surprises. These festive meals and unique takeaway options aim to make holiday celebrations even more memorable.
This year&amp;rsquo;s new gourmet takeaway options center around turkey with unique Asian flavors for savory dishes and chocolate-focused sweet treats.
Source: Goodwood Park Hotel. The 12 Treasures turkey is available for takeaways.
12 Treasures Turkey | S$268, serves eight to 10 people - New for 2017..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>