<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireless Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Wireless Broadband on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part IV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</guid><description>The most desirable wireless frequencies will soon be completely allocated. These prime frequencies, ranging from a few hundred to a few thousand MHz, offer high bandwidth, strong building penetration, and accommodate small antennas. The problem is that the number of these channels is finite. Similar to real estate, once the best spots are taken, expansion continues into less ideal areas.
Finding more bandwidth means moving up or down the electromagnetic spectrum, which presents challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will WiMAX Become WiMedium?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</guid><description>WiMAX, a wireless broadband standard, was envisioned as the key to 4G mobile networks and roaming. However, other technologies are catching up and might become the dominant force in 4G.
WiMAX aimed to broaden WiFi&amp;rsquo;s reach from a few hundred feet to many miles, allowing mobile devices to seamlessly switch between towers for continuous connectivity, similar to cell phone networks. It promised significantly faster speeds compared to existing cellular broadband, suitable for indoor and outdoor use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Broadband Available In A Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</guid><description>Imagine this: your new store is ready to open, everything is in place, but you can&amp;rsquo;t start selling because your internet service isn&amp;rsquo;t working. This is where Accel Networks comes in, offering a wireless solution that can get you online in just a few days.
Why choose Accel Networks? Traditional broadband often involves time-consuming installations. Accel Networks bypasses this by using existing cell tower infrastructure. Their service is secure, meets payment industry standards, and covers most of the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XOHM, XOHM's Got The Range</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</guid><description>Sprint&amp;rsquo;s XOHM (pronounced &amp;ldquo;zome,&amp;rdquo; like &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;) wireless broadband service has launched in Baltimore, marking the start of the highly anticipated rollout of WiMAX as the next generation of high-speed internet. If Sprint successfully implements its 4G vision, WiFi hotspots could become obsolete. DSL? Cable? Why bother with wires when you can have the freedom of wireless connectivity?
This vision relies on a new wireless technology standardized for global use in both fixed and mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>