<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Corporate LAN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/corporate-lan/</link><description>Recent content in Corporate LAN on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/corporate-lan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Why The WAN Lags The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</guid><description>Corporate networks are often set up to ensure smooth data flow within the organization (LAN), but the real bottleneck often lies in the connection to the outside world (WAN).
LANs typically use Ethernet standards with speeds of 10/100/1000 Mbps, while WAN connections like T1 or DS3 lines operate at much slower speeds (1.5 Mbps to 45 Mbps). This disparity in speed results in significant slowdowns when transferring files outside the organization.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item></channel></rss>