<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airline on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airline/</link><description>Recent content in Airline on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Delta is launching Delta Innovation Classes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines has devised a novel method for premium customers to distinguish themselves and share contact information, using a compelling offer.
As stated on the Delta Innovation Class website, the airline is offering a &amp;ldquo;mentoring program – that just so happens to take place at 35,000 feet.&amp;rdquo;
This program, Delta Innovation Class, a play on flight classes, gives one fortunate customer a complimentary seat next to a notable figure or celebrity on a designated flight.</description></item><item><title>Asiana discontinues codeshare agreement with US Airways, impacting flights to Japan and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Asiana Airlines will end its codeshare agreement with US Airways on March 30, 2014. Passengers are advised to review their flight reservations. The affected routes are listed below:
Asiana Airlines flights
Japan
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Fukuoka, Osaka, Nagoya, Okinawa, and Shizuoka
America
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Chicago, New York, and Honolulu
US Airways flights
America
Los Angeles to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia San Francisco to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Seattle to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Chicago to/from Atlanta, Orlando, Indianapolis, Columbus, Cleveland, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Aeromexico introduces an additional flight connecting Shanghai and Mexico City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Aeromexico will expand its service between Shanghai and Mexico City to include a third weekly flight on Sundays. This increase will bring the total number of seats available on the route to over 1,500 each week. The flights, operated by Boeing 777 aircraft, accommodate 277 passengers with 49 business class seats and 228 economy seats.
Each Aeromexico flight features personal entertainment systems, increased passenger space, and lie-flat seats in Clase Premier, its business class section.</description></item><item><title>US airlines may now reject your standard carry-on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</guid><description>According to George Hobica from Airfarewatchdog, several US airlines have reduced the allowed size for carry-on luggage.
Traveling Hello Kitty statue at Taoyuan Airport,
Taiwan in 2008.
American, Delta, and United Airlines now permit carry-on bags with a maximum size of 22 inches in length, 14 inches in width, and 9 inches in height. The previous allowed width was 15 inches.
A Yahoo article from March highlighted United Airlines&amp;rsquo; stricter enforcement of carry-on size regulations.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd.</description></item><item><title>Vietjet's SkyBoss enhances the premium customer experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet.
Vietjet now offers SkyBoss, a premium travel class. SkyBoss passengers receive priority check-in, a 20kg checked baggage allowance, priority seat selection, airport lounge access, in-flight meals, extra legroom, and flexible flight date and time changes.
Established in 2011, Vietjet Air is Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s first privately held airline. Since its inception, Vietjet has served over 12 million passengers across 32 domestic and international routes. The airline currently operates two daily flights between Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi International Airport and Ho Chi Minh City&amp;rsquo;s Tan Son Nhat International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes.</description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014.</description></item><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir have reduced their fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir, its regional subsidiary, have reduced their fuel surcharges due to decreasing fuel prices.
These new surcharge amounts apply to flights from both airlines and range from US$5 to US$83 lower per one-way trip, depending on the flight distance and class of travel.
Route Surcharge in US$* First Class, Suites Between Singapore and South East Asian gateways[1] 50 Between Singapore and Europe/South Africa[2] 175 Between Singapore and Americas 235 Between Europe and Australia/New Zealand[3] 265 All other flights[4] 131 * Figures in US Dollars, converted into currency of sale at time of ticketing</description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Firefly is back in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firefly-is-back-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firefly-is-back-in-singapore/</guid><description>Firefly Airlines has resumed flights between Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport in Subang, Malaysia, and Seletar Airport in Singapore.
Source: Firefly. Firefly reinstates Malaysia-Singapore route.
Firefly&amp;rsquo;s first flight on this route to Seletar took place in April 2019, but flights were put on hold in March 2020 due to the pandemic. Now, the airline will offer two flights every day between Kuala Lumpur and Singapore, operating out of Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport and Seletar Airport.</description></item><item><title>Etihad provides a wider range of choices for Mediterranean travel destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is increasing the number and capacity of flights to Athens, Greece, and Larnaca, Cyprus.
Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, stated that the new flights to Athens will offer travelers two different departure times to and from Abu Dhabi. The additional flights to Larnaca will provide more options and flexibility, as well as enhanced connectivity through Abu Dhabi.
He added that these additions will support business and leisure travel growth through Abu Dhabi and offer travelers a wider choice of destinations in the Gulf region, Indian Subcontinent, Asia, and Australia.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight.</description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals.</description></item><item><title>Etihad and Fiji Airways establish codeshare partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</guid><description>Fiji Airways and Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, have established an interline agreement. This partnership enables both airlines to sell tickets to and from a wider range of destinations. Passengers can now travel between 17 cities in the Middle East, 29 cities in Asia, and three cities in Australia to and from Fiji, along with other destinations.
James Hogan, President and CEO of Etihad Airways, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership, stating that Fiji is an excellent vacation destination and enhances Etihad&amp;rsquo;s global network.</description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport.</description></item><item><title>Take advantage of the week-long Vietjet promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet website.
Vietjet Aviation Joint Stock Company (Vietjet), an airline with 32 domestic and international routes, is offering a limited-time promotion with 500,000 discounted tickets. This offer is valid for one week, ending on Wednesday, July 29th, 2015.
The promotion applies to all of Vietjet&amp;rsquo;s current domestic and international routes for travel between September 7th, 2015 and December 31st, 2015. Discounted fares will be displayed in a separate column during booking.</description></item><item><title>Budget airline flyadeal plans to extend its reach to more destinations in the Middle East in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s new low-cost airline, flyadeal, was officially launched on August 23 at King Abdulaziz International Airport in Jeddah. The event showcased flyadeal&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft, named &amp;ldquo;Al-Nayyir&amp;rdquo; (meaning &amp;ldquo;bright star&amp;rdquo;), which arrived from the Airbus delivery center in Hamburg, Germany.
Source: flyadeal. The budget airline flyadeal was inaugurated at a ceremony on August 24. The airline’s colors – a distinct palette of purple and lime – was on full display at the delivery event, along with members of the cabin crew, which gave guests a tour of the unique features onboard.</description></item><item><title>Vistara, a new airline, launches in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</guid><description>Tata SIA Airlines Limited (TSAL) revealed &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; as the name for its new airline on August 11th. This announcement follows a September 2013 agreement between Tata Sons and Singapore Airlines to create a new Indian airline, aiming to further boost air travel demand.
Source: Twitter. The Vistara logo was unveiled on Twitter and Facebook.
The name &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; originates from the Sanskrit word &amp;ldquo;vistaar,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;limitless expanse,&amp;rdquo; symbolizing the boundless sky, the airline&amp;rsquo;s domain.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is using Dreamliners on the route between the UAE and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched daily Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flights between the UAE and Singapore, setting a new standard for luxury travel on this route. Passengers can choose from First Suites, Business Studios, and Economy Smart Seats on the Abu Dhabi-Singapore route. The flight schedule is designed for smooth connections to 35 destinations within Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; network.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and Chief Executive Officer, stated that the Dreamliner&amp;rsquo;s deployment on the Singapore route demonstrates the route&amp;rsquo;s significance and the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a top-tier travel experience.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has observed that 20% of its users access the website via iPads, prompting the airline to develop an iPad app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 10:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</guid><description>Emirates airline has introduced the Emirates App for iPad, available globally through the App Store. This app allows users to easily explore destinations and manage their Emirates travel experiences.
With a simple tap, users can discover information on over 130 Emirates destinations across six continents and learn about the airline&amp;rsquo;s renowned services.
The Emirates App for iPad simplifies travel management for Emirates customers, whether they&amp;rsquo;re on the move, in flight, or at home.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines introduces new flights to Okinawa, Hangzhou, and Ho Chi Minh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</guid><description>On March 19th, Hong Kong Airlines launched new flights for its Hong Kong-Okinawa and Hong Kong-Hangzhou routes to meet the increasing demand from business and leisure travelers. The airline celebrated the occasion with events at Hong Kong International Airport and both destination airports.
Alex Wu, Hong Kong Airlines General Manager of the Hong Kong Sales Office, welcomed passengers on the inaugural Okinawa flight HX678 with model airplanes. At the gate, passengers received certificates acknowledging their support for the new route.</description></item><item><title>Air China is providing a 50% discount on excess baggage fees to North America if paid in advance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</guid><description>Air China is the first Chinese airline to offer a prepaid excess baggage fee service for flights to North America. Travelers on Air China flights between Beijing and North America who anticipate exceeding their baggage allowance can now pay a discounted fee in advance. This service can be accessed through Air China ticketing offices globally or by calling their Member Services hotline.
Passengers who prepay for excess baggage will save 50% compared to airport rates, paying RMB 650 per piece or the equivalent in local currency.</description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes.</description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia has relocated its Surabaya operations to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 04:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</guid><description>AirAsia has relocated its operations from Terminal 1 to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport.
All AirAsia domestic and international flights to and from Surabaya will keep their original schedules and operate as usual.
Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport opened on February 14th. The terminal is designed to be environmentally friendly and can accommodate 6 million passengers annually. It features 40 check-in counters, an updated baggage handling system, six gates for domestic use, three gates for international flights, 12 avirobridges, and 14 parking stands for both narrow and wide-bodied aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is increasing the number of weekly flights between Abu Dhabi and Manila</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2016, Etihad Airways will increase its Abu Dhabi to Manila route from 14 to 17 roundtrip flights per week. This provides convenient connections from Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s hub to popular destinations for Philippine travelers, including Bahrain, Kuwait, Dammam, Doha, Jeddah, and Riyadh.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, highlighted the Abu Dhabi-Manila route&amp;rsquo;s high demand and limited capacity in recent years. The added flights will increase capacity by nearly 2,500 seats weekly, improving travel options between the UAE and the Philippines.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is adding another daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates has launched an additional daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka. Starting August 1, 2016, the airline will offer five daily flights between the two cities, except on Wednesdays, when four flights will be available. This new flight will provide an extra 2,520 seats and boost cargo capacity by 161 tonnes weekly in both directions, increasing the total weekly services on this route to 34.</description></item></channel></rss>