<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crossover on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crossover/</link><description>Recent content in Crossover on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:04:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crossover/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Usagyuuun will make an appearance in the Claw Stars universe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usagyuuun-will-make-an-appearance-in-the-claw-stars-universe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:04:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usagyuuun-will-make-an-appearance-in-the-claw-stars-universe/</guid><description>Source: Appxplore. The mobile game Claw Stars will soon feature characters from the popular sticker app, Usagyuuun.
Minto, the company behind Usagyuuun, and Appxplore, the developer of Claw Stars, are collaborating to bring the beloved sticker character to the award-winning mobile game. This marks the first game collaboration for Minto, a global leader in character IPs with over 6 billion downloads worldwide.
Appxplore, known for its expertise in game development and creator of games with over 40 million downloads, sees this partnership as a strategic move to merge its experience with the massive popularity of Usagyuuun.</description></item><item><title>Lexus has launched the new NX luxury crossover, accompanied by video advertisements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</guid><description>Source: Lexus. The Lexus NX.
Lexus has launched the NX, a luxury crossover. The 2015 NX marketing campaign highlights how the vehicle surpasses typical SUVs to provide urban drivers with a stylish option that suits their dynamic lifestyles.
“This is Lexus&amp;rsquo; first venture into the entry luxury crossover market. The NX is a dynamic vehicle that combines high-end design with practicality,” said Brian Smith, Lexus&amp;rsquo; VP of marketing. “This campaign showcases the fun driving experience and adventurous spirit of this vehicle, which boasts a bold, angular design and a powerful turbocharged engine.</description></item></channel></rss>