<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crack on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crack/</link><description>Recent content in Crack on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Exchange of Trim, Fixing Cracked Hinges, Spray Painting Corroded Metal Parts and Polishing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a damaged dust cover. It was scratched, the metal hinges were corroded, the plexiglass around the hinges was cracked, and it had the typical early-model plastic trim that imitated aluminum.
To start, I removed the plastic trim. It was attached with contact cement, so I warmed the dust cover in the oven at approximately 80 degrees Celsius (wrapped in aluminum foil to prevent hot spots) to soften the adhesive.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of a Cracked Hood - Another Process Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on has a cracked hood around the hinge attachments. The left side was entirely detached, and the right side had a crack extending around one of the holes.
The right side had a crack going all the way around one of the attachment holes:
To begin, I glued the broken pieces back together using Weld-On #4 acrylic solvent. This low-viscosity solvent is ideal for injecting into cracks, as capillary action draws it in.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Plexiglass Hood With Laser Cut Patches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</guid><description>The hinge area is the most delicate part of plexiglass hoods found on Beogram turntables. It&amp;rsquo;s subject to significant stress when opened and closed, while the presence of screw holes for the metal hinge makes it structurally vulnerable. I recently worked on a Beogram 4000 with a cracked hood and a broken-off piece.
Inspired by a previous restoration of a Beogram 3000 hinge, I aimed to create a similar solution for the 4000/4002 models.</description></item></channel></rss>