<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Television on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-television/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Television on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Video Kill The Internet Star?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</guid><description>The considerable growth of online video streaming and downloads has positioned them as the primary bandwidth consumers on the internet today. This begs the question: will the rapid proliferation of video packets lead to internet congestion, similar to traffic jams on physical highways?
Video content follows the same trajectory as previous &amp;ldquo;killer apps&amp;rdquo; such as email, web browsing, instant messaging, blogging, and social networking. These applications all began with a small user base, expanded quickly, and eventually became mainstream.</description></item><item><title>DTV Transition For Wireless Mic Users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dtv-transition-for-wireless-mic-users/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dtv-transition-for-wireless-mic-users/</guid><description>The U.S. is in the middle of transitioning to digital television, a process that began on February 17th and will continue until June 12th. This shift brings significant changes for many wireless microphone users, potentially disrupting their ability to operate.
The transition, often called the DTV transition, signifies a complete reallocation of VHF and UHF frequencies that have been used for over-the-air television broadcasting for the past five decades. While the main goal is to switch from analog to digital broadcasting, the implications extend far beyond this.</description></item></channel></rss>