<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Broadband Phone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband-phone/</link><description>Recent content in Broadband Phone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband-phone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Know the Lingo to Save Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</guid><description>To succeed with technology, you need to understand the terminology. This is especially true for VoIP telephony, where &amp;ldquo;Lingo&amp;rdquo; can refer to both the industry jargon and a specific company.
Lingo, the company, offers broadband phone services for residential and business users. These services provide significant cost savings compared to traditional landlines, especially for international calls from the US.
Residential plans include options like Chatter Box, Global Gabber, and Lingo Link, each with unique features and pricing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phone Power... To The People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:43:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</guid><description>VoIP and broadband phone services for businesses and residential customers are steadily replacing the century-old traditional phone industry. The reason? Price!
Traditional phone service relies on tariffs that charge for every little thing. You pay for the line, local service, long distance, and extra features like Caller ID. They even charge a monthly fee for maintaining the wiring in your home! It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that phone bills can be shockingly high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>866 Toll Free Numbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 18:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</guid><description>Everyone knows about 800 numbers; they were the original toll-free option. But did you know there are others, like 866? Is it truly toll-free?
Yes, 866 is indeed toll-free. It functions identically to 800; the difference is simply in the prefix. Just like area codes (202 for Washington, DC, 302 for Delaware), these prefixes are assigned nationwide.
This highlights a key difference: toll prefixes are location-specific (area codes), while toll-free prefixes are not...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of Business Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Over time, business phone lines have evolved from a single analog option to a variety of choices. While you can still get traditional analog lines, various digital options offer potential cost and performance benefits.
The standard business phone line remains largely unchanged from its origins over a century ago, using a single twisted pair of copper wires to carry signals. This analog line, also called POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is the basis for multi-line phones connecting to multiple POTS lines, commonly seen in small office phone systems with one to four lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Analog Telephone Adaptor Enables VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</guid><description>Analog Telephone Adapters (ATAs) bridge the gap between traditional analog phones and Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) technology. They essentially trick both the phone and the internet connection into thinking they&amp;rsquo;re interacting with familiar systems.
On one side, the ATA connects to a regular phone using a standard RJ-11 jack, providing the necessary power and signals like dial tone and caller ID. It also translates the phone&amp;rsquo;s touch-tone signals into a digital format for VoIP communication using the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>