<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CDMA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cdma/</link><description>Recent content in CDMA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cdma/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID 2 Global is a World Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 03:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</guid><description>The DROID 2 Global is a smartphone with a 1.2 GHz processor capable of making and receiving calls in over 200 countries. This Verizon phone works internationally through its unique ability to utilize both GSM and CDMA networks.
While Verizon primarily uses CDMA, incompatible with most global networks, the DROID 2 Global incorporates multiple network support. This includes WCDMA, GSM, HSDPA, CDMA EV-DO, EDGE, GPRS, and HSUPA, encompassing various forms of communication...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I'm Not Paying For That Aircard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 07:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</guid><description>Fast and dependable office internet connections are great when you&amp;rsquo;re stationary, but mobile work demands solutions like WiFi hotspots or cellular broadband. While these options are suitable, not all laptops are equipped for cellular broadband.
Aircards, sometimes called wireless modems, bridge this gap. Similar to WiFi access cards, these devices allow laptops to connect to cellular broadband networks. In the past, laptops primarily used built-in modems, requiring separate cards for WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>