<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conferencing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/conferencing/</link><description>Recent content in Conferencing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:52:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/conferencing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telepresence as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</guid><description>Think of telepresence as the next step beyond the telephone and television: instead of sending your voice or an image, you&amp;rsquo;re projecting your presence across distances. While not as futuristic as Star Trek&amp;rsquo;s transporter, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool for businesses, especially now that companies like Cisco and AT&amp;amp;T offer it as a more accessible service. This shift could mark a significant increase in the use of virtual meetings.
Telepresence evolved from video conferencing, which a decade ago was clunky and unreliable.</description></item><item><title>Ultra Conference Dual Conference Calling Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ultra-conference-dual-conference-calling-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ultra-conference-dual-conference-calling-solution/</guid><description>When your teleconferencing needs expand beyond small, local groups, it&amp;rsquo;s time to explore conference call solutions. While some phone systems offer conference bridges to connect multiple phones, outsourced conferencing solutions can accommodate significantly more participants from various locations.
Ultra Conference provides a robust and affordable conferencing solution suitable for a wide range of applications. It offers flexible pricing options with both fixed and per-minute rates.
Training calls are a popular use for Ultra Conference.</description></item><item><title>Lark Technologies is providing a free collaboration tool for businesses in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:59:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lark-technologies-is-providing-a-free-collaboration-tool-for-businesses-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Lark Technologies, headquartered in Singapore, is now offering its comprehensive, enterprise-level collaboration platform, Lark, free of charge across Southeast Asia. This includes Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, the Philippines, Thailand, and Vietnam. Lark provides a range of features, including unlimited video calls and online collaboration tools, to facilitate seamless teamwork remotely. Users can view colleagues&amp;rsquo; schedules, initiate video calls directly from calendar events, and collaborate on documents during video meetings.
Joey Lim, APAC Commercial Lead at Lark, highlighted that with an estimated 90% of Asia Pacific employees currently working remotely, the company aims to empower teams to maintain productivity regardless of physical location.</description></item><item><title>Taming The Video Bandwidth Monster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 01:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</guid><description>Cisco forecasts that video will represent over half of all internet traffic by the close of next year, reaching 62% by 2015&amp;rsquo;s end. This surge in video consumption, driven by streaming and downloads, necessitates that both providers and consumers adapt to the escalating demand for bandwidth.
Netflix&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a cable and satellite TV competitor is accelerating the dominance of video data on the internet. Consumers are experiencing a transformation in how they consume &amp;ldquo;TV,&amp;rdquo; now utilizing computers, tablets, and smartphones.</description></item></channel></rss>