<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Glasses on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/glasses/</link><description>Recent content in Glasses on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/glasses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Epson Singapore has released the new Moverio Pro smart glasses with augmented reality capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</guid><description>Epson, a global provider of projection technology and visual communication tools, has introduced the Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset. This binocular headset offers an augmented reality experience for applications such as inspections, training, and remote field service support for intricate repairs and troubleshooting.
Source: Epson Singapore. The new
Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset.
Augmented reality smart glasses have the potential to boost worker efficiency across various sectors, including warehousing, logistics, field service, automotive, manufacturing, construction, and retail.</description></item><item><title>Rodenstock is bringing back vintage shapes and sizes in eyewear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rodenstock-is-bringing-back-vintage-shapes-and-sizes-in-eyewear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rodenstock-is-bringing-back-vintage-shapes-and-sizes-in-eyewear/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, fashion icon Claudia Schiffer and German eyewear company Rodenstock debuted their first collaborative eyewear collection. Later, in September, they launched an autumn/winter collection, featuring fresh color variations for several styles.
&amp;ldquo;Sunglasses are a simple yet impactful way to define a look,&amp;rdquo; explains Schiffer, who serves as Creative Director for the collection. &amp;ldquo;Paired with the right coat, bag, or jeans, the right pair can make a real statement.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces the latest Moverio smart glasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the third generation of its Moverio smart glasses, designed for augmented reality applications. The Moverio BT-300 utilizes Epson&amp;rsquo;s innovative silicon-based OLED display technology, providing a truly transparent mobile augmented reality (AR) experience for both businesses and consumers.
Epson highlights the Moverio BT-300 as the lightest binocular see-through smart glasses available, boasting a weight reduction of over 20% compared to its predecessor, the Moverio BT-200. These glasses are powered by a quad-core Intel Atom X5 processor and run on Android 5.</description></item></channel></rss>