<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cwdm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cwdm/</link><description>Recent content in Cwdm on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cwdm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Wavelengths to Serve You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</guid><description>When your network reaches its maximum capacity, you typically need to upgrade to a faster network with faster components. Upgrading your entire network infrastructure can be extremely expensive. However, with fiber optic networks, you can significantly increase bandwidth within the same cables using a technique called Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM).
WDM allows multiple light beams to transmit data simultaneously over a single fiber optic cable. Each beam operates on a different wavelength, increasing capacity proportionally to the number of beams...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services For The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</guid><description>Initially only utilized by telecom companies, wavelength services are now accessible to large organizations. These high-bandwidth fiber optic services are necessary for entities like hospitals, financial institutions, government service providers, video production companies, content delivery networks, and research facilities. The demand for faster data transfer solutions is constantly increasing. But are wavelength services the answer?
A wavelength, or lambda, is light at a specific frequency, similar to a distinct color. It is usually measured in nanometers (wavelength) rather than terabits per second (frequency)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>