<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mandarin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mandarin/</link><description>Recent content in Mandarin on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mandarin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas.</description></item><item><title>Iftar gatherings at AquaMarine, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 03:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</guid><description>Originally from the Marina Mandarin Singapore website, this photo displays the Bakar Station&amp;rsquo;s offerings of chicken, oxtail, prawns, and sea bass cooked in banana leaves.
AquaMarine, a Halal-certified buffet restaurant, has recently renovated its Terrace@AquaMarine space. Now fully air-conditioned, it&amp;rsquo;s an ideal location for larger gatherings.
The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s current iftar menu, available until July 17th, features dishes like dates, slow-roasted baby lamb seasoned with Moroccan spices, bulgur wheat with raita, and a traditional Indonesian oxtail soup.</description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities.</description></item><item><title>The Marina Mandarin Singapore welcomes the arrival of hairy crabs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</guid><description>Peach Blossoms, the renowned Cantonese restaurant located on the 5th level of Marina Mandarin Singapore, is now offering a seasonal delicacy flown in from Shanghai, China: hairy crabs.
Also at the Marina Mandarin, on the 4th level, the AquaMarine buffet restaurant is spotlighting seafood until October 29th.
Source: Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
AquaMarine features an array of Asian dishes, including Vietnamese Braised Fish in Clay Pot, Thai Curry Mud Crab, authentic Filipino Beef Adobo, fresh Cambodian Fish Curry, and many more.</description></item></channel></rss>