<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>91HBBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/91hbbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 91HBBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/91hbbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Deteriorated Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002, deteriorated transport lock bushings, evidenced by small orange plastic pieces within the unit, were discovered. To address this, 3D-printed replacement bushings were designed for convenient installation without major disassembly. These bushings are comprised of two halves, insertable from above and below the sub-chassis.
The replacement bushings are available for purchase, with each bushing requiring two of the 3D-printed parts. A video detailing the installation process is accessible online.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Adjusting Platter and Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 23:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</guid><description>The visual appeal of a Beogram 400x relies heavily on the platter&amp;rsquo;s alignment with its surrounding aluminum panels. A correctly aligned platter sits flush with these panels, allowing the black &amp;lsquo;ribs&amp;rsquo; to stand out against a flat aluminum surface. Achieving this alignment is intricate, requiring several parameters to be perfectly adjusted. I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that a sensor arm that isn&amp;rsquo;t entirely parallel to the floating chassis often complicates this process. Both the service manual and my videos detail an adjustment procedure assuming the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s parallelism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: First Prototype Installed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</guid><description>I was tasked with creating an internal RIAA preamplifier for a restored Beogram 4002 (5521). This addition makes sense since many modern receivers lack a dedicated phono input. Additionally, the pre-opamp RIAA preamps found in many vintage B&amp;amp;O receivers introduce more noise compared to modern low-noise audio op-amps.
Researching contemporary RIAA preamp designs led me to the LM833 operational amplifier, a specialized low-noise op-amp for audio applications. I adapted a high-precision RIAA preamp circuit from a Texas Instruments application note AN-346, as established RIAA preamplifier designs exist.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A Stuck Tonearm and Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously repaired, returned with a tonearm tracking issue. The problem was a misaligned tracking sensor aperture obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. To fix this, I slightly repositioned the aperture after loosening its screw. I replaced the original screw with a more secure flat socket head screw to prevent future misalignment. I then recalibrated the tracking sensor feedback.
While the Beogram was with me, the customer decided to have the dust cover polished.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: A New Power Supply Design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous one about the RIAA preamplifier I&amp;rsquo;m building for a Beogram 4002 turntable. This preamp will allow the Beogram to connect directly to a modern amplifier&amp;rsquo;s AUX or TAPE input. While initially pleased with my prototype, I redesigned it for a cleaner layout and had it manufactured.
The new boards arrived, and I assembled a preamplifier, thrilled with its appearance. After installing and testing it, however, I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t tested it thoroughly enough beforehand.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Rebuilding the DC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-rebuilding-the-dc-motor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:32:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-rebuilding-the-dc-motor/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the recently acquired Beogram 4002 turntable revealed a noisy DC motor. The sleeve bearings were dry, causing a high-pitched sound when spinning without the load of the belt and platter. To restore peace to my workspace and enjoy some vinyl, I decided to fix this first.
The motor was removed from its mounting plate by unscrewing two screws and carefully prying off the glued pulley. After opening the outer enclosure, the motor was extracted.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5521) in visually appealing condition recently arrived for restoration. The turntable came with a known faulty tracking sensor, burned-out 33 RPM indicator lights, and was secured in a double box for safe transport. A previous video on packing a 4002/4 for shipping can be found here. This image shows the inner packaging:
Here is the unit unpacked: Foam pads secured the sub-platter, and importantly, the tonearm and RPM panel were protected with removable tape for shipping.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit.</description></item></channel></rss>