<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prepaid on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/prepaid/</link><description>Recent content in Prepaid on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:55:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/prepaid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting from December 21, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM for Japan will be available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</guid><description>Source: Plus One Marketing.
Plus One Marketing, a Japanese company known for its FREETEL brand of mobile devices, is launching a prepaid data SIM card specifically for travelers in Japan. Starting December 21, 2015, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM will be available for purchase.
The SIM card is designed with tourists in mind, allowing unlimited access to popular social media platforms like Facebook, Kakao Talk, WeChat, LINE, and WhatsApp for seven days...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a special upgrade offer for owners of 2G phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced a special offer as they prepare to discontinue 2G services in Singapore, starting in April 2017.
Source: Singtel.
The Alcatel Onetouch 2052x is available for S$48, and the Onetouch Pop D3 is priced at S$95.
Prepaid customers can take advantage of S$70 in free talk time and 350MB of data, along with an additional S$30 in free talk time when they trade in a 2G phone.
Postpaid customers on Silver Plan Combo 1 and 2 will receive a 20% discount on their monthly bills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Bill Shock Is So Easy To Avoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission is looking into new regulations due to a high volume of complaints regarding unexpected cell phone charges. While this intervention is welcomed by those who have faced this issue, understanding how to avoid such situations is key.
&amp;ldquo;Bill shock&amp;rdquo; refers to the unpleasant surprise of discovering unexpectedly high charges on your cell phone bill, often leaving you in disbelief and frantically searching for errors. While billing mistakes can occur, these charges are typically accurate, stemming from a lack of awareness regarding contract details or exceeding usage limits, often unknowingly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In May 2015, Digi prepaid customers have the chance to win smartphones, tablets, and cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Thrane.
Digi Telecommunication (Digi) is celebrating its 20th anniversary by giving back to its prepaid customers. Throughout May, Digi will be offering prizes like smartphones, tablets, and even cars.
From May 1st to May 31st, customers who top-up their prepaid credit are eligible to win prizes. Every day, 20 smartphones will be given away, with 200 tablets awarded weekly. Two lucky winners will even drive home a Ford Ranger...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepaid Business Calling Controls Phone Expense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 17:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/</guid><description>Your business phone costs are becoming unmanageable, especially in today&amp;rsquo;s economic climate. While unlimited calling might have been acceptable in the past, now it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to minimize expenses. This year, prioritize controlling calling habits and securing the most cost-effective rates for both domestic and international calls.
TEL3Business offers tools to manage your business calls, whether from landlines or mobile phones. Their strategy combines technology with competitive rates, empowering managers to optimize their telephone budgets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China is providing a 50% discount on excess baggage fees to North America if paid in advance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</guid><description>Air China is the first Chinese airline to offer a prepaid excess baggage fee service for flights to North America. Travelers on Air China flights between Beijing and North America who anticipate exceeding their baggage allowance can now pay a discounted fee in advance. This service can be accessed through Air China ticketing offices globally or by calling their Member Services hotline.
Passengers who prepay for excess baggage will save 50% compared to airport rates, paying RMB 650 per piece or the equivalent in local currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australian businesses have the option to utilize uChoose for their corporate rewards program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-businesses-have-the-option-to-utilize-uchoose-for-their-corporate-rewards-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-businesses-have-the-option-to-utilize-uchoose-for-their-corporate-rewards-program/</guid><description>Source: uChoose website.
i2c, a company providing card processing and new financial service solutions, partnered with Corporate Prepaid Solutions (CPS), a prepaid program manager, to launch the first of several corporate prepaid programs. This launch features the uChoose corporate rewards gift card in Australia.
The uChoose card, enabled by i2c&amp;rsquo;s global processing platform, is a ready-made solution for companies wanting to provide a Visa-branded gift card. Businesses can personalize the card to match their branding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-businesses-have-the-option-to-utilize-uchoose-for-their-corporate-rewards-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-businesses-have-the-option-to-utilize-uchoose-for-their-corporate-rewards-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoPhones For Hurricane Gustav</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 08:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/</guid><description>During the preparations for Hurricane Gustav, AT&amp;amp;T gave out over 2,000 GoPhones with $15 of pre-loaded airtime to Gulf Coast evacuees. This act of generosity brought attention to the GoPhone and its potential use as an emergency phone.
AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s GoPhone isn&amp;rsquo;t a specific phone model but a prepaid cellular service. Unlike traditional cell phone plans that require contracts and monthly fees regardless of usage, GoPhone lets you pay for airtime in advance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>