<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Small Medium Business on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small-medium-business/</link><description>Recent content in Small Medium Business on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small-medium-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T-1 Bandwidth Suits the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), despite being independently owned, are no longer isolated entities. They rely heavily on the internet, from small insurance offices to quick-service restaurants (QSRs). This reliance stems from the cost-effectiveness of internet-based solutions.
The T1 line is widely used by SMBs for digital communication. This business-grade telecommunication service has become more affordable in recent years due to increased competition and demand. Costs for T1 services have been cut by more than half in some instances.</description></item><item><title>Can You Benefit From New Cloud Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about cloud computing and might be wondering if it can help your small or medium-sized business (SMB). While it seems like cloud services are designed for large corporations, they offer significant potential for businesses of all sizes.
The cloud can be even more beneficial for SMBs because it levels the playing field. Large companies often have the resources to build their own private clouds, while smaller companies may struggle with the cost and staffing required for such an undertaking.</description></item><item><title>Broadview Networks OfficeSuite Brings The Cloud To SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</guid><description>Smaller companies often want to adopt money-saving technologies like VoIP, private networks, and cloud services, but the initial investment can be daunting. While internet-based options seem appealing, their quality and reliability are often a concern. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for businesses of all sizes to access these advanced tools without breaking the bank.
Broadview Networks&amp;rsquo; OfficeSuite offers a comprehensive solution, effectively serving as a company&amp;rsquo;s central office across multiple locations. This enterprise-grade PBX system provides the functionality of a traditional system with the convenience of easy administration through a web browser.</description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user.</description></item></channel></rss>