<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disaster Recovery on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disaster-recovery/</link><description>Recent content in Disaster Recovery on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disaster-recovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Store Your Files For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</guid><description>With the current state of the economy, you&amp;rsquo;d expect the best price for file storage to be free – and you&amp;rsquo;d be right! Anything more would be asking too much.
Of course, this applies to storing digital files, not physical ones. Don&amp;rsquo;t show up at a self-storage facility with boxes of papers expecting free storage – they won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to show you the door!
Instead, try storing your computer files for free with Mozy (http://www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/store-your-files-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Build Your Own Private Cloud Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</guid><description>Lots of small and midsize businesses are using cloud storage, particularly for disaster recovery. However, local storage is still necessary. While Storage Attached Networks (SANs) are a common solution, they&amp;rsquo;re expensive and complex. A simpler option exists.
Introducing Drobo, an advanced hard disk storage solution that&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to use. It works with standard 3.5&amp;quot; SATA drives of any capacity, resembling a straightforward multi-bay drive enclosure. Adding or removing drives, even swapping a 1 TB for a 2 TB, is always possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Server vs Cloud Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</guid><description>Cloud backup services have gained immense popularity among both individuals and businesses. Most people store at least some files online for easy sharing and mobile access, exceeding the need for encrypted backups. Essentially, there&amp;rsquo;s a massive shift of data towards the cloud.
While online file storage has become second nature, cloud computing hasn&amp;rsquo;t gained the same widespread adoption, despite a clear trend in that direction. However, there are strong indicators suggesting that cloud computing will reach a similar level of popularity as cloud storage within a few years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Cost Cloud Backup For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</guid><description>Lots of companies are exploring cloud services these days. While not every business needs its own data center or web servers, every business has critical data they can&amp;rsquo;t afford to lose. Imagine a natural disaster like a tornado or fire destroying all your physical and digital files – the impact would be significant. Even something as common as a hard drive crash can be devastating.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a simple and cost-effective way to protect your business without complex outsourcing contracts: backing up your important files to a secure offsite location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Service Without The Outages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</guid><description>The internet has become an essential tool for accessing information, connecting with others, and conducting business. It offers a vast repository of knowledge, real-time services, and entertainment options. However, internet outages can occur, causing frustration and disruption.
While complete internet blackouts are rare, local outages can still happen. These outages can be planned maintenance, accidental disruptions, or natural disasters. For businesses and individuals who rely heavily on the internet, these outages can be costly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Offers Business Continuity Planning Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offers-business-continuity-planning-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 22:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offers-business-continuity-planning-guide/</guid><description>XO Communications, a significant player in the competitive telecom industry, offers a useful resource in their Business Continuity Planning Guide.
But what exactly is business continuity, and how does it relate to telecommunications? Think of it as disaster recovery, a term we&amp;rsquo;re all familiar with.
We&amp;rsquo;ve all encountered setbacks in our lives, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a robbery that wipes out our work computers, a flood that ruins important documents, or simply losing a smartphone with valuable data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offers-business-continuity-planning-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offers-business-continuity-planning-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud IT Online Backup For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-it-online-backup-for-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-it-online-backup-for-business/</guid><description>Cloud backups are gaining popularity for personal use, safeguarding against data loss. But what about businesses? Are cloud-based backup services beneficial for them too?
Independent professionals might find consumer-oriented services like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iCloud sufficient. However, businesses, especially those with multiple employees and locations, often benefit from business-specific cloud services, particularly when part of a managed IT solution.
Two primary approaches exist for cloud-based file backup. One treats the cloud as a separate repository for copies of essential business files...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-it-online-backup-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-it-online-backup-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth For Remote Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</guid><description>Businesses need to have a solid plan to safeguard their important data. While basic backups on disks or tapes can help with minor issues like a crashed computer, they are inadequate for major events like natural disasters. Offsite backup is crucial in these situations.
The key is choosing a location geographically distant from your primary site to avoid shared risks. Backing up data across regional offices, separated by significant distances, enhances data protection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backup and Recovery For All Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</guid><description>Businesses are exposed to various risks, not just economic fluctuations or environmental factors. Your data, whether on your computer or in your data center, might be your biggest vulnerability. Without backup and recovery solutions, you&amp;rsquo;re one mishap away from major problems.
Your data is the most valuable asset at risk. While paper records were once the norm, with fire as a primary threat, today&amp;rsquo;s electronic records face risks like corruption and deletion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ElephantDrive Never Forgets Your Files</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elephantdrive-never-forgets-your-files/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 04:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elephantdrive-never-forgets-your-files/</guid><description>Elephants are known for their impressive memory. What if you could harness that power for your data? ElephantDrive is an online storage service that offers the digital equivalent of an elephant&amp;rsquo;s memory.
ElephantDrive provides unlimited, encrypted storage that&amp;rsquo;s easily accessible and budget-friendly for individuals and businesses.
Think of it as storage in the cloud. This offsite backup ensures your data&amp;rsquo;s safety, even if disaster strikes your primary location. Imagine losing your computer and backups to a tornado...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elephantdrive-never-forgets-your-files/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elephantdrive-never-forgets-your-files/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will 2013 Be Your Year of the Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing was a major trend in 2012, with numerous vendors offering a wide range of solutions. Cloud services are no longer limited to powerful supercomputers; they&amp;rsquo;ve become accessible and practical for everyday resources, often surpassing the benefits of in-house solutions. This raises the question: will 2013 be the year you transition to the cloud?
For many businesses, the answer is a clear &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Cost-effectiveness, support, and accessibility are key drivers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TelePacific Takes Business Continuity Seriously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications, a telecommunications company serving California and Nevada, emphasizes a thorough approach to disaster preparedness and business continuity.
Their Business Continuity Services aim to keep your voice and data operational, even if a trunk line or your entire facility goes down. But how is this achieved?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with telephone service. Many businesses utilize digital trunk lines like T1 PRI and SIP Trunks, which offer cost savings compared to individual lines but pose a single point of failure risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>