<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Poland on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/poland/</link><description>Recent content in Poland on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/poland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use.</description></item><item><title>European academics are appealing for the EU to avoid becoming a lawless zone.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</guid><description>The situation at the Polish-Belarusian border briefly gained public awareness, with images of suffering refugees stranded in terrible conditions sparking outrage. While there were discussions and reactions, the humanitarian crisis persists.
Since September 2021, the Polish government has restricted access to the border zone, putting migrants in danger and denying aid organizations access. People are facing dire circumstances, including death, due to lack of basic necessities and medical help.</description></item><item><title>The request for a preliminary ruling from the Polish Supreme Court on 2 August 2018 and its implications for the rule of law in Poland: A commentary on the CJEU's involvement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</guid><description>Alicja Sikora, Chair EU Law, Jagiellonian University
As the playwright Eugene Ionesco once said, predictions are only possible after events have occurred.
Last Thursday, the Polish Supreme Court presented the European Court of Justice with a request for a preliminary ruling. This type of request, outlined in Article 267 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, is used to clarify questions regarding EU law. In doing so, the Polish court also paused the enforcement of a Polish law mandating early retirement for Supreme Court justices over 65.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights under ordinary EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Can the EU penalize its member states for consistently violating human rights and the rule of law? And if so, how?
This article, the second in a three-part series, explores this question. The first installment analyzed the official mechanism designed for this purpose: Article 7 TEU. As previously discussed, this process, which could result in the suspension of certain EU membership rights for a member state, is highly political, offers limited involvement from EU courts, and is challenging to implement.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that self-employed workers are protected from discrimination, including on the basis of sexual orientation, under anti-discrimination and labor rights laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</guid><description>A Closer Look at Worker Protections: Analyzing the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in Case C-356/21 By Chiara De Capitani, linguist agent at the European Commission and PhD candidate and honorary fellow in European law at the University of Naples “L&amp;rsquo;Orientale”. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Photo credit: Silar, via Wikimedia Commons</description></item><item><title>The CJEU issues its first ruling on interim measures regarding the rule of law in Poland.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-issues-its-first-ruling-on-interim-measures-regarding-the-rule-of-law-in-poland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-issues-its-first-ruling-on-interim-measures-regarding-the-rule-of-law-in-poland/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The October 19th decision by the Vice-President of the Court of Justice concerning Poland&amp;rsquo;s Judiciary Reform Act is groundbreaking. This decision, which orders Poland to halt the implementation of the Act and prevents the removal of judges due to the new retirement age, represents uncharted territory. It places the Court of Justice in the unprecedented position of compelling a sovereign member state to decide between adhering to European integration principles or embracing illiberalism.</description></item><item><title>Dear Colleague, Do You Possess Sufficient Independence? The Impact of Systemic Deficiencies in a Member State's Justice System on the Principle of Mutual Trust</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah*
*Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund For Scientific Research (F.R.S.-FNRS). The author wishes to thank Pr. S. Van Drooghenbroeck. The usual disclaimer applies.
Advocate General Tanchev recently presented his opinion on case C-216/18 PPU. This case involves multiple European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) issued by Polish authorities against an individual, LM, suspected of drug trafficking. The case, brought before the European Court of Justice (ECJ) by the Irish High Court, questions whether an EAW is enforceable if the issuing Member State&amp;rsquo;s conditions contradict the fundamental right to a fair trial due to systemic rule of law issues within its justice system.</description></item><item><title>Is Poland violating the principle of effective judicial protection? Recent developments in the CJEU suggest so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</guid><description>Femke Gremmelprez, PhD Researcher and Academic Assistant, Department of European, Public and International Law, Research group Ghent European Law Institute
While the Court of Justice plays a significant role in enforcing EU law through infringement and preliminary ruling procedures (Articles 258 and 267 TFEU, respectively), it has largely been excluded from enforcing EU values, particularly the rule of law. The EU Treaties lack explicit provisions granting the Court of Justice the power to address rule of law breaches by Member States.</description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the downfall of Poland's controversial "judicial reforms"? Reflections on the recent ECJ decision in Commission v Poland regarding the Independence of the Supreme Court.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-downfall-of-poland-s-controversial-judicial-reforms-reflections-on-the-recent-ecj-decision-in-commission-v-poland-regarding-the-independence-of-the-supreme-court/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-downfall-of-poland-s-controversial-judicial-reforms-reflections-on-the-recent-ecj-decision-in-commission-v-poland-regarding-the-independence-of-the-supreme-court/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, a Professor of European Law at Middlesex University London, and Sébastien Platon, a Professor of Public Law at the University of Bordeaux, have written about a situation unfolding in a country within the EU where the government and parliament, both controlled by the same political party, have made changes to their judicial system.
These changes include lowering the retirement age for judges on the country&amp;rsquo;s highest court. This move has been presented by the government as a necessary reform to hold accountable judges who were supposedly involved in the country&amp;rsquo;s previous communist regime, even though that regime ended three decades ago.</description></item><item><title>Is the CJEU judgment in LM a new era for mutual trust and independence of the judiciary, or just business as usual?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-cjeu-judgment-in-lm-a-new-era-for-mutual-trust-and-independence-of-the-judiciary-or-just-business-as-usual/</guid><description>Dr. Agnieszka Frąckowiak-Adamska, Faculty of Law, University of Wroclaw
In the case of C-216/18 PPU LM, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was asked by an Irish court to consider a significant legal issue facing the EU: how restrictions on judicial independence in one member state impact other EU member states. A series of laws enacted in Poland from 2015 to 2018 has been widely criticized by numerous institutions, both within and outside Poland, for enabling legislative and executive branches to significantly interfere with the judicial process.</description></item><item><title>Comments on the Polish ruling party's "fake judges" in Case C-824/18 AB and Case C-132/20 Getin Noble Bank before the European Court of Justice.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-polish-ruling-party-s-fake-judges-in-case-c-824-18-ab-and-case-c-132-20-getin-noble-bank-before-the-european-court-of-justice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 14:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-polish-ruling-party-s-fake-judges-in-case-c-824-18-ab-and-case-c-132-20-getin-noble-bank-before-the-european-court-of-justice/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, University of Middlesex On March 2, 2021, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) delivered its third judgment in a preliminary ruling case from a Polish court. This case pertained to the deterioration of the rule of law in Poland, an ongoing issue for over five years. Notably, there have been 35 requests for preliminary rulings from Polish courts compared to only three infringement actions brought by the Commission.</description></item><item><title>The complete text of the Commission Opinion on the Rule of Law in Poland, dated 1 June 2016, is now accessible.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complete-text-of-the-commission-opinion-on-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-dated-1-june-2016-is-now-accessible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 03:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complete-text-of-the-commission-opinion-on-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-dated-1-june-2016-is-now-accessible/</guid><description>Professor Laurent Pech
Those interested in the rule of law might find the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s unpublished Opinion on the Rule of Law in Poland, adopted June 1, 2016, insightful (see the Annex for the full text).
This post aims to provide context for non-experts. It will briefly outline the instrument used by the Commission to formulate its Rule of Law Opinion and then summarize why the Commission felt compelled to address rule of law concerns in Poland.</description></item><item><title>Copyright and the Internet: Poland vs. Parliament and Council (Case C-401/19), Advocate General's Opinion, July 15, 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
The rise of &amp;ldquo;Web 2.0&amp;rdquo; and social media has enabled widespread content sharing, but also raised questions about managing user rights and the role of online platforms in addressing challenges that their services might facilitate. One issue is the use of filtering technologies, particularly their impact on users&amp;rsquo; freedom of expression. Courts have previously voiced concerns about these techniques in copyright cases.</description></item></channel></rss>