<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hybrid Fiber Cable on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hybrid-fiber-cable/</link><description>Recent content in Hybrid Fiber Cable on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hybrid-fiber-cable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>