<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Uber on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uber/</link><description>Recent content in Uber on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finally, a Directive safeguarding platform work - What's next?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</guid><description>Catherine Jacqueson, Professor of EU law and Alberto Barrio, postdoctoral researcher on the WorkWel-project, Law Faculty, University of Copenhagen
Photo credit: conceptphoto.info, via Flickr On April 24th, the European Parliament officially approved the directive designed to protect platform workers. Although formal endorsement from the Council is still pending, this is largely a formality. The directive&amp;rsquo;s passage, despite the challenges and last-minute negotiations, signifies a victory. Initially, the Council presented resistance, making its unexpected adoption of the compromise agreement on March 11th surprising.</description></item><item><title>Uber Malaysia users now have the option to request a driver who speaks Mandarin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-malaysia-users-now-have-the-option-to-request-a-driver-who-speaks-mandarin/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia.
Uber Malaysia is introducing UberMANDARIN, a new service in Johor Bahru, Kota Kinabalu, and Penang that connects riders with Mandarin-speaking UberX drivers.
According to Warren Tseng, GM of Uber Malaysia and Singapore, the Ministry of Tourism and Culture projects a significant increase in Chinese tourists, from 3 million this year to potentially 8 million by 2020. UberMANDARIN aims to support the government&amp;rsquo;s tourism initiatives by offering Mandarin-speaking visitors a more comfortable and convenient experience, aligning with Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s renowned hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Uber for Business is growing with a new transportation solution for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-for-business-is-growing-with-a-new-transportation-solution-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-for-business-is-growing-with-a-new-transportation-solution-for-customers/</guid><description>Uber for Business is a platform designed to help companies enhance their operational efficiency through streamlined billing, reporting, and management tools. Initially focused on business travel, the platform has expanded to encompass various facets of customer transportation.
This expansion is facilitated by UberCENTRAL, a solution integrated into the Uber for Business platform. UberCENTRAL enables companies to elevate the customer experience by offering on-demand, door-to-door transportation.
UberCENTRAL empowers organizations to modernize customer transportation in several ways:</description></item><item><title>Is the gig economy protected by EU law? Conflicting opinions in the CJEU's legal decisions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-gig-economy-protected-by-eu-law-conflicting-opinions-in-the-cjeu-s-legal-decisions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 10:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-gig-economy-protected-by-eu-law-conflicting-opinions-in-the-cjeu-s-legal-decisions/</guid><description>Dr Maria Tzanakopoulou, Teaching Fellow, King&amp;rsquo;s College London and University College London
BACKGROUND
The expanding gig economy is sparking debates about working conditions, including issues like working hours, pay, parental leave, and the crucial classification of gig workers. The case of King is the first time the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has ruled on business conduct and worker rights in this sector. The CJEU upheld the right of self-employed individuals to retain unused paid leave indefinitely and affirmed Mr.</description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*.</description></item></channel></rss>