<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-network/</link><description>Recent content in Access Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Growing By Leaps and Bounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</guid><description>The hottest new access network service is Ethernet over Copper (EoC), with competitive carriers rushing to expand coverage.
What makes EoC so popular? It stems from evolving network needs. Wide Area Networks (WANs) have been dominated by the telephone industry, adapting phone technology for data and video transmission.
T1 lines, using two pairs of copper telephone wires, have been the standard for businesses needing dedicated Ethernet connections. They offer 1.5 Mbps upload and download speeds.</description></item></channel></rss>