<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advocate-General on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advocate-general/</link><description>Recent content in Advocate-General on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advocate-general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Legal Standing of a Third Country before the CJEU: AG Hogan's Opinion in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council in Relation to State Immunity and Comity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
In a legal opinion issued on February 20, 2021, Advocate General Hogan addressed a crucial procedural issue: Can a non-EU country legally challenge EU actions before the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)? This question holds significance because the Court has never directly ruled on it within the context of sanctions, and it delves into the principles governing the relationship between EU law and other international law subjects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The extent of the 'household exception' to EU data protection law: Is it like Big Brother's Little Brother?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, co-author of &amp;ldquo;EU Law&amp;rdquo; by Steiner and Woods, examines a case about data protection and CCTV use.
Introduction
The Czech Supreme Administrative Court referred a question to the Court of Justice regarding the &amp;ldquo;household activity&amp;rdquo; exception in the EU Data Protection Directive. This case, Ryneš, involved CCTV footage capturing images beyond the operator&amp;rsquo;s property, raising questions about the exception&amp;rsquo;s scope, especially since the Directive states data processing must be &amp;ldquo;exclusively&amp;rdquo; for personal and household purposes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Determining the Impact of the Advocate General on the European Union Court of Justice: Is it Correlation or Causation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</guid><description>Carlos Arrebola and Ana Julia Mauricio (PhD students at the University of Cambridge)
It is widely claimed, especially in publications like The Guardian, that Advocate Generals significantly influence the European Court of Justice (ECJ)&amp;rsquo;s decisions. This belief is also prevalent among legal professionals specializing in EU law. However, there is limited empirical evidence to support this assumption. Our research investigates whether this perceived influence is accurate or merely a misconception...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can obesity be considered a disability?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</guid><description>By Katharina Ó Cathaoir, PhD Fellow, University of Copenhagen
==============================================================================================
Does being obese qualify as a disability? This complex issue was the focus of Advocate General Jääskinen&amp;rsquo;s opinion on July 17, 2014, in the case of Kaltoft v. Municipality of Billund. The case has drawn significant interest, particularly regarding potential impacts on employment and healthcare. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to note that the Advocate General&amp;rsquo;s opinion is not legally binding and the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will issue its own judgment in the coming months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-obesity-be-considered-a-disability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The labeling of the European Union in the International Maritime Organization is more of a focus than the EU's actual competence.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 16:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</guid><description>Cathleen Berg, doctoral student, University of Bayreuth
Advocate General (‘AG’) Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s November 25, 2021, opinion regarding a legal challenge from the European Commission against the European Council (Case C-161/20) highlights the contrasting interests between the European Union (‘EU’) and its Member States. This disagreement centers around how they exercise their authority within the International Maritime Organization (‘IMO’), an organization where the EU currently holds neither membership nor observer status. If the Court of Justice sides with AG Szpunar&amp;rsquo;s analysis, this case could significantly impact how the EU interest is represented within IMO committees, potentially shifting power from the Commission to the Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-labeling-of-the-european-union-in-the-international-maritime-organization-is-more-of-a-focus-than-the-eu-s-actual-competence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tele 2 and Watson case: Human Rights and National Data Retention Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The Advocate General recently issued an opinion on two cases referred by national courts. These cases stem from the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in Digital Rights Ireland, which invalidated the Data Retention Directive. Both cases examine whether the mass retention of communications data aligns with EU law, raising a critical question: can such broad data retention ever truly comply with human rights?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gathering of EU citizens residing in their home country: Understanding the Surinder Singh and Carpenter rulings for family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
This article examines when an EU citizen residing in their home country can assert rights under EU law for family members to join them. This analysis stems from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressing judgments in the Surinder Singh and Carpenter cases. These cases involve family reunification for EU citizens who return to their home country after residing in another Member State and for EU citizens who provide services in another Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there Friendly Fire in the European Union? AG Sharpston's view on the revised firearms Directive's validity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</guid><description>Niels Kirst (University Paris II – Panthéon-Assas)
Advocate General Sharpston (AG) issued an opinion on April 11, 2019, regarding the legitimacy of Directive 2017/853, known as the Firearms Directive. The Czech Republic challenged this directive, arguing that the European Parliament and the Council should not have used the internal market harmonization clause (Article 114 TFEU) as the legal basis for its adoption.
This case is noteworthy for several reasons. First, it centers around the crucial aspect of legal basis, drawing considerable attention from EU legal experts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-friendly-fire-in-the-european-union-ag-sharpston-s-view-on-the-revised-firearms-directive-s-validity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion of Advocate General Szpunar on the compatibility of the Energy Charter Treaty with the Treaties and the jurisdiction of the CJEU in Case C-741/19.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</guid><description>Hannes Lenk, an Assistant Professor in Law at Aarhus University, examines a September 24, 2019 request by the French Cour d’appel de Paris. The court asked the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) to interpret &amp;ldquo;investment&amp;rdquo; as used in Article 1.6 of the Energy Charter Treaty (ECT). The intersection of the ECT and EU law, especially following the Achmea judgment against investor-state dispute settlement (ISDS) provisions in bilateral investment treaties (BITs) between EU Member States, has drawn scrutiny...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions of the Attorney General on recent CJEU cases regarding national data retention laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
Advocate General Campos Sanchez-Bordana has presented his opinions on three cases concerning data retention: SpaceNet and Telekom Deutschland, GD v Commissioner of the Garda Síochána, and VD and SR. These opinions are the latest development in a series of legal challenges related to data retention that began with an Irish challenge to the Data Retention Directive.
The Data Retention Directive, which allowed for the retention of communications data under certain exceptions to privacy principles, was invalidated in the Digital Rights Ireland case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dear Colleague, Do You Possess Sufficient Independence? The Impact of Systemic Deficiencies in a Member State's Justice System on the Principle of Mutual Trust</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah*
*Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund For Scientific Research (F.R.S.-FNRS). The author wishes to thank Pr. S. Van Drooghenbroeck. The usual disclaimer applies.
Advocate General Tanchev recently presented his opinion on case C-216/18 PPU. This case involves multiple European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) issued by Polish authorities against an individual, LM, suspected of drug trafficking. The case, brought before the European Court of Justice (ECJ) by the Irish High Court, questions whether an EAW is enforceable if the issuing Member State&amp;rsquo;s conditions contradict the fundamental right to a fair trial due to systemic rule of law issues within its justice system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-colleague-do-you-possess-sufficient-independence-the-impact-of-systemic-deficiencies-in-a-member-state-s-justice-system-on-the-principle-of-mutual-trust/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AG Kokott dismisses challenges to the legality of the Tobacco Products Directive - what does this mean for standardized packaging laws in Member States?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</guid><description>Jonathan Griffiths, Reader in Intellectual Property Law, Queen Mary University of London
The Tobacco Products Directive (Directive 2014/40/EU, revising Directive 2001/37/EC) implements strict rules for selling tobacco products. This includes requiring larger image and text health warnings on cigarettes and rolling tobacco, tighter marketing regulations for tobacco products (including e-cigarettes), and a ban on marketing tobacco products with &amp;ldquo;characterizing flavors,&amp;rdquo; such as menthol cigarettes.
On December 23rd, Advocate General Kokott presented her Opinions on three cases regarding the validity of specific parts of the Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the notice to withdraw from the EU being revoked? Wightman's opinion suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
Is initiating the Article 50 withdrawal process from the EU irreversible, like jumping off a cliff? Or is it more like going shopping, where you can change your mind along the way, in the parking lot, or even inside the store? Perhaps this change of heart might be due to discovering the promised sale doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, the management is under investigation, and the supposed extensive international food section is just a couple of dusty packages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's upcoming trade policy is beginning to form with the release of the Opinion on the EU/Singapore FTA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s authority regarding trade agreements has been debated for years in the European Court of Justice (ECJ), as it significantly affects the balance of power between the EU and its Member States concerning international economic policies. Treaty revisions, especially the Treaty of Lisbon, have altered these rules, making this issue even more important due to recent controversies surrounding EU trade negotiations (notably with Canada and the USA) and the UK-EU trade talks post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What authority should the Court of Justice have in EU Foreign Policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Luigi Lonardo, PhD student, King’s College London
Article 24(1) of the Treaty on the European Union states that the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) operates under distinct rules and procedures, explicitly stating that the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) holds no jurisdiction over these provisions.
Legal experts are debating whether &amp;ldquo;the CJEU shall not have jurisdiction&amp;rdquo; implies a degree of jurisdiction. AG Wahl articulated this question: Does the exclusion of CJEU jurisdiction encompass all CFSP actions or only specific categories?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumer law and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR): Case C-319/20 involving Facebook Ireland - Advocate General's opinion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 05:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Facts
The Federation of German Consumer Organisations initiated legal proceedings in German courts against Facebook. They claimed that Facebook violated data protection rules by failing to provide sufficient information about data collection practices related to free, third-party games offered on its platform. The Federation argued that this also infringed upon unfair competition and consumer protection regulations. The case reached the Bundesgerischtshof, which raised concerns about the Federation&amp;rsquo;s legal standing to bring the action following the implementation of the GDPR...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copyright and the Internet: Poland vs. Parliament and Council (Case C-401/19), Advocate General's Opinion, July 15, 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
The rise of &amp;ldquo;Web 2.0&amp;rdquo; and social media has enabled widespread content sharing, but also raised questions about managing user rights and the role of online platforms in addressing challenges that their services might facilitate. One issue is the use of filtering technologies, particularly their impact on users&amp;rsquo; freedom of expression. Courts have previously voiced concerns about these techniques in copyright cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the ECB's OMT program in question? The Advocate-General's opinion in Gauweiler suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 01:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective (OUP)
On January 14th, Advocate General Cruz Villalon presented his legal opinion on the Gauweiler case (C-62/14), which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. He believes the OMT program generally complies with EU treaties, provided certain conditions are met if it&amp;rsquo;s activated in the future. This case has significant implications for the European Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s (EMU) constitutional framework, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s role, and the relationship between the German Constitutional Court (Bundesverfassungsgericht) and the Court of Justice of the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experimenting with EU governance in the Telecoms sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:29:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</guid><description>Marta Cantero (Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Helsinki | FiDiPro Project)
Creating a unified digital market for telecommunications within Europe is a primary goal of the current European Commission. [i] However, achieving this single market remains a distant prospect. The current multi-tiered regulatory model for European telecommunications relies heavily on individual nations&amp;rsquo; regulatory bodies to implement the EU&amp;rsquo;s telecom framework. Furthermore, enforcing this framework falls upon the Member States themselves under their own national procedures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of an Advocate-General's opinion reveals that Brexit will result in the end of EU citizenship for UK nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 11:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The question of whether British citizens retained their EU citizenship after Brexit is disputed. While the EU and UK governments assert that they did not, some British individuals disagree.
This issue has been raised before EU courts through various avenues. Three cases directly appealed to the EU General Court, contesting the EU Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to finalize the withdrawal agreement. These appeals argued that the agreement improperly revoked their EU citizenship...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>