<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fast Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fast-ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Fast Ethernet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fast-ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Diverse Connections For Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</guid><description>The reliability of data connections is crucial for data centers and colocation facilities to ensure service availability. Having multiple separate network connections is not enough; you need multiple diverse data connections from different providers that take different routes to your facility.
Simply having multiple connections from a single provider offers limited protection because a catastrophic failure could take down the entire connection. This risk is amplified in your own facility, where a single connection runs for miles and is vulnerable to disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet as a DS3 Upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line provides have historically opted for DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. This high-speed digital connection typically runs on a SONET fiber optic circuit, with the final connection to the customer&amp;rsquo;s location installed and maintained by the local phone company. DS3 is fast, very reliable, and more affordable than ever before. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new contender – Fast Ethernet.
Fast Ethernet is a standard Ethernet LAN speed that delivers 100 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pricing Slashed For Michigan 100 Mbps Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</guid><description>Michigan businesses are facing a common problem: the need for faster internet speeds. Traditional options like T1 lines are no longer sufficient for handling increased data demands from video conferencing, cloud-based applications, and automation. While fiber optic services offer the necessary bandwidth, their high cost often makes them inaccessible.
Comcast Business Class emerges as a potential solution, delivering 100 Mbps download and 10 Mbps upload speeds at a price comparable to T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100, 1000, 10000 Mbps Internet Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As technology progresses, businesses require significantly faster internet speeds. Our Wide Area Networks (WANs) are now crucial for operations. Today, internet connections of 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps, and even 10,000 Mbps are standard and essential. Fortunately, pricing has decreased as speeds have increased, making these bandwidth levels attainable.
100 Mbps Fast Ethernet
100 Mbps is the current standard bandwidth, replacing the older 45 Mbps DS3 bandwidth. DS3, an upgrade from slower T1 lines, is part of the TDM telecom standard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Colocation Center Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 23:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/</guid><description>Businesses frequently turn to colocation to avoid the financial burden of owning and operating their own data centers. A major advantage of colocation is access to high bandwidth at significantly reduced costs.
](http://www.etherrabbit.com/)Colocation centers, or colos, are facilities that house the data center needs of numerous businesses. Maintaining a server farm involves considerable infrastructure and resources, including servers, network equipment, racks, power, cooling, security, and round-the-clock staff. Colocation provides all these elements as a service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-colocation-center-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE Is The New DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than their T1 lines can provide have usually upgraded to DS3. However, a faster and more affordable option, Fast Ethernet (FastE), is now available.
While you might not know Fast Ethernet as a Metro or Carrier bandwidth service, the term is likely familiar. Fast Ethernet refers to 100 Mbps Ethernet, one of the standard LAN speeds alongside 10 Mbps and 1,000 Mbps Ethernet (Gigabit Ethernet or GigE)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>