<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microwave Radio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microwave-radio/</link><description>Recent content in Microwave Radio on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microwave-radio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles.</description></item><item><title>3G Fixed Wireless For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</guid><description>The same 3G technology that revolutionized mobile phones is also available as a fixed wireless service, offering a cost-effective solution for businesses in areas with limited internet options. Cellular networks have established a wide infrastructure of base stations, effectively blanketing the country with both voice and data coverage. These familiar cell towers transmit signals using microwave radio equipment.
Essentially, the 3G wireless broadband service functions as a network of interconnected Wi-Fi hotspots with a significantly larger coverage area.</description></item></channel></rss>