<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Privacy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/privacy/</link><description>Recent content in Privacy on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the UK's new data retention bill in violation of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Despite the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidating the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive in April, the UK government is pushing for continued data retention authority. This piece examines whether the proposed law aligns with EU law and if it violates the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.
The connection to EU law lies in Article 15(1) of the EU&amp;rsquo;s e-privacy Directive. This article allows Member States to restrict certain rights concerning communication confidentiality for safeguarding national security and other serious matters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tele 2 and Watson case: Human Rights and National Data Retention Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The Advocate General recently issued an opinion on two cases referred by national courts. These cases stem from the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in Digital Rights Ireland, which invalidated the Data Retention Directive. Both cases examine whether the mass retention of communications data aligns with EU law, raising a critical question: can such broad data retention ever truly comply with human rights?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Live. Die. Repeat. Is the 'Privacy Shield' deal stuck in a never-ending cycle of repeating the same mistakes like in the movie 'Groundhog Day'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the USA is globally recognized, some of its customs remain perplexing. Take &amp;ldquo;Groundhog Day,&amp;rdquo; where the presence or absence of a groundhog&amp;rsquo;s shadow on February 2nd supposedly predicts six more weeks of winter. Beyond the USA, it&amp;rsquo;s more famous as a film where Bill Murray relives the same day, striving for perfection and Andie MacDowell&amp;rsquo;s affections. This concept has inspired others: Tom Cruise battling aliens and wooing Emily Blunt in Edge of Tomorrow, and Peter Capaldi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to breach a diamond wall and resurrect Jenna Coleman in Doctor Who&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hell Bent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mozilla has launched Firefox Focus on Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</guid><description>Source: Mozilla. Mozilla launches Firefox Focus for Android.
Mozilla, a strong advocate for an open and accessible internet, has released Firefox Focus for Android devices. This launch caters to the increasing number of mobile users seeking enhanced online privacy.
Firefox Focus allows users to browse the internet without being tracked by advertisements, which are infamous for slowing down mobile browsing. This announcement comes six months after the successful iPhone and iPad launch in November...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Impact on UK's Participation in EU Policing and Criminal Law: EU Referendum Brief 5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
This piece examines the relationship between EU membership and UK policing and criminal law, exploring potential impacts of Brexit.
Summary
The UK held veto power over EU laws in this domain before the Treaty of Lisbon (enacted December 1, 2009). Subsequently, the UK secured two opt-out mechanisms: the ability to opt into (or out of) any new EU law in this area post-Treaty, and the option to retroactively opt out of pre-existing EU laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions regarding consent for cookies in accordance with data protection laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A significant ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the use of cookies and the interpretation of consent under the e-Privacy Directive was issued last week in the Planet49 case. This ruling holds implications for comprehending cookie requirements under both the existing and forthcoming data protection regulations.
Judgment
At the heart of the matter was an online lottery requiring participants to provide their name and address...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is privacy prioritized over transparency in CJEU cases?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</guid><description>Peter Oliver, Barrister, Monckton Chambers; Visiting Professor, Université Libre de Bruxelles
Having a name is essential, as not having one can lead to problems. This is why courts in Strasbourg and Luxembourg have acknowledged a person’s fundamental right to use their own name.
The Court of Justice has traditionally used initials to protect the identities of vulnerable individuals like asylum seekers and children involved in sensitive litigation. However, in a recent announcement, the Court stated its intention to partially overturn this long-standing practice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Commission's draft EU-US Privacy Shield adequacy decision a new shield for transatlantic privacy or just more of the same?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</guid><description>Dr. Maria Tzanou (Lecturer in Law, Keele University)
In October 2015, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruled in the Schrems case that the US Safe Harbor framework did not adequately protect personal data transfers from the EU. The court found that US mass electronic surveillance practices violated fundamental EU privacy rights.
To address this, the European Commission and the US agreed on a new framework called the EU-US Privacy Shield...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regardless of the CJEU's decision, data retention could potentially continue to exist under national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
A central question regarding internet privacy is whether governments should be allowed to store data about everyone&amp;rsquo;s online and phone activities in the name of fighting terrorism and serious crime. This issue, known as &amp;ldquo;data retention,&amp;rdquo; raises crucial questions about balancing privacy and security, both nationally and within the European Union. Initially, the EU&amp;rsquo;s electronic privacy (e-Privacy) Directive offered member states the choice to implement data retention rules, deviating from the usual rule of communication confidentiality outlined in the directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Retention is still a permanent fixture, at least for the time being.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-retention-is-still-a-permanent-fixture-at-least-for-the-time-being/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 04:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-retention-is-still-a-permanent-fixture-at-least-for-the-time-being/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University.
Introduction
On January 30, 2018, the human rights organization Liberty announced on Twitter that the Court of Appeal found the UK government to be acting illegally. The government was gathering internet and phone records from the entire country and allowing public bodies to access them without any suspicion of serious crime or independent approval.
This referred to the Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s (CoA) decision in the case of Tom Watson and Others v Secretary of State for the Home Department concerning access to communication data under the Data Retention and Investigatory Power Act 2014 (DRIPA 2014)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-retention-is-still-a-permanent-fixture-at-least-for-the-time-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-retention-is-still-a-permanent-fixture-at-least-for-the-time-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECtHR Grand Chamber makes a ruling on mass surveillance in the case of Big Brother Watch v UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, an expert in internet law from the University of Essex, provides an in-depth analysis of a significant ruling by the Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) concerning the United Kingdom&amp;rsquo;s surveillance regime, specifically its Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA).
This ruling is the culmination of a series of legal challenges against the UK&amp;rsquo;s surveillance practices, brought to light by revelations of extensive government surveillance programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECHR provides clarification on the use of hidden cameras in relation to human rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Bremner v Turkey provides clarity on the use of hidden cameras by journalists and potential human rights violations. The case involved an Australian citizen, Bremner, who was secretly filmed in his apartment discussing Christianity for a documentary about &amp;ldquo;foreign peddlers of religion&amp;rdquo; in Turkey. The program aired footage of Bremner with his face unblurred...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>