<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Communication on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/communication/</link><description>Recent content in Communication on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states.</description></item><item><title>Encouraging an open workplace culture: the role of leaders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</guid><description>Open communication and strong relationships are essential for a thriving workplace. UK-based sales and marketing firm Forrest Bell emphasizes that openness involves respectful and constructive dialogue about needs, opinions, and concerns. It also means actively listening to and considering new ideas, questions, and feedback.
Forrest Bell believes that a culture of openness fosters trust and facilitates collaboration on projects. It also promotes transparency and streamlines processes in dynamic business environments.</description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>WebRTC set to boost business productivity for browsers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably used a web browser like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, or Safari on your phone or computer to visit websites.
Some companies believe browsers can be much more than tools for accessing websites; they think browsers can simplify our lives. Tata Communications suggests that incorporating the right features into browsers could significantly boost employee productivity.
&amp;ldquo;Despite some positive developments, most of us are still dealing with separate, disconnected communication platforms.</description></item><item><title>The Handbook on Marriages of Convenience by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
In September 2014, the Commission introduced a Handbook designed to guide Member States in addressing marriages of convenience between EU citizens and non-EU nationals. The goal is to combat these marriages without unduly restricting the free movement rights of EU citizens. The Commission emphasizes that the guidelines, developed in collaboration with Member States, are not legally binding and don&amp;rsquo;t supersede existing EU law or its future interpretations.</description></item><item><title>The enhanced Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB from ALE simplifies collaboration and boosts productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</guid><description>Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise, operating under the Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise brand, helps small and medium businesses provide a streamlined user experience and enhanced onsite mobility for their employees, while ensuring business continuity. This is achieved through the latest update of their product, Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB.
The latest improvements to OpenTouch Suite for SMB focus on increasing productivity and efficiency. This is achieved through expanded communication and collaborative tools, as well as enabling employees to access the company environment from any location, at any time, using mobile applications.</description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing.</description></item></channel></rss>