<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Managed Router on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-router/</link><description>Recent content in Managed Router on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-router/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet DS3 Bandwidth Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has grown continuously since T1 lines became the norm for dedicated internet access and private point-to-point connections. If you currently use DS3 bandwidth services or are thinking about an upgrade, comparing your wide area network (WAN) bandwidth choices is essential.
DS3, a 45 Mbps service, represents the traditional high-bandwidth network connection and is equivalent in speed to a T3 line. These days, most DS3 services are delivered via fiber optic cables, with a copper handoff point at the demarcation point.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Network Monitoring Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</guid><description>The increasing reliance on electronic transactions, online services, and cloud technologies has made networks essential for businesses. This dependence requires IT departments to prioritize network monitoring, either through in-house solutions or external providers.
While companies have traditionally monitored their internal networks, extending this practice to telecom connections is crucial. This includes dedicated lines, public internet connections, and VPNs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to enhance network monitoring processes.
Smaller businesses often face challenges with network monitoring outside of business hours.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Expansion With Multiple T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 22:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</guid><description>For many years, T1 lines have been a reliable network connection, especially when bandwidth demands are low. However, with increasing bandwidth requirements exceeding 1.5 Mbps, upgrading from the traditional T1 line becomes necessary.
One solution to increase bandwidth without abandoning existing T1 lines is &amp;ldquo;bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines the capacity of multiple T1 lines, effectively creating a single, faster connection. A managed router with multiple interface cards connects and manages the combined bandwidth from the T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>The LAN WAN Connection Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 18:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lan-wan-connection-made-easy/</guid><description>Local area networks (LANs) are standardized and consistent, making them easy to understand and work with. However, connecting to a wide area network (WAN) introduces a new set of telephone company standards that can be challenging for network professionals familiar with LAN technologies.
In the past, connecting to a WAN required specialized knowledge of complex technologies like DS channels and SONET multiplexing. This often involved significant effort to bridge the gap between LAN and WAN environments.</description></item><item><title>SDN Performance Takes a Leaf of Faith</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cloud computing has highlighted the importance of reliable internet connections, known as WANs (Wide Area Networks). In the past, slow file transfers or unreliable internet were acceptable because crucial tasks were handled within the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network. However, now that businesses rely on cloud services, the performance of the WAN is just as crucial as the internal network (LAN).
WAN Challenges
The main challenge with WANs is that businesses don&amp;rsquo;t control them like they do their internal networks.</description></item></channel></rss>