<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Purchase Order on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/purchase-order/</link><description>Recent content in Purchase Order on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:49:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/purchase-order/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up the item: Where it all begins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</guid><description>My recent focus on Sure Step training reminded me how crucial item setup is. Many Sales Order Processing (SOP) and Purchase Order Processing (POP) problems stem from those initial item setup choices. Users might misunderstand how the system works, not realizing their settings are dictating the behavior – settings that are often easy to change. This happens because setup and transaction entry are often done by different people, or so much time has passed that the reasoning behind setup decisions is forgotten (hence the need for good documentation, though I doubt my coworkers would be thrilled to hear that again)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Modifying PO Distributions in Summary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</guid><description>Since the release of service packs GP 10 (SP2 and later) and GP 9 (SP3 and later), users can no longer make changes to summary distributions in Receivings Transaction Entry and Purchasing Invoice Entry. Instead, they must access the Item Detail expansion and adjust the account assigned to the line item.
While this change makes sense from an inventory management perspective, as reconciling inventory with the general ledger was difficult when summary distributions could be modified, it has made the process more complex for clients who use the POP module without inventory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Issue with upgrading Project Accounting and Purchase Order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 03:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</guid><description>A recent upgrade from GP9 to GP10 resulted in an unexpected issue: purchase order line items were missing account numbers. This was perplexing because previous upgrades, even those involving project accounting, had gone smoothly.
The problem became evident when a user discovered that upon receiving purchase orders, no Cost of Goods Sold account defaulted. This was because the purchase order line items lacked account numbers. Database examination confirmed that the INVINDX field, which stores account indexes for purchase order lines in the POP10110 table, was empty for all 7500 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Land of Landed Costs: Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 08:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about landed costs. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover the three main ways landed costs are used, building on the previous example of setting up insurance costs to connect insurance invoices with product shipments.
Three Ways to Use Landed Costs 1. Landed Costs by Line Item Assign a landed cost group to each line item upon receipt. This can be done by default (from item setup or the purchase order) or manually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Land of Landed Costs - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</guid><description>Landed cost represents the total expense of getting an item to your location. This includes the item price plus charges like shipping, customs fees, and processing. More companies are focusing on landed costs as they increasingly source products from global suppliers and manufacturers. Using landed costs provides a more accurate view of the &amp;ldquo;total&amp;rdquo; cost, reflecting it in inventory value as an asset, rather than treating additional expenses separately.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate with an example: you buy 100 widgets from a European supplier at $20 per widget...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>