<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Symantec on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/symantec/</link><description>Recent content in Symantec on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:43:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/symantec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The impact of GDPR will be remembered in 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</guid><description>The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) heavily influenced how we addressed online privacy in 2018. While it primarily protects residents of the European Union, the GDPR&amp;rsquo;s global reach impacts any company conducting business with EU residents. This broad scope has shifted GDPR from a regional concern to a worldwide one.
Several industry leaders have shared their perspectives on GDPR&amp;rsquo;s significant effects:
Source: Sage. Wherrett.
Arlene Wherrett, VP and MD of Sage Asia, observed that GDPR was a major catalyst for change in business operations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The attitudes towards cybercrime and security in Singapore vary across different generations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</guid><description>This past week, I encountered WhatsApp spam shortly after a friend forwarded a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s discount coupon from Sniflr. Upon researching, I discovered Sniflr is a phishing scam that tricks people into sharing the coupon with 10 friends on WhatsApp, adding those numbers to a spam list.
Yesterday, a promoted tweet on my Twitter feed advertised a S$100 discount on a S$120 purchase at NTUC, a popular Singaporean supermarket chain. However, a Google search revealed a months-old news article warning about fake NTUC coupons on Facebook, a claim supported by NTUC&amp;rsquo;s official Twitter account...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia is included in global ransomware attacks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 20:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</guid><description>WannaCrypt, also referred to as WannaCry or WCry, holds data files hostage and demands a $300 USD ransom in Bitcoin. The ransom message warns that the payment will double after three days. If payment isn&amp;rsquo;t received within seven days, the encrypted files are permanently deleted.
A key feature of WannaCrypt is its ability to self-propagate within company networks without any user intervention. This is achieved by exploiting a known weakness in the Microsoft Windows operating system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-included-in-global-ransomware-attacks/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>