<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yahoo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/yahoo/</link><description>Recent content in Yahoo on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 02:37:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/yahoo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yahoo has published its 2016 Year in Review for Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 02:37:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</guid><description>Yahoo, a popular online platform, has released its &amp;ldquo;2016 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; (YIR) for Singapore. This yearly recap highlights the major search trends and events that captivated Singaporean internet users, based on their search history and online activity on Yahoo throughout 2016.
Topping the list of &amp;ldquo;Top 10 Singapore Headlines&amp;rdquo; is swimmer Joseph Schooling winning Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first Olympic gold medal. Significant political events like changes to the Elected Presidency and MP David Ong&amp;rsquo;s resignation also feature prominently.</description></item><item><title>Yahoo's latest Messenger is designed for socializing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-s-latest-messenger-is-designed-for-socializing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-s-latest-messenger-is-designed-for-socializing/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a brand new Yahoo Messenger, available on mobile devices, the web, and within Yahoo Mail on desktop computers. This updated version of Yahoo Messenger simplifies the process of sharing, liking, and interacting with messages, images, and animated GIFs.
According to Jeff Bonforte, Senior VP of communication products and engineering at Yahoo, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to present the next generation of Yahoo Messenger. While it has always been a key offering for us, it was time for a complete overhaul, a rebuilding from the ground up, to reinvest in a product that holds such significance in our company&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>The Flickr App for iPad has been optimized for iOS 8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a new Flickr app designed for iPads, allowing users seamless photo management across all devices. Yahoo claims the app is optimized for iOS 8, providing an enhanced experience for capturing, editing, and browsing images.
Source: Yahoo.
Current iPad users can update their existing Flickr app, while new users can download it from the App Store. The app supports multiple languages, including English, French, Indonesian, Korean, Chinese, and Vietnamese.</description></item><item><title>Flickr Wall Art is now available worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</guid><description>Yahoo has expanded its Flickr wall art service to global markets, enabling businesses worldwide to adorn their walls with photographic artwork from Flickr artists.
Initially introduced in October, the Flickr Wall Art service allows the transformation of photographs from licensed artists within the Flickr Marketplace into high-quality wall prints available for purchase directly on Flickr.
The Flickr team has curated a collection of licensed photographs from popular categories such as abstract, landscapes, travel, and animals.</description></item><item><title>The new version of Flickr is now available for iOS 9</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 02:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s Flickr app for iOS 9 now includes features designed for the updated operating system.
Source: Yahoo.
The app utilizes 3D Touch on the latest iPhones. This allows users to preview content by pressing lightly on the screen. For example, in the Camera Roll, lightly pressing a photo shows a preview, while a harder press expands it to full screen.
Another 3D Touch feature, &amp;ldquo;Quick Actions,&amp;rdquo; lets users perform certain tasks directly from the app icon.</description></item><item><title>The 2019 Year in Review by Yahoo highlights Singapore's obsession with celebrity, wealth, and the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 05:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s 2019 Year in Review (YIR) reveals that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s internet users were captivated by stories surrounding Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s former PM Najib Razak, NUS student Monica Baey, and the Hong Kong protests.
The YIR, which analyzes search trends on Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s platforms, highlighted Najib Razak&amp;rsquo;s connection to the 1MDB scandal as a topic of significant interest. The Orchard Towers murder case, particularly Natalie Siow&amp;rsquo;s involvement, also drew considerable attention.
Actor Aloysius Pang&amp;rsquo;s passing during reservist training prompted searches related to training safety, while his girlfriend, actress Jayley Woo, also became a top search.</description></item></channel></rss>