<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Earth Day on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earth-day/</link><description>Recent content in Earth Day on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 18:53:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earth-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Earth Day Means Money For Electronics Recycling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-day-means-money-for-electronics-recycling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 18:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-day-means-money-for-electronics-recycling/</guid><description>Today is Earth Day, a day to appreciate nature and consider our impact. We should treat our planet with respect or face the consequences. Speaking of which, why not make some money while being environmentally conscious?
It&amp;rsquo;s entirely possible to earn money by responsibly discarding old electronics. Even someone very frugal would see the value in making a little cash while helping the environment. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree? How about making some easy money through recycling?</description></item><item><title>Save the Cell Phone, Save the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</guid><description>Cell phones are frequently overlooked as a source of environmental concern, valuable resources, and potential income. While seemingly harmless, these devices contain toxic materials and represent a significant waste problem due to their short lifespans and frequent replacement.
A cell phone&amp;rsquo;s small size and durable exterior might make it seem environmentally benign, but the internal components tell a different story. Lead, cadmium, arsenic, mercury, plastics, and glass are all found within these devices.</description></item><item><title>Why Alternative Energy Makes Sense for Technology Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 10:04:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</guid><description>The digital world&amp;rsquo;s dependence on energy is deeply intertwined and may be its downfall, just as energy production&amp;rsquo;s side effects threaten our physical world. Climate change, for instance, directly impacts the sustainability of Business 2.0.
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume that dirty, resource-intensive energy is a relic of the industrial age, replaced by a cleaner information age, especially online. However, the online world can create a false sense of detachment from the physical resources it relies on.</description></item><item><title>Eco Friendly Hosting $3.75/mo.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eco-friendly-hosting-375mo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eco-friendly-hosting-375mo/</guid><description>As Earth Day approaches, you might feel uneasy about using a web host that relies on electricity from a coal-powered plant, further consuming energy for server cooling. This conflict is especially true if environmental responsibility aligns with your values.
Fortunately, eco-friendly hosting services are available for under $4 per month.
Dotster offers affordable domains and web hosting, including basic web hosting for $3.75 a month. Beyond affordability, Dotster is committed to environmental responsibility through its green hosting program.</description></item><item><title>Going Green Office Tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-green-office-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 11:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-green-office-tips/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s commemorate Earth Day by remembering that every day presents an opportunity to minimize waste and enhance energy efficiency. This approach is not only ethically sound but also financially beneficial. Let&amp;rsquo;s pinpoint some straightforward adjustments we can implement and evaluate their impact as we progress.
My compact office used to be unbearably hot in the summer and excessively warm even during Northern Illinois winters. Upon closer inspection, it became evident that several computers, a monitor, a TV, printers, overhead lights, and desk lamps were emitting a substantial amount of heat.</description></item><item><title>Get Paid To Celebrate National Cell Phone Recycling Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s National Cell Phone Recycling Week, and there&amp;rsquo;s a way to make some money while participating! This initiative, spearheaded by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), highlights the importance of recycling valuable and potentially harmful materials found in cell phones.
Wireless carriers and various retailers are accepting old cell phones to ensure these devices are properly processed and their components are reused in new products. By taking part, you contribute to environmental protection by preventing hazardous materials from ending up in landfills.</description></item><item><title>Dotster Eco-Friendly Hosting Commitment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dotster-eco-friendly-hosting-commitment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 09:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dotster-eco-friendly-hosting-commitment/</guid><description>For over a decade, Dotster has been a familiar name in the online world, especially for domain registration services. However, Dotster is also a significant player in the eco-friendly hosting arena, offering services from budget-friendly email hosting to large-scale website hosting.
Eco-conscious hosting is gaining traction among those seeking environmentally responsible options, and contrary to popular belief, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to break the bank. Dotster provides eco-friendly hosting starting at $5.</description></item></channel></rss>