<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephone Companies on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-companies/</link><description>Recent content in Telephone Companies on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-companies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching.</description></item><item><title>Your Right to Competitive T1 Prices Protected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) recently upheld your right to benefit from competition among wireline telecommunication services. The FCC unanimously rejected a request from Verizon Telephone Companies to be released from regulations requiring them to provide competitive access to their lines in six Northeastern cities.
This regulation, part of the Telecommunications Act of 1996, aims to level the playing field between established phone companies and newer competitors. Historically, these incumbent companies, descendants of the Bell System monopoly, operated without competition for a century.</description></item><item><title>Phone Power... To The People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:43:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-to-the-people/</guid><description>VoIP and broadband phone services for businesses and residential customers are steadily replacing the century-old traditional phone industry. The reason? Price!
Traditional phone service relies on tariffs that charge for every little thing. You pay for the line, local service, long distance, and extra features like Caller ID. They even charge a monthly fee for maintaining the wiring in your home! It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that phone bills can be shockingly high.</description></item></channel></rss>