<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>177AABG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/177aabg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 177AABG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/177aabg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustments, Cleaning the Aluminum Surfaces and a First Spin with Freddie Hubbard!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</guid><description>Following the installation of a new gold-plated DIN 5 plug, the Beogram 4000 was ready for its initial test. The RPM was fine-tuned using a custom Beolover RPM device, aided by the recently installed precision multi-turn trimmers. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that allowing the unit to warm up for approximately 15 minutes before this adjustment is recommended, as the RPM can fluctuate slightly during this period. For fellow enthusiasts, the Beolover RPM device is available upon request via email or the contact form and includes a separate base for convenient setup and occasional RPM checks.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from California with a Bit of Shipping Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived needing some care, but unfortunately experienced additional damage during shipping. Upon opening the box, it was discovered that the carriage had detached from the pulley, which was stuck to tape residue. Thankfully, the tonearm was secured with tape, preventing it from ejecting through the platter opening and causing more severe damage. However, the tonearm did sustain some impact. This highlights the importance of securing the carriage during transport using foam and tape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the carriage transport and arm lowering mechanisms, the electrolytic capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration project required attention. Replacing the original reservoir and motor capacitors in AC motor Beograms is always satisfying, and the 4000 boasts an impressive collection of large capacitors.
The initial step involved removing the outdated capacitors. A quick assessment using a BK LCR tester identified two faulty capacitors. One of the 2200uF capacitors registered a meager 7.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Plexiglass Hood With Laser Cut Patches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</guid><description>The hinge area is the most delicate part of plexiglass hoods found on Beogram turntables. It&amp;rsquo;s subject to significant stress when opened and closed, while the presence of screw holes for the metal hinge makes it structurally vulnerable. I recently worked on a Beogram 4000 with a cracked hood and a broken-off piece.
Inspired by a previous restoration of a Beogram 3000 hinge, I aimed to create a similar solution for the 4000/4002 models.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</guid><description>I noticed a knocking sound coming from my Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s AC motor, which meant the Oilite brass bearing needed lubrication. These bearings are designed to release oil onto the motor shaft over time. Eventually, they need to be replaced or re-lubricated. Using a food vacuum sealer and a mason jar, you can replenish the oil. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I did it:
First, I removed the motor.
Next, I removed the two rivets holding the motor together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Control Panel - LEDs and Gold Plating of Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the enhancement of the carriage position switches, the control panel restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable commenced. The project involved a typical upgrade of incandescent bulbs to LED assemblies and gold plating of switch terminals for enhanced longevity and performance.
The initial stage revealed significantly oxidized keypad switch terminals:
The terminals were carefully removed:
Following oxidation removal using a fiberglass pen, the terminals were gold-coated:
An oversight led to one terminal being missed initially:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs - New Capacitors, RPM Trimmers and RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the motor and reservoir capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step involved rebuilding the PCBs. This typically involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM trimmers, and the RPM relay. The main PCB, which is difficult to remove due to its hardwiring, was &amp;lsquo;flipped&amp;rsquo; for component replacement.
After replacing the components, the rebuilt board was ready for installation. A new relay was used, as the original Siemens relays often experience oxidation, hindering proper RPM switching.</description></item></channel></rss>