<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lifestyle on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lifestyle/</link><description>Recent content in Lifestyle on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24.</description></item><item><title>Adidas Originals is reintroducing the Superstar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</guid><description>Source: adidas.
This year, adidas Originals launches a campaign exploring the meaning of being a superstar, coinciding with the anniversary of the iconic Superstar shoe, first released in 1969.
A short film by adidas Originals, directed by Karim Huu Do, examines what it means to be a superstar in 2015. Footballer David Beckham states, &amp;ldquo;It’s not about trying to be the next big thing.&amp;rdquo; Entertainer Pharrell Williams believes &amp;ldquo;It’s not about the number of views, likes or shares.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Targus Geo 15.6" Backpack designed for lasting durability and comfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-targus-geo-15-6-backpack-designed-for-lasting-durability-and-comfort/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 20:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-targus-geo-15-6-backpack-designed-for-lasting-durability-and-comfort/</guid><description>Source: Targus.
Targus, a company known for its business-oriented laptop cases, introduced the Geo lifestyle collection in August. The company states that the collection features a modern style with neutral colors and unique design elements, appealing to both weekend adventurers and daily commuters.
The Geo Collection boasts premium materials, including cross-dyed polyester fabric, patterned lining, soft-touch accents, and soft leather-like details. Targus highlights the signature engineered stripe of the Geo collection, which is individually screen-printed for an artisanal feel.</description></item><item><title>TINKR combines fashion, design, and 3D printing technology in a unique way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</guid><description>TINKR, a company from Singapore, has transitioned its business model from solely offering 3D printing services. They now focus on merging fashion, design, and technology to produce unique corporate gifts.
In a recent announcement, company founders Xiaohui and Freda expressed their passion for blending craftsmanship with technology. They are excited to introduce their latest venture: high-quality, locally and regionally designed prints. They plan to collaborate with various artisans and designers in the upcoming months to create fresh, unique prints with a distinctive style.</description></item><item><title>The groundbreaking ceremony for Jewel has been successfully completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Changi Airport.
Jewel Changi Airport Trustee (JCAT), a collaboration between Changi Airport Group (CAG) and CapitaMalls Asia (the shopping mall branch of CapitaLand), has initiated the construction of Jewel Changi Airport. This mixed-use development, situated in front of Terminal 1 (T1), will feature attractions, retail spaces, a hotel, and airport operational facilities.
Strategically placed at the airport&amp;rsquo;s core, Jewel aims to be a premier lifestyle destination enhancing Changi Airport&amp;rsquo;s global standing and solidifying Singapore&amp;rsquo;s attractiveness as a layover spot for travelers.</description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace.</description></item><item><title>Making small changes to your lifestyle can lead to a healthier you in the long run, according to Herbalife</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-small-changes-to-your-lifestyle-can-lead-to-a-healthier-you-in-the-long-run-according-to-herbalife/</guid><description>People in Asia are interested in expanding their fitness routines beyond traditional practices like yoga and tai chi. However, Samantha Clayton, Director of Worldwide Fitness Education at Herbalife, notes that they face unique challenges, such as extreme weather and demanding work schedules, and need to adapt their fitness routines accordingly.
She emphasizes the importance of integrating fitness into everyday life, especially when environmental factors like air quality, heat, and humidity can be obstacles.</description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years.</description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa.</description></item><item><title>A Singapore retailer utilizes Qlik and Deloitte Digital solution to monitor customer narratives over time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singapore-retailer-utilizes-qlik-and-deloitte-digital-solution-to-monitor-customer-narratives-over-time/</guid><description>Inverted Edge, a Singapore-based online retailer, is enhancing the customer experience at its Scotts Square location. Using technology from Qlik, a visual analytics company, and design by Deloitte Digital, the store provides a unique and interactive digital shopping experience.
Source: Inverted Edge website.
In addition to its selection of high-quality, modern luxury clothing, the store features a dynamic display of customer photos and stories from social media. This constantly updated feed showcases how customers style their purchases and shares their experiences.</description></item><item><title>AIN has added English and Chinese websites for those interested in fashion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</guid><description>Source: AIN English website.
A Korean women&amp;rsquo;s fashion brand is aiming to become a global name, focusing particularly on mainland China, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
AIN has seen positive results selling on international e-commerce platforms. To further expand its reach, the company has launched English and Chinese websites through cafe24, a leading Korean e-commerce platform. AIN&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Park A-In, shared that customers appreciate the brand&amp;rsquo;s distinct, contemporary designs and overall aesthetic.</description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains.</description></item><item><title>Men's cufflinks that can be customized are now offered on Indiegogo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</guid><description>CuffloCs, customizable cufflinks designed for men, are seeking funding on Indiegogo. These unique cufflinks feature a secure compartment for holding small items. According to creator Josh Jablonski, CuffloCs can accommodate a variety of small objects, such as jewelry charms, pebbles, or even photographs.
Source: Indiegogo.
&amp;ldquo;The screw/on off design ensures the security of your items within the double-sided glass, and the cufflink can be effortlessly disassembled to switch up the design,&amp;rdquo; explains Jablonski on his Indiegogo page.</description></item><item><title>The last adidas Originals = PHARRELL WILLIAMS collection of 2014 will be released on November 28th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</guid><description>The last adidas Originals and Pharrell Williams collaboration of 2014 features a playful use of polka dots. More releases are planned for 2015. The bold and cheerful polka dot motif symbolizes energy and happiness.
Source: adidas Originals. The Polka Dot Pack includes Stan Smith sneakers.
Launching in Southeast Asia on November 28th, the Polka Dot Pack features leather Stan Smith sneakers. This collection embodies the profound joy of love. The youthful and optimistic designs aim for a relatable and authentic feel, representing the collaboration&amp;rsquo;s core value.</description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius.</description></item></channel></rss>