<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brazil on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brazil/</link><description>Recent content in Brazil on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 04:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brazil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Should Brazil be considered a cyber security threat?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 04:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</guid><description>Cybercriminals frequently target major events like the Olympics to spread malware, and the 2016 Rio Games were no exception. While it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to stay vigilant against phishing attempts that exploit current events, a report from Fortinet, &amp;ldquo;FortiGuard Eye of the Storm,&amp;rdquo; highlights why the 2016 Olympics warranted particular concern.
Although cyberattacks at the Olympics are not a recent phenomenon, with incidents dating back to the 2004 Athens Games, Fortinet raised concerns about the Rio Games for two key reasons that could impact attendees and have a ripple effect on those back home:</description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats.</description></item><item><title>Is Free Movement in Europe Unusual? The Recent Open Borders Policy in South America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 01:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</guid><description>Dr Diego Acosta Arcarazo, Lecturer in Law at the University of Bristol, and member of the research project Prospects for International Migration Governance (MIGPROSP)
While the freedom of movement within the European Union (EU) faces criticism and limitations from certain political and media outlets, other areas of the globe, such as South America, are embracing similar systems. This highlights that the EU model isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual, contrary to some opinions. Examining these different regional approaches offers valuable insights for refining existing legislation and policies.</description></item><item><title>Before you decide to check out Ronaldo, reconsider your decision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</guid><description>A study by McAfee, a part of Intel Security, reveals that cybercriminals often use popular figures like Cristiano Ronaldo to lure unsuspecting users to malicious websites. These websites, designed to look like legitimate fan pages, can infect devices with malware capable of stealing personal information. McAfee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Red Card Club&amp;rdquo; list highlights the top eleven footballers whose names are most frequently used in these scams, with Ronaldo topping the list, followed by Lionel Messi and Iker Cassillas.</description></item></channel></rss>