<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Black Friday on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/black-friday/</link><description>Recent content in Black Friday on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 15:19:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/black-friday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It’s Free Phones Time For The Holidays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 15:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>The holiday season is about to start, and many people will rush to buy things like new smartphones. But before you spend a lot of money, consider getting a free phone.
You can find free phones by using a special search engine that focuses on phones offered for free when you sign up for a new service contract. You can find this search engine at Cell Phone Plan Finder.
You might think these free phones are outdated models.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Picking On Cyber Monday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</guid><description>Similar to how Black Friday has become a tradition for in-person shopping, Cyber Monday is now the time for finding exceptional online deals. With that in mind, let&amp;rsquo;s explore a standout product line this year: BlackBerry devices from Research in Motion.
Business users have long favored BlackBerry for mobile communication. RIM has prioritized supporting corporate IT with the performance and security needed for serious business use on the go. But how affordable are these popular BlackBerry models?</description></item><item><title>Cash In Old Gadgets To Buy New Gadgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 03:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</guid><description>The holiday shopping season is here, and with it comes the temptation of new electronics and gadgets. However, it&amp;rsquo;s also a time to be mindful of spending. One smart solution is to turn your old electronics into cash to fund those new purchases.
It&amp;rsquo;s common to have unused electronics lying around. We hesitate to discard them because they still hold value. This unused tech represents a potential savings account that can help you afford those tempting new gadgets.</description></item><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</guid><description>Wishing you a cozy and enjoyable Thanksgiving!
We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share a special Black Friday surprise with you tomorrow&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>MegaPath’s Black Friday Strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</guid><description>Black Friday, the day following Thanksgiving, is the traditional kickoff for Christmas shopping. Its success is crucial for retailers, as it can significantly impact their yearly profitability.
The term &amp;ldquo;Black Friday&amp;rdquo; is believed to originate from the accounting practice of using red ink for losses and black ink for profits. Many retailers struggle throughout the year, making the holiday shopping season, especially Black Friday, vital for their financial stability.
Black Friday, along with its online counterpart Cyber Monday (the Monday after Thanksgiving), initiates the busiest and most demanding sales period for retailers.</description></item></channel></rss>