<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CFSP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cfsp/</link><description>Recent content in CFSP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cfsp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Evaluation of the updated EU Council Guidelines on Freedom of Expression in both digital and physical spaces.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods from the University of Essex, and co-author of Steiner and Woods, EU Law, discusses new EU guidelines on freedom of expression.
The European Union Council recently established guidelines for freedom of expression. These guidelines, falling under the Foreign Affairs Council, are designed for application within the framework of the Union’s Common Foreign and Security Policy, similar to previous guidelines addressing issues like torture, capital punishment, and human rights advocates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Judicial oversight of suspected violations of fundamental rights in the execution of Eulex Kosovo and the Advocate General's Ćapeta's Opinion in Joined Cases C-29/22 P and C-44/22 P.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/</guid><description>Antje Kunst*
Photo credit: Sharon Hahn Darlin, via Wikimedia Commons
In a recent legal opinion, Advocate General Ćapeta addressed the question of whether individuals can sue the European Union for damages related to alleged fundamental rights violations during an EU mission. The case involved KS and KD, whose family members disappeared and were killed in Kosovo in 1999. They allege that Eulex Kosovo, an EU mission tasked with investigating such crimes, failed to adequately investigate their cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council needs to quickly establish a legal framework similar to the CEOS for employees working in CSDP missions: Analysis of the Jenkinson case (Case C-46/22 P)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</guid><description>Antje Kunst*
Photo credit: Jan-Tore Egge, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
In a January 18, 2024, ruling, the European Union Court of Justice dismissed an appeal by Irish citizen Mr. Jenkinson. This decision impacts thousands of individuals working in EU international missions governed by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). While the Court sided with the defendants (the Council, Commission, European External Action Service, and Eulex Kosovo), their victory is questionable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Council v H: Another Court victory in the Common Foreign and Security Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</guid><description>Graham Butler, PhD Fellow at the Centre for Comparative and European Constitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen, Denmark
Introduction
This summer, the Court of Justice (the Court) issued two significant decisions influencing the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) legal landscape. Despite the Treaty of Lisbon&amp;rsquo;s integration of this largely intergovernmental area (previously the Second Pillar) into the unified ‘EU’, its legacy persists. Enduring evidence of CFSP as a distinct yet incorporated legal domain allows it to be termed ‘CFSP law’...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is the appropriate response from the EU to the unlawful blocking of the Lachin corridor?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-appropriate-response-from-the-eu-to-the-unlawful-blocking-of-the-lachin-corridor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-appropriate-response-from-the-eu-to-the-unlawful-blocking-of-the-lachin-corridor/</guid><description>Nariné Ghazaryan, Assistant Professor in International and European Law, Radboud University Nijmegen
Photo credit: Alexander Naumov, via Wikimedia Commons
The 2020 Nagorno-Karabakh war ceasefire agreement, brokered by Russia, was seen with skepticism by close observers of the region. By mid-2021, attacks on Armenian territory made it evident that the ceasefire was unstable. This prompted the EU to take a leading role in peace negotiations between Armenia and Azerbaijan. This leadership involved high-profile mediation by European Council President Charles Michel, focusing on prisoner exchanges, discreet diplomatic initiatives, and a series of high-level trilateral meetings throughout 2021 and 2022...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-appropriate-response-from-the-eu-to-the-unlawful-blocking-of-the-lachin-corridor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-appropriate-response-from-the-eu-to-the-unlawful-blocking-of-the-lachin-corridor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon examine important legal matters related to EU sanctions against non-EU countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:46:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*
I recently attended a hearing at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning a case brought by Russian energy company Rosneft against EU sanctions imposed after Russia&amp;rsquo;s intervention in Crimea. The case, heard by the High Court of Justice (England &amp;amp; Wales), asks the CJEU to clarify the legitimacy of several aspects of these EU sanctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice in Bank Refah Kargaran making a groundbreaking decision by allowing action for damages in relation to CFSP decisions regarding restrictive measures?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</guid><description>Professor Dr. Peter Van Elsuwege and Joyce De Coninck (PhD Researcher), Ghent European Law Institute
The recent Grand Chamber judgment in the case of Bank Refah Kargaran v Council, issued on October 6, 2020, sheds further light on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) jurisdiction concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). Drawing on previous judgments such as Elitaliana, H v. Council, Rosneft, and SatCen vs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Continuing the saga of EU/Armenia relations with Case C-180/20 Commission v Council (CEPA) and the 'centre of gravity' test in the CFSP.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</guid><description>Narine Ghazaryan, Assistant Professor in EU and International Law, Radboud University Nijmegen
Photo credit: Jesper Ahlin Marceta via Wikicommons
Introduction
The recent ruling in Case C-180/20 (the CEPA case) marks a new chapter in the ongoing debate about the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) and its boundaries. This case saw the Commission challenge the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to deviate from a proposed Council Decision concerning the EU-Armenian Comprehensive and Enhanced Partnership Agreement (CEPA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can a third state legally challenge EU restrictive measures? The Court of Justice says 'yes'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-third-state-legally-challenge-eu-restrictive-measures-the-court-of-justice-says-yes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 07:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-third-state-legally-challenge-eu-restrictive-measures-the-court-of-justice-says-yes/</guid><description>Francesca Finelli, PhD student, University of Luxembourg
In the legal case Venezuela v Council (C-872/19 P), the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) reversed a prior General Court decision. It determined that Venezuela has the right to legally challenge EU sanctions imposed against it. This judgment is groundbreaking as it allows any third-party country facing EU economic sanctions to challenge them in EU courts, a precedent not previously established...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-third-state-legally-challenge-eu-restrictive-measures-the-court-of-justice-says-yes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-third-state-legally-challenge-eu-restrictive-measures-the-court-of-justice-says-yes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU guarantees the fundamental democratic and judicial oversight of the EU's foreign policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirmed in its recent decision in European Parliament v Council that the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) is subject to a minimum standard of democratic and judicial oversight.
The case involved a challenge by the European Parliament (EP) to the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign and ratify a treaty between the EU and Mauritius. This treaty pertained to the EU&amp;rsquo;s military operations against pirates operating in the Indian Ocean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Could the EU be considering the formation of a military force, and would the UK have the power to block it?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent discussions have centered around whether the EU is forming an army and if the UK has the power to veto such a move before Brexit. This debate, while heated, often lacks clarity. This piece aims to provide a clear understanding of the situation, concluding that the recent proposals don&amp;rsquo;t constitute an EU army, making a UK veto irrelevant.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy initially avoided defense matters, respecting Irish neutrality and the UK&amp;rsquo;s commitment to NATO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there another accountability gap with the European Peace Facility?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</guid><description>Ellen Cantraine, PhD researcher, Ghent European Law Institute
Photo credit: Dietmar Rabich / Wikimedia Commons / “Münster, Stadtweinhaus, Beflaggung Ukraine und EU &amp;ndash; 2022 &amp;ndash; 0219” / CC BY-SA 4.0 / see also
Introduction
Following the 2021 coup attempt in Mali, the EU&amp;rsquo;s mission in Mali (EUTM) continued operating despite concerning reports of serious misconduct by EU-trained soldiers. Funded by the European Peace Facility (EPF), EUTM&amp;rsquo;s case exposed significant flaws in the EU&amp;rsquo;s external funding mechanisms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What authority should the Court of Justice have in EU Foreign Policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Luigi Lonardo, PhD student, King’s College London
Article 24(1) of the Treaty on the European Union states that the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) operates under distinct rules and procedures, explicitly stating that the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) holds no jurisdiction over these provisions.
Legal experts are debating whether &amp;ldquo;the CJEU shall not have jurisdiction&amp;rdquo; implies a degree of jurisdiction. AG Wahl articulated this question: Does the exclusion of CJEU jurisdiction encompass all CFSP actions or only specific categories?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU foreign policy sanctions: utilizing EU criminal law powers to extend and enforce them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 02:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post draws upon research for the forthcoming 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law (OUP, 2023)
The EU Council recently decided to expand its criminal law authority to encompass breaches of EU foreign policy sanctions. Following this, the EU Commission presented a proposal for a Directive that aims to utilize this expanded authority to harmonize the criminal laws of Member States on this subject...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmonisation of criminal law and foreign policy sanctions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post builds on and updates research for the 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law(OUP, 2023)
In late 2023, EU Member States and the European Parliament reached an agreement on a Directive designed to standardize criminal law related to violations of EU foreign policy sanctions. (Update: The Directive was formally adopted in April 2024 and subsequently published in the EU Official Journal)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmonisation-of-criminal-law-and-foreign-policy-sanctions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Global Court? The European Court of Justice's Ruling in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-global-court-the-european-court-of-justice-s-ruling-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-global-court-the-european-court-of-justice-s-ruling-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti* and Alina Carrozzini**
*Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
**MPhil/PhD Candidate, Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London. Email: alina.carrozzini@kcl.ac.uk
A June 22, 2021, ruling by the Grand Chamber of the Court of Justice determined that Venezuela can legally challenge a set of European Union restrictive measures if it meets the remaining conditions outlined in Article 263 (4) TFEU. (Previous analyses of this judgment can be found here and here)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-global-court-the-european-court-of-justice-s-ruling-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-global-court-the-european-court-of-justice-s-ruling-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>