<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cx/</link><description>Recent content in CX on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever.</description></item><item><title>In 2024, 80% of service professionals in Singapore anticipate that customer service will play a larger role in generating revenue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</guid><description>A recent Salesforce report highlights the growing expectation for customer service to become a significant revenue driver in 2024. The report suggests that AI-powered personalized customer experiences empower service teams to capitalize on upselling, cross-selling, and customer retention to boost revenue.
This new &amp;ldquo;State of Service&amp;rdquo; report is based on insights from over 5,500 service professionals globally, including 100 from Singapore. It examines current trends, challenges, and strategies shaping the customer service landscape, emphasizing how service teams utilize AI and data to enhance revenue, efficiency, and customer satisfaction amidst rising customer expectations.</description></item></channel></rss>