<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Initial Assessment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/initial-assessment/</link><description>Recent content in Initial Assessment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 11:00:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/initial-assessment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Initial Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-initial-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-initial-assessment/</guid><description>This Beogram 8002 turntable, sent from California, is the next restoration project. I prefer working on the same type of audio equipment consecutively because it minimizes workbench setup time.
The owner followed our packing advice and packaged the turntable very well, using double boxes and protective foam. The turntable arrived without damage.
Upon opening, I noticed the metal tonearm lid wouldn&amp;rsquo;t stay up. The part that connects to the hinge with damping grease was detached, a problem I haven&amp;rsquo;t encountered before.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: Initial assessment of another Beosystem 5000 companion component.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-initial-assessment-of-another-beosystem-5000-companion-component/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-initial-assessment-of-another-beosystem-5000-companion-component/</guid><description>This Beocord 5000 is the second cassette deck from Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen to bear this name. The original Beocord 5000, a Type 47xx model, was manufactured in the late 1970s. While distinct, both are high-quality cassette decks.
[Image]
[Image]
The Beocord 5000 Type 4923 aligns with the Beomaster 5000 Type 2323 and the CD50 Beosystem 5000 components in terms of size and design. Control and display access are provided both on the front panel and through a master remote control.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Initial Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-initial-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-initial-assessment/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, dropped off by its long-time owner, appears to have been well-maintained.
The control panel buttons show typical wear from use, but the dust cover is in good condition with only minor marks. The tonearm requires adjustment as it sits too low when the turntable is not in use.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s interior is very clean, suggesting it was kept in a good environment.
The original washers for the floating suspension lock-down are intact.</description></item></channel></rss>