<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Grounding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grounding/</link><description>Recent content in Grounding on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grounding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Original DIN5 Plug with a Modern All-Metal Gold Plated Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</guid><description>To fully restore a 4002, replacing the often corroded DIN5 connector is essential. The delicate low-voltage signals need optimal contact. Gold is an ideal material due to its resistance to oxidation, ensuring a strong and long-lasting connection. The pictures illustrate this process, showing the old connector&amp;rsquo;s condition, preparing the cable for the new connector, the soldering process, and finally, the pristine new gold-plated connector installed. This upgrade is a significant step towards bringing the Beogram back to its former glory.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Installation of a New DIN5 Plug With Gold Coated Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration is coming along nicely. I believe a key part of revitalizing these turntables is installing a new, all-metal DIN 5 plug with gold-plated contacts. The old plugs often suffer from corrosion, which hinders the delicate signal transfer from the MMC cartridge. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the old plug with tarnished terminals:
This image showcases the soldering work within the updated plug:
And finally, the finished product:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adding a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adding-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adding-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a significant hum became apparent when connected to a Beomaster 6000 amplifier. This was unexpected, as a Beogram 4002 with the same grounding design showed no such issue. The only identifiable difference between the two models was the unshielded mains transformer in the 4000, unlike the shielded transformers in later models. While the relevance of this difference was unclear, it appeared to be the only variable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of a New All-Metal DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Contacts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</guid><description>I believe that any restoration of a Beogram 4002 isn&amp;rsquo;t truly finished until the old output plugs, which are often corroded, are replaced with modern, all-metal ones featuring gold-plated terminals. High-quality analog signals deserve the best possible connections. Here are some photos documenting the DIN5 plug replacement I completed on a Beogram 4002 (5503) restoration:
The original DIN5 plug is shown here:
This photo shows the &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; soldering work:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Upgrade of Signal Path with New DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The DIN5 plug on the Beogram 4000 being restored was heavily oxidized and needed replacement. A new, fully metal plug with gold-plated terminals was installed.
To improve the signal output, a switch was added to connect the signal and system grounds. This feature is beneficial when using a DIN5 to RCA adapter, as RCA cables lack a system ground. Connecting the system ground to the signal ground on the Beogram can reduce humming.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Gold Coated DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4000 is progressing well. I&amp;rsquo;ve added a grounding switch and a new gold-plated Neutrik DIN5 plug. The switch allows users to choose between the grounding setup of the older 4000/4002 models (separate signal and system grounds) and the later 4004 models (combined grounds). This option helps prevent ground loops and the resulting humming, depending on the amplifier being used. I wrote a detailed post on this topic a while back.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the DIN 5 Cable with a Cable Featuring RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-din-5-cable-with-a-cable-featuring-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 05:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-din-5-cable-with-a-cable-featuring-rca-plugs/</guid><description>I am rebuilding a Beogram 4002(5513) turntable to use with a McIntosh Preamplifier. The standard DIN5 connector on Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen equipment is incompatible, so I am replacing it with RCA connectors for the best shielding and lowest EMI. Direct installation inside the turntable offers superior performance compared to adapters.
For optimal sound, I chose high-quality, open-ended RCA cables from Sounds Heavenly in the UK. These cables feature individually shielded, twisted-pair left and right channels, embodying an &amp;ldquo;audiophile&amp;rdquo; design.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Bent System Ground Terminal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-bent-system-ground-terminal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:31:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-bent-system-ground-terminal/</guid><description>Following the installation of my newly designed BeoloverRIAA pre-amplifier into a recently restored Beogram 4002, I prepared to reassemble the casing. As I was about to secure the hood, I discovered the system ground terminal on the rear panel was severely bent and damaged.
The damage to the threads from rust and deformation prevented the nut&amp;rsquo;s removal. I was forced to cut the bolt off. Once removed, I replaced it with a new 3mm bolt and used appropriate insulating shoulder washers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Grounding Switch That Allows to Connect System and Signal Grounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</guid><description>During my latest restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I encountered a loud hum when playing records through my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s 4-channel phono input. The issue was resolved by connecting the signal and system grounds. Although the root cause of the hum remains unclear, I decided to install a switch to allow for easy toggling between the original separate grounding configuration and a direct connection between signal and system grounds at the turntable&amp;rsquo;s output.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Corroded RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 04:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) currently under restoration was equipped with RCA plugs and a grounding wire instead of the typical DIN 5 connector. The plugs and grounding terminal were noticeably dirty and corroded.
The RCA plugs were switched out for all-metal gold-plated ones, and a new grounding terminal was installed.
These compact RCA plugs lack color coding, so 3D-printed inserts were created. These inserts enclose the back of the plugs and provide a visual distinction between the left and right channels.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New DIN 5 Plug and Installation of a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:48:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a severely corroded and improperly installed DIN 5 plug, clearly not the original. The attached photos illustrate its poor condition.
One of the pictures highlights a loose black wire, potentially a makeshift attempt to address humming issues (unsurprising given the plug&amp;rsquo;s installation). Adding to the problem, a poorly executed soldering job had left one of the signal leads disconnected.
I removed the old plug and prepared the wires for a new one, as shown in the photo.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Pins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</guid><description>A gold-plated plug is the finishing touch for a fully restored signal path. Here&amp;rsquo;s the process on a Beogram 4002(5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on:
Above is the original plug in rough shape due to oxidation.
The new Rean plug offers a neat and tidy internal layout.
Placing the metal enclosure back results in an even more visually appealing look. That&amp;rsquo;s the Beolove!</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board and Adding a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>During the Beogram 4002 restoration, I took the opportunity to rebuild the output board while cleaning the keypad contacts. A common issue with these units is low or absent volume in one or both channels, often caused by the output relay. To address this, I replaced it with a modern, durable Japanese relay designed to last for many years. The original output board is shown here:
The old Siemens relay was swapped out for a custom-designed SMD relay assembly, pictured below:</description></item></channel></rss>