<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wavelength Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wavelength-services/</link><description>Recent content in Wavelength Services on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wavelength-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Gigabit Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Metropolitan and wide area networks are getting faster. Undersea cables are moving from 10 to 40 and even 100 Gbps, and land-based fiber lines are already at 100 Gbps. This means large companies, healthcare organizations, and video producers are starting to find their networks inadequate. The good news is that there are more affordable options than ever before.
There are several practical ways to boost your MAN or WAN bandwidth beyond one Gigabit per second, up to 10 Gbps.</description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity.</description></item><item><title>40 Gbps Bandwidth Available For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</guid><description>XO Communications has increased business bandwidth options by offering two 40 Gbps network services across its nationwide fiber optic network. Randy Nicklas, XO Communications&amp;rsquo; CTO, highlights the advantages of these new 40 Gbps services:
You can listen to the interview directly on this page:
Clearly, we&amp;rsquo;re entering a new era of high-bandwidth applications for businesses and service providers like cable companies. High-speed financial trading needs the fastest speeds, with even milliseconds of delay impacting outcomes.</description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers.</description></item><item><title>Improve Cloud Performance With Direct Network Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many companies are experiencing buyer&amp;rsquo;s remorse after transitioning to the cloud. They expected cost savings, increased performance, and limitless resources, but instead, they&amp;rsquo;re facing performance issues. The problem likely isn&amp;rsquo;t the cloud service itself, but the connection used to access it.
While your current internet connection might be sufficient for tasks like file transfers and email, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for real-time applications like VoIP, video conferencing, or cloud-based software.</description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services For The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</guid><description>Initially only utilized by telecom companies, wavelength services are now accessible to large organizations. These high-bandwidth fiber optic services are necessary for entities like hospitals, financial institutions, government service providers, video production companies, content delivery networks, and research facilities. The demand for faster data transfer solutions is constantly increasing. But are wavelength services the answer?
A wavelength, or lambda, is light at a specific frequency, similar to a distinct color. It is usually measured in nanometers (wavelength) rather than terabits per second (frequency).</description></item><item><title>Eastern Tennessee Gets Lit for Business Fiber Optic Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 09:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</guid><description>Nashville, Tennessee, is known for its robust fiber optic network infrastructure. The city&amp;rsquo;s thriving business sector, particularly in healthcare, publishing, banking, transportation, and music, demands high bandwidth, a need that extends across the state.
EarthLink, a leading bandwidth provider, has recently expanded its fiber optic network in eastern Tennessee. The project includes a 343-mile route connecting Nashville to Knoxville, with additional routes linking Knoxville to Chattanooga and Bristol. This network offers connection points in multiple cities, including Cookeville, Oak Ridge, and Cleveland, and major Points of Presence (PoPs) in Knoxville, Morristown, Johnson City, and Bristol.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet and Colocation For Texas Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</guid><description>Texas is known for its expansive size, thriving businesses, massive data generation, and a critical need for extensive bandwidth. Alpheus, a Texas-based telecommunications company, is acutely aware of these needs and caters its services to businesses across various sectors including finance, energy, government, healthcare, IT, legal, and media.
Headquartered in Houston, Alpheus boasts a robust fiber optic network that interconnects major Texan cities like Dallas, Fort Worth, Waco, Bryan, Austin, San Antonio, Laredo, McAllen, Harlingen, Corpus Christi, Victoria, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>When your business or applications need more bandwidth than T1 lines can offer, even multiple bonded ones, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider fiber optic solutions. But with various options available, how do you choose?
Traditionally, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was the primary fiber optic bandwidth option, pioneered by phone companies. SONET surpasses T-Carrier technology (T1 and T3 lines). While T1 provides 1.5 Mbps over copper and T3 offers 45 Mbps over coaxial cable, SONET scales up to OC-1, OC-3, OC-12, OC-24, OC-48, OC-192, OC-256, and OC-768.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item></channel></rss>