<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mechanism on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mechanism/</link><description>Recent content in Mechanism on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mechanism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): Removing the Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Note: This post documents an outdated method. There&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way to remove the drive that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve lifting the Pre-Amplifier board or disconnecting the solenoid linkage. See my later post for the updated procedure.
Following advice from &amp;lsquo;chartz&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;sonavor&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org (link to thread), I began replacing the belts in my Beocord 5000 (4716), which had become loose and stretched over time.
The first step is removing the drive mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Extraction of Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 12:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Having restored a Beocord 5000 before, I&amp;rsquo;ve refined the process of removing the tape mechanism, simplifying the steps from my previous post and video.
I began by removing the plexiglass cover for polishing, which provided better access to the tape mechanism. To prepare for a full recap, I also lifted the preamplifier and radio amplifier boards. The photo shows the unit opened up:
&amp;lsquo;Chartz&amp;rsquo; from Beoworld.org suggested leaving the solenoid in place during removal, which led me to realize that even loosening the solenoid fixture is unnecessary.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Exchanging the Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 12:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</guid><description>After removing the tape mechanism from the Beocord 5000 (4715) for rebuilding, I replaced the old, worn-out belts. My process was largely based on the one shown in my YouTube video.
However, I made one key improvement. I learned that the eject lever&amp;rsquo;s alignment with the tape mechanism is vital for the eject key to function correctly after reassembly. Previously, I had only marked the position of part #256 (&amp;ldquo;lever&amp;rdquo;) with a pencil, leading to time-consuming readjustments.</description></item></channel></rss>