<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Preliminary Rulings on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/preliminary-rulings/</link><description>Recent content in Preliminary Rulings on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:47:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/preliminary-rulings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Deceptive Client: The case that confused the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
John Grisham&amp;rsquo;s novels often feature a recurring theme: a determined but outmatched lawyer battling a powerful corporation that exploits the legal system, a vulnerable client harmed by the corporation, a polished corporate law firm doing the company&amp;rsquo;s bidding, and an eccentric judge striving for courtroom order. This formula has been a mainstay of his books for over two decades. However, the settings rarely venture beyond the Southern United States, except for occasional plot-driven trips to Caribbean islands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Putting an end to Brexit? Explaining the Wightman case on reversing the Article 50 notification independently.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
As the deadline for Brexit approaches and Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s conflicting negotiating goals become clearer, there are increasing demands for transparency regarding the Brexit process.
In late 2017, seven Scottish politicians from different parties and legislative bodies in Scotland (the Scottish Parliament, the UK Parliament, and the European Parliament) initiated a legal case in the Scottish Court of Session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The request for a preliminary ruling from the Polish Supreme Court on 2 August 2018 and its implications for the rule of law in Poland: A commentary on the CJEU's involvement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</guid><description>Alicja Sikora, Chair EU Law, Jagiellonian University
As the playwright Eugene Ionesco once said, predictions are only possible after events have occurred.
Last Thursday, the Polish Supreme Court presented the European Court of Justice with a request for a preliminary ruling. This type of request, outlined in Article 267 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, is used to clarify questions regarding EU law. In doing so, the Polish court also paused the enforcement of a Polish law mandating early retirement for Supreme Court justices over 65...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon examine important legal matters related to EU sanctions against non-EU countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:46:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*
I recently attended a hearing at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning a case brought by Russian energy company Rosneft against EU sanctions imposed after Russia&amp;rsquo;s intervention in Crimea. The case, heard by the High Court of Justice (England &amp;amp; Wales), asks the CJEU to clarify the legitimacy of several aspects of these EU sanctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-will-soon-examine-important-legal-matters-related-to-eu-sanctions-against-non-eu-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Luxembourg Court providing assistance in preliminary references and investment tribunals?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-luxembourg-court-providing-assistance-in-preliminary-references-and-investment-tribunals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:41:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-luxembourg-court-providing-assistance-in-preliminary-references-and-investment-tribunals/</guid><description>Hannes Lenk, PhD Candidate at the University of Gothenburg
The connection between arbitral tribunals and the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been a source of legal debate for many years. While the present situation is straightforward and practical, it is not without controversy. Commercial arbitration tribunals are not seen as &amp;ldquo;courts or tribunals of a Member State&amp;rdquo; as defined by Article 267 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-luxembourg-court-providing-assistance-in-preliminary-references-and-investment-tribunals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-luxembourg-court-providing-assistance-in-preliminary-references-and-investment-tribunals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the case of Schipani v Italy, under what circumstances is it necessary for national courts to seek guidance from the CJEU as per the ECHR?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo; (ECHR) judgment in the Schipani vs. Italy case, issued on July 21, 2015, revisited a topic of significant interest to EU legal experts: the violation of the ECHR by a national court due to its failure to request a preliminary ruling. This judgment, released just before the summer break, might have slipped under the radar for some...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Commentary on Arlewin v. Sweden: Libel Law, EU Law, and the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 02:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</guid><description>Athanassios Takis: PhD, Special Adviser to General Secretariat of Greek government
The European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruling of March 1, 2016, in the case of Arlewin v. Sweden examined how EU Regulation 44/2001, which decides which Member State&amp;rsquo;s courts hold jurisdiction over civil and commercial disputes, was used (or misused) by Swedish courts. This case highlighted the limitations of the &amp;lsquo;acte clair&amp;rsquo; doctrine – the idea that national courts don&amp;rsquo;t always need to consult the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on EU law matters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>