<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2014/41 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2014/41/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2014/41 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2014/41/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU missed an opportunity to address mass hacking and fundamental rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Hugo Partouche, a Paris Bar Attorney-at-law (avocat), and Chloé Berthélémy, a Senior Policy Advisor at EDRi, collaborated on this piece.
Photo credit: hacker-silhoutte, via Wikimedia commons
*This article initially appeared in French in Actualité Juridique (AJ) Pénal, Dalloz Revues. You can find it here.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on the ‘EncroChat’ case on April 30, 2024.
This case arose from large-scale European police operations targeting organized crime.</description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition.</description></item></channel></rss>