<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Constitutional Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/constitutional-law/</link><description>Recent content in Constitutional Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:11:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/constitutional-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beware of the Accountability Gap in the EU's Financial Supervisory Authorities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City Law School
The year 2010 saw the creation of three European Supervisory Authorities: the European Banking Authority, the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority, and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA). These authorities were established by the European Union in response to the then-unprecedented financial crisis. On January 22, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant judgment (Case C-270/12, United Kingdom v Council &amp;amp; Parliament) concerning recent legislation granting ESMA the authority to impose legally binding measures on financial institutions in Member States when the proper functioning of financial markets or the stability of the EU financial system is threatened...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Divergent rulings on Parliament's suspension in England and Scotland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The A-Z of Scots Law: From Avizandum to the Zany Antics of Boris Johnson
Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s recent actions are under scrutiny by the Scottish legal system. In the Cherry case, the Scottish court deemed the decision to suspend Parliament unlawful. Further legal action is anticipated regarding the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s reported refusal to adhere to the European Union (Withdrawal) (No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Arrest Warrant and the German Constitutional Court: A new development in the legal conversation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The German Constitutional Court (GCC) has issued another impactful ruling, this time concerning fundamental rights. In an order published yesterday, the GCC exercised its authority to review the implementation of a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) from Italy to Germany. The subject, a US citizen convicted in Italy in absentia, argued that his conviction lacked due process and that Italian law provided no recourse for appeal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Constitutional Conflict in the European Union: A Jurisprudential Analysis (OUP 2022)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</guid><description>Ana Bobić, Law Clerk at the Court of Justice of the European Union
Photo credit: Antoine Montulé, via Wikicommons
It has been almost 60 years since the Court of Justice established that EU law takes precedence. However, this principle still sparks discussions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s constitutional system. Initially, the integration of EU law into national legal frameworks caused tension between the Court of Justice and national constitutional courts. The Court of Justice believes strongly in the importance of EU law&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness and expects all national courts to share this view...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>