<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Women on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/women/</link><description>Recent content in Women on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS).</description></item><item><title>Reconsidering Gender-Based Asylum: Examining the Advocate General's Perspective on Female Refugees Escaping the Taliban</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand (Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law) and Salvo Nicolosi (Senior Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law)
Photo credit: USAIDAfghanistan, via Wikimedia Commons
A central question in international refugee law is whether women can qualify for refugee status based solely on their gender. This debate recently reached the Court of Justice through two connected cases, AH and FN, concerning women seeking asylum. Advocate General Richard de la Tour issued his opinion on these cases on November 9, 2023.</description></item><item><title>The Stevie Awards for Women in Business welcome participants and organizations from all around the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</guid><description>The Stevie Awards, a leading business awards organization, is accepting entries for the 2020 Stevie Awards for Women in Business. This global competition is open to all female entrepreneurs, executives, and employees, as well as the organizations they lead.
The Stevie Awards recognize exceptional workplace achievements worldwide across various organizations. The Stevie Awards for Women in Business specifically honor the accomplishments of working women in over 100 categories, such as Entrepreneur of the Year, Executive of the Year, and Innovator of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Advancing Gender-Sensitive EU Asylum Law: Examining the Situation of 'Westernised Women'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand, Assistant Professor, and Salvo Nicolosi, Senior Assistant Professor, University of Utrecht
Photo credit: Mystslav Chernov, via Wikimedia Commons
Recent developments in EU law show a growing recognition of gender-based asylum claims. A notable example is the June 11, 2024, judgment by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of K, L v Staatssecretaris van Justitie en Veiligheid. This case, concerning two Iraqi sisters seeking asylum in the Netherlands, centers around interpreting &amp;ldquo;membership of a particular social group&amp;rdquo; within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, specifically regarding &amp;ldquo;westernized women&amp;rdquo; who fear persecution upon returning to their home countries.</description></item><item><title>The Women in Business Asia Pageant hosts a workshop on digital marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</guid><description>Source: Women in Business Asia Pageant Facebook page.
To empower women entrepreneurs, the Women in Business Asia Pageant is holding a masterclass on digital marketing and social media strategies specifically for women in Singapore.
The session, titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Marketing and Social Media Hacks for Women in Business,&amp;rdquo; will run for one hour and teach participants how to build an effective, business-oriented website designed to generate leads. Attendees will discover how to incorporate both original and curated content into their marketing plans.</description></item><item><title>Benetton will concentrate on empowering women through their new collection, A Collection of Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</guid><description>The idea that women sharing their experiences and learning from each other is crucial for creating a brighter future is the driving force behind A Collection Of Us. This new United Colors of Benetton collection, launching in four parts throughout October 2015, December 2015, February 2016, and April 2016, embodies this philosophy.
Each capsule within the collection reimagines a core aspect of Benetton&amp;rsquo;s brand identity—heritage, technique, color, and performance—giving it a fresh and modern significance.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 in Singapore have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</guid><description>Source: The Ascendas-Singbridge Group. From left: Ho Kheng Lian, Venture Partner, Vectr Ventures; Natalie Loh, Vice President of Products, Vanitee; Kuik Xiao Shi, Co-Founder, Vanitee; Pocket Sun, Founding Partner of SoGal Ventures; Adrianna Tan, Founder, Wobe; Virginia Tan, Co-founder and Managing Director of Lean In China; Adeline Quek, Head of Regional Business Development, Grabtaxi; Mrs Nina Yang, Chief Operating Officer of Singbridge.
The Ascendas-Singbridge Group selected two startups from Singapore to compete in the finals of the Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 competition.</description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia honors female entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, marked International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day on March 8, 2017, by recognizing the achievements of women.
This year&amp;rsquo;s International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day centers around empowering women globally and inspiring them to make bold moves. Shopee Malaysia honored this theme by highlighting the stories of women entrepreneurs who took a leap of faith to launch their own ventures. The platform&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly design, free nationwide shipping, and zero-commission fees are designed to encourage more women to tap into their potential as leaders and business owners.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area.</description></item><item><title>The Dream Collective is empowering potential female leaders in Singapore with their first-ever bootcamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</guid><description>Source: The Dream Collective.
The Dream Collective, a global platform for training women in corporate leadership, has introduced the Emerging Leaders Bootcamp - Singapore Edition. This program offers a new approach to female empowerment and initiates a crucial conversation about developing female leadership talent in the corporate world. Modeled after MBA programs from top business schools, the program collaborates with major corporations to find, develop, and empower high-potential young women with leadership skills.</description></item><item><title>Today is International Women's Day: can you help create the future? #MakeWhatsNext</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft blog. Ada Lovelace was the world&amp;rsquo;s first computer programmer.
In honor of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day, a global celebration of the achievements of women, Microsoft is encouraging girls around the world to pursue careers in STEM fields with their #MakeWhatsNext campaign.
According to the World Economic Forum, the gender gap won&amp;rsquo;t close until 2133. This gap is especially prominent in computer science and STEM fields. Dr. Daiana Beitler, Microsoft Philanthropies Lead for Asia, notes in a blog post that the Asian Development Bank found women in the region are 70% less likely to be employed than men.</description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has received the Women Entrepreneur City Blueprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-received-the-women-entrepreneur-city-blueprint/</guid><description>Source: Dell SlideShare. Cover slide for the deck introducing the Dell 2018 Women Entrepreneur Cities Study.
At the 9th annual Dell Women Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN) in Toronto, Canada, Dell introduced new analytical resources for local governments and policymakers. These tools are intended to support the success of female entrepreneurs.
Based on the findings of the 2017 Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, Dell, in partnership with research firm IHS Markit, conducted in-depth analyses.</description></item><item><title>Singapore ranked among the top five in the 2016 WE Cities Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</guid><description>Dell has identified the top 25 cities worldwide that cultivate high-potential women entrepreneurs (HPWE) for 2016 through their Women Entrepreneur Cities Index (WE Cities). This unique index assesses a city&amp;rsquo;s capacity to attract and promote the growth of women-led businesses. The study focused on cities rather than countries to highlight how local policies and initiatives impact women entrepreneurs, in addition to national legislation and norms.
The WE Cities findings will serve as a starting point for discussions at the seventh annual Dell Women’s Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN).</description></item><item><title>The increasing involvement of women in commerce and industry in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) in the Philippines has reported a rise in the number of women participating in skills training programs for traditionally male-dominated fields.
Amelito Cardenas, a supervising specialist at TESDA Pangasinan, mentioned that more women are enrolling in technical-vocational (tech-voc) and private institutions to learn trades such as welding and automotive repair, as reported by the Philippines Information Agency.
Cardenas also shared that TESDA offers a free training program specifically for women who run sari-sari stores and carinderia.</description></item><item><title>The Fall/Winter 2015 Collections have been launched by CH Carolina Herrera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</guid><description>CH, a subsidiary brand under the Carolina Herrera fashion house, has launched their Fall/Winter 2015 collections for both men and women. The Women’s Collection uses vibrant pops of color like reds, sky blues, and fuchsias, which stand out against a darker color scheme with white and ivory accents.
Formal evening wear is designed using luxurious fabrics like silks, lace, and jacquard. The feminine looks are completed with signature CH Carolina Herrera details like bows and ruffles.</description></item><item><title>Female entrepreneurs need more than just determination to succeed, according to Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</guid><description>The first Mastercard Index of Women Entrepreneurs reveals that strong support systems, such as easy access to financial services and a business-friendly environment, are crucial for women-owned businesses to succeed. These enabling factors are essential in overcoming the two biggest hurdles women face in entrepreneurship: cultural bias and limited opportunities for advancement.
Developed economies lead the index, with New Zealand (74.4), Canada (72.4), and the US (69.9) claiming the top spots.</description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued.</description></item><item><title>The Great Women Connect Series begins with Great Women Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Great Women Malaysia. Puan Nadira Yusoff.
The Great Women Connect Series debuted today in Malaysia. This new program seeks to provide a space for women in business worldwide to connect and exchange ideas and experiences related to trade. It also aims to foster international partnerships, helping women, especially those in Malaysia, build networks and realize their full potential.
Great Women Malaysia (GMW) is an initiative that strives to empower Malaysian women, particularly those in underserved and rural areas.</description></item></channel></rss>