<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Parliament on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/parliament/</link><description>Recent content in Parliament on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:32:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/parliament/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The UK Supreme Court Justices: Defenders Against Anti-democratic Demagogues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-supreme-court-justices-defenders-against-anti-democratic-demagogues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-supreme-court-justices-defenders-against-anti-democratic-demagogues/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The Cherry/Miller case concluded with the significant ruling that Prime Minister Johnson&amp;rsquo;s prorogation of Parliament was unlawful. This decision, delivered unanimously, declared the prorogation legally void, effectively awakening Parliament from an illegal slumber.
This timely judgment allows for the illustration of constitutional law principles through current events. Law students will benefit from the numerous analyses and discussions surrounding this significant case.</description></item><item><title>Divergent rulings on Parliament's suspension in England and Scotland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The A-Z of Scots Law: From Avizandum to the Zany Antics of Boris Johnson
Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s recent actions are under scrutiny by the Scottish legal system. In the Cherry case, the Scottish court deemed the decision to suspend Parliament unlawful. Further legal action is anticipated regarding the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s reported refusal to adhere to the European Union (Withdrawal) (No.</description></item></channel></rss>