<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Election on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/election/</link><description>Recent content in Election on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:23:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bankers in the APAC region predict a decrease in M&amp;A activity under President Trump's administration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</guid><description>A recent survey of 300 Asia Pacific mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) professionals conducted by Intralinks, a secure platform used by dealmakers for content sharing, found that 75% of respondents believe a potential presidency under Donald Trump would negatively impact M&amp;amp;A activity in the region. This mirrors the global sentiment revealed by Intralinks&amp;rsquo; survey of 1,500 M&amp;amp;A professionals worldwide.
Intralinks&amp;rsquo; Global M&amp;amp;A Sentiment Survey shows 75% of Asian dealmakers consider Trump the most detrimental presidential candidate for M&amp;amp;A activity.</description></item><item><title>Intralinks APAC respondents predict that waves in China will have an impact on M&amp;A</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</guid><description>Dealmakers in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region believe that China&amp;rsquo;s economic and market activity will be the biggest influence on mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in the region over the coming six months.
This insight comes from a survey of over 1,600 global M&amp;amp;A professionals conducted by Intralinks, a leading provider of M&amp;amp;A deal management and secure collaboration solutions. The survey, conducted between October 4 and 11, 2016, gathered responses from dealmakers across APAC, Europe, the Middle East and Africa, North America, and Latin America.</description></item></channel></rss>