<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2004/83 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2004/83/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2004/83 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:38:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2004/83/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mixed messages are being sent by the CJEU regarding LGBTI asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many nations have severe punishments for individuals identifying as LGBTI, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recognizes persecution based on sexual orientation as grounds for asylum in the EU. This protection falls under the &amp;lsquo;particular social group&amp;rsquo; category within the EU&amp;rsquo;s qualification Directive.
The CJEU has previously clarified that individuals seeking asylum on the basis of sexual orientation are not required to conceal their sexual orientation in their home country.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's responses to the Iraq war and EU asylum law are uncertain.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Almost twelve years after it began, the Iraq war remains a point of contention, with many believing Tony Blair and George W. Bush initiated an unlawful conflict. These critics believe only a trial for war crimes for both Bush and Blair would be a satisfactory outcome. While I believe this may happen someday, it would require a jury of highly improbable individuals. (Perhaps those individuals disappeared alongside the supposed weapons of mass destruction).</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees.</description></item></channel></rss>