<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thailand on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/thailand/</link><description>Recent content in Thailand on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/thailand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The World Bank has released its 2017 forecast for the Thai economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</guid><description>The 2016 Thailand Economic Monitor, published today by the World Bank, projects Thailand&amp;rsquo;s economic growth to reach 3.1% in 2016 and 3.2% in 2017, surpassing the previous year&amp;rsquo;s 2.8%.
The report identifies private consumption and public investments, such as rail infrastructure projects, as primary growth drivers. Tourism has also performed well in 2016, with tourist arrivals, particularly from China, rising by 13.1% in the third quarter. A temporary slowdown and economic inactivity following the passing of HM King Bhumibol Adulyadej in October are anticipated to be partially counterbalanced by year-end holiday tax incentives for shopping and domestic tourism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-has-released-its-2017-forecast-for-the-thai-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers award in Thailand for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</guid><description>Leading employers in Thailand boast engagement scores that are 24 points higher than the average company. This trend is particularly noticeable among Gen Y employees (born between 1979 and 1990), who report engagement levels 22 points higher when working for a top employer. A striking 89% of employees at these leading companies would recommend their workplace to job seekers, significantly surpassing the 68% market average. Among the top performers, Advanced Info Services earned the distinguished title of &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Employers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sofitel SO Bangkok announces the chef lineup for So Amazing Chefs 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel SO Bangkok. The Sofitel SO Bangkok has announced that 12 world-renowned chefs will be in Thailand for the 4th So Amazing Chefs event, happening from October 6th to 11th, 2015.
Yves Mudry, General Manager of Sofitel SO Bangkok shared, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s food festival is our most prestigious yet, featuring an incredible lineup of chefs with a combined seven Michelin stars. This event highlights Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a culinary destination and fosters the exchange of culinary ideas and inspiration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Choose from a variety of MICE packages available in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Three travel companies — Chōsen, The Slate, and Samujana — have designed productivity programs for businesses and workgroups. These programs offer a variety of environments to help teams achieve their best results.
For adventure junkies Source: Chosen website. A view of Bali.
Chōsen provides experiences tailored for teams that thrive on new adventures and challenges:
Activities include cliff jumping, canyoning, surfing, and cooking classes. Accommodation is available at their estate in Bali and other locations, including New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor will assume management of the Star Convention Centre in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</guid><description>In 2020, Accor will assume management of the 571-room Star Convention Centre in Thailand, rebranding it as the Novotel Rayong Star Convention Centre. The hotel, situated in Rayong province&amp;rsquo;s city center, will undergo a significant two-year renovation. The initial phase will focus on revamping public spaces, dining establishments, and 235 guest rooms. Subsequently, the remaining 336 guest rooms will be renovated in the second phase.
Patrick Basset, COO of Accor for Upper Southeast &amp;amp; Northeast Asia and the Maldives, expressed enthusiasm about the hotel joining Accor&amp;rsquo;s network and expanding their presence in Rayong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the global culinary journey at THAIFEX Anuga Asia 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 16:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</guid><description>THAIFEX - Anuga Asia 2024, scheduled for May 28th to June 1st, 2024, is set to be the largest and most diverse edition yet, featuring exhibitors from 45 countries and regions and completely booked booth spaces.
_
Source: THAIFEX-Anuga Asia. Hosted buyer programme participants posing for a group picture during THAIFEX-Anuga Asia 2023.
This premier food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) trade show in Asia Pacific has experienced an unprecedented increase in global participation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The fourth akyra hotel in Sukhumvit, Bangkok has been launched by Akaryn</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</guid><description>Akaryn Hotel Group, a Thai hospitality company known for its luxurious hotels and resorts, will open its fourth akyra property, akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok, in December 2017.
The upscale boutique hotel is situated on Sukhumvit Soi 20, a vibrant area in the heart of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s main tourist zone, known for its excellent dining, lively nightlife, high-end shopping malls, spas, and green spaces.
akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok offers 50 rooms, ranging from 30 to 60 square meters, with city views...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park in Bangkok provides a versatile indoor-outdoor option for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</guid><description>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park, Bangkok – Marriott Executive Apartments is a unique venue for gatherings in the Sukhumvit area. Combining indoor and outdoor elements, it offers a versatile space for 30 to 160 guests. High ceilings and comfortable furniture create a welcoming atmosphere.
This lounge seamlessly blends several design concepts, creating a space that is both modern and traditional, as well as casual and elegant. Featuring lawn and garden views, the Lounge covers over 400 square meters and can host a variety of events from meetings to cocktail receptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 will commence operations on January 1, 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</guid><description>Source: Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 website.
Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20, a lifestyle hotel focused on health and wellness, will softly open its doors on January 1, 2016. The hotel provides tailored food and drinks, spa treatments, fitness facilities, and wellness activities.
Conveniently situated on Sukhumvit 20, the hotel is a short walk from the BTS Asok Skytrain, MRT Sukhumvit Subway, Terminal 21 Mall, The EmQuartier, and the Emporium...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group is celebrating the expansion of its Radisson Blu brand with the debut of its first Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok.
The Radisson Blu Plaza Hotel Bangkok, boasting 290 rooms, is strategically situated in Sukhumvit, a vibrant area known for its numerous offices, corporate headquarters, and retail outlets. This property marks Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s first Radisson Blu establishment in the city and is owned by G&amp;amp;P Asset Holding Company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at Avani+ Samui can take advantage of a complimentary longtail boat ride</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/</guid><description>Source: Minor Hotels. Avani+Samui Resort beachfront villa.
Guests at Avani+ Samui can enjoy a complimentary trip to Koh Madsum on a traditional longtail fishing boat.
Departing daily at 10 am and returning at 1 pm, the excursion allows ample time for a leisurely lunch at the resort&amp;rsquo;s Essence restaurant. For those seeking a full day of exploration, additional longtail boat trips for island hopping and snorkeling can be arranged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-avani-samui-can-take-advantage-of-a-complimentary-longtail-boat-ride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Audiophile Triad HS-3 Audio Transformer Auction for Elephants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 13:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As many know, I&amp;rsquo;m deeply passionate about protecting both captive and wild elephants globally. What people may not realize is that our generation might be the last to coexist with these magnificent creatures. In recent times, wild elephant populations have been decimated, their numbers plummeting from millions to mere thousands. This decline threatens their genetic diversity, jeopardizing the species&amp;rsquo; survival.
Each elephant is precious. One organization close to my heart is the Friends of the Asian Elephant hospital (FAE) in Thailand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023 begins in Bangkok on May 23rd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</guid><description>The upcoming THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023, a premier food and beverage industry event, will take place from May 23-27, 2023 at IMPACT Muang Thong Thani in Bangkok, Thailand. This year&amp;rsquo;s event features 11 signature trade shows, six special shows, and a focus on innovation, bold concepts, and advanced solutions. With approximately 3,000 exhibitors from 43 countries and over 60,000 trade visitors from more than 120 countries anticipated, organizers aim for a total transaction value of 70,000 million baht, including over 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates now offers a total of seven daily flights between Dubai and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Emirates will introduce a seventh daily flight between Dubai and Bangkok to accommodate rising passenger numbers. This will make Bangkok a top destination for Emirates, equal to Kuwait and Doha.
This new Boeing 777-300ER service will bring the total weekly flights to 49, increasing weekly seat capacity by 2,520 and cargo capacity by 134 tonnes each way. This addition complements the existing four daily A380 and two daily 777 flights, boosting travel and trade between Thailand and Emirates&amp;rsquo; global network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Frost introduces the Thailand Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</guid><description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, a global business growth consulting firm, granted 28 Thailand Excellence Awards to companies that exhibited remarkable accomplishments and exceptional performance across various sectors.
Koh Eng Lok, Country Head of Thailand at Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, highlighted the recipients&amp;rsquo; dedication to their clients. He explained that the award categories are carefully chosen each year to represent the prevailing market trends and encompass both established and emerging segments. The sectors range from ICT, automotive, energy &amp;amp; power, healthcare, building technologies to chemicals and palm oil...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn in Bangkok is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Bangkok has reopened with a new focus on natural elements.
The traditional lobby is gone, replaced with an open space that blends the front desk, restaurant, bar, lounge, and business center in a modern style. This design approach extends to the 379 guest rooms, each envisioned as a home away from home.
Two new dining options are available: Ginger, offering all-day dining, and Beer Republic, a bar designed to evoke a 1920s European industrial warehouse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Citizens of Thailand holding ordinary passports can travel to Taiwan without a visa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 07:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</guid><description>Holders of regular Thai passports can now travel without a visa to 26 countries, along with Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau. Beginning August 1st, Taiwan initiated a year-long trial program waiving visa requirements for Thai citizens with regular passports visiting for tourism purposes.
This program permits eligible travelers to stay in Taiwan for a maximum of 30 days. To qualify, Thai nationals must possess a valid regular passport with at least six months of validity remaining, hold a return or onward ticket to another destination, and meet Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s entry requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Khiri Travel reveals the hidden gems of Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:27:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/</guid><description>Hidden Gems of Phuket: A Local&amp;rsquo;s Guide Have some free time during your Phuket business trip? Gonzalo Gil Lavedra, manager of Khiri Travel Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Phuket branch, suggests exploring the island&amp;rsquo;s lesser-known attractions and authentic experiences.
&amp;ldquo;Discovering the quiet side of Phuket, away from the typical tourist spots, is what makes me appreciate calling this place home,&amp;rdquo; he shares.
One such gem is the Gibbon Rehabilitation Centre within the Khao Phra Taeo forest reserve...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the new Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. This hotel, the Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel, aims to create a beach resort atmosphere.
The recently opened Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel is a 72-room boutique hotel located in the city center. Its convenient location provides guests with easy walking access to shopping, dining, and entertainment. Designed around a nautical theme, the hotel offers 60 Deluxe rooms, eight Baraquda Suites, and four Baraquda Grand Suites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong is the inaugural Hyatt Place in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Hyatt and Boutique Corporation have announced the launch of the Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong in Phuket, Thailand. This 161-room beachfront property is the first Hyatt Place hotel in Southeast Asia. It embodies the Hyatt Place brand&amp;rsquo;s relaxed style and offers convenient amenities like complimentary Wi-Fi and 24/7 dining options.
&amp;ldquo;Thailand remains a crucial market for Hyatt, and Phuket is a top tourist spot in Southeast Asia with rising demand from both leisure and business travelers,&amp;rdquo; said David Udell, Group President – Asia Pacific, Hyatt Hotels Corporation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is heavily involved in digital communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. This data represents the Brandindex rankings for brands in Thailand in 2016.
According to the YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016, digital brands were highly favored in Thailand. Facebook, Line, and 7-Eleven secured the top three spots, while YouTube and Google were among the top 10. Other notable tech brands included Apple iPhone and the e-commerce platform Lazada.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents whether their exposure to the brand, whether through advertising, news, or word of mouth, in the past two weeks has been positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BDMS Connect Center in Bangkok now offers a wider range of MICE options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</guid><description>Source: Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok. BDMS Connect Center.
The BDMS Wellness Campus is proud to introduce its latest addition, the BDMS Connect Center. This cutting-edge facility, spanning over 3,400 square meters in the heart of Bangkok, is set to redefine the standards of meeting and event spaces.
Dan Smith, General Manager of Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok, expressed his enthusiasm for the new facility, stating that the BDMS Connect Center is a one-of-a-kind space, emphasizing both functionality and a commitment to wellness and sustainability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways releases statement regarding military coup in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has recommended that passengers on flight EY407 from Bangkok to Abu Dhabi be prepared to show their passports and tickets if asked by military personnel. This applies when traveling to Suvarnabhumi Airport during the curfew, which is in effect from 10:00 PM to 5:00 AM local time. The airline advises, &amp;ldquo;Guests are advised to allow extra time to reach the airport.&amp;rdquo;
Due to the suspension of public transportation starting at 9:00 PM local time and possible limited taxi services, Etihad suggests that hotel guests consider booking airport limousine services through their hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TCEB commemorates achievements in Thailand's MICE Venue Standard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</guid><description>Forty-two venues in Thailand have now received the Thailand MICE Venue Standard award from the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB). The announcement was made at the Thailand MICE Venue Standard Certification Ceremony held last month.
This standard is a key element of a robust plan to accelerate the growth of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s MICE industry. Emphasizing Thailand&amp;rsquo;s prominent role in the region, TCEB underscored the need to utilize the expertise of MICE operators...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing a new food tour by Isan Explorer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</guid><description>Source: Isan Explorer website.
Isan Explorer, a tour operator specializing in Northeast Thailand, has launched a culinary tour showcasing the cuisine of the lesser-known Isan region.
The day-long tour starts with a visit to a bustling fresh market to gather ingredients for lunch and dinner. Afterward, the tour proceeds to a nearby village.
Participants will enjoy a tasting menu featuring 20 main dishes, such as bamboo shoot curry, sour fish, grilled chicken, steamed mushrooms, green bean salad, and eggplant dipping sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Henley &amp; Partners has been selected as the worldwide concessionaire for the Thai residency program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</guid><description>Henley &amp;amp; Partners, a global firm specializing in residence and citizenship advisory, has been chosen to promote Thailand&amp;rsquo;s residence visa program, Thailand Elite. This program allows foreigners to reside in Thailand for up to 20 years.
Thailand&amp;rsquo;s welcoming atmosphere has made it a desirable destination in Southeast Asia. Individuals and families from affluent nations are increasingly drawn to its climate, scenery, and recreational opportunities. The 2017 &amp;ldquo;Best Countries&amp;rdquo; report highlighted Thailand as a prime location for starting a business due to its affordability, efficient bureaucracy, and accessible capital...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is gaining traction as a top choice for hosting business events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</guid><description>Source: TCEB.
Thailand, with the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB) at the helm, is establishing itself as a prime location for business events. As the Thai government&amp;rsquo;s primary representative for this sector, TCEB plays a vital role in solidifying Thailand&amp;rsquo;s leading position in the Asian business events industry and Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a top-tier destination for international business events.
The Thai business events sector is projected to experience robust growth in 2015, anticipating over a million visitors and generating approximately US$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 now accepts e-signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</guid><description>Source: Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 website.
The Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 has introduced a paperless check-in experience featuring electronic signatures. This system aims to eliminate the need for printed documents and expedite the arrival process for guests. Aloft Bangkok claims to be the first hotel within the Starwood brand to offer this service.
This innovative approach streamlines the check-in procedure by presenting all reservation details on a tablet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>