<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Emirates on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/emirates/</link><description>Recent content in Emirates on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/emirates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates reveals updated interiors for its Boeing 777 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced redesigned interiors for its Boeing 777 fleet, featuring upgraded seats and entertainment systems across all cabins. This multi-million dollar investment reflects the airline&amp;rsquo;s focus on enhancing the customer experience.
The new First Class cabins, designed in collaboration with several firms, offer private suites with sliding doors inspired by Mercedes-Benz S-Class. These suites prioritize comfort and luxury with features like soft leather seats, mood lighting, and ample storage. Retained features include personal minibars and wireless controls for seat adjustment and entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new premium offerings in First and Business Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced new luxury products for its First and Business Class passengers, partnering with brands like BYREDO, Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, and Bulgari to elevate the travel experience.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgd9y3iVi6anaC1N4Cso7QmgPJovqGEwEKcXCffrreFoqNcy3Bnr-B79U45k6PqBzF2gV2uzc94przcIphwRp2ecePtOYdspt9-PjYc3KQTh976kDvFOItJfkbCCO02xL93YGyDNrANYHYE/s1600/Emirates+byredo+wellness.jpg)
Source: Emirates. The BYREDO for Emirates Wellness kit.
First Class passengers in Emirates&amp;rsquo; private suites will receive a specially designed BYREDO travel wellness kit. This hypoallergenic skincare line, featuring chamomile, was created specifically for Emirates and introduced initially on the airline&amp;rsquo;s new Boeing 777 suites.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates is offering reduced fares to more than 70 locations. Bookings must be made by August 20, 2018, for travel dates between September 1, 2018, and March 31, 2019.
Economy Class fares start at AED945 to Beirut, Lebanon, AED995 to Mumbai, India, and AED2,345 to Bangkok, Thailand. Business Class fares to these destinations cost AED5,245, AED2,795, and AED9,795, respectively.
Travelers can enhance their experience with Emirates Holidays, adding a five-star hotel stay to their trip.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has prohibited hoverboards and reminds passengers of the approved items for carry-on luggage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates reminds passengers to check before packing, for hassle-free travel this holiday season.
Emirates Airlines is reminding travelers to review the allowed carry-on and checked baggage items for a smooth and secure journey during this holiday period.
To maintain the safety of everyone onboard, loose lithium batteries used in devices like cameras, cell phones, and laptops are not allowed in checked luggage. This includes &amp;ldquo;hoverboards&amp;rdquo; or self-balancing scooters, whether or not the batteries have been removed.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new flights to Istanbul's Sabiha Gokcen Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</guid><description>Emirates now offers 18 flights to Istanbul every week, including a new daily service to Sabiha Gökçen Airport in addition to its existing flights to Istanbul Atatürk Airport. This makes Istanbul the third city after London and Tokyo to be served by Emirates from two airports. The new daily flight is operated with an Airbus A330-200, offering 12 First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 183 Economy Class seats, and also provides up to 12 tonnes of cargo capacity each way.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats.</description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new route connecting Dubai with Yinchuan and Zhengzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</guid><description>Emirates airline is increasing its commitment to China by starting a new service from Dubai to Yinchuan and Zhengzhou, two rapidly developing cities in Midwest China. This addition brings Emirates&amp;rsquo; total destinations in mainland China to five, including existing service to Beijing, Shanghai, and Guangzhou.
Source; Emirates. Emirates&amp;rsquo; Chairman and Chief Executive, HH Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, along with other company executives and a delegation of UAE business leaders, were on the inaugural flight.</description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www.</description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers.</description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility.</description></item><item><title>Discover Emirates aircraft in 3D</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates pioneers VR experience on its website.
Emirates has become the first airline to use web-based virtual reality (VR) technology. They&amp;rsquo;ve added 3D seat models to emirates.com.
This 3D model shows a 360-degree view of the inside of their A380 and Boeing 777 aircraft. It allows customers to view the Economy, Business, and First Class cabins, as well as the onboard lounge and shower spa on the A380.</description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal.</description></item><item><title>Emirates provides appealing packages for stopovers in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s skyline, featuring the Burj Khalifa on the right.
Travelers flying with Emirates can benefit from appealing Dubai packages. These packages offer special prices at top-rated hotels and include access to entertainment options like city shows and attractions*.
Starting from US$49 per night, based on double occupancy, visitors can experience Dubai at the Rove Dubai Marina, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s vibrant waterfront area. This package also includes two tickets to Dubai Parks and Resorts, the region&amp;rsquo;s most extensive integrated theme park destination, encompassing MOTIONGATE Dubai, BOLLYWOOD PARKS Dubai, LEGOLAND Dubai, and LEGOLAND Water Park.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces a mobile site in Arabic language</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced an Arabic version of its mobile website. This platform allows customers to book flights, check in online, upgrade their travel class, and access and download Apple Passbook boarding passes directly to their smartphones, regardless of the language they use on the Emirates mobile site.
The Arabic mobile platform has been launched concurrently in 15 countries across the Middle East and North Africa, including the UAE, Bahrain, Iraq, Jordan, Kuwait, Lebanon, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Morocco, and Sudan.</description></item><item><title>Emirates offers passengers complimentary or heavily discounted in-flight Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates provides complimentary* Wi-Fi on a significant portion of its fleet, currently 106 aircraft, and is continuously expanding this service. Passengers on ultra long-haul flights (flights exceeding 14 hours) frequently utilize this service, with over 30% connecting to Wi-Fi.
All 59 Airbus A380s and 47 Boeing 777s in Emirates&amp;rsquo; fleet offer Wi-Fi connectivity. A majority of these aircraft provide the first 10MB of data free of charge, allowing passengers to update social media or use messaging apps.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has observed that 20% of its users access the website via iPads, prompting the airline to develop an iPad app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 10:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</guid><description>Emirates airline has introduced the Emirates App for iPad, available globally through the App Store. This app allows users to easily explore destinations and manage their Emirates travel experiences.
With a simple tap, users can discover information on over 130 Emirates destinations across six continents and learn about the airline&amp;rsquo;s renowned services.
The Emirates App for iPad simplifies travel management for Emirates customers, whether they&amp;rsquo;re on the move, in flight, or at home.</description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new Home Check-in service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. The Home Check-in service utilizes a newly acquired fleet of vans and has been undergoing rigorous testing since October of the previous year.
Emirates has launched its &amp;ldquo;Home Check-in&amp;rdquo; service, allowing passengers departing from Dubai, UAE, to check in for their flights from any location. This service is offered to all Emirates passengers, regardless of their travel class, and demonstrates the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to delivering exceptional service and convenience.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is set to introduce a third daily service to Brisbane</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates will begin offering a third daily flight to Brisbane, Australia starting December 1, 2017, adding to their current two daily flights.
This direct flight will utilize a Boeing 777-200LR, which boasts eight First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 216 Economy Class seats. This will increase the route&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3,724 seats weekly, both to and from Brisbane and Emirates&amp;rsquo; Dubai hub.</description></item><item><title>First and business class customers on Emirates can now enjoy a new Japanese menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 01:36:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. A sample dish from the new Japanese menu.
Emirates now offers a specialized Japanese menu to its first and business class passengers traveling between Dubai and Haneda, Narita, and Kansai airports in Japan. The airline&amp;rsquo;s Dubai catering team partnered with a Japanese culinary provider to develop the dishes using the highest quality ingredients.
In addition to their international menu, first-class passengers can enjoy traditional kaiseki, a multi-course Japanese meal, while those in business class have the option of a bento box.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is adding another daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates has launched an additional daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka. Starting August 1, 2016, the airline will offer five daily flights between the two cities, except on Wednesdays, when four flights will be available. This new flight will provide an extra 2,520 seats and boost cargo capacity by 161 tonnes weekly in both directions, increasing the total weekly services on this route to 34.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can enjoy Careem services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 14:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</guid><description>Source: Careem website. Emirates Skywards partners with Careem to provide benefits for their members.
Emirates Skywards, the loyalty program for Emirates, has partnered with Careem. This makes Emirates Skywards the only frequent flyer program to provide both earning and redemption opportunities with the leading car booking app in the region.
Careem is a rapidly growing company, currently operating in nine countries. Members can earn and redeem Skywards Miles when using Careem services in the UAE, Qatar, KSA, Lebanon, Jordan, Egypt, Pakistan, Kuwait, and Morocco.</description></item><item><title>Emirates provides LinkedIn Learning courses during flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates will offer LinkedIn courses inflight.
Emirates has teamed up with LinkedIn to offer a selection of LinkedIn Learning courses on its inflight entertainment system, ice. This makes Emirates the first international airline to provide these courses during flights.
This new addition to the ice system will launch in November and reflects Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to offering passengers fresh and diverse entertainment options. The free LinkedIn Learning courses, led by experts, range from 20 minutes to over two hours in length.</description></item><item><title>Emirates and flydubai will share a common frequent flyer program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-and-flydubai-will-share-a-common-frequent-flyer-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:49:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-and-flydubai-will-share-a-common-frequent-flyer-program/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates Skywards is now the loyalty program for both Emirates and flydubai, replacing flydubai&amp;rsquo;s OPEN program. This decision builds on the strong partnership between the two airlines, which already includes code-sharing across a wide global network and collaborations in areas like commercial strategies, network planning, and airport operations.
Members of Emirates Skywards can now earn both Skywards miles and tier miles when flying with either airline. They can also use these miles, or a combination of miles and cash, to book flydubai flights* and purchase extras like pre-ordered meals or extra legroom seats.</description></item></channel></rss>