<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>West on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/west/</link><description>Recent content in West on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/west/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing.</description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality.</description></item></channel></rss>