<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>New Year on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/new-year/</link><description>Recent content in New Year on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/new-year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore is invited to a new year countdown at Clarke Quay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay.
Clarke Quay invites everyone in Singapore to celebrate the end of the year with exciting festivities. Popular radio DJs Glenn Ong from Class95FM and Sonia Chew from 987FM will host the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve countdown. The event will feature live music by the band Goodfellas, a vibrant street parade with a glow theme, and roving percussionists.
The entire event at Clarke Quay will be broadcasted live on 987FM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a unique twist on French-inspired dining this holiday season at Sofitel So Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel So Singapore. Paulo.
At Sofitel So Singapore, Xperience restaurant&amp;rsquo;s head chef, Trevor Paulo, is celebrating his first Christmas season at the hotel with a special four-course Christmas Eve dinner.
The dinner starts with a small bite of blinis topped with dill yogurt and herring roe. The first course is a visually appealing dish of house-cured Salmon Gravlax arranged to look like a miniature garden with edible truffle &amp;ldquo;soil&amp;rdquo; and pickled shallots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the end of the year with eco-friendly festivities at East, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</guid><description>The environmentally conscious EAST, Hong Kong hotel is ready to celebrate the holiday season this year with special decorations and exciting events.
Continuing a tradition that began in 2014, EAST&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Village highlights creative recycling. This year, the EAST team gathered fallen logs left behind by Typhoon Mangkhut from the city streets to create unique Christmas decorations. Students from Jockey Club Sarah Roe School (JCSRS), the only school in Hong Kong offering an English curriculum for students with additional learning needs, collaborated with the EAST team on this project...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vacationing at Black Sheep Restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Elevate your holiday celebrations with the Black Sheep Restaurants group in Hong Kong:
Carbone
This New York-Italian establishment will be serving up generous portions of classics, like their 40oz Prime Porterhouse with a rosemary infusion. For a luxurious New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, enjoy an early dinner (6pm-8:45pm) or partake in The Fiasco, a mobster-themed dinner theater experience from 9pm-1am (HK$1,500).
Details:
Carbone is located at 9/F, LKF Tower, 33 Wyndham St, Central, Hong Kong..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vacationing-at-black-sheep-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an unexpected Christmas at Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel in Singapore has designed a Christmas menu featuring new versions of classic dishes, playful food presentations, and delightful surprises. These festive meals and unique takeaway options aim to make holiday celebrations even more memorable.
This year&amp;rsquo;s new gourmet takeaway options center around turkey with unique Asian flavors for savory dishes and chocolate-focused sweet treats.
Source: Goodwood Park Hotel. The 12 Treasures turkey is available for takeaways.
12 Treasures Turkey | S$268, serves eight to 10 people - New for 2017..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>