<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/software/</link><description>Recent content in Software on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars.</description></item><item><title>KODAK CapturePro Software v5.0 has been released by Kodak Alaris</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</guid><description>Large businesses are constantly looking for ways to manage information more efficiently and productively. Extracting data from documents for business processes and getting information into digital storage can slow things down, impacting expenses and customer happiness.
Source: Kodak Alaris.
&amp;ldquo;As organizations rely more on online platforms for profit, it&amp;rsquo;s critical to manage remaining paper documents effectively,&amp;rdquo; says Harvey Spencer, President of leading capture software analyst firm Harvey Spencer Associates. &amp;ldquo;The best approach is quickly converting paper into usable electronic data.</description></item><item><title>Aptugo develops customized web software without requiring any training</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 03:31:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</guid><description>Aptugo, a software tool designed to help individuals without coding experience build websites, is currently in beta testing. Developed by the company Aptugo, the software is expected to launch in 2015.
&amp;ldquo;Aptugo has the potential to bridge the gap between large and small businesses. Users don&amp;rsquo;t need any programming knowledge to use it,&amp;rdquo; stated Gaston Gorosterrazu, Head of Aptugo. &amp;ldquo;However, those with coding experience can further enhance what Aptugo can do, as it is designed to empower users and expand their capabilities.</description></item><item><title>What’s Coming with Snow Leopard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-coming-with-snow-leopard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-coming-with-snow-leopard/</guid><description>In the coming month, Apple is set to launch a substantial update for its Mac OS X operating system. This upgrade, priced at a reasonable $29 from the existing Leopard OS X 10.5, promises a range of new features. But what exactly justifies the cost?
Personally, I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to upgrade operating systems beyond the minor updates that are provided automatically for free. Major upgrades often come at a cost and while they typically offer enhanced functionality, they also demand more processing power and memory.</description></item><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server.</description></item><item><title>Readsoft Online version 9 has been released by Kofax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</guid><description>Kofax, a company that produces software to streamline and transform the initial stages of business operations, has introduced the 9th release of ReadSoft Online, a cloud-based solution for capturing and processing invoices.
ReadSoft Online provides small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) with a cost-effective and adaptable way to automate their accounts payable procedures. The solution captures invoices, extracts invoice data, and exports verified data to enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems, accounting software, and other applications.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography.</description></item><item><title>60% of software installations in APAC are unlicensed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-software-installations-in-apac-are-unlicensed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:44:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-software-installations-in-apac-are-unlicensed/</guid><description>In 2013, the Asia Pacific region had the world&amp;rsquo;s highest rate of unlicensed PC software installations at 62%, resulting in an estimated US$21 billion in lost revenue, according to the BSA Global Software Survey.
The Middle East and Africa followed closely with a rate of 59%, mirroring Central and Eastern Europe. Latin America also reported 59%, while North America and Western Europe had lower rates at 19% and 29% respectively. Globally, the average rate of unlicensed software installations was 43%.</description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality.</description></item><item><title>HubSpot for Startups simplifies the onboarding process for new businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</guid><description>HubSpot, a company that provides marketing and sales technology, has launched a new program called HubSpot for Startups. This program is specifically designed to support startups that are working with accelerators, incubators, and entrepreneurial organizations.
The program aims to help these small businesses gain momentum in their marketing and sales efforts by offering a substantial 90% discount on HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s products. These products include tools for customer relationship management (CRM), sales, and marketing.</description></item><item><title>Visa introduces Visa Business Hub to assist small and medium-sized businesses with technology and strategic planning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-introduces-visa-business-hub-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-with-technology-and-strategic-planning/</guid><description>Visa has launched the Visa Business Hub, a platform designed to assist small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in navigating technology and improving their management practices. The hub, initially launched in Singapore and Malaysia, offers software-as-a-service (SaaS) solutions that can potentially reduce IT costs by up to 25% through a pay-as-you-use model. This approach minimizes upfront expenses and implementation time.
Research indicates that a significant number of businesses in Singapore (80%) view SaaS/cloud adoption as a strategic move rather than a passing trend.</description></item><item><title>Local computer vendor in Singapore raided by police, counterfeit Microsoft software discovered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-computer-vendor-in-singapore-raided-by-police-counterfeit-microsoft-software-discovered/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-computer-vendor-in-singapore-raided-by-police-counterfeit-microsoft-software-discovered/</guid><description>Microsoft is urging consumers and small businesses to be cautious when buying software, warning them about the risks of accidentally purchasing and using counterfeit products. This advisory comes after a recent raid on a computer vendor in Kembangan Plaza by the Intellectual Property Rights Branch (IPRB) of the Singapore Police Force.
The shop in question had been advertising unauthorized &amp;ldquo;Microsoft license keys&amp;rdquo; as genuine and offering computers bundled with counterfeit software at heavily discounted prices through their online store.</description></item><item><title>SMBs can access Office 365 through GoDaddy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a technology company that supports small businesses, has partnered with Microsoft to offer Microsoft Office 365 to small businesses in Asian markets. This collaboration is part of GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s ongoing effort to provide top-tier business management solutions worldwide.
By offering Office 365, GoDaddy allows its customers to easily access professional email linked to a domain name, secure cloud storage, and a wide range of productivity and collaboration tools.
&amp;ldquo;GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s understanding of small businesses combined with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s email and productivity suite gives small business owners in Asia the tools they need to simplify their operations,&amp;rdquo; said Roger Chen, Vice President of Asia, GoDaddy.</description></item><item><title>The Important Contribution of Small Business [Infographic]</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 23:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The expense of utilizing unlicensed software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-expense-of-utilizing-unlicensed-software/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 08:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-expense-of-utilizing-unlicensed-software/</guid><description>The recent 2018 Global Software Survey from BSA | The Software Alliance, titled Software Management: Security Imperative, Business Opportunity, supports the findings of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Asia PC Test Purchase Sweep. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s study revealed that a significant number of PCs in Asia, approximately four out of five (83%), are equipped with pirated software.
Tarun Sawney, the Senior Director for Asia Pacific at BSA, highlighted the persistent issue of unlicensed software. Globally, unlicensed software constitutes 37% of all software installed on personal computers, marking a 2% decrease from 2016.</description></item><item><title>The TINA ERP system is compatible with GCC VAT calculations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</guid><description>Source: dcs plus. Graphic for the TINA travel ERP software.
dcs plus, a Romanian company with a Dubai office, has announced that its TINA web-based travel ERP system now supports value-added tax (VAT) calculations for businesses operating in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) region. This development comes as GCC member states prepare to fully implement VAT based on a framework agreement from 2016.
TINA streamlines business operations by collecting booking details from various sales channels and organizing them into standardized, automated workflows.</description></item><item><title>ItSeez3D has released an updated version of its 3D scanner app for iPad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</guid><description>Source: itSeez3D page on the App Store.
itSeez3D, a company that develops 3D scanning software, has released an updated version of their mobile scanning app, also named itSeez3D. This app, designed for use with the Occipital Structure Sensor 3D device, now allows iPads to generate lifelike, full-body 3D models.
This updated app serves as a valuable tool for 3D printing, enabling the scanning of a full-color figurine in under two minutes.</description></item><item><title>Accounting solution in the cloud specifically created for individuals without accounting expertise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 03:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</guid><description>Asian Business Software Solutions (ABSS) has introduced Financio, a cloud-based accounting software designed for micro and small businesses in Singapore. This secure solution simplifies financial tracking without requiring accounting expertise.
Developed by ABSS and utilizing Microsoft Azure, Financio allows users to easily monitor sales, purchases, and other transactions through a user-friendly dashboard. It automates tasks like generating financial reports, tax records, and sending invoices, and enables seamless collaboration and document sharing through Financio Connect.</description></item><item><title>How the ZAC Browser Helps Autistic Kids</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-zac-browser-helps-autistic-kids/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 03:54:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-zac-browser-helps-autistic-kids/</guid><description>Occasionally, you find a story that leaves you amazed. I recently encountered one such story, &amp;ldquo;Grandfather builds Web browser for autistic boy,&amp;rdquo; about a software developer who took action when his six-year-old grandson struggled to use the internet. This might not seem unusual at first, but the situation becomes clearer with more context.
Zackary, the six-year-old grandson, has autism, making communication and interaction difficult, and he rarely speaks. He finds joy in games, music, and puzzles, many available online.</description></item><item><title>TeamAhoy introduces a new project management software that focuses on people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teamahoy-introduces-a-new-project-management-software-that-focuses-on-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teamahoy-introduces-a-new-project-management-software-that-focuses-on-people/</guid><description>Source: TeamAhoy.
Bramanis.
TeamAhoy (previously known as Birds Eye View), an Australian company, has introduced the first public version of its project management software. The startup highlights that its software differentiates itself by prioritizing the human element, unlike competitors.
Founder Damian Bramanis explains that while teams consist of people, most project management tools don&amp;rsquo;t reflect this in their design. He believes TeamAhoy stands out by offering managers a user-friendly platform that centers around individuals.</description></item><item><title>Companies in the Asia Pacific region are allocating funds for security, infrastructure, and business intelligence applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</guid><description>When planning technology budgets for the year, remember to allocate resources for infrastructure software, business intelligence applications, and, most importantly, security. Research firm Forrester states that security software is now the fastest-growing software category in the Asia Pacific region, leading in projected software spending growth for 2014.
In a survey of 3,382 IT executives and technology decision-makers across Asia Pacific organizations, 55% indicated they would increase their security software budget by &amp;lsquo;5% to 10%, or more&amp;rsquo; in 2014 compared to 2013.</description></item></channel></rss>