<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Peak Program Meter on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/peak-program-meter/</link><description>Recent content in Peak Program Meter on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:08:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/peak-program-meter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (I)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m waiting for a part for a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, I&amp;rsquo;ve started restoring another one with faulty displays. It seems cassettes are making a comeback! I&amp;rsquo;m even hoping for new tapes and maybe even a revival of the Sony Walkman II.
This particular Beocord 9000 has a very dim display:
[Image of dim display]
The &amp;ldquo;Time Cal&amp;rdquo; bulb is also weak, a common issue. I began with the VU meter (or Peak Program Meter), as I haven&amp;rsquo;t refurbished this type before...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (III)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</guid><description>This article, the third in a series about restoring a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s peak program meters (PPM), focuses on installing and calibrating the rebuilt PPM.
The initial step involved switching the original current limiting resistors with values suitable for modern SMD LEDs. These LEDs are more efficient and brighter, requiring significantly larger resistors to match the original brightness. Testing showed that 470 Ohm and 330 Ohm resistors for red and green LEDs, respectively, produced slightly brighter output compared to the original 180 Ohm and 120 Ohm resistors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoring the Peak Program Meters with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s Peak Program Meter (PPM), even though it was fully functional. This decision stemmed from my success in restoring a different Beocord&amp;rsquo;s PPM that had several broken segments.
Since the technology behind these PPMs is similar to that of a 7-segment display, I realized that the segments in this unit were also susceptible to future breakage. Therefore, I chose to preemptively address the issue while I had the opportunity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating Recording Current and Bias</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</guid><description>Pleased with the seemingly functional Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape mechanism, an initial test recording was conducted using a waveform generator. Playback revealed a 3 dB channel imbalance on the Peak Program Meter (PPM), indicating a calibration issue. This was unsurprising given the deck&amp;rsquo;s age and highlighted the fortunate performance of a previously rebuilt Beocord 5000 in a Beolab 6000 setup, which operated well without calibration. To establish a solid calibration baseline, a reliable frequency response measurement was deemed essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating the Peak Program Meters (VU Meters)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</guid><description>After reassembling and successfully testing a Beocord 5000 tape deck, I decided to calibrate its Peak Program Meters (PPMs) according to the service manual.
Instead of directly inputting a 300 Hz signal into the Dolby B ICs as the manual suggested, I opted to feed a 25 mV, 300 Hz signal into the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inputs while in record mode (paused). Using a multimeter, I adjusted the recording levels to achieve the specified 740 mV RMS output at the Dolby B ICs (pin 7), allowing for the calibration of the PPMs&amp;rsquo; 0 dB level...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (II)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s rebuilt Peak Program Meters (PPM) display passed a 24-hour test, confirming its functionality.
To reattach the red-green covers, I secured the display to ensure a tight seal, preventing light leakage. Using a soldering iron, I melted the plastic posts of the covers, replicating the original attachment method.
During cleaning, the glue holding the light guide dissolved, indicating it was likely polyvinyl ester-based. I used &amp;lsquo;Aleene&amp;rsquo;s Original Tacky Glue&amp;rsquo; as a substitute, providing a clear and durable bond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-ii-/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>