<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VSAT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vsat/</link><description>Recent content in VSAT on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vsat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Maestro Smart Antenna Improves Fixed Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</guid><description>Accel Technologies, a branch of Accel Networks, is launching a groundbreaking product for fixed wireless connections: the Maestro smart antenna system. Maestro aims to make 3G and 4G fixed wireless broadband a more attractive alternative to pricier business connectivity options like T1, MPLS, VSAT, Frame Relay, and point-to-point microwave services.
What makes Maestro so special? Like other smart devices, Maestro utilizes active technology to enhance performance. In this situation, it improves the performance of a typically passive component: the RF antenna.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:</description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>