<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FDI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fdi/</link><description>Recent content in FDI on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fdi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vietnam, a country experiencing growth, is attracting investments from various regions, according to UOB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</guid><description>A recent study by the United Overseas Bank (UOB) suggests Vietnam will experience a surge in investments from nearby countries like Malaysia, Thailand, and Singapore over the next three to five years.
The 2016 UOB Asian Enterprise Survey found that Vietnam is a top expansion target for businesses in Malaysia (38%), Thailand (35%), and Singapore (29%). These nations are among the 28% of surveyed enterprises that selected Vietnam as their preferred expansion destination within the next three to five years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investors are increasingly optimistic about placing foreign direct investment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore achieved a top-ten ranking in the 2016 AT Kearney Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) Confidence Index. The city-state climbed five positions, representing the most significant advancement in the rankings, securing the 10th spot.
This index provides a future-oriented assessment of how political, economic, and regulatory shifts are likely to influence FDI inflows into various countries in the coming years. Since its inception in 1998, the study has consistently identified the preferred global destinations for FDI, with the index rankings closely mirroring actual global FDI inflows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Kazakhstan are working together to enhance their bilateral trade relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/</guid><description>Singapore and Kazakhstan have signed a bilateral investment treaty designed to encourage greater investment between the two nations.
This agreement is intended to safeguard investors from both Singapore and Kazakhstan, giving them more confidence to pursue investment opportunities in each other&amp;rsquo;s countries. The treaty ensures that Singaporean companies operating in Kazakhstan will have additional protection for their investments beyond what is provided by Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s domestic laws, and the same applies to Kazakh companies in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-kazakhstan-are-working-together-to-enhance-their-bilateral-trade-relationship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BERI considers Taiwan to be a top candidate for establishing its Asia Pacific headquarters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 09:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</guid><description>Is your business searching for a new Asia-Pacific regional headquarters? Taiwan might be the ideal location.
Business Environment Risk Intelligence (BERI) released its third &amp;ldquo;Report on the Evaluation of Environmental Risks of Investment&amp;rdquo; for 2013 in December 2013. The report ranks 50 countries and territories based on their &amp;ldquo;Profit Opportunity Recommendation&amp;rdquo; metric. Switzerland secured the top position, followed by Singapore and then Taiwan.
Taiwan holds the second position globally, just behind Singapore, for operational risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, ASEAN received the highest amount of foreign direct investment (FDI) among developing countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The latest ASEAN Investment Report examines the growth of foreign direct investment (FDI) into the ASEAN region, particularly the influence of corporations on infrastructure expansion and regional integration.
In 2014, ASEAN emerged as the top recipient of FDI among developing nations. FDI inflows to the region experienced a third consecutive year of growth, reaching US$136.2 billion, a rise from US$117.7 billion in 2013. This achievement occurred despite a 16% global decline in FDI and inconsistent global economic progress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai is optimistic about its FDI prospects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</guid><description>His Highness Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai and Chairman of The Executive Council, stated that the increase in foreign direct investment (FDI) inflows demonstrates growing investor confidence in Dubai, UAE.
His Highness reported that FDI into Dubai reached US$4.84 billion, a 26% increase compared to the first half of last year, during the first half of 2018. The number of FDI projects also rose significantly to 248, a 40% increase over the same period last year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>