<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sony/</link><description>Recent content in Sony on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:33:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sony Singapore's year-end promotions are valid until the beginning of January 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</guid><description>Are you looking for some of Sony&amp;rsquo;s top products from 2019? Here are a few:
Digital imaging
Sony A7 III
Source: Sony. The α7 III.
The A7 III boasts five-axis stabilization, 4D Focus for reliable focusing in low light (down to EV-3), and the capability to record 4K HDR videos.
Promotional price: S$2,699 (usual price S$2,899)
Sony α7 III with 35mm full-frame image sensor (ILCE7M3K) Sony RX100 VII
The compact RX100 VII features an extensive zoom range and remarkable speed.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces two high-end wireless speakers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-two-high-end-wireless-speakers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 23:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-two-high-end-wireless-speakers/</guid><description>• Experience immersive, room-filling audio with features like Immersive Audio Enhancement and 360 Reality Audio.
• Effortlessly calibrate the speakers to your environment for optimal sound performance.
• Enjoy a seamless and intuitive music listening experience with intelligent features.
Sony introduces the SRS-RA5000 and SRS-RA3000, premium wireless speakers engineered for an immersive audio experience. These speakers utilize Sony&amp;rsquo;s advanced spatial sound technologies and smart features to deliver sound that envelops the listener.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces hard disk drives with high speed and high capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-hard-disk-drives-with-high-speed-and-high-capacity/</guid><description>Sony Introduces Speedy and Durable Portable Hard Drives Boasting data transfer speeds up to 138MBps for both reading and writing, Sony&amp;rsquo;s latest portable hard disk drives (HDDs) promise both performance and resilience. Built to withstand the bumps of everyday use, these drives are shock-resistant, splash-resistant (IPX4 rating), and dust-resistant (IP5X rating). They can even tolerate drops from up to 6.5 feet thanks to their robust rubber damper design.
Source: Sony. The new 2TB drive.</description></item><item><title>Sony has expanded its range of full-frame lenses and introduced a new OSS Super-Telephoto lens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-expanded-its-range-of-full-frame-lenses-and-introduced-a-new-oss-super-telephoto-lens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-expanded-its-range-of-full-frame-lenses-and-introduced-a-new-oss-super-telephoto-lens/</guid><description>Sony unveiled its latest addition to the full-frame E-mount lens lineup: the FE 24-105mm F4 G OSS Standard Zoom (model SEL24105G). This new lens covers the popular 24-105mm focal length range, offering exceptional G Lens image quality in a lightweight design. Its fast, precise, and quiet autofocus makes it suitable for both still photography and video recording with Sony E-mount cameras.
High-Quality Optics The Sony FE 24-105mm F4 G OSS lens provides excellent sharpness across the entire zoom range, along with aesthetically pleasing background blur (bokeh) at all focal lengths.</description></item><item><title>The new bronze pink Xperia XZ Premium phones are now on sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The Bronze Pink Sony Xperia XZ.
After the June release of the Sony Xperia XZ Premium, Sony Mobile has launched a third color option in Singapore: Bronze Pink.
This new pink-hued phone will be available at select retailers starting July 8th. The Xperia XZ Premium has a suggested retail price of S$1,098.
Sony claims its Xperia XZ Premium is the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest smartphone, boasting a 4K HDR display.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new 4K HDR camcorders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-4k-hdr-camcorders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-4k-hdr-camcorders/</guid><description>Sony has introduced three new 4K HDR1 camcorders—the XDCAM PXW-Z90, the NXCAM HXR-NX80, and the Handycam FDR-AX700—all featuring Sony&amp;rsquo;s Fast Hybrid AF system.
Source: Sony. Sony launches new 4K HDR camcorders.
These compact camcorders all share the same fast and dependable autofocus system, designed specifically for their 1.0-type stacked Exmor RS CMOS image sensor. This allows them to capture high-quality footage with excellent clarity and offer a variety of shooting options.</description></item><item><title>Pre-orders for the Sony Mobile Xperia XZs are now open in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-sony-mobile-xperia-xzs-are-now-open-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-sony-mobile-xperia-xzs-are-now-open-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sony Mobile. The Xperia XZs.
In Singapore, the Sony Xperia XZs can be pre-ordered exclusively at Sony&amp;rsquo;s retail locations (six stores and two centers) until April 14th.
Pre-orders will come with a complimentary accessory package, including MDR-XB70BT Extra Bass Bluetooth In-ear Headphones (S$149 value), a DK60 Micro USB Charging Dock (S$58 value), and a clear crystal phone case (S$20.90 value)*.
Additionally, a special offer allows customers to purchase a tempered glass screen protector for the Xperia XZs at a discounted price of S$14.</description></item><item><title>The new α7R III camera from Sony offers a combination of high resolution and fast speed for interchangeable lenses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-7r-iii-camera-from-sony-offers-a-combination-of-high-resolution-and-fast-speed-for-interchangeable-lenses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-7r-iii-camera-from-sony-offers-a-combination-of-high-resolution-and-fast-speed-for-interchangeable-lenses/</guid><description>Sony has introduced the α7R III (model ILCE-7RM3), a new full-frame mirrorless camera. This camera boasts a high-resolution 42.4MP back-illuminated Exmor R CMOS image sensor and advanced image processing. It can shoot continuously at up to 10 fps with full AF/AE tracking and produces stunning image and 4K video quality. Other notable features include a 15-stop dynamic range, high sensitivity with reduced noise, and more.
Exceptional Image Quality The camera&amp;rsquo;s 42.</description></item><item><title>The deadline for submissions to the Sony World Photography Awards 2019 is January 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deadline-for-submissions-to-the-sony-world-photography-awards-2019-is-january-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deadline-for-submissions-to-the-sony-world-photography-awards-2019-is-january-2019/</guid><description>Global photographers have less than a month to submit their entries to the 12th annual Sony World Photography Awards’ Professional, Open and Youth competitions. Considered a major event in the photography world, the awards acknowledge the finest contemporary photography from the past year across a diverse range of photographic genres.
Scott Gray, the CEO and founder of the World Photography Organisation, remarked that each year, the Sony World Photography Awards brings new photographic talents to light and provides established artists with a global stage for their work.</description></item><item><title>Sony Electronics Singapore is marking the first anniversary of the Sony Store with a celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-electronics-singapore-is-marking-the-first-anniversary-of-the-sony-store-with-a-celebration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-electronics-singapore-is-marking-the-first-anniversary-of-the-sony-store-with-a-celebration/</guid><description>Source: Sony Electronics Singapore. Sony Singapore’s Lifestyle Concept Store at Isetan Wisma Atria.
Sony Electronics is commemorating the first anniversary of its Sony Store located within Isetan Wisma Atria in Singapore. The celebration includes a store revamp and a variety of workshops and special deals offered throughout October.
Designed with the female shopper in mind, the Sony Store presents themed displays to demonstrate how the various products can complement their lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Sony Xperia XA1, Xperia XZ1, and Xperia XZ1 Compact by #SonyMobileSG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-sony-xperia-xa1-xperia-xz1-and-xperia-xz1-compact-by-sonymobilesg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-sony-xperia-xa1-xperia-xz1-and-xperia-xz1-compact-by-sonymobilesg/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications has introduced the Xperia XZ1 and Xperia XZ1 Compact, expanding its flagship smartphone lineup. These phones are equipped with cutting-edge technology, including the Motion Eye camera, capable of capturing detail beyond human perception, and innovative 3D scanning for mobile devices.
The Xperia XZ1 boasts a 5.2” Full HD HDR display enhanced with Sony&amp;rsquo;s BRAVIA TV technology, delivering vibrant colors and sharp contrast. In contrast, the Xperia XZ1 Compact offers top-tier features in a compact design with a 4.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Gadget Gift Guide for Christmas 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</guid><description>As 2017 comes to a close, treat yourself to a range of exciting new gadgets! WorkSmart Asia presents its top picks for this year, featuring:
Limited Edition Star Wars Shavers Source: Philips Singapore. Philips limited edition shavers, inspired by Star Wars. From left: the Poe Dameron-inspired Philips _Star Wars _Shaver SW6700/14; the BB-8-inspired SW5700/07 and the Stormtrooper-inspired SW170/04.
Philips introduces a new line of limited-edition shavers inspired by iconic Star Wars characters.</description></item><item><title>Sony has introduced the Picture This Festival for the Planet competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</guid><description>Sony Pictures Television Networks (SPTN), working with the United Nations Foundation, has launched the Picture This Festival for the Planet. The short-film competition encourages emerging filmmakers, storytellers, and changemakers globally to share their visions for a positive future for the planet.
Representing over 70 countries, participants are invited to submit videos inspired by the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The SDGs are a collection of global goals adopted by the United Nations to address poverty, protect the planet, and promote prosperity for everyone.</description></item><item><title>The LinkBuds S from Sony provide an immersive audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The LinkBuds S.
Sony has expanded its LinkBuds series with the new LinkBuds S. This model offers a new audio experience by utilizing Sony&amp;rsquo;s sensor technology and collaborations, while still providing a seamless &amp;ldquo;always-on&amp;rdquo; experience.
The LinkBuds S boast both noise cancellation and high-resolution audio capabilities. These headphones allow users to stay connected to their surroundings with the LinkBuds&amp;rsquo; ambient sound feature or minimize distractions with high-quality noise cancellation, letting them fully enjoy their preferred content.</description></item><item><title>The winners of the 2017 Sony World Photography Awards in Singapore have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-2017-sony-world-photography-awards-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 08:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-2017-sony-world-photography-awards-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</guid><description>Lester Koh Meng Hua has been named the winner of the Singapore National Award, as part of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest photography competition.
Source: Sony. Singapore at dawn won the Singapore National Award for the Sony World Photography Awards 2017.
The photograph titled Singapore at dawn by Lester Koh Meng Hua has been chosen by the judges of the 2017 Sony World Photography Awards as the winner of the Singapore National Award.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new smartphones and audio-visual solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications (Sony Mobile) has introduced new consumer experiences centered around innovation.
“Xperia Touch represents a groundbreaking interface,&amp;quot; stated Hiroki Totoki, President and CEO of Sony Mobile Communications. &amp;ldquo;A year after revealing our updated brand direction and vision for the future of communications, we are not only introducing the Xperia XZ Premium, packed with cutting-edge technologies to improve core smartphone features, but also creating entirely new interactive communication experiences with our Xperia Smart Products.</description></item></channel></rss>