<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Preamp on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/preamp/</link><description>Recent content in Preamp on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:46:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/preamp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: First Prototype Installed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</guid><description>I was tasked with creating an internal RIAA preamplifier for a restored Beogram 4002 (5521). This addition makes sense since many modern receivers lack a dedicated phono input. Additionally, the pre-opamp RIAA preamps found in many vintage B&amp;amp;O receivers introduce more noise compared to modern low-noise audio op-amps.
Researching contemporary RIAA preamp designs led me to the LM833 operational amplifier, a specialized low-noise op-amp for audio applications. I adapted a high-precision RIAA preamp circuit from a Texas Instruments application note AN-346, as established RIAA preamplifier designs exist.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Newly Adapted Beolover RIAA Pre-Amp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</guid><description>Following the recent redesign of the Beolover internal RIAA pre-amplifier for DC-motor Beogram 4002/4 turntables and its adaptation for the Beogram 4000, the final stage of the design process involved adjusting the circuit for the AC-motor Beogram 4002. The owner of a recently restored 4002 (5504) requested the RIAA installation, making his Beogram the first AC-motor 4002 to feature a Beolover RIAA.
The new board features an input jack that connects to a replicated Beogram-style plug through a multi-lead wiring harness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of Upgrades - Internal RIAA Preamp, Commander Remote Control and a New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</guid><description>Following the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) from Oklahoma, the next step was to add the customer&amp;rsquo;s desired upgrades. These included an internal Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier (designed for AC motor Beogram 4002s), a Beolover Commander remote control system, and a new hood for a pristine appearance.
The first upgrade was preparing the keypad for the Commander remote system. AC motor Beograms primarily use directly soldered wiring harnesses, so Commander installation isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;plug and play&amp;rdquo; like the DC motor version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: A New Power Supply Design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous one about the RIAA preamplifier I&amp;rsquo;m building for a Beogram 4002 turntable. This preamp will allow the Beogram to connect directly to a modern amplifier&amp;rsquo;s AUX or TAPE input. While initially pleased with my prototype, I redesigned it for a cleaner layout and had it manufactured.
The new boards arrived, and I assembled a preamplifier, thrilled with its appearance. After installing and testing it, however, I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t tested it thoroughly enough beforehand.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Upgrade with SyncDrive Platter Motor, Commander Remote Control and Internal RIAA Pre-Amplifier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</guid><description>A customer from Kentucky requested a full upgrade for their Beogram 4002 turntable, including three modifications: a SyncDrive motor for enhanced speed stability, a Commander remote control system for convenient operation and keypad protection, and a Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier for direct connection to modern audio equipment.
All upgrades were installed without soldering. The SyncDrive replaced the original DC motor, connecting to existing mounting points and the main circuit board. The Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier replaced the output board, using compatible connectors for easy installation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Newly Designed Beolover RIAA Pre-Amplifier Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-newly-designed-beolover-riaa-pre-amplifier-board/</guid><description>Due to demand, I designed an internal RIAA pre-amplifier board for the Beogram 4000, adapting the circuit from my recent redesign for the DC motor Beogram 4002 and 4004. I installed this new board in a Beogram 4000 that was in for a warranty repair. This post details the installation process; for technical data, refer to my previous post about the 4002/4 version&amp;rsquo;s performance, as the circuits are identical.
The current prototype board has some features that will be absent in the final version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of Beolover Commander MkII Remote and Internal RIAA Pre-Amp Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 09:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</guid><description>The owner of the Beogram 4002 (5513) requested the installation of a 4002 Commander remote control and an internal RIAA pre-amplifier module. The Commander enables complete control of the 4002 using an Apple remote, while the RIAA provides a strong output signal, allowing direct connection to modern amplifiers via CD/DVD/AUX inputs.
The first image displays the RIAA board and its mounting adapter, which elevates it above the output PCB headers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of 4002 Commander MkII Remote Control and Internal RIAA Preamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</guid><description>I recently completed a Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration, and the customer requested two upgrades I developed: the Beolover 4002 Commander MkII remote control receiver and the internal RIAA pre-amplifier. These upgrades are detailed further on my blog, along with installation instructions. Both are available for purchase; feel free to contact me for more information.
This image showcases both boards:
The lower board is the Commander MkII. This version includes a repeat function, indicated by the CD4 light on the keypad.</description></item></channel></rss>