<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EoC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eoc/</link><description>Recent content in EoC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eoc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Increase Bandwidth Without Increasing Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</guid><description>Companies need more bandwidth, especially for their wide area networks (WANs), but it can be very expensive. While high speeds are affordable within a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN, connecting to the outside world traditionally comes with much higher costs.
This is because WAN connections were typically provided by telecom companies using technology initially meant for phone services. While more modern providers have entered the market with updated infrastructure, even traditional providers are adapting to the demand for data services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper WAN Bandwidth Headed to 500 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</guid><description>Ericsson has developed a new technology that could significantly boost data transmission speeds over existing copper wire infrastructure. This innovation allows for WAN connections over copper, achieving speeds up to 500 Mbps.
While Gigabit Ethernet is achievable with Cat-6 wiring for LAN connections, this technology focuses on connecting businesses to broadband providers using existing copper infrastructure. This is significant because many businesses require increased bandwidth for various purposes, including server farms, internet access, data transfer between locations, and the growing need for electronic medical record transfers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Services over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:35:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</guid><description>Connecting networks logically often involves Ethernet, a technology that has recently expanded its reach beyond local boundaries. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) connections are increasing in availability and often come at a lower cost compared to other options.
EoC enables standard Ethernet services to be delivered through existing copper telephone wiring. Unlike typical Cat 5E or Cat 6 wiring, EoC is compatible with older copper infrastructure not initially intended for Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper vs Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</guid><description>T1 lines have long been considered a reliable connection option for small to medium businesses, gaining traction as prices dropped in recent years. However, a new technology called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers even greater bandwidth at a lower cost and with simpler connectivity.
EoC, like T1, uses existing twisted-pair telephone wiring commonly found in business locations. Traditional T1 lines use two twisted pairs within this wiring, allowing for simultaneous two-way data transfer at 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over TDM</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 23:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</guid><description>You might be familiar with Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber, but have you encountered Ethernet over TDM? It&amp;rsquo;s worth understanding this technology and its potential benefits.
](http://www.copperethernet.com/)
TDM, or Time Division Multiplexing, forms the foundation of T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. It became the standard for the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) during its transition from analog to digital in the mid-20th century and remains relevant due to its continued prevalence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-tdm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2x2 Ethernet Takes on T-1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</guid><description>For the past decade, small and medium businesses have relied on T1 lines as their primary commercial telecom solution. However, a new competitor called 2x2 Ethernet, recently introduced by major nationwide carrier MegaPath, is emerging to challenge the long-standing T1. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what 2x2 Ethernet offers.
It might seem surprising that T1 lines would face competition, considering their 50-year history and widespread adoption. As the first widely available broadband digital connection for businesses, T1 emerged from telephone company research...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lock In Telecom Cost Savings For Next Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</guid><description>As we wrap up the year and analyze our performance, it&amp;rsquo;s common to wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re overspending on business operations, especially networking and telecom. A thorough market analysis often reveals opportunities to secure better rates for the same services. By doing this now, you can lock in savings for the entire next year.
Why are such savings possible? Primarily, increased competition and technological advancements. Previously, businesses were limited to local telephone companies for their communication needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing Bandwidth By Pair Bonding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</guid><description>When your T1 line starts reaching its bandwidth limit, upgrading to a DS3 line might seem like the next step, but it comes with challenges. DS3 often requires fiber optic cable instead of the copper used for T1, and the cost difference is significant.
A simpler solution for a moderate bandwidth boost is adding another T1 line and using &amp;ldquo;pair bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines two lines into one, effectively doubling your bandwidth to 3 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s The Best Business Internet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</guid><description>Is your new business in need of internet service for the first time, or does your existing business require better access? You might suspect you could be getting more for your money, and you&amp;rsquo;d probably be right. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the current business internet service options to determine the best fit for you.
The long-standing favored business internet connection for professionals has been the T1 line, recognized for its high reliability and consistent 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses currently using T1 lines for dedicated internet or point-to-point connections might be seeking ways to increase bandwidth without the high costs of upgrading to DS3 fiber optic cable. Metro Ethernet offers a solution. But how can you find it?
Locating Metro Ethernet service is straightforward with the right approach. Similar to finding anything else, the key is knowing where to look. A specialized tool designed to locate and map available Ethernet bandwidth in your vicinity is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Bandwidth is Cheap Downtown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</guid><description>Want to increase your business internet speed without breaking the bank? Head downtown! The city center offers more competition and cheaper prices than anywhere else. Can&amp;rsquo;t relocate for better bandwidth deals? There&amp;rsquo;s a comparable solution that works for many businesses.
Why is bandwidth cheaper downtown when real estate is so expensive? The answer is density. Imagine real estate as a pie: limited supply and high demand for the best slices drive up prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS1 Bandwidth vs Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</guid><description>DS1, commonly called T1, is a popular choice for business internet. This article will explain DS1 and compare it to another popular option: Ethernet over Copper.
While the terms are often used synonymously, DS1 and T1 are slightly different. They both come from a set of technical standards created by Bell Labs called the T-carrier system, which was originally a digital replacement for analog phone lines. Though designed for telephones, DS1 and T1 are now widely used for dedicated internet connections and private lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Cost Reduction Ideas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</guid><description>Getting the best price on everything your business buys is crucial for success, and bandwidth is no exception. Telecom expenses can be significant, but there are ways to save without sacrificing productivity.
One surprisingly simple step is to get updated competitive quotes. Bandwidth prices change rapidly, so your current understanding might be outdated.
While gathering quotes used to be time-consuming, online tools like GeoQuote by Telarus have simplified the process. This automated engine collects pricing from various providers, delivering budgetary quotes for services like T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and Ethernet connections almost instantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP T1 Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been around for a long time, initially used by phone companies to carry multiple calls between their facilities. Eventually, businesses adopted them for their phone systems. When the Internet became widespread, T1 lines were adapted to serve as dedicated internet connections. This might seem odd given their history, but in today&amp;rsquo;s internet-centric world, T1 lines can indeed function as IP connections.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/) While T1 technology was originally designed for voice calls, the fundamental principle is that digital data is just a series of ones and zeros...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Embraces Ethernet over Copper to Reach Rural Business Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</guid><description>Qwest Communications, a leading telecom provider in the US, boasts a nationwide fiber optic network capable of transmitting data at 40 Gbps, with plans to upgrade to 100 Gbps. While this caters to large enterprises requiring substantial bandwidth, what options are available for remotely located businesses?
Remote offices, even those belonging to large corporations, often face challenges justifying the cost of installing fiber optic cables due to their distance from carrier Points of Presence (POPs)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</guid><description>Metropolitan and Wide Area Networks can send your data anywhere you want. To access these networks, you need a connection known as &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connectivity. Ethernet offers advantages for this first mile link.
Several technologies, such as T1 lines, DSL, SONET fiber optic services, and even microwave or 3G/4G wireless, work well for first mile connections. These options connect your building to your service provider or a gateway to their network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Copper Really Replace Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-copper-really-replace-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-copper-really-replace-fiber/</guid><description>Advancements in telecommunications technology consistently push for increased bandwidth. While twisted pair copper wiring has been the backbone of telecom services since the invention of the telephone, its limitations have become apparent with the demand for higher bandwidths.
Is it possible that copper pair wiring could compete with fiber optic transmission for bandwidths exceeding 1.5 Mbps or support telephone trunks with more than 24 lines? Surprisingly, it can, and the technology is currently available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-copper-really-replace-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-copper-really-replace-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps to 6 Mbps Bonded Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</guid><description>Reliable and fast business internet access is crucial for customer interaction and order processing. While you aim for a stable connection with sufficient bandwidth, you also need a budget-friendly option. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to incrementally boost your internet speed in line with your business requirements.
](http://www.T1Rex.com/)
Dedicated internet access used to be limited to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line or a 45 Mbps T3 line (DS3 bandwidth). Shared bandwidth services offer more choices, but their performance and availability can fluctuate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Data Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</guid><description>While traditional data services rely on technologies like T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, OC-3, SONET fiber optics, Frame Relay, and MPLS networks for connectivity, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a modern alternative for the last mile. Although not available coast-to-coast, EoC provides a cost-effective, high-performance solution, especially for connecting businesses to larger private or public networks.
EoC leverages existing copper infrastructure, eliminating the need for costly fiber optic installations or dealing with line-of-sight issues encountered with fixed wireless solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper While Waiting For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</guid><description>Fiber optic connections are the optimal choice for high bandwidth, offering speeds from 10 Mbps to 10 Gbps using either SONET or Carrier Ethernet protocols. However, accessing these options requires &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber service, which can take several months or more due to potential construction delays. So, how do you maintain connectivity in the meantime?
While waiting for fiber activation was once the only option, many carriers now offer a two-stage solution for businesses needing immediate bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Business-grade Carrier Ethernet services are gaining popularity. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about Ethernet and its potential benefits, read on.
Ethernet dominates as a LAN protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable how quickly it outpaced competitors. Switched Ethernet is nearly ubiquitous. A similar shift is happening with telecom services, moving from traditional circuit-switched technologies to packet-switched networks that align better with modern devices. Ethernet is poised to become the standard for both metropolitan and long-distance networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoC and EoTDM Complement Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:35:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a significant disparity in bandwidth offered by traditional telecom services, particularly between smaller businesses and large corporations. Smaller businesses often rely on slower T1 lines (1.5 Mbps), while larger corporations enjoy significantly faster speeds (100-1000 times faster) through fiber optic connections.
However, technologies like Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and Ethernet over TDM (EoTDM) are bridging this gap by enabling a broader range of bandwidths on existing copper infrastructure. This allows for a smoother transition between T1 speeds and gigabit or even higher speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Distance Sensitivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</guid><description>The arrival of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers businesses a range of bandwidth options previously unavailable without fiber optic connections. EoC surpasses the speed limits of traditional T1 lines, provides easy scalability, and often comes at a lower price point, making it an attractive option for businesses seeking robust internet solutions.
However, a few limitations hinder the widespread use of EoC. Firstly, it requires compatible equipment at the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office (CO), where your copper lines terminate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Combine T1 Lines For Higher Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a popular choice for small and medium-sized businesses for many years due to their reliability, security, dedicated bandwidth, and accessibility. While their affordability has increased in recent years, their speed has remained a limitation. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution to overcome this without sacrificing the benefits of T1 technology: bonding.
Bonding is a standard industry technique that allows you to combine the bandwidth of multiple T1 lines. This effectively merges them into a single, faster connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10x10 Mbps Ethernet Providers in Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many believe that 10 Mbps Ethernet is replacing traditional T1 lines, and for good reason. This article will explore why that is, how this technology works, and the steps to upgrade.
Businesses have relied on T1 lines for decades due to their high reliability, guaranteed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps, and symmetrical upload and download speeds. Prices have also decreased over time, and availability is now widespread.
The main drawback of T1 lines is their limited bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Flavors of Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting your business to the internet is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world. It&amp;rsquo;s practically impossible to operate without a broadband connection. Customers, cloud services, backups, suppliers, and even connections to home offices or remote locations rely on it. The question is, how can you establish the best connection for your business?
Businesses have numerous options for internet service, but the variety can be overwhelming. Choosing the cheapest option might leave you frustrated if it can&amp;rsquo;t handle your needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 and EoC When There Is No Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</guid><description>The future of business undoubtedly lies in fiber optic bandwidth, particularly given the surge in video content and the increasing shift towards cloud computing. While copper infrastructure is still prevalent, it is gradually becoming outdated. So, how can businesses adapt during this transitional period?
One practical approach is to maximize the use of existing copper infrastructure while it remains viable. Many assume that relying on copper limits bandwidth, but this is not necessarily true...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Communications Ups the Ante on Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</guid><description>A major telecommunications provider is expanding its Metro Ethernet services, offering businesses more options for high-bandwidth connectivity. This provider leverages its vast fiber optic network, numerous points of presence, and advanced Ethernet over Copper technology to make Ethernet an even more attractive option for Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.
Why is Ethernet so important? It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a natural progression for network technology that businesses of all sizes already rely on. This means Metro Ethernet provides a nearly effortless solution for connecting various locations, effectively unifying them under a single network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrated Access Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>T1 lines can be used for broadband data or digital phone lines. However, needing separate lines for voice and data was expensive for smaller businesses. Integrated T1 offered a solution by combining voice and data on a single line, proving cost-effective for a while. But now, Integrated Access using Ethernet over Copper is an even better option.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a strong competitor to T1 lines. Both use existing copper telephone wiring, offering reliability and dedicated bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LAN to WAN Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard protocol for local area networks (LANs), but connecting beyond a single location requires a way to bridge the gap to wide area network (WAN) technologies. Traditionally, this meant converting between protocols, which was inefficient. However, Metro and Carrier Ethernet connections now offer a seamless way to link LANs and WANs.
Packet-based networks, especially those using IP, benefit significantly from using the same technology across the entire network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Takes Over, Mbps Prices Fall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/</guid><description>The current economic slump is causing a major shift in the telecommunications industry. While it may seem like a downturn, it&amp;rsquo;s actually creating opportunities for new technologies to emerge, replacing traditional telephone systems with IP-based Ethernet connections.
What&amp;rsquo;s behind this transformation? Surprisingly, it&amp;rsquo;s the high cost of doing business. Although some companies are downsizing, others are seeking better network services at lower costs. As their contracts expire, these businesses are exploring the market for competitive deals, looking beyond just pricing to consider newer technologies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-takes-over-mbps-prices-fall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Beefs Up Last Mile Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</guid><description>The main obstacle for companies aiming to boost their WAN (Wide Area Network) bandwidth is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; access problem. Although network bandwidth has become more affordable and easier to access, the final connection between a business and the carrier&amp;rsquo;s network often poses a significant challenge.
Think of it this way: a superhighway might be close to your company, but if the only route to your facility is a rough, narrow road, transportation will be slow and limited...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Rising Rapidly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</guid><description>Enhanced business environments and productivity gains through automation are pushing businesses towards higher bandwidth network solutions. Instead of simply increasing their current T1 or other line services, smart managers are exploring new technology that delivers more bandwidth at a lower cost. Ethernet over Copper is emerging as a leading WAN network service.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a straightforward concept: it&amp;rsquo;s an Ethernet service delivered through existing twisted pair copper wiring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Covad and ADTRAN Make Everything Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</guid><description>The arrival of Carrier Ethernet is generating considerable excitement around IP core networks and Ethernet access solutions. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean traditional TDM services are obsolete. DS1 and DS3 circuits can be adapted for Ethernet transport with the right equipment, as demonstrated by Carrier Covad and equipment manufacturer ADTRAN.
Covad is expanding its Ethernet service area using ADTRAN&amp;rsquo;s central office and network termination equipment. With a nationwide core network, Covad serves 44 states and 235 major markets, specializing in business DSL, data T1, fixed wireless, bonded T1, and integrated voice and data solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>If you need a significant bandwidth upgrade but find traditional options limited or excessively expensive, consider 20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper (EoC). This technology delivers a symmetrical 20 Mbps upload and download speed over readily available twisted pair copper cable.
This professional-grade service provides dedicated, full-duplex bandwidth, allowing simultaneous uploads and downloads at maximum speed. In contrast, T1 lines offer a base speed of 1.5 Mbps and require bonding multiple lines to achieve higher bandwidth, becoming cost-prohibitive beyond 10-12 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Lifesaver</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</guid><description>Imagine your company facing a critical situation. It&amp;rsquo;s growing, and you need more bandwidth than your reliable T1 line can offer. Upgrading to DS3 seems logical, but your provider can only offer a limited increase, nowhere near the 25 or 50 Mbps you require. They suggest fiber optic service, but your location lacks it, meaning months of waiting and a hefty construction bill.
This presents a difficult choice: secure funding and wait for fiber installation, or relocate to a fiber-ready area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Connection Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</guid><description>Businesses require internet access for both customer communication and internal operations. Unlike residential internet, business connections demand higher reliability because downtime directly translates to financial losses, especially for online businesses. Cost-effectiveness is also crucial.
Ethernet Internet is a relatively new technology that offers advantages in both cost and reliability. Additionally, it may provide bandwidth options previously unavailable in your area. A quick search with this Ethernet Internet Finder can reveal your options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing T1 Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</guid><description>For decades, T1 lines have been the standard for business network connections, offering ample bandwidth initially. However, like computer advancements, what was sufficient before is now inadequate. While upgrading to fiber is an option, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only solution.
Many companies opt for the traditional upgrade path from T1 (1.5 Mbps) to T3 (45 Mbps) speeds. This offers a significant speed increase at a premium, though T3 costs have decreased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper First, Then Fiber Bandwidth Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</guid><description>When your business needs a fast internet connection but fiber optic installation isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible yet, there&amp;rsquo;s a two-step solution that uses existing technology as a stopgap. This method combines the strengths of different connection types to get you online quickly and upgrade seamlessly later on.
Fiber optic connections, whether SONET or Ethernet, provide the highest bandwidth– starting from 50-100 Mbps and reaching up to 10 Gbps or even higher in some areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cable, T1 and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have three primary broadband options today: Cable, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper (EoC). While their costs are relatively similar, each offers distinct advantages. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options further.
T1 lines, a long-standing choice for SMBs, utilize half-century-old telephone industry technology. This technology transmits digital signals across standard copper telephone wiring. A T1 line consists of two copper pairs, one for uploads and the other for downloads, achieving a consistent speed of 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity Expansion With Multiple T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 22:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</guid><description>For many years, T1 lines have been a reliable network connection, especially when bandwidth demands are low. However, with increasing bandwidth requirements exceeding 1.5 Mbps, upgrading from the traditional T1 line becomes necessary.
One solution to increase bandwidth without abandoning existing T1 lines is &amp;ldquo;bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines the capacity of multiple T1 lines, effectively creating a single, faster connection. A managed router with multiple interface cards connects and manages the combined bandwidth from the T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Growing By Leaps and Bounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</guid><description>The hottest new access network service is Ethernet over Copper (EoC), with competitive carriers rushing to expand coverage.
What makes EoC so popular? It stems from evolving network needs. Wide Area Networks (WANs) have been dominated by the telephone industry, adapting phone technology for data and video transmission.
T1 lines, using two pairs of copper telephone wires, have been the standard for businesses needing dedicated Ethernet connections. They offer 1.5 Mbps upload and download speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoC Takes On Fractional DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</guid><description>Prior to the widespread adoption of Carrier Ethernet, businesses seeking increased bandwidth from T1 lines faced two primary options: upgrading to T3/DS3 for a substantial leap in capacity, or incrementally combining multiple T1 lines through bonding. However, the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative for dedicated bandwidth.
T1 lines gained popularity due to their accessibility and sufficient bandwidth for smaller businesses or specialized applications within larger organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Now Faster and Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>For a long time, T1 lines have been the top choice for bandwidth for small and medium businesses. They are popular for good reason: they are widely available, reliable, secure, dedicated, adaptable, and relatively affordable.
While T1 services have many advantages, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get even more value: Ethernet, particularly Ethernet over Copper.
Many people are not familiar with Carrier Ethernet services, as they have only become available recently. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is primarily found in large cities, as it has a limited reach and requires businesses to be within a few miles of the provider&amp;rsquo;s office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated Internet Access Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 02:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes now have near-universal access to broadband internet. However, are you utilizing the optimal internet connection for your needs? It might be time to consider Ethernet.
Metro Ethernet Networks are rapidly expanding and provide significant benefits to businesses. Cost savings are a key advantage, potentially cutting your internet bandwidth expenses by half or more compared to your current solution. This significant cost reduction comes without compromising reliability or dedicated bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 is Your Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While metropolitan areas have many choices for broadband internet, rural areas often only have access to limited options like mobile 4G or satellite internet. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option that is often overlooked but may be a perfect fit for rural businesses and remote work: T1 dedicated internet access.
T1 is Everywhere T1 lines are widely available, often wherever standard phone lines exist. This is because T1 utilizes the same copper wiring infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Ethernet Line Prices Instantly!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-ethernet-line-prices-instantly-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 22:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-ethernet-line-prices-instantly-/</guid><description>Businesses are increasingly choosing Ethernet over Copper (EoC) for its impressive bandwidth and affordability. If EoC is an option, its value proposition is quite compelling. Curious about the specifics? You can easily find out how much bandwidth is available and the potential cost savings. Explore current Ethernet over Copper prices instantly!
Thanks to the Telarus GeoQuote automated pricing system, you can receive immediate Ethernet quotes whenever you need them. Simply input your information on the user-friendly form at CopperEthernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-ethernet-line-prices-instantly-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-ethernet-line-prices-instantly-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs T1 in Under 3 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Ethernet bandwidth services are generating a lot of interest, but are they truly superior to traditional T1 lines? Is switching from copper to fiber a wise decision financially? This brief comparison of Ethernet and T1 services will provide clarity.
Interested in determining which connectivity and hosted services best meet your business needs? Get instant pricing and availability for Ethernet, T1, and other connectivity options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trade In Your T1 Line For 10 Mbps Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-in-your-t1-line-for-10-mbps-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-in-your-t1-line-for-10-mbps-ethernet/</guid><description>If your T1 line contract is expiring soon or has already ended and you&amp;rsquo;re on a month-to-month plan, don&amp;rsquo;t rush to renew. You might be able to obtain a 10 Mbps Ethernet connection for the same price.
It might seem implausible to get 10 Mbps for the price of 1.5 Mbps at the same location, given that business telecom pricing is based on bandwidth and distance. However, due to recent advancements in the telecommunications industry, many businesses can upgrade from their outdated T1 services to significantly faster options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-in-your-t1-line-for-10-mbps-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-in-your-t1-line-for-10-mbps-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Speeds Without DS3 Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</guid><description>Businesses needing substantial bandwidth for tasks like online commerce, video streaming, medical data transfer, or dedicated internet access have historically relied on DS3 connections. These provided speeds exceeding T1 lines. However, a new option delivers comparable speeds without the high price tag: Metro Ethernet and Carrier Ethernet.
These terms represent regional and long-distance high-bandwidth transport services using the Ethernet protocol. An Ethernet WAN connection connects your LAN to another business location, a network of multiple locations, or a dedicated high-speed internet connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Service Access For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</guid><description>Having internet access is essential for businesses today, whether they operate primarily online or from a physical location. It&amp;rsquo;s how businesses connect with customers, suppliers, remote employees, and even their own offices. But is the internet service used by businesses the same as what individuals use at home?
There are actually different options for internet service, each with unique features: dedicated or shared bandwidth, symmetrical or asymmetrical speeds, wired or wireless connection, copper or fiber optic cables, and varying levels of bandwidth and cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Speed Challenged By EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</guid><description>When a company needs more bandwidth than its T1 lines can provide, the typical upgrade has been to DS3. However, DS3 is usually delivered through fiber optic SONET connections, which can be costly to install unless a building is already equipped for fiber optic services. A new service called EoC offers a potential solution by providing DS3 speeds over existing copper telephone wiring.
EoC stands for Ethernet over Copper. It delivers high bandwidth services, up to DS3 levels of 45 Mbps, without needing fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard about Metro Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s rise in popularity for business WAN connections, particularly in major cities with concentrated business areas. These areas have been the primary focus of competitive bandwidth providers offering lower per-Mbps pricing. However, you might assume that Ethernet WAN services are only accessible in downtown areas or large suburbs.
This is about to change. Hatteras Networks has introduced a line of repeater and line power modules that extend Mid-Band Ethernet service up to 25 miles over standard telephone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs EoC vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</guid><description>Not long ago, businesses seeking a dedicated, symmetrical bandwidth line had only one option: T1. However, the landscape has changed with the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and SIP Trunks. While options like DSL, Cable, satellite, and 3G wireless offer shared and asymmetrical bandwidth, and DS3, SONET, and Ethernet over Fiber provide higher bandwidths at higher costs, they fall outside the scope of this comparison.
Similar to their copper-based counterparts, Ethernet over Fiber, DS3, and SONET are higher bandwidth alternatives to EoC, T1, and SIP Trunks, respectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Bonding Buys Breathing Room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</guid><description>Businesses often face the challenge of needing more resources, like network bandwidth, without the budget to acquire them. This is particularly true for WAN bandwidth. Companies often start with a modest plan, assuming they can upgrade when demand (and revenue) increase. However, in times of economic uncertainty, business activity might grow while revenue lags. So how can businesses meet their needs without overspending?
One solution is incrementalism, specifically &amp;ldquo;just in time&amp;rdquo; incrementalism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Pushes EoC to 400 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services are constantly achieving higher bandwidth capacities, making businesses reconsider the need for fiber optic installations. MegaPath, for example, now offers EoC speeds up to 400 Mbps.
Many companies use EoC as a cost-effective alternative to T1 lines, obtaining double the bandwidth at the same price. Options like 2x2 Mbps and 3x3 Mbps are particularly favored. Others transition to mid-band Ethernet, offering 10 to 20 Mbps, which exceeds bonded T1 capabilities and suits mid-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Believe 200 Mbps EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a widely used technology that delivers mid-band Ethernet connections without the delays and costs of fiber optic installation. Although initially considered a temporary solution, EoC has become a strong competitor to fiber services.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/)Businesses currently using T1 lines or considering them are a key market for EoC. T1 is a well-established, dependable, and cost-effective telecom service that offers 1.5 Mbps using one or two pairs of twisted copper telephone wiring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Copper 50 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</guid><description>Businesses that need to connect numerous employees to the internet or move large files, particularly high-resolution images, require more bandwidth than a standard connection provides. Traditionally, they&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded their T1 lines to DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. Now, there are more choices for around 50 Mbps using both copper and fiber optic connections.
DS3 is often considered a copper wireline service because it connects with coaxial cables and uses BNC connectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth For Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</guid><description>Contrary to popular belief, Ethernet WAN service isn&amp;rsquo;t confined to cities. There are ways to get Ethernet connectivity even in rural areas.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity among small and medium businesses. It uses existing telephone wiring to deliver Ethernet speeds from 3 to 50 Mbps, and even over 100 Mbps in some places. This makes it a cost-effective option for businesses that need high bandwidth. However, EoC has distance limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</guid><description>Traditional business bandwidth solutions, typically offering low to moderate speeds, have long relied on T1 lines and their bonded counterparts. However, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) solutions are rapidly replacing these older technologies, delivering enhanced bandwidth at a lower cost.
We&amp;rsquo;re focusing on services ranging from 1 to 20 Mbps, encompassing both dedicated point-to-point private lines and dedicated internet connections. Ethernet standards also enable private LAN services, facilitating connections between multiple business locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>