<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SPD on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spd/</link><description>Recent content in SPD on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customize SPD paper and electronic greeting cards with your own branding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</guid><description>Source: SPD website.
The SPD, a Singaporean organization supporting individuals with disabilities, operates a supported employment facility that creates physical and digital greeting cards. These cards are suitable for various events like birthdays and holidays such as Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, and Chinese New Year.
Customization options are available for these cards, including adding company branding, personalized notes, or designs for other special events.
Interested parties can explore the complete selection of cards on the SPD e-shop.</description></item><item><title>Helping individuals with disabilities transition from training programs to meaningful employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Individuals with disabilities should be placed in jobs where they can acquire skills on the job, rather than receiving training without a clear path to employment. Christy Lynch, CEO of KARE Ireland, an organization supporting individuals with intellectual disabilities and their families, emphasized the importance of collaborating with both individuals with disabilities and employers to create truly empowering opportunities. He spoke at the &amp;ldquo;Towards an Inclusive Workforce 2015&amp;rdquo; event, co-organized by SPD and supported by SG Enable and the Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA).</description></item></channel></rss>