<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-fiber-optic-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Business Fiber Optic Connections on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-fiber-optic-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>