<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2in1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2in1/</link><description>Recent content in 2in1 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2in1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The HP 2 in 1 printer is perfect for home offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new PC and printer designed for home offices.
The HP Pavilion x2, available in Singapore starting in October from S$499, offers a stylish and practical solution. This versatile device functions as a 10-inch Windows tablet and easily transforms into a fully functional laptop. It features a detachable magnetic keyboard cover that doubles as both a screen protector and a multi-position stand. Equipped with an Intel Atom processor, the Pavilion x2 boasts front-facing speakers with DTS sound and a battery life of up to 11.</description></item><item><title>Dell introduces an improved range of PCs for both consumer and commercial markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</guid><description>Dell debuted groundbreaking personal computing innovations at the annual Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in the US. They also updated their XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware consumer lines. Their OptiPlex, Latitude, and Precision commercial products received upgrades to 7th Gen Intel Core processors, USB-C with Thunderbolt 3 connectivity, and new professional graphics from NVIDIA and AMD. Dell&amp;rsquo;s monitor lineup also saw a refresh. The new Dell PC portfolio is equipped with Windows 10 and 7th Gen Intel Core processors, designed to maximize user productivity and creativity.</description></item><item><title>Acer unveils three convertible notebooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</guid><description>Acer has expanded its line of 2-in-1 notebooks with the new 11.6&amp;quot; Aspire Switch 11 series and a new Switch 10 featuring a 1080p Full HD 10.1&amp;quot; display. The Aspire Switch 2-in-1 series combines a Microsoft Windows notebook and tablet in one device.
Source: Acer. The Aspire Switch 10.
The Aspire Switch series is thin, lightweight, and durable, designed for work and travel. It supports four modes: touch, typing, viewing, and sharing.</description></item></channel></rss>