<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Schengen Visa on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/schengen-visa/</link><description>Recent content in Schengen Visa on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:12:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/schengen-visa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the EU visa policy driving growth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-visa-policy-driving-growth/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s visa policy has traditionally focused on managing illegal immigration and security threats while considering foreign policy goals. However, in recent years, promoting economic growth, particularly in the tourism sector, has become increasingly important. This shift, initiated by a 2012 Commission communication, is evident in recent updates to the EU&amp;rsquo;s visa &amp;lsquo;whitelist&amp;rsquo;. The criteria for visa liberalization now include trade and investment, leading to the inclusion of Peru and Colombia after they signed a trade agreement with the EU.</description></item><item><title>Farewell, harsh world: will there be visas for holidays post-Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Previously, I maintained that British citizens needing visas for short trips to the EU after Brexit was highly unlikely. I even disagreed with some &amp;ldquo;Remain&amp;rdquo; supporters who feared this outcome. The EU consistently lifts short-term visa requirements for wealthy nations (like the USA, Canada, and Japan) if they reciprocate for EU citizens. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t envision those on the &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; side supporting short-term visa requirements for EU citizens visiting the UK post-Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Updating the visa policy of the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
In 2014, the European Commission put forward a proposal to update the EU&amp;rsquo;s visa policy for short-term visits by revising the existing Visa Code. This proposal ultimately stalled due to disagreements between the European Parliament and the Council on whether or not to incorporate &amp;ldquo;safe passage&amp;rdquo; visas for individuals requiring protection. Currently, the Commission is revisiting this issue, this time prioritizing security concerns rather than economic benefits.</description></item></channel></rss>