<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip/</link><description>Recent content in SIP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buy Convergence By The Byte</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</guid><description>XO Communications is revolutionizing telecommunications by offering IP Network services priced by bandwidth usage instead of traditional lines or channels. This shift to an IP-based network and the use of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for telephone trunking are rendering traditional telephony services obsolete. By utilizing a packet-switched network and transmitting everything in packet protocol, voice, and data traffic can easily share a single circuit.
The concept of convergence, using one network for voice, video, and data, has gained traction with IT departments aiming to simplify network management and executives seeking cost reductions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</a></p></description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs EoC vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</guid><description>Not long ago, businesses seeking a dedicated, symmetrical bandwidth line had only one option: T1. However, the landscape has changed with the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and SIP Trunks. While options like DSL, Cable, satellite, and 3G wireless offer shared and asymmetrical bandwidth, and DS3, SONET, and Ethernet over Fiber provide higher bandwidths at higher costs, they fall outside the scope of this comparison.
Similar to their copper-based counterparts, Ethernet over Fiber, DS3, and SONET are higher bandwidth alternatives to EoC, T1, and SIP Trunks, respectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Analog Telephone Adaptor Enables VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</guid><description>Analog Telephone Adapters (ATAs) bridge the gap between traditional analog phones and Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) technology. They essentially trick both the phone and the internet connection into thinking they&amp;rsquo;re interacting with familiar systems.
On one side, the ATA connects to a regular phone using a standard RJ-11 jack, providing the necessary power and signals like dial tone and caller ID. It also translates the phone&amp;rsquo;s touch-tone signals into a digital format for VoIP communication using the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>