<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise Telephony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/enterprise-telephony/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise Telephony on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/enterprise-telephony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SIP Trunks vs ISDN PRI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses have moved past analog phone lines, embracing PBX systems and ISDN PRI for their communication needs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: SIP Trunking. This technology offers potential cost and performance benefits for companies looking to enhance their voice services. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SIP Trunks with ISDN PRI to understand the best choice for your organization.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that both technologies rely on digital telephony, eliminating analog transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Voice over MPLS For High Quality Enterprise Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations are realizing the financial and operational benefits of MPLS networks. MPLS VPNs are emerging as the go-to solution for connecting multiple sites nationally and globally. But what about voice services?
Traditionally, voice and data are kept separate. Telephone systems rely on a proven infrastructure of switched circuit analog and digital trunking. Most PBX systems are designed to connect to standard copper-pair analog business lines or ISDN PRI digital trunks, which act as gateways to the global PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) connecting every phone on Earth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>