<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Xiaomi on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/xiaomi/</link><description>Recent content in Xiaomi on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:33:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/xiaomi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Xiaomi's latest flagship smartphone is the MIX Fold 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:33:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xiaomi-s-latest-flagship-smartphone-is-the-mix-fold-2/</guid><description>Source: Xiaomi. The MIX Fold 2 is available in Black and Gold colourways.
Xiaomi recently debuted its most advanced foldable phone, the Xiaomi MIX Fold 2, in Mainland China. The company also introduced the Xiaomi Pad 5 Pro, Redmi K50 Ultra, and a variety of other ecosystem devices.
When unfolded, the Xiaomi MIX Fold 2 measures a mere 5.4mm1, providing a seamless viewing experience across its inner and outer screens.</description></item><item><title>Check Point has discovered a vulnerability in a preinstalled app on Xiaomi devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</guid><description>Slava Makkaveev, a researcher from cybersecurity firm Check Point Software, recently discovered a concerning security flaw in Xiaomi phones.
This vulnerability was found within the pre-installed &amp;ldquo;Guard Provider&amp;rdquo; app (com.miui.guardprovider), designed to identify malware. Ironically, this app could allow attackers on the same Wi-Fi network to perform a man-in-the-middle (MiTM) attack. This type of attack enables the interception and copying of data transmitted between the phone and online services.
Furthermore, by exploiting a third-party software development kit (SDK) update mechanism, attackers could potentially disable malware protection and inject malicious code.</description></item><item><title>Less expensive smartphones are available for those in developing markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</guid><description>To prepare for future growth, smartphone manufacturers are looking beyond China to other emerging markets. Although China represented a third of global smartphone shipments in 2013, the International Data Corporation (IDC) indicates this market is reaching its saturation point.
IDC reports that smartphones constitute over 80% of China&amp;rsquo;s total phone sales. Consequently, they predict that India and Africa will be the primary sources of the next half billion smartphone customers.</description></item><item><title>The Xiaomi 13 Series makes its debut in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-xiaomi-13-series-makes-its-debut-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 05:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-xiaomi-13-series-makes-its-debut-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Xiaomi Singapore. Pictured are the Xiaomi 13 Series phones (from left): Xiaomi 13 in white, Xiaomi 13 in Flora Green, and Xiaomi 13 in black.
Xiaomi launched its latest top-tier smartphone series, the Xiaomi 13 Series, in Singapore. The Xiaomi 13 and Xiaomi 13 Pro are the result of a collaboration with Leica, aiming to redefine the smartphone photography landscape for users in Singapore.
Developed in partnership with Leica, these flagship phones boast a triple camera system featuring Leica&amp;rsquo;s professional-grade lenses.</description></item></channel></rss>