<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BlackBerry on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blackberry/</link><description>Recent content in BlackBerry on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blackberry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer.</description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission.</description></item><item><title>It’s Free Phones Time For The Holidays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 15:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-free-phones-time-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>The holiday season is about to start, and many people will rush to buy things like new smartphones. But before you spend a lot of money, consider getting a free phone.
You can find free phones by using a special search engine that focuses on phones offered for free when you sign up for a new service contract. You can find this search engine at Cell Phone Plan Finder.
You might think these free phones are outdated models.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday Cell Phone Deals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</guid><description>The best deals on cell phones can be found online, especially during sales like Cyber Monday. These limited-time offers on free and discounted phones are valid until midnight today, Monday.
For a limited time, get a free BlackBerry Bold 9700 for AT&amp;amp;T after an instant online discount. This offer includes a bonus of free activation for up to five lines, making it perfect for family plans.
Prefer a different BlackBerry? The BlackBerry Curve in Titanium or silver is also available.</description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>How BlackBerry Touch Screen Technology Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</guid><description>The BlackBerry Storm is a unique addition to the BlackBerry lineup, featuring a touch screen instead of the traditional physical QWERTY keyboard. Though the keyboard is now virtual, it still aims to provide a tactile experience.
Why this change? Primarily, to accommodate a larger display screen without increasing the phone&amp;rsquo;s overall size. To achieve this, the physical keyboard was removed, leaving only essential call, menu, and navigation buttons below the screen.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Picking On Cyber Monday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</guid><description>Similar to how Black Friday has become a tradition for in-person shopping, Cyber Monday is now the time for finding exceptional online deals. With that in mind, let&amp;rsquo;s explore a standout product line this year: BlackBerry devices from Research in Motion.
Business users have long favored BlackBerry for mobile communication. RIM has prioritized supporting corporate IT with the performance and security needed for serious business use on the go. But how affordable are these popular BlackBerry models?</description></item><item><title>Recycle Your BlackBerry Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-blackberry-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-blackberry-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You can make money off your old BlackBerry phone instead of throwing it away. Even without a service plan, your old BlackBerry might be worth a significant amount of money depending on its model, age, and condition. Selling it yourself can be a hassle, but there&amp;rsquo;s an easier way.
An electronics recycling company will pay cash for used BlackBerry phones and other cell phone models. To see if yours qualifies, visit their website and search for your BlackBerry model.</description></item><item><title>Cheap Used Cell Phones For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 12:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</guid><description>Need a new cell phone but dread dealing with carriers and contracts? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Carrier stores are notorious for expensive phones and restrictive contracts. They might offer a &amp;ldquo;cheap&amp;rdquo; phone, but it comes with strings attached – usually a pricey new contract and limited model options.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been with your carrier long enough for an upgrade or prefer not to sign a new contract, carriers will charge full retail price for a new phone.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry introduces WatchDox by BlackBerry Email Protector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-introduces-watchdox-by-blackberry-email-protector/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 22:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-introduces-watchdox-by-blackberry-email-protector/</guid><description>BlackBerry has launched WatchDox by BlackBerry Email Protector, a new product designed to give businesses greater control over file security. This is achieved by incorporating digital rights management (DRM) at the file level for emails, ensuring protection beyond the company&amp;rsquo;s firewall.
WatchDox by BlackBerry is a comprehensive file management platform that facilitates file syncing and sharing across multiple operating systems. By integrating DRM security into individual files, the solution reduces the risks of data breaches.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Fun and Games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-fun-and-games/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 05:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-fun-and-games/</guid><description>Need a break from work? How about a quick game of Guitar Hero? Right on your BlackBerry! You don&amp;rsquo;t need your console for this. Choose your favorite guitar, character, and venue, and start rocking!
Yeah, you read that right – Guitar Hero on your BlackBerry. Not exactly ideal for a serious meeting, but perfect for when you&amp;rsquo;re off the clock. It&amp;rsquo;s your phone, customize it with whatever helps you unwind!</description></item></channel></rss>