<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>APAC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apac/</link><description>Recent content in APAC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, Singaporean small and medium-sized businesses are leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</guid><description>Source: Cisco ebook. This Cisco report, the APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, evaluates digital maturity based on four key aspects.
· Singaporean SMBs achieved the highest ranking on the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index.
· Cybersecurity is the primary technology that Singaporean SMBs are investing in, followed by cloud computing and analytics.
· The most significant challenges cited by SMBs across Singapore are a shortage of digital skills and talent within their organizations and a lack of understanding of operational and customer data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There was a significant increase in early-stage M&amp;A activity in the APAC region during the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>The Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor, which forecasts future merger and acquisition (M&amp;amp;A) announcements, anticipates a 6% rise in the total number of global M&amp;amp;A deals announced in the first half of 2017 compared to the same period in 2016. This would establish a new record for global announced deals in the first six months of a year.
The Asia Pacific (APAC) region leads in early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity, demonstrating 44% year-over-year growth in the fourth quarter of 2016, and is positioned to significantly contribute to the projected record deal count in the first half of 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe: Consumer sentiment in the Asia-Pacific region remains positive in the middle of 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</guid><description>Even though many COVID-19 lockdown restrictions have been lifted globally, research from Adobe, presented at their Adobe Experience Makers Live event, reveals that the extended home confinement has significantly altered consumer shopping habits and brand interactions.
The research highlights how COVID-19 has impacted daily life, with nearly seven in ten consumers (67%) concerned about the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s overall impact, particularly regarding personal health (73%), job security (40%), and the economy (36%). Millennials (72%) expressed higher concern levels compared to Gen Z (58%), Boomers (62%), and Traditionalists (48%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Entries are now being accepted for the inaugural HUAWEI Film Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</guid><description>Filmmakers in the Asia Pacific region can win prizes for films made on Huawei smartphones.
The top prize includes $20,000 and a trip to Bangkok for the awards ceremony.
An event in Singapore on December 21 will showcase a film by local director Boris Boo.
Source: Huawei. Poster for the HFA.
Huawei has launched its first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), in the Asia Pacific region. The competition aims to encourage filmmakers and content creators to use Huawei smartphones to demonstrate their creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SAP reported that small and medium-sized enterprises in the Asia-Pacific region have adopted remote work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</guid><description>A recent study titled &amp;ldquo;Digital, Resilient, and Experience-driven: How Small and Midsize Organisations Can Prepare for the New Economy,&amp;rdquo; conducted by SAP in conjunction with Oxford Economics, reveals that small and mid-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the Asia-Pacific region are well-situated to flourish in the evolving business landscape following the COVID-19 pandemic.
The study, which surveyed 2,000 senior executives globally, including 832 from APAC countries like Singapore, Australia, and Japan, examined the priorities and digital readiness of SMEs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe aims to achieve the highest level of performance in order to increase repeat visits and online sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</guid><description>Source: Adobe.
Recent Adobe research indicates that marketers in the Asia Pacific region who use best practices are significantly outperforming their competitors.
The Adobe Digital Index Best of the Best Benchmark for Asia Pacific analyzed websites across six regions: Australia and New Zealand, Southeast Asia, India, South Korea, Hong Kong, and China, comparing the average website performance with the top 20% based on six key performance indicators: mobile and tablet traffic, stick rate, visits per visitor, time spent, and conversion rate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to a global survey by YouGov, body confidence increases with age</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 19:45:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</guid><description>A recent global survey by YouGov revealed that most adults feel content with their weight and body image, and this satisfaction generally increases with age. However, the survey also highlighted a widespread concern that celebrity culture negatively impacts young people&amp;rsquo;s body image across almost all countries surveyed.
The survey, spanning the US, Australia, and most of Europe and the Asia Pacific region, found that older individuals are considerably more likely to feel satisfied with their bodies compared to those in their twenties and thirties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>