<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-services/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional DS3 Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 23:40:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</guid><description>The most popular high-reliability broadband option for businesses, T1 lines, are widely accessible, budget-friendly for most small and medium-sized businesses, and come with various options like PBX telephone lines, dedicated internet, point-to-point electronic data interchange, and Integrated T1 (voice and data combined). The main issue with T1 service is the possibility of outgrowing its capacity.
T1 connections offer 1.5 Mbps full-duplex bandwidth, also known as symmetrical, for internet service, providing 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pricing Slashed For Michigan 100 Mbps Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</guid><description>Michigan businesses are facing a common problem: the need for faster internet speeds. Traditional options like T1 lines are no longer sufficient for handling increased data demands from video conferencing, cloud-based applications, and automation. While fiber optic services offer the necessary bandwidth, their high cost often makes them inaccessible.
Comcast Business Class emerges as a potential solution, delivering 100 Mbps download and 10 Mbps upload speeds at a price comparable to T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Getting Network Connections Into Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</guid><description>Although many businesses only require domestic WAN connections, a growing number are seeking global connectivity, particularly with European markets for financial trading, sales, and support. This raises the question of how US-based companies can establish cost-effective connections with Europe.
Fortunately, several carriers offer transatlantic connectivity to major European cities. Some US carriers have partnerships for traffic handover to European data centers, as illustrated by AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement with ancotel GmbH in Frankfurt, Germany...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Now Faster and Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>For a long time, T1 lines have been the top choice for bandwidth for small and medium businesses. They are popular for good reason: they are widely available, reliable, secure, dedicated, adaptable, and relatively affordable.
While T1 services have many advantages, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get even more value: Ethernet, particularly Ethernet over Copper.
Many people are not familiar with Carrier Ethernet services, as they have only become available recently. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is primarily found in large cities, as it has a limited reach and requires businesses to be within a few miles of the provider&amp;rsquo;s office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Double Bonded T1 Cost and Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 23:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</guid><description>Many businesses appreciate their reliable T1 service, but eventually, the 1.5 Mbps bandwidth becomes insufficient. Instead of abandoning T1, companies can opt for double bonded T1 service, which combines two lines to provide 3 Mbps. This bonding is implemented within customer premises equipment, usually a router with two T1 inputs.
The bandwidth can be further increased by triple bonding (4.5 Mbps) or quadruple bonding (6 Mbps), up to a practical limit of eight bonded lines for 12 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Believe 200 Mbps EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a widely used technology that delivers mid-band Ethernet connections without the delays and costs of fiber optic installation. Although initially considered a temporary solution, EoC has become a strong competitor to fiber services.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/)Businesses currently using T1 lines or considering them are a key market for EoC. T1 is a well-established, dependable, and cost-effective telecom service that offers 1.5 Mbps using one or two pairs of twisted copper telephone wiring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>