<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Garmin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/garmin/</link><description>Recent content in Garmin on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:07:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/garmin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Garmin unveils a new smartwatch with GPS and music capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-unveils-a-new-smartwatch-with-gps-and-music-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-unveils-a-new-smartwatch-with-gps-and-music-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Garmin.
The vivoactive 3 Music. Garmin Singapore has launched the vívoactive 3 Music, a GPS smartwatch that incorporates both music playback and Garmin Pay contactless payments. Users can make purchases directly from their wrist using their Garmin Pay wallet, enjoying the same benefits as their physical cards but with added convenience.
According to Jimmy Chuang, Regional Product Manager at Garmin, the company aims to make its products an integral part of everyday life, and they believe music is a key feature in achieving that goal.</description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day.</description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces three new fēnix 5 multisport GPS wearables</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-three-new-f-nix-5-multisport-gps-wearables/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-three-new-f-nix-5-multisport-gps-wearables/</guid><description>Source: Garmin. The fēnix 5 family of multisport GPS watches.
Garmin International has released the fēnix 5, fēnix 5S, and fēnix 5X multisport GPS watches. These wearables are designed for adventurers of all sizes.
Each fēnix 5 model offers 24/7 wearability, extended battery life, daily activity tracking*, Garmin Elevate wrist heart rate technology, and various connected features**. At 47mm, the fēnix 5 is more compact than past models like the fēnix 3HR, while still providing extensive multisport features.</description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces complimentary live services for 2017 Garmin Drive models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</guid><description>Garmin International has refreshed its Garmin Drive portable navigation device (PND) lineup with free live services* for the most up-to-date content and driver alerts to improve safety. These upgrades to the Garmin Drive, Garmin DriveSmart, Garmin DriveAssist, and Garmin DriveLuxe models show the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving PNDs.
The base model Garmin Drive 51/61 includes helpful driver alerts. The Garmin DriveSmart 51/61 adds smart features. The camera-equipped Garmin DriveAssist 51 is for recording drives, while the premium Garmin DriveLuxe 51 has an elegant metal design.</description></item></channel></rss>