<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Hosted Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-hosted-services/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Hosted Services on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-hosted-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve Cloud Performance With Direct Network Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many companies are experiencing buyer&amp;rsquo;s remorse after transitioning to the cloud. They expected cost savings, increased performance, and limitless resources, but instead, they&amp;rsquo;re facing performance issues. The problem likely isn&amp;rsquo;t the cloud service itself, but the connection used to access it.
While your current internet connection might be sufficient for tasks like file transfers and email, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for real-time applications like VoIP, video conferencing, or cloud-based software.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers.</description></item></channel></rss>