<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UHF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uhf/</link><description>Recent content in UHF on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 17:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uhf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Looking For Spectrum In All The White Spaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 17:51:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</guid><description>With the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction concluded, the wireless industry is feeling a sense of scarcity. All the valuable over-the-air spectrum, much like desirable beachfront property, has seemingly been claimed.
However, instead of viewing the spectrum as fully allocated, consider it as a landscape inhabited by powerful entities, like T-Rexes in the Cretaceous period. These dominant players, representing major TV stations, control their portions of the spectrum, leaving little room for newcomers.</description></item><item><title>White Spaces Debate Outs Wireless Mics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/white-spaces-debate-outs-wireless-mics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/white-spaces-debate-outs-wireless-mics/</guid><description>An unexpected result of the debate about the &amp;ldquo;white space&amp;rdquo; TV spectrum is the exposure of unauthorized wireless microphone users like churches, theaters, and conference rooms. Many have been using unused UHF TV channels undetected for years. They must now cease or face interference from the new owners of the 700 MHz spectrum when those services begin next February. Finding new channels by simply re-tuning is becoming less feasible.
Wireless microphones have become increasingly common in any situation involving vocal performance, from televised concerts to news shows and Broadway plays.</description></item></channel></rss>