<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Public on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/public/</link><description>Recent content in Public on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KSA is progressing with the privatization process</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</guid><description>The National Center for Privatization &amp;amp; PPP (NCP) is a new Saudi Arabian agency created to empower the nation&amp;rsquo;s private sector. Along with Supervisory Committees (SCs) established to oversee each privatization sector, the NCP will manage the transfer of government assets to private ownership.
Formed in April 2017 by the Council of Ministers, the NCP and the SCs are the first of their kind in the Middle East and North Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verify the authenticity of KSA sales and promotions using this app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</guid><description>Source: MCI. HE the Minister of Commerce and Investment Dr Majid bin Abdullah Al Qasabi launched the Sales app on 31 January 2017.
The Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) in Saudi Arabia has introduced a mobile application called &amp;ldquo;Sales.&amp;rdquo; This app allows the public to access the MCI&amp;rsquo;s database of authorized sales and promotional offers. The goal is to help users find genuine deals and discounts quickly.
Through the app, consumers can browse information on more than 27,000 retail locations and over 700,000 licensed products registered with the MCI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2023 goals of Singapore's Digital Government Blueprint are outlined</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</guid><description>Source: GovTech Singapore website.
Infographic, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s _Digital
Government Blueprint. _
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Deputy Prime Minister, Teo Chee Hean, who also oversees National Security, recently introduced the Digital Government Blueprint (DGB) at the Smart Nation Innovations Week Opening Symposium. This blueprint outlines the government&amp;rsquo;s goal to utilize data and emerging technologies to enhance services for citizens, businesses, and public officials. It also aims to foster a digital economy and society, aligning with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation vision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>