<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellular Data on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-data/</link><description>Recent content in Cellular Data on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables.</description></item><item><title>iPhone Getting its Video in a Sling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</guid><description>The mobile video landscape is seeing growth in various forms, including carrier-specific services like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s VCAST and Sprint TV, and dedicated channels such as MediaFLO. Sling Media&amp;rsquo;s introduction of a SlingPlayer for iPhone has the potential to disrupt the market by giving control of content back to the user.
Sling Media is known for its Slingbox, a device that connects to your television source (satellite receiver, DVR, or cable box) and a broadband connection.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile 3G Aircard For PC and Mac</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</guid><description>Want to connect your laptop to T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s 3G network and get free access to their HotSpots? The T-Mobile webConnect USB Laptop Stick can make that happen.
This device is a wireless modem with a USB connector that plugs into your PC or Mac. PCs require Windows XP or Vista, while Macs need OS X 10.3.9 or higher.
This aircard provides internet access virtually anywhere in the U.S. with T-Mobile cellular coverage.</description></item></channel></rss>