<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Central on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/central/</link><description>Recent content in Central on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Join us at Smile Singapore in Clarke Quay Central and share your beautiful smile with us!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</guid><description>The installation of the Smile project at Clarke Quay Central is currently underway.
Clarke Quay Central mall is promoting a happier Singapore with its Smile Singapore campaign. Launched as part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Jubilee celebrations, this project gives companies a platform to share their happy moments in the nation.
Caine Teo, head of Ape Works, the Creative Partner of the Smile Singapore Campaign, believes happiness is infectious. By showcasing pictures of smiling faces, they hope to remind Singaporeans of the many reasons to smile in their country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-smile-singapore-in-clarke-quay-central-and-share-your-beautiful-smile-with-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UAE Central Bank has introduced raised marks on certain currency notes to assist individuals with visual impairments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</guid><description>The Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates has introduced new AED1,000, AED20, and AED10 banknotes featuring raised tactile marks designed to assist people with visual impairments, according to the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
These new banknotes incorporate tactile elements created using the intaglio printing method on their widths. The AED1,000 note now includes two sets of four horizontal lines, evenly spaced, on both the left and right edges.
Similarly, the AED20 denomination features three distinct horizontal lines in the same position, while the AED10 denomination has two...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pottinger Hong Kong is now open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</guid><description>Sino Group, a hospitality branch of Sino Land Company, manages various properties including hotels, a yacht club, serviced apartments, and residential dining establishments. They have recently introduced The Pottinger Hong Kong, a luxurious 68-room boutique hotel. Situated on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s oldest paved street, the hotel holds a notable position on a site recognized as a Grade I historic place by the Antiquities Advisory Board of Hong Kong.
As per the Sino Group of Hotels, The Pottinger Hong Kong features 68 upscale guestrooms and suites, with sizes varying from 23 to 68 square meters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>