<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expatriate on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expatriate/</link><description>Recent content in Expatriate on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:13:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expatriate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Skills and challenges for global citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</guid><description>A new book by an INSEAD professor explores the unique skills and challenges faced by &amp;ldquo;citizens of the world&amp;rdquo; – individuals who hold multiple passports or live outside their home country. These individuals often come from diverse backgrounds, navigating multiple cultures and languages, which has driven their success. Author Linda Brimm, an Emeritus Professor of Organisational Behaviour at INSEAD, emphasizes the importance of a global mindset in international business and problem-solving, stating that these individuals offer valuable insights for addressing today&amp;rsquo;s complex challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Salary growth is expected in Southeast Asia as there is a high demand for IT skillsets in key sectors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s IT sector is expected to experience high demand for skilled professionals and contract workers in 2018, particularly in fintech, healthcare, and technology.
Specialized skills will be highly sought after in 2018 across accounting and finance, human resources, sales and marketing, and technology sectors.
According to the 2018 Salary Survey by Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, the economic outlook for the coming year is positive. The survey anticipates that continued digitalization and market expansion in Southeast Asia will fuel salary growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Expatstoday provides important advice for expatriates living in the Gulf region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</guid><description>Source: Expatstoday
A new online platform, Expatstoday, aims to attract individuals considering a move to Bahrain, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, or the UAE. The website provides insights into living conditions in these Gulf countries.
The company behind the platform emphasizes its commitment to providing accurate, current, and trustworthy information. While the sections dedicated to Gulf countries appear well-established, suggesting an active user base, pages for other countries seem relatively new, often lacking listings in various categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New report on Expatriate Services launched by Alliott Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 13:49:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/</guid><description>The Alliott Group has released a new &amp;ldquo;Expatriate Services&amp;rdquo; report to assist businesses in relocating employees internationally. Alliott Group&amp;rsquo;s global member firms help companies optimize their mobility process, evaluate compensation packages, and manage cross-border employment structures and expenses.
The report, produced by a renowned international alliance of professional services firms, spans 29 countries, including Turkey, Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, New Zealand, and Singapore. It serves as a resource for navigating the complex web of tax, immigration, and employment laws impacting globally mobile workforces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-report-on-expatriate-services-launched-by-alliott-group/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>