<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Circuit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/circuit/</link><description>Recent content in Circuit on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/circuit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Prematurely Activating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is progressing well. Rebuilding the deck led to a successful initial power-up where the carriage moved to the correct position, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower. A visual inspection showed a disconnected thin grey wire from the SK3054 NPN power transistor (0TR4).
Tracing the wiring and consulting the schematic revealed that the grey wire connected to the transistor&amp;rsquo;s emitter, responsible for bypassing a current-limiting resistor (7R1) during the arm&amp;rsquo;s initial descent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors on the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</guid><description>I began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) by replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards with high-quality 105C capacitors. I made sure to use components from reputable Japanese brands like Nichicon and Rubycon, sourcing them through trusted distributors like Newark and Mouser. The process was straightforward, aside from uncovering a spider web (and its architect) beneath the main PCB. This restoration project also highlighted the existence of at least two different solenoid control circuits within the 5513 series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Afternoon Exploring the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem arose with its record detection system. While it functioned correctly at the 12-inch LP position, it frequently failed to detect records at the 7-inch singles position. This malfunction was observed when the turntable, starting without a record on the platter, bypassed the LP position but stopped at the singles position.
An examination of the circuit diagram revealed the signal path of the detection system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Evening Exploring the Differential Stop Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</guid><description>Before returning a refurbished unit to a customer, we put it through rigorous real-world testing. This involves playing music for several weeks to ensure consistent functionality. This listening process is a delightful part of working with Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen equipment, as our workshop is always filled with music! A recent case involving a restored Beogram 4000 turntable highlights the value of this testing phase.
During playback, I noticed the arm occasionally failed to return to its resting position after reaching the record&amp;rsquo;s end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-evening-exploring-the-differential-stop-circuit/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>