<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Connectivity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/connectivity/</link><description>Recent content in Connectivity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/connectivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is 5G Bandwidth Slicing The New Private Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet is great for connecting, but it&amp;rsquo;s not always reliable. While it provides widespread access, low costs, and supports most applications, it can fall short when high performance and reliability are crucial. Issues like latency, packet loss, and congestion can hinder or even prevent interactive applications from working correctly. The solution? Private networks.
What is a Private Network?
The internet is a public network, accessible to almost anyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity for Telemedicine and Remote Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The rapid emergence of the Coronavirus pandemic is speeding up existing trends, particularly telemedicine and remote work. Both heavily rely on broadband internet bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available connection options.
Connecting the User
Most remote workers and telemedicine patients connect from home using devices like desktops, smartphones, laptops, or tablets. Home users often prefer cable broadband with speeds of 30 to 100 Mbps, while remote users rely on public WiFi or 4G/5G cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telx Cloud Exchange Reduces Service Lag Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</guid><description>Cloud services promise cost savings by replacing your data center with rented infrastructure, platforms, and software. While this sounds good in theory, some users experience performance issues.
Cloud computing boasts virtually unlimited resources, instantly available when needed. So why do some cloud-based operations become slower than their local counterparts?
It boils down to connectivity. Although electrical signals travel at the speed of light, distance still matters. Light speed is significantly reduced in terrestrial circuits compared to a vacuum, and signals face further delays due to network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation and Connectivity in Miami</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</guid><description>Miami, Florida, serves as a strategic location for businesses aiming to connect with South America, Central America, the Caribbean, and regions across the Atlantic. Telx, a prominent provider of colocation services, offers comprehensive solutions tailored to meet these connectivity needs.
Telx has established a strong reputation in the financial services sector by delivering ultra-low latency connections to electronic trading floors. Their extensive network encompasses 15 colocation facilities within the United States and global connectivity to over 800 carriers, ensuring comprehensive and reliable connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business moves online and companies shift their IT to the cloud, the demand for WAN bandwidth continues to rise. These days, even small businesses frequently require reliable dedicated internet and inter-office network bandwidth in the range of 100 Mbps to 1 Gbps. Larger companies, particularly those dealing with tech-heavy products, services, or medical imaging, can easily saturate Gigabit connections, making a transition to 10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN a worthwhile consideration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-1 Bandwidth Suits the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), despite being independently owned, are no longer isolated entities. They rely heavily on the internet, from small insurance offices to quick-service restaurants (QSRs). This reliance stems from the cost-effectiveness of internet-based solutions.
The T1 line is widely used by SMBs for digital communication. This business-grade telecommunication service has become more affordable in recent years due to increased competition and demand. Costs for T1 services have been cut by more than half in some instances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless For Rural Retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</guid><description>Small businesses outside of cities often struggle to obtain affordable and reliable broadband. While some resort to satellite or T1 lines for internet and point-of-sale systems, others have discovered that 3G wireless offers a secure and cost-effective alternative for credit card processing.
](http://www.sheepfort1.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
We associate 3G with mobile phones and laptops, but a lesser-known application exists. This service combines the widespread availability of 3G signals with powerful multi-carrier equipment and a secure VPN network, making it suitable for business needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides an explanation of mobile performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</guid><description>Singtel contributed to the Infocomm Development Authority&amp;rsquo;s (IDA) MyConnection SG study, highlighting connectivity, speed, and coverage as crucial aspects of user experience.
Singtel emphasized that, based on study feedback, users prioritize network coverage, call stability, customer service, and reliable data connections over pure speed. Consistent speed across a broad coverage area is key for a positive user experience. This feedback helps Singtel pinpoint areas for service enhancement.
Connectivity, as defined by Singtel, is the server connection response time, measured in milliseconds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-an-explanation-of-mobile-performance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Neutral Connectivity at Colocation Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses struggling to find enough bandwidth might be overlooking a simpler solution. Instead of waiting for carriers to come to them, companies can benefit by going where the carriers already are.
Colocation Centers: A Hub for Connectivity
Carriers are drawn to locations called colocation centers, or colos, and carrier hotels. These large data centers are designed to accommodate multiple tenants, unlike typical data centers that serve a single company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Twice the T1 Line Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your internet connection feeling a little slow? That T1 line that used to be more than enough might be struggling to keep up with your current needs. You&amp;rsquo;re not the only one experiencing this. While T1 bandwidth was sufficient for even large companies a decade ago, today, even small and medium-sized businesses are finding themselves needing more. The shift towards online applications and connectivity, while beneficial for productivity, has led to a significant increase in bandwidth demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Siren Song of Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</guid><description>The pervasiveness of cloud computing, services, and networks in technological discussions today is undeniable. This buzz might even remind you of the catchy tune, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Computing,&amp;rdquo; by Loose Bruce Kerr (a playful nod to Joni Mitchell).
Similar to the shift from mainframes to networked PCs and back to a centralized system in the cloud, cloud services represent a significant technological advancement. While security and connectivity concerns exist, the widespread adoption of cloud services could make purchasing and updating software seem as outdated as physical switches on computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity For Multi-Business Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</guid><description>Instead of constructing their own offices, many businesses rent space in large buildings like office complexes, shopping centers, or strip malls. This shared situation offers a unique opportunity to secure better bandwidth at lower costs by joining forces with other tenants in the building.
There are a few approaches to leverage the collective bandwidth requirements of multiple businesses. One method is for the building owner to become an ISP, providing bandwidth to all tenants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps T1 vs EoC Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</guid><description>A significant battle is occurring in the telecommunications market between traditional T1 lines and the newer Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services. Both technologies aim to provide businesses with increased bandwidth at lower costs, catering to the growing reliance on internet connectivity, remote data center access, and cloud-based services.
The core of this competition lies in how these technologies utilize existing copper telephone wiring to deliver data services. While T1 lines have long been the standard, EoC presents a compelling alternative with potentially higher bandwidth at competitive prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Internet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</guid><description>Ethernet point-to-point and LAN services have gained popularity among businesses, often replacing T1 lines and outdated Frame Relay networks. Ethernet is also a great way to connect to MPLS VPN networks and the internet.
Carrier Ethernet began as a business-oriented Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) service known as Metro Ethernet, often used by companies to connect multiple locations within a specific geographic region. E-Line point-to-point services like EPL and EVPL provide comparable or superior connectivity to T1 lines, even when multiple T1 lines are used...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Chance to Invent Payphone 2.0</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-chance-to-invent-payphone-20/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:51:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-chance-to-invent-payphone-20/</guid><description>Remember payphones? Before cellphones, they were everywhere, especially in busy areas. Now that everyone has a cellphone, you might think payphones are gone, like horses and buggies. Not quite.
Public payphones are still important for communication. Think about Hurricane Sandy: cell towers failed, and people desperately needed to communicate. VoIP and broadband were also down. Surprisingly, old payphones still worked. You could just insert coins and make a call.
Why did old technology work when modern technology failed?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-chance-to-invent-payphone-20/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-chance-to-invent-payphone-20/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Insatiable Demand For Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>10 Gbps used to be a bandwidth amount so large that only major telecommunications companies needed it. That&amp;rsquo;s no longer true, as businesses are now using that much WAN bandwidth and wanting even more.
Beyond internet providers, who could need 10 Gbps? According to Carrier Ethernet News, the finance, streaming entertainment, and medical industries are leading the demand for high bandwidth. Some are even hoping for 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Lines For MPLS Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</guid><description>Companies needing to link numerous locations are increasingly choosing MPLS networks, often finding T1 lines to be the optimal solution for network access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Consider an MPLS (Multi Protocol Label Switching) network as a private internet. This private ownership allows the MPLS operator to guarantee the bandwidth and service quality needed for your applications&amp;rsquo; reliable operation. Security is also strengthened as access is exclusive to subscribing businesses.
An MPLS network functions as a customized cloud, connecting only your specified locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Managed SD-WAN Can Help Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Going digital can be great for business until you hit roadblocks trying to make it work. One of these unexpected hurdles is the need for way more internet bandwidth than you anticipated. You can struggle to make it work without going bankrupt, or you can use managed SD-WAN to make your connectivity invisible.
Why Is Connectivity Such a Big Deal Now?
When your business was primarily physical, a standard broadband connection for internet access was probably enough...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Build Your Own World Wide Web</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet has its downsides despite the benefits of global and instant information access. Sharing large files between offices, conducting high-quality teleconferences, and experiencing seamless application interactions can be challenging. Network crashes, congestion from high-bandwidth activities, and constant security threats further diminish the internet&amp;rsquo;s appeal. So, is there a better alternative?
The Connectivity Conundrum
Imagine having an exclusive internet solely for your business, customers, and suppliers. Bandwidth wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue, and the network would operate seamlessly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Helping Your Business Achieve Hyperconnectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It took a whole generation to connect the entire world to the internet. Now, get ready for an even bigger change: we&amp;rsquo;re moving towards hyperconnectivity, and it&amp;rsquo;s happening fast.
Everything, Everywhere, All at Once
Hyperconnectivity means that anything and anyone who can be connected will be connected all the time. We&amp;rsquo;ve already shifted from logging in to having always-on internet for our computers and phones. The next step is to let our devices communicate with each other without us...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs T1 in Under 3 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Ethernet bandwidth services are generating a lot of interest, but are they truly superior to traditional T1 lines? Is switching from copper to fiber a wise decision financially? This brief comparison of Ethernet and T1 services will provide clarity.
Interested in determining which connectivity and hosted services best meet your business needs? Get instant pricing and availability for Ethernet, T1, and other connectivity options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tata Communications announces Global Scrapbook Challenge ahead of upcoming Formula 1 race</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications company, has launched its second technology challenge offering US$50,000 in prizes. This challenge focuses on harnessing innovative connectivity solutions, a key aspect of Formula 1 racing.
Leading up to the FORMULA 1 GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2014, Tata Communications is challenging the public to create a digital scrapbook celebrating the history of the Mercedes-Benz Silver Arrows in Formula 1. This Global Scrapbook Challenge aims to build a virtual museum, a captivating online archive of stories, memories, and intrigue for fans of the sport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Content Delivery Networks Transformed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth is steadily growing, largely due to the rise of IP video streaming, downloads, and more sophisticated websites with larger graphics and interactive features. To keep up with this demand, networks and websites themselves need to change.
While increasing WAN bandwidth is a given, it&amp;rsquo;s not a complete solution. Despite significant growth in WAN bandwidth, internet traffic congestion persists, leading to the emergence of Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) as a bypass...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Is Making Obsolescence Obsolete</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</guid><description>Keeping up with technology is a constant struggle, similar to swimming against a strong current. Any pause or delay can cause you to fall behind competitors who are advancing rapidly.
Technology is constantly evolving, becoming outdated quickly. The longer you rely on existing technology, the more outdated it gets, eventually lacking support or functionality. While the physical hardware may remain functional, it struggles to utilize the latest resources and software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Port At Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</guid><description>You might be surprised to learn that a connection to the outside world could be as simple as an Ethernet port in your telecom closet. This is due to a relatively new technology called Ethernet WAN (Wide Area Network).
Traditionally, organizations have relied on the public switched telephone network (PSTN) for external connections. Technologies designed for phone calls, like T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services, were adapted to carry data traffic and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber WAN is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that your business needs the speed of fiber optic WAN service to ensure cloud-based applications are responsive and your team stays productive. However, you may have struggled to find this service in the past. It&amp;rsquo;s time to try again.
Why Is Fiber More Accessible Now?
Fiber optic used to be a rare and costly option limited to large corporations. You had to rely on the telephone company and hope they serviced your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>