<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Small Business on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small-business/</link><description>Recent content in Small Business on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:21:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$8.33/mo Small Business &amp; Residential VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</guid><description>Forget expensive phone plans advertised on TV, there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for homes and small businesses. For just $8.33 a month, Phone Power offers unlimited calls within the US and Canada, plus a free hour of international calls.
This Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) service works with your existing internet connection. Phone Power provides a free adapter that connects to your modem and lets you use two phones on a single line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small Business Merchant Accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:36:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</guid><description>Could you be missing out on sales because you don&amp;rsquo;t accept credit cards? While setting up credit and debit card processing might seem expensive and complex, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be. With the right processing partner, it can be a smooth and straightforward process.
Don&amp;rsquo;t mistake this for implying that credit card processing is simple. Behind the scenes, it involves a network of banks, credit card companies, merchant service providers, computer systems, and specialized equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Broadband Available In A Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</guid><description>Imagine this: your new store is ready to open, everything is in place, but you can&amp;rsquo;t start selling because your internet service isn&amp;rsquo;t working. This is where Accel Networks comes in, offering a wireless solution that can get you online in just a few days.
Why choose Accel Networks? Traditional broadband often involves time-consuming installations. Accel Networks bypasses this by using existing cell tower infrastructure. Their service is secure, meets payment industry standards, and covers most of the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Services Give Small Companies an Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</guid><description>During the ongoing economic downturn, businesses of all sizes face the challenge of maintaining competitive electronic services with limited budgets. Managed services present a solution, particularly for smaller companies lacking substantial IT departments and hiring capacity.
The concept of managed services is straightforward: you delegate management to an external provider. Consider your phone system. One option is to independently research, purchase, and install a PBX system, along with the necessary hardware and staff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-services-give-small-companies-an-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For the initial six months, HP Touchpoint Manager is being offered at a discounted rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Touchpoint Manager, a cloud-based IT management solution specifically designed for small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs).
Managing IT systems has become more challenging due to the increasing variety of devices and operating systems used in business, from company-provided equipment to personal devices.
HP Touchpoint Manager simplifies IT management for SMBs, helping them ensure device functionality, data security, and IT staff effectiveness. Its adaptability allows it to manage a wide array of devices and operating systems, including iOS, Android, and Windows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrated T1 Gives You Phone and Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:42:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</guid><description>Small businesses need high-quality telecom services without the high price tag of large corporations. While you might not need the same capacity as a major company, you can still access reliable phone and internet services tailored to your needs.
Achieving this involves using a T1 line, a standard for voice and data transmission. While medium-sized companies might have multiple T1 lines, a single line can suffice for smaller businesses by combining phone and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>