<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Border on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/border/</link><description>Recent content in Border on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 01:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/border/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instarem introduces a new mobile application for consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 01:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Instarem, a digital platform for international payments, has updated its website and mobile app for users in Singapore. The company will also introduce a groundbreaking consumer debit card called Amaze later this year.
Instarem has revamped its brand and released a new app specifically designed for the Singapore market.
This rebranding goes beyond simply improving global consumer remittances. Instarem aims to simplify the complexities of international payments, providing its customers with an intuitive, transparent, and affordable way to manage their money...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is prepared to take action in response to Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Health (MOH) has implemented the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s (WHO) recommendations for Ebola virus disease (EVD) preparedness and is going even further. The ministry is prepared to adjust its measures as the situation changes.
One of the recommendations is to educate travelers about the potential dangers of EVD. The MOH is using various channels, such as its website and media releases, to inform the public and potential travelers about the disease...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>