<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shopee on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shopee/</link><description>Recent content in Shopee on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 03:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shopee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Success in business relies on establishing a broad network, having a strong passion, dedicating time, and learning from numerous failures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 03:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</guid><description>Alex Foo, co-founder of the entrepreneur-focused psychometric profiling tool Starteur, offers three key tips for entrepreneurial success. These insights, derived from both his attendance at the Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 (June 22-24, USA) and his personal journey as a young entrepreneur, were shared during a Shopee University session. Foo&amp;rsquo;s trip to GES 2016 was sponsored by Shopee, the e-commerce platform by Garena. This sponsorship reflects Shopee&amp;rsquo;s commitment to nurturing the next generation of Singaporean entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>The best beauty products chosen by Shopee Malaysia for the month of July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</guid><description>Shopee, a Southeast Asia-focused mobile marketplace designed for simple and secure online buying and selling, monitors top-selling items across various categories. Here are some of the best-selling beauty products on Shopee Malaysia during July:
Source: Shopee Malaysia portal. Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream.
Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream
According to its Shopee description, this cream is enriched with natural organic herbs to provide an immediate whitening effect that can last up to 12 hours.</description></item><item><title>Check out Shopee Malaysia's Christmas gift ideas!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:02:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, offers a convenient way to shop for Christmas.
Here are some gift ideas available in Malaysia:
Stay Connected
[Image of PINENG PN966 power bank]
This power bank, available in blue and green, ensures you stay connected all day.
[Buy now]
Capture the Moment
[Image of OPPO F1s phone]
The OPPO F1s, dubbed &amp;ldquo;The Selfie Expert,&amp;rdquo; boasts a 5.5&amp;quot; display with 1,280 x 720 pixels resolution, a 13-megapixel rear camera, and a 16-megapixel front camera.</description></item><item><title>Shopee's 12.12 sale: 12 million items sold in just 24 minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-s-12-12-sale-12-million-items-sold-in-just-24-minutes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-s-12-12-sale-12-million-items-sold-in-just-24-minutes/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, achieved record-breaking success during its annual 12.12 Birthday Sale. On December 12th, the platform sold an astounding 12 million items within the first 24 minutes. At its peak, Shopee recorded an incredible 1 million items purchased per minute. Notably, one of the top-performing sellers generated S$1 million in sales within just 24 hours on December 12th.
Zhou Junjie, Chief Commercial Officer at Shopee, expressed gratitude for the overwhelming response to their 12.</description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia is showing support for breast cancer awareness by going pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</guid><description>Shopee, a popular online marketplace in Malaysia, is partnering with the Pink Ribbon Deeds (PRIDE) Foundation for a &amp;ldquo;Goes Pink&amp;rdquo; campaign throughout October to raise awareness about breast cancer. The campaign involves both online and offline initiatives.
Shopee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Goes Pink&amp;rdquo; collection features pink and white products across various categories like mobile accessories, beauty products, and home goods, encouraging users to purchase and show their support. With over 2 million app installs in Malaysia, Shopee aims to leverage its platform to spread awareness nationwide.</description></item><item><title>Preorders for GoPro HERO5 cameras and Karma drones are now available at Shopee Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorders-for-gopro-hero5-cameras-and-karma-drones-are-now-available-at-shopee-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorders-for-gopro-hero5-cameras-and-karma-drones-are-now-available-at-shopee-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a popular online marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is now offering preorders for the new GoPro HERO5 cameras.
Source: GoPro. The HERO5 series.
GoPro&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO, Nicholas Woodman, introduced the HERO5 on September 19th, alongside a cloud-based software platform and the Karma drone.
Woodman emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to easy storytelling: &amp;ldquo;With these new products, we&amp;rsquo;re making it simpler to capture and share compelling stories. HERO5&amp;rsquo;s automatic photo and video uploads to GoPro Plus streamline the entire process of editing, sharing, and enjoying your experiences on the go.</description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3.</description></item></channel></rss>