<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General Election on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-election/</link><description>Recent content in General Election on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:04:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Failed Gamble: Brexit Election aftermath and the future steps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent UK election concluded with an unexpected &amp;lsquo;hung Parliament,&amp;rsquo; where no single party secured a majority in the House of Commons. This raises questions about the future of Brexit.
Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s Conservative party undeniably faced a major setback. The Prime Minister called for this election three years ahead of schedule, seeking a stronger majority to solidify her Brexit plan. Instead, voters reduced her majority, resulting in a minority government.</description></item><item><title>Will Brexit be unavoidable? The UK's EU membership post-General Election.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Conservative majority win in the UK brings up significant questions regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued membership in the European Union. This piece will initially address concerns surrounding the referendum and the renegotiation process.
The Brexit Referendum
What are the main issues surrounding the approaching referendum?
The new government&amp;rsquo;s plan to renegotiate the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership followed by a referendum (Brexit) based on the renegotiation&amp;rsquo;s results by the end of 2017 is paramount.</description></item><item><title>What would be the effect on the UK's relations with the EU if Scotland gained independence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:31:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the Scottish independence referendum approaches, with the &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; campaign gaining momentum and even leading some polls, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to analyze the potential impact of Scottish independence on the European Union (EU). This analysis will focus on the EU membership of both an independent Scotland and the remaining UK (rUK).
Scottish independence would trigger four significant, near-simultaneous events: negotiations between Scotland and rUK about their future relationship; negotiations for Scotland to rejoin the EU; renegotiation of the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership; and a UK general election.</description></item></channel></rss>