<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hinge on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hinge/</link><description>Recent content in Hinge on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hinge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Brand New Hood Fatally Damaged Due to Bent Hood Hinges! - Straightening Hinges Out and Installation of Another Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) for a Florida-based client and installed a new dust cover purchased from beoparts-shop in Denmark. These dust covers are remarkable replicas, made with the same die-cast process as the originals, resulting in a seamless finish.
However, a problem arose with this particular dust cover. When closing it, there was slight friction on the hinge approximately halfway through its movement. While I initially dismissed it as an insignificant tolerance issue common in older manufacturing, the issue escalated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Polishing and Exchange of the Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 19:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration project required a hood restoration. I had two hoods: one had a cracked corner, and the other had a good plexiglass body but a corroded hinge.
Corrosion is common on Beogram 4000 hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s fixable with sanding and repainting, but finding a good hinge is preferable. Luckily, the cracked hood had a usable hinge, so I decided to swap them.
Removing the hinge requires care to avoid damaging the aluminum strip on the back of the hood.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of a Cracked Hood - Another Process Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on has a cracked hood around the hinge attachments. The left side was entirely detached, and the right side had a crack extending around one of the holes.
The right side had a crack going all the way around one of the attachment holes:
To begin, I glued the broken pieces back together using Weld-On #4 acrylic solvent. This low-viscosity solvent is ideal for injecting into cracks, as capillary action draws it in.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Polishing the Hood and a Strange Hinge Pin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 12:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m completing the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable by addressing the final detail: polishing the dust cover. This one, like many I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered, had scratches from improper storage.
This particular unit had a non-original hinge pin, longer than the original, causing it to protrude. I shortened it, restoring a flush fit. The aluminum trim on the other side had also detached, which I reattached using double-sided tape for easy future removal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Plexiglass Hood With Laser Cut Patches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</guid><description>The hinge area is the most delicate part of plexiglass hoods found on Beogram turntables. It&amp;rsquo;s subject to significant stress when opened and closed, while the presence of screw holes for the metal hinge makes it structurally vulnerable. I recently worked on a Beogram 4000 with a cracked hood and a broken-off piece.
Inspired by a previous restoration of a Beogram 3000 hinge, I aimed to create a similar solution for the 4000/4002 models.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 3000 (5228): Restoration of the Plexiglass Hood - Repair of a Cracked Hinge and Installation of 3D Printed Mounting Brackets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 3000 turntable with a damaged plexiglass dust cover. The plastic mounting brackets that held the cover were broken, and one of the plexiglass hinges was also broken.
and one of the plexiglass hinges was broken off:
To address these issues, I created a repair kit. This kit includes 3D-printed replacement mounting brackets, a specialized tool for reinstalling the spring tensioning block, and laser-cut plexiglass pieces for fixing the broken hinge.</description></item></channel></rss>