<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hipster on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hipster/</link><description>Recent content in Hipster on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:19:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hipster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JWT has identified 100 trends for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jwt-has-identified-100-trends-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Source: JWT website.
The renowned marketing communications company, JWT, has unveiled &amp;ldquo;The Future 100,&amp;rdquo; a report that offers unique perspectives and analyses of 100 significant trends and cultural shifts to monitor in the coming year.
Lucie Greene, JWTIntelligence&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Director, emphasizes the importance of understanding the direction and implications of change for brands today. She points out that the rapid evolution of the digital world, readily available information, globalization, and social media have significantly accelerated the pace of trends.</description></item><item><title>Strangers' Reunion cafe introduces new menu items</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strangers-reunion-cafe-introduces-new-menu-items/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:32:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strangers-reunion-cafe-introduces-new-menu-items/</guid><description>Source: Strangers&amp;rsquo; Reunion. Ocean Trout on Hash.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a new lunch spot, you might want to try Strangers’ Reunion, a cafe in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Kampong Bahru district that recently updated its menu. World Gourmet Summit-recognized chef Daniel Chin has crafted dishes with a minimum of five components to entice your taste buds.
The cafe is well-known for its coffee, which is chosen and curated by Ryan Tan, a three-time Singapore Barista Champion and Co-founder of Strangers’ Reunion.</description></item></channel></rss>