<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ATT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/att/</link><description>Recent content in ATT on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/att/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Monday Cell Phone Deals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-cell-phone-deals/</guid><description>The best deals on cell phones can be found online, especially during sales like Cyber Monday. These limited-time offers on free and discounted phones are valid until midnight today, Monday.
For a limited time, get a free BlackBerry Bold 9700 for AT&amp;amp;T after an instant online discount. This offer includes a bonus of free activation for up to five lines, making it perfect for family plans.
Prefer a different BlackBerry? The BlackBerry Curve in Titanium or silver is also available.</description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Cheap Used Cell Phones For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 12:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</guid><description>Need a new cell phone but dread dealing with carriers and contracts? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Carrier stores are notorious for expensive phones and restrictive contracts. They might offer a &amp;ldquo;cheap&amp;rdquo; phone, but it comes with strings attached – usually a pricey new contract and limited model options.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been with your carrier long enough for an upgrade or prefer not to sign a new contract, carriers will charge full retail price for a new phone.</description></item><item><title>HTC Aria Social Networking Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to stay connected, forget dogs – get FriendStream! This service lets you interact with friends through Facebook, Twitter, and Flickr, all from the HTC Aria, a cutting-edge Android smartphone.
The Aria boasts a sleek, seamless design crafted from a single piece of black aluminum. It&amp;rsquo;s compact enough for your pocket yet powerful enough for work and play. Its sizable 3.2-inch touchscreen features pinch-to-zoom functionality, automatically adjusting text size for comfortable website browsing.</description></item><item><title>Media Flos to Mobile TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 12:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</guid><description>Television is everywhere. While it started with over-the-air broadcasts, it quickly spread to cable, satellite, and the internet through platforms like YouTube and IPTV. Now, mobile devices like cell phones are the new frontier for watching TV on the go.
Early mobile video relied on downloadable clips using cellular broadband networks like EV-DO. However, these networks struggle with bandwidth limitations, making it difficult to deliver high-quality real-time video without overloading the system.</description></item></channel></rss>