<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call Center on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call-center/</link><description>Recent content in Call Center on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:18:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>End of the Premises Contact Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business telephone systems have evolved significantly. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from single-line phones to switchboards, automated systems, and sophisticated call center PBXs. However, one thing remained constant: these systems were all located on-site.
What’s Wrong With Premises Equipment?
Keeping everything in-house seems appealing because it gives you control over functionality, access, and services. You might even believe that in-house systems are more reliable than off-site solutions.
On-premises systems offer visibility and control.</description></item><item><title>Private Branch Exchange Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</guid><description>PBX telephone systems are the preferred business phone technology for medium and large businesses, though recent advancements have made them affordable for smaller companies as well, replacing outdated hardwired or key systems. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a new PBX system, reaching out to VAR Network can provide insights into pricing and available options.
Beyond hardware, PBX systems require connectivity, with various options offering different cost and performance benefits. The most basic connection is an FXO, or analog phone line, connecting to a central office.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient.</description></item></channel></rss>