<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Floral on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/floral/</link><description>Recent content in Floral on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/floral/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Viva La Fleur has launched online sales of its durable, all-natural floral arrangements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</guid><description>Since its establishment in October 2013, Viva La Fleur Floral Boutique has impressed businesses with its enduring, all-natural floral arrangements and bouquets. The company holds the exclusive distribution rights for LavieFlo, a technology that makes flowers appear freshly cut for months, eliminating the need for water or sunlight.
Sourced globally, fresh flowers from countries like Japan and China undergo a meticulous preservation process. This process substitutes the plant&amp;rsquo;s sap with a solution that retains the natural appearance and texture of the petals and leaves.</description></item><item><title>Immerse yourself in the holiday spirit with the Holiday fragrance by House of Sillage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</guid><description>Source: House of Sillage.
House of Sillage, a high-end perfume maker, introduces its Holiday fragrance for the Christmas season. The perfume features a blend of mandarin, peach, and vetiver, creating a festive aroma.
The design of the fragrance bottle draws inspiration from the illuminated Rockefeller Center Christmas tree in New York City. Its snow globe cap, crafted from 18-karat gold and white gold, depicts a scene of falling snow. The floral and citrus perfume is housed in a hand-polished glass bottle with an ombre lacquer finish.</description></item></channel></rss>