<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Art on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/art/</link><description>Recent content in Art on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eko Nugroho is currently showcasing his street art exhibition through digital prints produced by HP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</guid><description>This image, from HP Inc., showcases embroidered artwork by Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho. It features his signature masked characters and intricate designs reminiscent of Japanese woodcuts.
HP Inc is the Innovation Sponsor for the &amp;ldquo;Art from the Streets&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the ArtScience Museum in Singapore. For the exhibition, HP created nine large-scale prints of significant artworks. They are also using their digital printing technology to showcase the work of Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho in fresh and unexpected ways, demonstrating that street art can be displayed anywhere and on any medium...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An easy solution for sprucing up your office walls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-easy-solution-for-sprucing-up-your-office-walls/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 07:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-easy-solution-for-sprucing-up-your-office-walls/</guid><description>Source: Photos.com website
Getty Images, a stock image provider, has launched Photos.com, a new platform for purchasing stock images as wall art. This opens up a new avenue for sourcing images suitable for workplace decoration.
Being backed by a stock image company, the site boasts an extensive collection of high-quality images. These images are available in color and monochrome, spanning a wide range of categories.
The website states, &amp;ldquo;Each photograph on Photos...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-easy-solution-for-sprucing-up-your-office-walls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-easy-solution-for-sprucing-up-your-office-walls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Art covering Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 08:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</guid><description>Brand Dubai, the creative branch of the Government of Dubai Media Office (GDMO), and the Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) have joined forces to enhance the city&amp;rsquo;s aesthetics. This three-year partnership will involve a series of city beautification projects.
Their first initiative, the Dubai Metro Murals Project, will feature artwork on the pillars of the Dubai Metro line along Sheikh Zayed Road. Renowned artists Daniel Cortez from Peru and Evoca1 (Elio Mercado) from the Dominican Republic will create murals between the Dubai International Financial Centre and Emirates Towers stations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New sculptures have been added to the Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi Coralarium</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</guid><description>The Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi resort has added new sculptures to its Coralarium, an underwater art installation that doubles as the Maldives&amp;rsquo; first and only coral regeneration project. This structure, now teeming with marine life, serves as an artificial reef.
The abstract sculptures, conceived by environmentalist and eco-artist Jason deCaires Taylor, draw inspiration from the natural beauty of coral reefs and are designed to resemble coral colonies. These ten partially submerged plinths, reaching heights of up to 5 meters, aim to raise awareness about endangered ecosystems, educate visitors about marine life, and help rehabilitate the reef...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Caffè Vergnano 1882 has chosen the top three baristas in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Caffè Vergnano 1882. From left: third place winner Rudel Rivera, first place winner Joseph Bringcula, and second placer Stephen Wong.
Caffè Vergnano 1882 held its first-ever Barista Challenge at South Beach. Out of 16 participants, three distinguished themselves as top contenders.
Source: Caffè Vergnano 1882. The winning latte art from Bringcula.
The competition assessed fundamental barista techniques, including the ability to brew espresso properly and steam milk to enhance its flavor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caff-vergnano-1882-has-chosen-the-top-three-baristas-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels &amp; Resorts presents an art installation in Singapore to commemorate its 200 properties worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</guid><description>Video of Hall with the bottles shaping the number &amp;lsquo;200&amp;rsquo;.
To mark the opening of their 200th hotel, InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts commissioned contemporary British artist Alexander Hall, known professionally as Haut de Gamme, to create a commemorative installation.
The artwork features 200 champagne bottles, each hand-painted by Hall in his signature drip technique. Inspired by the unique character of each InterContinental property, the individually designed bottles collectively form the number “200”...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Art Stage Singapore will be back in January 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 06:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/</guid><description>Source: Art Stage Singapore.
Art Stage Singapore, the leading art fair in Southeast Asia, will take place from January 21st to 24th, 2016, with a preview day on January 20th. This year&amp;rsquo;s event aims to showcase a new perspective on contemporary art from the region, highlighting the fair&amp;rsquo;s role in its development.
The sixth edition of Art Stage Singapore draws inspiration from ancient gathering places like the Roman Forum and the Greek Agora, aiming to be a hub for the exchange of both art and ideas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the limits of art in the 1950s paved the way for the contemporary art scene we see today</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-limits-of-art-in-the-1950s-paved-the-way-for-the-contemporary-art-scene-we-see-today/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-limits-of-art-in-the-1950s-paved-the-way-for-the-contemporary-art-scene-we-see-today/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Minimalism: Space. Light. Object.&amp;rdquo; a groundbreaking exhibition for Southeast Asia, showcases the evolution of Minimalism, an art form that challenges conventions.
Presented in Singapore through a partnership between the National Gallery Singapore and ArtScience Museum, Singapore, this exhibition presents significant Minimalist works from the 1950s to today. Visitors can experience over 100 pieces by 70 artists, including prominent names like Donald Judd, Mark Rothko, Mona Hatoum, Anish Kapoor, Ai Weiwei, Olafur Eliasson, and Haegue Yang...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-limits-of-art-in-the-1950s-paved-the-way-for-the-contemporary-art-scene-we-see-today/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-limits-of-art-in-the-1950s-paved-the-way-for-the-contemporary-art-scene-we-see-today/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The KOGEI Future Forward exhibition at Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store showcases the work of 15 artists</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</guid><description>The Mitsukoshi Nihombashi Main Store in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a contemporary art exhibition, KOGEI Future Forward, from February 15 to 20, 2017. The exhibition showcases the work of 15 Japanese artists, highlighting kogei as a unique form of Japanese fine art.
Kogei, meaning &amp;ldquo;craft,&amp;rdquo; emerged during the Meiji Period (1868-1912) and has evolved over time to gain recognition as fine art. This exhibition offers a fresh perspective on kogei, curated by Yuji Akimoto, a renowned art professor and museum director...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kogei-future-forward-exhibition-at-mitsukoshi-nihombashi-main-store-showcases-the-work-of-15-artists/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean restaurant and art gallery are showcasing hypebeast artworks for diners to enjoy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 19:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</guid><description>Until March 2021, enthusiasts of modern pop culture and Japanese cuisine in Singapore can experience a unique collaboration that blends contemporary art with specialized dining.
Source: simpleArte by iCare.4u. Artworks by the featured artists participating in Hypebeast@Uni.
Doraemon Here We Go by Takashi Murakami (left), Hero number 12 by Shen Jingdong (right, top left quadrant), Chiho Aoshima, artist (right, top right quadrant), Sky Year by Aoshima (right, bottom right quadrant), and Steven Harrington (right, bottom left quadrant)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The exhibition titled LAUREATES at the National Gallery Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exhibition-titled-laureates-at-the-national-gallery-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 15:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exhibition-titled-laureates-at-the-national-gallery-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Little Artists Art Studio. Poster for The LAUREATES Exhibition.
The Little Artists Art Studio, celebrating its 20th anniversary, presents The LAUREATES Exhibition at the National Gallery Singapore. This exhibition showcases artwork from 260 students, exploring themes like &amp;ldquo;Candy,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Environment,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Beautiful Still Life.&amp;rdquo;
The exhibition is a collaborative effort with Artrageous, a sister company that organizes contemporary art events and programs. Artrageous aims to spotlight the talents of emerging artists of all ages from across the globe, while Little Artists Art Studio is a fine arts school dedicated to nurturing creativity in children...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exhibition-titled-laureates-at-the-national-gallery-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exhibition-titled-laureates-at-the-national-gallery-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Private Museum is taking a new approach to printmaking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</guid><description>The Private Museum (TPM) in Singapore is hosting an exhibition curated by Zaki Razak, titled Repeat, Repeat, Repeat; revising the phenomenon of printing. The exhibition runs from May 17th to July 7th, 2019, and features printmaking works by seven artists: Miguel Chew, Weixin Chong, Mona Choo, Urich Lau, Nadia Oh, Shin-Young Park, and Shih Yun Yeo.
Source: Eventbrite page. Poster for Repeat, Repeat, Repeat; revising the phenomenon of printing.
This is the second exhibition in TPM&amp;rsquo;s Guest Curator series, which aims to promote independent curatorial practices and diverse perspectives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flickr Wall Art is now available worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</guid><description>Yahoo has expanded its Flickr wall art service to global markets, enabling businesses worldwide to adorn their walls with photographic artwork from Flickr artists.
Initially introduced in October, the Flickr Wall Art service allows the transformation of photographs from licensed artists within the Flickr Marketplace into high-quality wall prints available for purchase directly on Flickr.
The Flickr team has curated a collection of licensed photographs from popular categories such as abstract, landscapes, travel, and animals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Embark on an artistic adventure with Hotel Indigo Singapore Katong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/embark-on-an-artistic-adventure-with-hotel-indigo-singapore-katong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/embark-on-an-artistic-adventure-with-hotel-indigo-singapore-katong/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Indigo Singapore Katong website. The rooms showcase artwork by Don Low, including this mural featuring durians.
Hotel Indigo encourages guests to embark on a journey of artistic discovery with its #staysurprised campaign. Explore some of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s most impressive street art, all within a 15-minute radius of the Katong neighborhood.
The Hotel Indigo Singapore Katong boasts 131 rooms adorned with murals created by local urban artist Don Low. His work highlights Singapore&amp;rsquo;s passion for traditional cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/embark-on-an-artistic-adventure-with-hotel-indigo-singapore-katong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/embark-on-an-artistic-adventure-with-hotel-indigo-singapore-katong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indonesia emerges victorious in the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, an Indonesian artist has earned the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award. This year, the United Overseas Bank (UOB) recognized 36-year-old Gatot Indrajati for his relief acrylic painting, Right or Wrong My Home. This artwork also garnered him the 2016 UOB Painting of the Year, Indonesia award.
Judges praised Indrajati&amp;rsquo;s innovative combination of wood, a traditional Indonesian art material, with paint. This creates a visually captivating and modern piece of art...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>