<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Exercise on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/exercise/</link><description>Recent content in Exercise on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:37:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/exercise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ASICS introduces its lightest-ever cushioning shoe for runners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The DynaFlyte.
ASICS has released its lightest cushioned running shoe to date. The DynaFlyte combines lightness and cushioning with a full-length FlyteFoam midsole, utilizing the company&amp;rsquo;s patented midsole technology in its most basic form. According to ASICS, the shoe&amp;rsquo;s reduced weight minimizes energy loss during the stride, resulting in more efficient running and the potential for increased speed at any distance.
Balancing efficient cushioning with minimizing weight is a significant challenge in running shoe design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increase your productivity by installing a treadmill at your desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</guid><description>A recent study featured in the journal Plos One found that using a treadmill desk could lead to higher productivity compared to a traditional desk setup.
[Image of a treadmill desk]
Source: Plos One
This study, titled &amp;ldquo;Treadmill Workstations: The Effects of Walking while Working on Physical Activity and Work Performance&amp;rdquo;, was conducted by researchers from the University of Minnesota-Twin Cities, University of Texas-Arlington, Mayo Clinic, and Arizona State University. Over 12 months, they observed the impact of treadmill desks on physical activity and work output at a financial services company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kinetika Xtreme is unveiling innovative workout technology designed to enhance fitness levels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</guid><description>Ghaneswaran Sukumaran holds a certification from Italy and is one of only two TechnoGym Master Trainers in Singapore. His wife, Santhi Haridass, is the other. As the owner of Kinetika Xtreme, a gym in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Turf City that specializes in movement-based functional training, Sukumaran expresses concern that many individuals join gyms without proper research and engage in exercises that may be detrimental in the long term.
&amp;ldquo;Many people equate weight loss with fat loss and believe that excessive jogging is the key to achieving a slim physique...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consuming a balanced amount of protein helps dieters maintain muscle mass at a slower rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</guid><description>Source: Nestlé.
Nestlé Research Center collaborated with global scientists and found that consistent protein intake throughout the day might reduce muscle loss during weight loss attempts.
Published in the American Journal of Physiology - Endocrinology and Metabolism, the study explored ways to promote weight loss in obese older men while preventing muscle loss. Muscle loss can hinder weight loss, decrease strength and functional capacity, and heighten the risk of disability and mortality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASICS introduces the versatile fuzeX TR, an all-in-one fitness solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 08:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The fuzeX TR training shoe.
ASICS has introduced the fuzeX TR, a training shoe designed for greater workout efficiency with its lightweight cushioning and versatile design. This all-in-one shoe supports athletes of all backgrounds and experience levels, accommodating activities from high-intensity interval training (HIIT) and weightlifting to treadmill running.
The fuzeX TR launch is part of ASICS&amp;rsquo;s larger expansion into the training category, a market expected to exceed US$55 billion globally by 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>