<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>International Labour Organisation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-labour-organisation/</link><description>Recent content in International Labour Organisation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-labour-organisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and Labour Standards during COVID-19: Will they Align or Separate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</guid><description>Jeff Kenner, Professor of European Law, University of Nottingham*
The COVID-19 pandemic has taken center stage, demanding an urgent worldwide response that is yet to materialize. In light of this global crisis, the issue of Brexit, particularly its self-serving nature and political maneuvering, has understandably faded from the minds of both policymakers and the public. However, despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s onset in mid-March 2020, which coincided with the start of negotiations for a new EU-UK partnership and led to widespread lockdowns across Europe, the UK government remains steadfast in its refusal to extend the post-Brexit transition period beyond the December 31, 2020, deadline established in the October 2019 EU-UK Withdrawal Agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to effectively help in the prohibition of forced labor by the ILO?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although often used lightly, the term &amp;ldquo;wage slaves&amp;rdquo; reflects a harsh reality for millions trapped in forced labor globally, a modern form of slavery. This exploitation represents a significant aspect of human trafficking, alongside sexual exploitation.
Key international entities like the United Nations and the Council of Europe have been at the forefront of combating human trafficking. However, the International Labour Organisation (ILO) brings long-standing expertise, particularly concerning labor exploitation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>