<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Furniture on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/furniture/</link><description>Recent content in Furniture on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:05:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/furniture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Madison Group introduces the Venini and Rimadesio collection to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/</guid><description>The Madison Group, headquartered in Hong Kong, has expanded its Southeast Asian presence by introducing two Italian interior design brands to Singapore: Venini and Rimadesio.
Source: The Madison Group.
Rimadesio products.
Venini is renowned for its handcrafted Venetian mouth-blown glassware, while Rimadesio specializes in glass and aluminum furniture and accessories. The Madison Group holds exclusive distribution rights for both brands in Singapore. There are also plans to offer Venini glassware at select locations and retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evernote is unveiling new additions to the Pfeiffer Collection of desktop accessories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</guid><description>Evernote has expanded its Pfeiffer Collection, a line of modern desktop accessories designed in collaboration with Eric Pfeiffer.
The latest additions are bent plywood platforms crafted to securely elevate laptops, tablets, and monitors on desks, while also providing extra storage space.
Source: Evernote blog.
The new products include:
Laptop platform: This stand, made of walnut bent ply, supports 13” or 15” laptops. A curved front trough can hold small items, and cables can be routed through the back...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the thoughts of a designer who has won awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 02:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/</guid><description>Dr. Cingoli recently gave a presentation at the National Design Centre.
Dr. Andrea Cingoli, the driving force behind ConceptIcon, has been making a name for his team at Zo_loft architecture &amp;amp; design, and more recently, for himself through ConceptIcon. He sees design awards as a reliable measure of quality and believes that sharing designs is crucial for growth and inspiration within the design community.
Dr. Cingoli finds inspiration in his personal experiences and surroundings, aiming to create designs that are both meaningful and thought-provoking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the standing desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 03:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</guid><description>If you need a desk that allows you to work comfortably while standing, Steven Yu might have a solution. His StandDesk is height-adjustable, ranging from 71cm to 114cm, and incorporates design elements that make frequent adjustments easy.
Source: Kickstarter. The all-black StandDesk version.
&amp;ldquo;The StandDesk is more than a product; it&amp;rsquo;s a positive step towards improving people&amp;rsquo;s lives globally,&amp;rdquo; Yu stated on his Kickstarter page.
An intuitive &amp;lsquo;up/down&amp;rsquo; control button effortlessly raises or lowers the desk to the desired height...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Castlery combines online and offline retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/castlery-combines-online-and-offline-retail/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 21:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/castlery-combines-online-and-offline-retail/</guid><description>Source: Castlery. The Castlery team at the launch of the experience centre.
Companies in Singapore seeking office furniture can now turn to Castlery, an online furniture platform that recently opened a 7,000 square meter experience center. Castlery designs and sells its own furniture through a model that blends online shopping with an offline showroom. Customers can explore the selection and check availability online, then visit the experience center to see the furniture in person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/castlery-combines-online-and-offline-retail/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/castlery-combines-online-and-offline-retail/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>