<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FTTP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fttp/</link><description>Recent content in FTTP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fttp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Fiber Gold Rush Is On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</guid><description>The transition from copper wires to fiber optic strands has been recognized as a necessity for some time. This shift is driven by the growing need for bandwidth as technology progresses. Over the past few decades, various sectors, including internet service providers, cable companies, healthcare facilities, and large enterprises, have progressively adopted fiber optic connections. Services like Metro Ethernet have made this transition feasible even for mid-sized businesses. Now, small businesses and individual consumers are poised to benefit from this technology.</description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Curb and Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Copper is quickly disappearing from telecommunications networks, being replaced by fiber optic cabling. While this new cabling might be installed in the same spaces as the old copper, the outdated copper lines are often left behind.
You might be thinking, &amp;ldquo;But I still use copper connections!&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s true that many devices use copper wiring. So where exactly is all this fiber?
Mostly Fiber Outside, Mostly Copper Inside</description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Internet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</guid><description>Ethernet point-to-point and LAN services have gained popularity among businesses, often replacing T1 lines and outdated Frame Relay networks. Ethernet is also a great way to connect to MPLS VPN networks and the internet.
Carrier Ethernet began as a business-oriented Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) service known as Metro Ethernet, often used by companies to connect multiple locations within a specific geographic region. E-Line point-to-point services like EPL and EVPL provide comparable or superior connectivity to T1 lines, even when multiple T1 lines are used.</description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.0 Fiberizes Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Cable companies have been envious of Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS fiber optic service because it surpasses the broadband capabilities of coaxial cable. However, a new upgrade to the DOCSIS cable broadband standard might change that. This upgrade boosts digital download speeds to rival those of fiber optic connections, all without needing a fiber optic line to the home.
DOCSIS, which stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification, is the standard for cable modems.</description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>