<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-lines/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Lines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage.</description></item><item><title>Increase Bandwidth Without Increasing Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</guid><description>Companies need more bandwidth, especially for their wide area networks (WANs), but it can be very expensive. While high speeds are affordable within a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN, connecting to the outside world traditionally comes with much higher costs.
This is because WAN connections were typically provided by telecom companies using technology initially meant for phone services. While more modern providers have entered the market with updated infrastructure, even traditional providers are adapting to the demand for data services.</description></item><item><title>Business Ethernet Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</guid><description>For decades, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have relied heavily on T1 lines. However, a new service called Business Ethernet is emerging as a strong competitor, offering comparable performance at a lower cost.
Business Ethernet, also referred to as Metro Ethernet, Ethernet over Copper, or Ethernet over Fiber, provides advantages such as scalable bandwidth options, reduced cost per Mbps, and wider availability. Its name emphasizes that Ethernet is no longer limited to Local Area Networks (LANs) and carriers, as it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly being adopted by SMBs.</description></item><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light.</description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Lines Connect Dealerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 05:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</guid><description>Many businesses, from car dealerships to restaurants, benefit from having multiple locations. However, managing these locations as a unified company requires connecting them effectively. Point-to-point lines and MPLS networks offer solutions for this need.
Consider a car dealership expanding by acquiring another dealership. While this offers strategic advantages, consolidating operations like accounting, marketing, and IT can lead to cost savings. Centralizing these functions requires reliable and efficient connectivity between locations.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>How Maestro Smart Antenna Improves Fixed Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</guid><description>Accel Technologies, a branch of Accel Networks, is launching a groundbreaking product for fixed wireless connections: the Maestro smart antenna system. Maestro aims to make 3G and 4G fixed wireless broadband a more attractive alternative to pricier business connectivity options like T1, MPLS, VSAT, Frame Relay, and point-to-point microwave services.
What makes Maestro so special? Like other smart devices, Maestro utilizes active technology to enhance performance. In this situation, it improves the performance of a typically passive component: the RF antenna.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste</description></item><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Lock In Telecom Cost Savings For Next Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</guid><description>As we wrap up the year and analyze our performance, it&amp;rsquo;s common to wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re overspending on business operations, especially networking and telecom. A thorough market analysis often reveals opportunities to secure better rates for the same services. By doing this now, you can lock in savings for the entire next year.
Why are such savings possible? Primarily, increased competition and technological advancements. Previously, businesses were limited to local telephone companies for their communication needs.</description></item><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company.</description></item><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>Last Mile Connections That Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</guid><description>The US is covered in a network of competing telecom companies, reaching into every major city. Businesses of all sizes are drawn to their advanced IP networks, fiber optic infrastructure, and significantly lower prices. But how can businesses connect to these networks?
The final connection to a customer&amp;rsquo;s location, often called the &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; is frequently the most critical, expensive, and limiting part of a wide area network. It gets its name from the typical distance between a business and the nearest carrier Point of Presence (POP).</description></item><item><title>Cloud Server vs Cloud Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</guid><description>Cloud backup services have gained immense popularity among both individuals and businesses. Most people store at least some files online for easy sharing and mobile access, exceeding the need for encrypted backups. Essentially, there&amp;rsquo;s a massive shift of data towards the cloud.
While online file storage has become second nature, cloud computing hasn&amp;rsquo;t gained the same widespread adoption, despite a clear trend in that direction. However, there are strong indicators suggesting that cloud computing will reach a similar level of popularity as cloud storage within a few years.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Bandwidth vs Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</guid><description>Businesses choose dedicated internet services, like T1 lines and Ethernet over Copper, when they prioritize consistent performance and service guarantees, or when shared options aren&amp;rsquo;t available. Cable broadband, on the other hand, attracts businesses with its high bandwidth for a lower cost. Although cable lacks service guarantees, its proven track record and widespread availability, especially during business hours, make it appealing.
The term &amp;ldquo;dedicated&amp;rdquo; in this context signifies that a specific bandwidth amount is exclusively allocated to the user.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>Ethernet WAN is the most significant advancement in business broadband since T1 service prices dropped. What exactly is Ethernet WAN, and why should you care?
Ethernet has become the dominant standard for Local Area Networks (LANs). You could say that Ethernet is everywhere. An RJ45 Ethernet jack is standard on every desktop and laptop computer. You might not get a CD-ROM drive, probably won&amp;rsquo;t get a floppy disc drive, and may never use the phone modem jack again.</description></item><item><title>T1 Broadband For Rural Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</guid><description>Government funding is being used to expand rural broadband access, as it&amp;rsquo;s generally understood that service providers have overlooked these areas due to their sparse populations. But what about businesses in these locations? Do they face similar internet limitations?
In most cases, businesses in rural areas shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be deprived of reliable internet any more than they are deprived of multi-line phone service. The existing copper telephone lines can also deliver broadband.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Access Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</guid><description>Consumers access the internet in various ways, and businesses have similar options, along with some exclusive ones. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the choices available for companies at their business locations.
Popular consumer broadband choices include DSL and cable for stationary setups, and 3G for mobile use. 4G wireless is emerging, with providers like CLEAR offering it for both fixed and mobile applications. In remote areas, satellite broadband delivers connectivity where wires can&amp;rsquo;t reach.</description></item><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points.</description></item><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Mid-sized and larger businesses that have outgrown the capacity of T1 lines have turned to DS3 Internet Service as the next step in their telecommunications services. Currently, there are more choices for businesses, both small businesses with high bandwidth demands and larger companies seeking this service level.
DS3, short for Digital Signal level 3, is a well-established telecommunications standard for transmitting digital data. It provides a reliable 45 Mbps bandwidth suitable for dedicated point-to-point connections, PBX telephone systems, or internet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>DS1 Bandwidth vs Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</guid><description>DS1, commonly called T1, is a popular choice for business internet. This article will explain DS1 and compare it to another popular option: Ethernet over Copper.
While the terms are often used synonymously, DS1 and T1 are slightly different. They both come from a set of technical standards created by Bell Labs called the T-carrier system, which was originally a digital replacement for analog phone lines. Though designed for telephones, DS1 and T1 are now widely used for dedicated internet connections and private lines.</description></item><item><title>Business Broadband Options in Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses located in bustling city centers have a wide array of broadband Internet options, unlike their rural counterparts. While the lack of service providers in less populated areas might make it seem like broadband is a luxury they can&amp;rsquo;t afford, there are actually several options available, depending on the location.
Rural businesses might feel limited in their connectivity choices. Unlike their city counterparts, they don&amp;rsquo;t have numerous service providers vying for their business.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Cost Reduction Ideas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</guid><description>Getting the best price on everything your business buys is crucial for success, and bandwidth is no exception. Telecom expenses can be significant, but there are ways to save without sacrificing productivity.
One surprisingly simple step is to get updated competitive quotes. Bandwidth prices change rapidly, so your current understanding might be outdated.
While gathering quotes used to be time-consuming, online tools like GeoQuote by Telarus have simplified the process. This automated engine collects pricing from various providers, delivering budgetary quotes for services like T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and Ethernet connections almost instantly.</description></item><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Why T1 Is Available Where Other Line Services Aren’t</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:47:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-t1-is-available-where-other-line-services-aren-t/</guid><description>Businesses located outside of city centers may struggle to obtain the same quality of network services as their downtown counterparts. While it may seem like options are limited, a reliable and affordable digital telecom service called T1 is often accessible in these areas.
Contrary to outdated beliefs, T1 lines are no longer prohibitively expensive or geographically restricted. They are widely available for businesses, though they may not be suitable for residential use.</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing business internet services, bandwidth is important, but understanding the difference between dedicated and shared connections is crucial.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated bandwidth is exclusively for your use. This might seem obvious, but the recent rise of shared bandwidth makes it worth clarifying. The cost-effectiveness of shared bandwidth often makes businesses reconsider their need for a dedicated line.
Cost Considerations
Shared bandwidth is significantly cheaper than dedicated bandwidth at similar speeds.</description></item><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price.</description></item><item><title>Voice over Internet Protocol Phone Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) suggests it will likely replace traditional phone services, including landlines and ISDN PRI. This shift is primarily driven by the transition from traditional telephone networks to computer-based networks, further complicated by the emergence of wireless voice and data services.
Telephone networks, largely analog during their long history, were initially designed solely for voice communication. While attempts were made to use them for data transfer with analog modems, the limited bandwidth of these networks proved insufficient for anything beyond low-speed data.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Reviving The Local Loop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</guid><description>Local loop usage has decreased as people switch from traditional phone lines to wireless or internet-based phone services. This has prompted some to suggest that these copper lines be completely removed. However, just as this idea emerges, new technology is giving these old lines a new purpose.
Fiber optic connections may be the future, but they’re not widely available yet. Only a small percentage of businesses currently have fiber, due to lack of demand, high installation costs, or limited infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Free Telecom Consulting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, many companies are hesitant to hire consultants due to budget constraints. While consultants can potentially save money in the long run, the initial expense can be difficult to justify. So, how can businesses access consulting services without breaking the bank? The answer is free consulting.
One company offers free technical consulting specializing in business telecommunications. By submitting an online inquiry or calling their toll-free number, businesses can connect with a consultant for immediate assistance.</description></item><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>Data Caps: What They Are and How to Avoid Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent internet user, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably encountered data caps. This article explains these usage limits and how to navigate them.
OK, What IS a Data Cap? A data cap restricts the amount of data transferred over a connection within a specific timeframe. Usually set monthly, these limits, measured in MB or GB, reset every 30 days. Activities like browsing, file transfers, and cloud backups consume this data.</description></item><item><title>Use a Telecom Broker Before You Go Broker</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-a-telecom-broker-before-you-go-broker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-a-telecom-broker-before-you-go-broker/</guid><description>Are you getting the best deal on your telecom services? It&amp;rsquo;s hard to know when every provider claims to offer the best rates. Comparing plans and prices from multiple companies is time-consuming and challenging.
That&amp;rsquo;s where telecom brokers come in. Telecom brokers are independent experts who work on your behalf to find the best telecom deals. They are not affiliated with any specific provider, ensuring unbiased recommendations.
Similar to independent insurance agents, telecom brokers represent multiple carriers, giving you access to a wide range of options.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Data Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</guid><description>While traditional data services rely on technologies like T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, OC-3, SONET fiber optics, Frame Relay, and MPLS networks for connectivity, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a modern alternative for the last mile. Although not available coast-to-coast, EoC provides a cost-effective, high-performance solution, especially for connecting businesses to larger private or public networks.
EoC leverages existing copper infrastructure, eliminating the need for costly fiber optic installations or dealing with line-of-sight issues encountered with fixed wireless solutions.</description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle.</description></item><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest.</description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Obsolete?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you been relying on a T1 line for a long time? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable, given their long history. When the Internet was new, a T1 line provided businesses with a dependable, high-bandwidth connection that made dial-up modems seem incredibly slow. These days, similar bandwidth options are available at comparable prices, making those old T1 lines appear slow in comparison. So, are T1 lines still a viable business solution, or are they outdated?</description></item><item><title>Can You Save 50% On Telecom Costs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Even with a tough economy, you might be overpaying for your business telecom services. Want a simple way to reduce your budget without sacrificing staff or essential services? The answer is to lower your telecom expenses.
To start saving immediately, get a cost savings evaluation now and return to this article later. We&amp;rsquo;ll explain how your company can potentially achieve a 50% cost reduction.
Most businesses rely on two primary telecom services: telephone and broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels.</description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1.</description></item><item><title>Copper While Waiting For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-while-waiting-for-fiber/</guid><description>Fiber optic connections are the optimal choice for high bandwidth, offering speeds from 10 Mbps to 10 Gbps using either SONET or Carrier Ethernet protocols. However, accessing these options requires &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber service, which can take several months or more due to potential construction delays. So, how do you maintain connectivity in the meantime?
While waiting for fiber activation was once the only option, many carriers now offer a two-stage solution for businesses needing immediate bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>MAN and MEN - Metropolitan Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are the solution for expanding local networks across different locations within a city. Unlike confined on-site wiring, MANs tackle the challenge of connecting across larger distances.
Traditionally, businesses leased dedicated lines like T1 or DS3 from telecom companies to link their offices. However, this method proved costly and demanded self-management. MANs offer a practical alternative by providing shared fiber optic infrastructure, leading to cost savings and scalability for businesses.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>Covad Ethernet Now Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-ethernet-now-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>Prepare to be surprised! Covad is now offering Ethernet bandwidth at prices even lower than T1 solutions of comparable speeds. That&amp;rsquo;s right, the tide has turned, and Ethernet is now a more budget-friendly option.
While this is an initial launch in 12 markets across California, Michigan, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, and Texas, it could be a sign of a nationwide shift in telecommunication pricing. To see if your location qualifies, you can check Ethernet availability online.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</guid><description>Global telecommunication companies are updating their networks from circuit-based to packet-based systems. With the growth of internet-based networks, Ethernet WAN services have become more accessible and affordable. However, businesses often still rely on older technologies like T1, DS3, or SONET for connecting to these services and cloud networks.
While these older technologies are reliable and getting cheaper, using Ethernet for the initial connection, known as the &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; offers several benefits.</description></item><item><title>10x10 Mbps Ethernet Providers in Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many believe that 10 Mbps Ethernet is replacing traditional T1 lines, and for good reason. This article will explore why that is, how this technology works, and the steps to upgrade.
Businesses have relied on T1 lines for decades due to their high reliability, guaranteed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps, and symmetrical upload and download speeds. Prices have also decreased over time, and availability is now widespread.
The main drawback of T1 lines is their limited bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Internet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</guid><description>Ethernet point-to-point and LAN services have gained popularity among businesses, often replacing T1 lines and outdated Frame Relay networks. Ethernet is also a great way to connect to MPLS VPN networks and the internet.
Carrier Ethernet began as a business-oriented Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) service known as Metro Ethernet, often used by companies to connect multiple locations within a specific geographic region. E-Line point-to-point services like EPL and EVPL provide comparable or superior connectivity to T1 lines, even when multiple T1 lines are used.</description></item><item><title>Many Flavors of Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting your business to the internet is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world. It&amp;rsquo;s practically impossible to operate without a broadband connection. Customers, cloud services, backups, suppliers, and even connections to home offices or remote locations rely on it. The question is, how can you establish the best connection for your business?
Businesses have numerous options for internet service, but the variety can be overwhelming. Choosing the cheapest option might leave you frustrated if it can&amp;rsquo;t handle your needs.</description></item><item><title>PRI Lines For Domestic Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-lines-for-domestic-call-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are turning to domestic call centers, whether they are in-house or independent contractors. All call centers rely on telephone service, and PRI lines are the preferred choice. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, belongs to the Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) standard. ISDN aimed to transition all telephone lines from analog to digital. The basic offering, BRI (Basic Rate Interface), provides two phone lines or one phone line with either a 64 Kbps or 128 Kbps data service.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards.</description></item><item><title>T1 and EoC When There Is No Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</guid><description>The future of business undoubtedly lies in fiber optic bandwidth, particularly given the surge in video content and the increasing shift towards cloud computing. While copper infrastructure is still prevalent, it is gradually becoming outdated. So, how can businesses adapt during this transitional period?
One practical approach is to maximize the use of existing copper infrastructure while it remains viable. Many assume that relying on copper limits bandwidth, but this is not necessarily true.</description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses.</description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet as a DS3 Upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line provides have historically opted for DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. This high-speed digital connection typically runs on a SONET fiber optic circuit, with the final connection to the customer&amp;rsquo;s location installed and maintained by the local phone company. DS3 is fast, very reliable, and more affordable than ever before. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new contender – Fast Ethernet.
Fast Ethernet is a standard Ethernet LAN speed that delivers 100 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Where Are T1 Lines Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of unreliable DSL and cable internet for your business, consider a T1 line. While DSL and cable are suitable for home use, T1 offers a different level of service. As a regulated telecommunications service, T1 ensures consistent bandwidth and reliable uptime, unlike the consumer-grade alternatives.
T1 lines are widely accessible for businesses and function similarly to utilities. If your business has electricity, water, and phone service, you can likely get a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>Talking About Regeneration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talking-about-regeneration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talking-about-regeneration/</guid><description>Signal transmission, whether through wires, fiber optics, or wireless methods, has distance limitations. While this is true, we can easily communicate globally via the internet and private networks. How is this possible?
Signals weaken as they travel, so the solution is to periodically strengthen them and restore the original signal wave. Analog phone lines use components like capacitors and coils to counteract signal degradation. Over long distances, amplifiers are used to boost signals weakened due to resistance in the wiring.</description></item><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service.</description></item><item><title>Integrated Access Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>T1 lines can be used for broadband data or digital phone lines. However, needing separate lines for voice and data was expensive for smaller businesses. Integrated T1 offered a solution by combining voice and data on a single line, proving cost-effective for a while. But now, Integrated Access using Ethernet over Copper is an even better option.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a strong competitor to T1 lines. Both use existing copper telephone wiring, offering reliability and dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Who Says You Can't Sell T1 Lines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</guid><description>While your business thrives by selling business phone systems or computer networking services, you might be missing out on providing clients a complete package. This missing piece? PBX trunk lines or WAN network connections. You&amp;rsquo;d definitely want a share of this profitable market.
You might assume this area belongs solely to phone companies. They prefer you think that way. When businesses see an available &amp;ldquo;T1&amp;rdquo; jack, they often contact their local phone provider directly.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Is a Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</guid><description>Internet access has evolved from slow modems, but connecting still requires converting between protocols and Ethernet used in offices. Now, direct Ethernet internet is possible.
Ethernet for internet access is popular in cities, mainly due to cost savings and simpler networking. Called Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet, it extends your network using Ethernet across cities, countries, or to the internet.
Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) is the top choice for businesses, providing exclusive bandwidth unlike shared services like DSL, WiFi, and cable.</description></item><item><title>Why, Oh Why, PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</guid><description>You might know the terms PRI, T1 PRI, Telephone PRI, PRI Trunk, or ISDN PRI, but what do they actually mean, and why choose this service?
PRI stands for Primary Rate Interface. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN or Integrated Services Digital Network and is a step up from BRI or Basic Rate Interface. Simply put, PRI is a digital line connecting to your PBX phone system. It combines numerous phone lines into a single digital line, leading to cost savings on monthly phone bills.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Stimulus For The Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 04:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</guid><description>Rural America is on the verge of a major internet transformation thanks to a new broadband stimulus program. This program aims to bridge the digital divide by providing $7.2 billion in funding to states, enabling them to improve internet access significantly.
While South Korea is making strides in providing gigabit internet speeds to its citizens, many Americans struggle with significantly slower connections. This disparity stems from two main issues. Firstly, rural areas often lack the infrastructure and competition found in metropolitan areas, resulting in limited internet options.</description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option.</description></item><item><title>Maxed Out On Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your business pushing the limits of its WAN bandwidth? Are you facing network congestion during peak hours? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are solutions to improve your situation.
Start by evaluating your network efficiency. Are you using quality of service management, or are you simply hoping for the best? Prioritizing voice packets can resolve issues with VoIP calls without impacting other processes.
Consider the timing of bandwidth-heavy tasks. Running backups to remote sites during peak hours can hinder employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>Covad and ADTRAN Make Everything Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-and-adtran-make-everything-ethernet/</guid><description>The arrival of Carrier Ethernet is generating considerable excitement around IP core networks and Ethernet access solutions. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean traditional TDM services are obsolete. DS1 and DS3 circuits can be adapted for Ethernet transport with the right equipment, as demonstrated by Carrier Covad and equipment manufacturer ADTRAN.
Covad is expanding its Ethernet service area using ADTRAN&amp;rsquo;s central office and network termination equipment. With a nationwide core network, Covad serves 44 states and 235 major markets, specializing in business DSL, data T1, fixed wireless, bonded T1, and integrated voice and data solutions.</description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>Using T1 Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:54:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</guid><description>T1 lines have diverse applications, including linking offices within a city or across the country. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how this is achieved and the available options.
The fundamental interoffice connection is a point-to-point T1 line, a circuit connecting two specific locations. It runs from one business site to the nearest telecom central office, then between central offices, and finally to the other location.
You might wonder why not directly connect locations with wires.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks.</description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements.</description></item><item><title>T1 Lines For MPLS Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</guid><description>Companies needing to link numerous locations are increasingly choosing MPLS networks, often finding T1 lines to be the optimal solution for network access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Consider an MPLS (Multi Protocol Label Switching) network as a private internet. This private ownership allows the MPLS operator to guarantee the bandwidth and service quality needed for your applications&amp;rsquo; reliable operation. Security is also strengthened as access is exclusive to subscribing businesses.
An MPLS network functions as a customized cloud, connecting only your specified locations.</description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers.</description></item><item><title>GigE For Business Not So Far-Fetched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</guid><description>The increasing demands of online technologies, particularly those using graphics and video, are putting pressure on Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. While ordering a T1 line was once a big decision, businesses may soon need to consider Gigabit Ethernet connections.
While Gigabit Ethernet is often associated with large-scale networks, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly relevant for businesses. With corporate LANs already transitioning to faster speeds, the WAN connection often becomes a bottleneck.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Lifesaver</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</guid><description>Imagine your company facing a critical situation. It&amp;rsquo;s growing, and you need more bandwidth than your reliable T1 line can offer. Upgrading to DS3 seems logical, but your provider can only offer a limited increase, nowhere near the 25 or 50 Mbps you require. They suggest fiber optic service, but your location lacks it, meaning months of waiting and a hefty construction bill.
This presents a difficult choice: secure funding and wait for fiber installation, or relocate to a fiber-ready area.</description></item><item><title>POS For Temporary Store Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</guid><description>A common sight during the holidays is the &amp;ldquo;pop-up shop.&amp;rdquo; These temporary stores occupy vacant spaces in malls and shopping centers, offering seasonal goods like decorations, costumes, and calendars. Once the season ends, so do their operations. Despite their temporary nature, these businesses require robust point-of-sale (POS) systems, even more so than traditional stores.
The need for efficient POS systems stems from the concentrated bursts of customer traffic these stores experience.</description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1.</description></item><item><title>What XO’s 1,000,000 VoIP Customers Predicts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</guid><description>XO Communications, a leading competitor in the telecom industry, recently celebrated a significant achievement: reaching one million business VoIP users.
Reaching this milestone in just five years surprised even XO. This rapid adoption might be unexpected for those hesitant about embracing VoIP technology. We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the downsides of poorly implemented VoIP – distortion, dropped calls, and poor sound quality. However, successful implementations demonstrate that these issues are avoidable. After all, a million businesses can&amp;rsquo;t be wrong.</description></item><item><title>Finding An Ethernet Internet Provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</guid><description>Looking for a better alternative to traditional internet services like T1 lines? Ethernet Internet might be the answer. But finding the right provider can be tricky. That’s where the Ethernet Internet Finder comes in.
This free tool, powered by Telarus, a leading telecom brokerage firm, helps businesses easily find and compare Ethernet Internet providers. Just enter your basic business contact information, preferably your main business phone number, and let the system do the rest.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points.</description></item><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>T1's for Business Parks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</guid><description>Most businesses require reliable communication services, but options can be limited outside of major city centers. While downtown areas boast a variety of high-speed internet providers, businesses in industrial parks often face fewer choices.
Similar to essential utilities, reliable internet access is crucial for modern businesses. However, many older industrial parks were developed before the internet&amp;rsquo;s prominence, lacking the infrastructure for high-speed connections.
Despite this, businesses in these areas still have reliable options.</description></item><item><title>Who Needs A T1 Line at Home?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 12:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</guid><description>T1 lines are famous for their reliability and accessibility wherever there&amp;rsquo;s telephone service, but they might not be suitable for everyone&amp;rsquo;s home broadband needs. The cost alone is a major deterrent for most people. However, in some situations, a T1 line might be the only practical option.
Residential broadband prioritizes affordability to reach a broad market. That&amp;rsquo;s why DSL services can cost under $20 monthly, and Cable broadband with 3 to 6 Mbps typically costs $30 to $40.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?</description></item><item><title>Cable, T1 and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have three primary broadband options today: Cable, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper (EoC). While their costs are relatively similar, each offers distinct advantages. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options further.
T1 lines, a long-standing choice for SMBs, utilize half-century-old telephone industry technology. This technology transmits digital signals across standard copper telephone wiring. A T1 line consists of two copper pairs, one for uploads and the other for downloads, achieving a consistent speed of 1.</description></item><item><title>HFC Broadband For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>Many small businesses don&amp;rsquo;t fit into the &amp;ldquo;residential&amp;rdquo; user category but don&amp;rsquo;t require or can&amp;rsquo;t afford expensive traditional business telecom services like T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper. One solution is HFC, or Hybrid Fiber Coax, broadband services.
You might know this as &amp;ldquo;Cable broadband for business.&amp;rdquo; Many home-based businesses successfully use it to manage websites, access online information, and send and receive emails. However, ordering residential service for a business location usually results in rejection.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1.</description></item><item><title>Redundant Business Internet Connection Using Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Large companies have avoided using consumer-grade broadband services due to concerns about their reliability and performance. While it is prudent to use dedicated circuits with service level agreements for critical business operations, there is a cost-effective solution available for backing up telecom services and enhancing internet speed.
Cable broadband has grown rapidly and seen continuous technological advancements, primarily due to its popularity as a consumer internet service. While alternatives like satellite, wireless, dial-up, and fiber optic exist, they often come with limitations in bandwidth, high installation costs, or limited availability.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines.</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires.</description></item><item><title>3G Fixed Wireless For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</guid><description>The same 3G technology that revolutionized mobile phones is also available as a fixed wireless service, offering a cost-effective solution for businesses in areas with limited internet options. Cellular networks have established a wide infrastructure of base stations, effectively blanketing the country with both voice and data coverage. These familiar cell towers transmit signals using microwave radio equipment.
Essentially, the 3G wireless broadband service functions as a network of interconnected Wi-Fi hotspots with a significantly larger coverage area.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>Is There Business Fiber Optic Internet Near Me?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:29:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you still dealing with slow internet service plagued by low speeds, network congestion, high latency, packet loss, or all of the above? It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, right? You&amp;rsquo;re likely spending more on subpar service than you would on a high-performance fiber optic broadband upgrade. The question is: &amp;ldquo;Is business fiber optic internet available in my area?&amp;rdquo;
Times Have Changed
When broadband first became an option, choices were limited. DSL was once the leading technology, with even basic ADSL shared connections offering a significant speed boost over previous options.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Now Faster and Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>For a long time, T1 lines have been the top choice for bandwidth for small and medium businesses. They are popular for good reason: they are widely available, reliable, secure, dedicated, adaptable, and relatively affordable.
While T1 services have many advantages, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get even more value: Ethernet, particularly Ethernet over Copper.
Many people are not familiar with Carrier Ethernet services, as they have only become available recently. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is primarily found in large cities, as it has a limited reach and requires businesses to be within a few miles of the provider&amp;rsquo;s office.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI Offers Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</guid><description>If your company relies heavily on phone communication, using numerous phone lines managed by an internal system, ISDN PRI might be the solution for you. It provides excellent voice quality, quick call transfers, and additional features like Caller ID, all while potentially saving you money.
ISDN PRI, or Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is an advanced form of the traditional T1 digital phone line. While it utilizes the same T1 line infrastructure, making it widely accessible, its channel organization sets it apart.</description></item><item><title>Signaling for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signaling-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signaling-for-call-centers/</guid><description>Every phone call involves two parts: the conversation itself and the signaling that manages the phone network. While signaling might seem purely technical, its implementation significantly impacts call center efficiency.
Traditional analog phone lines use the same copper wires, called the local loop, for both voice and signaling. Touchtone dialing, handset lifting, and ringing all rely on electrical signals sent over this shared connection. This method, known as in-band signaling, has limitations.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3.</description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1.</description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Apartment Manager's Little Money Maker</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apartment-managers-little-money-maker/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apartment-managers-little-money-maker/</guid><description>Even though real estate prices are declining, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance to make more money from your current tenants and even bring in new ones. It&amp;rsquo;s something they need and are already paying for, but would be happy to get from you at a lower price. This opportunity is providing broadband internet service.
You might wonder how apartment managers can become internet providers. The reality is that, regardless of the size of your building, your tenants are spending a significant amount on internet services.</description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Bandwidth Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</guid><description>DS3 WAN connections are a popular choice for businesses that need more bandwidth than T1 lines offer but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for a full OC-3 fiber optic SONET service. However, exploring alternative options might be beneficial due to cost or performance considerations.
There are several bandwidth options available today that might be a better fit than your existing DS3 connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some alternatives.
DS3 bridges the gap between copper wireline and fiber optic bandwidth services.</description></item><item><title>Looking For A Lit Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</guid><description>When seeking high-speed internet for your business, you need more than just a building with lights on at night. You need a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; – one connected to a fiber optic network.
Fiber optic connectivity is crucial for high bandwidth. While most buildings have copper wiring for traditional phone lines and T1 connections, these offer limited bandwidth (1.5 Mbps per line). Fiber optics, on the other hand, provide significantly faster speeds (10 Gbps or more per fiber) using light to transmit data.</description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet Broadband For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>When considering broadband, we usually think of DSL, cable internet, or cellular wireless. However, these options are typically consumer-grade and might not be suitable for business needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why these services might be frustrating for businesses and examine a promising alternative.
Cellular wireless, including 3G and 4G, relies on cell towers with limited bandwidth shared among many users. Smartphones consume significant bandwidth, and a high concentration of devices can overload the network.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage.</description></item><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities.</description></item><item><title>Yes, There IS Rural Broadband For Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</guid><description>Many people are excited about the economic stimulus plan&amp;rsquo;s promise of expanded rural broadband access. However, you might already be able to get the internet speeds your rural business needs.
Most major internet providers have overlooked rural areas, not because rural businesses are less important, but because the cost of installing infrastructure like coaxial cables or fiber optic cables is difficult to recoup when there are fewer customers. This is why cable and DSL internet services are less common in the countryside.</description></item><item><title>How T1 and E1 Lines Compare</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-and-e1-lines-compare/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-and-e1-lines-compare/</guid><description>T1 and E1 are two widely used digital line services for voice and data, each prevalent in different geographical regions. While T1 is common in the US, Canada, Japan, and South Korea, E1 dominates Europe and most other parts of the world. The &amp;ldquo;T&amp;rdquo; in T1 comes from &amp;ldquo;T-Carrier,&amp;rdquo; a standard developed by Bell Labs after World War II for carrying multiple phone calls between switching centers. Similarly, the &amp;ldquo;E&amp;rdquo; in E1 stands for &amp;ldquo;Europe.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits.</description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent.</description></item><item><title>Where Competition Is Cutting Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</guid><description>In this day and age, everyone is trying to save money. Your monthly telecom costs are a great place to start. Telecom expenses are often high and confusing, so it’s a good idea to take a close look at your bills and see if you can find ways to reduce costs or find a better deal. Keep in mind that pricing can vary significantly depending on your location.
We often assume that the cost of goods and services is relatively consistent regardless of location.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard about Metro Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s rise in popularity for business WAN connections, particularly in major cities with concentrated business areas. These areas have been the primary focus of competitive bandwidth providers offering lower per-Mbps pricing. However, you might assume that Ethernet WAN services are only accessible in downtown areas or large suburbs.
This is about to change. Hatteras Networks has introduced a line of repeater and line power modules that extend Mid-Band Ethernet service up to 25 miles over standard telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions.</description></item><item><title>How Broadband Bonding is Mushrooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:52:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</guid><description>Businesses with high bandwidth demands now have a delicious new option for boosting their WAN capacity thanks to the TRUFFLE from Mushroom Networks, Inc.
What makes the TRUFFLE so appealing? This device can combine the bandwidth of multiple broadband connections – think DSL, Cable, T1, even satellite – to create a single, faster, and more reliable connection, similar to T1 line bonding but with more flexibility. The TRUFFLE BBNA6401 model, for instance, can aggregate up to 6 different connections, reaching download speeds of up to 50 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Business VoIP Solution Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about switching your business phone system from the traditional analog or PBX setup to VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), it&amp;rsquo;s wise to explore the various business VoIP options available before making a complete overhaul. The best choice for you depends on your specific needs and, by selecting wisely, you can maximize your telephony investment.
The main reasons to consider VoIP are cost savings, enhanced calling features, or a combination of both.</description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Insurance Keeps You in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 05:32:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Constant connectivity has its perks for individuals and businesses, but technology isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof. A broadband outage can be incredibly isolating. Fortunately, there are safeguards against such situations.
Consumers can utilize their mobile data as a backup. Modern smartphones can act as wireless hotspots, allowing devices like computers and printers to connect. While speed and data limits might be concerns, it provides a temporary solution. Another option is using public Wi-Fi hotspots, though availability might be an issue during widespread outages.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Vocal IP Networx Offers Free SNMP Monitoring</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with the challenges of managing T1 lines and bandwidth, especially keeping track of service availability across different vendors and equipment. While large companies have dedicated IT teams, smaller businesses often handle this responsibility as issues arise.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be beneficial to have affordable network monitoring support? Vocal IP Networx, a leading IP telephony provider, offers a solution: free, continuous SNMP monitoring for all circuits and customer premises equipment (CPE) they provide.</description></item><item><title>Can You Believe 200 Mbps EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a widely used technology that delivers mid-band Ethernet connections without the delays and costs of fiber optic installation. Although initially considered a temporary solution, EoC has become a strong competitor to fiber services.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/)Businesses currently using T1 lines or considering them are a key market for EoC. T1 is a well-established, dependable, and cost-effective telecom service that offers 1.5 Mbps using one or two pairs of twisted copper telephone wiring.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Copper 50 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</guid><description>Businesses that need to connect numerous employees to the internet or move large files, particularly high-resolution images, require more bandwidth than a standard connection provides. Traditionally, they&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded their T1 lines to DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. Now, there are more choices for around 50 Mbps using both copper and fiber optic connections.
DS3 is often considered a copper wireline service because it connects with coaxial cables and uses BNC connectors.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth For Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</guid><description>Contrary to popular belief, Ethernet WAN service isn&amp;rsquo;t confined to cities. There are ways to get Ethernet connectivity even in rural areas.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity among small and medium businesses. It uses existing telephone wiring to deliver Ethernet speeds from 3 to 50 Mbps, and even over 100 Mbps in some places. This makes it a cost-effective option for businesses that need high bandwidth. However, EoC has distance limitations.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services.</description></item><item><title>Will Ethernet Crush DS3?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</guid><description>Companies needing more bandwidth than a 1.5 Mbps T1 line often upgraded to DS3, but its 45 Mbps speed was often more than they needed. A newer option, Carrier Ethernet (also known as Metro Ethernet), offers a more practical solution with scalable bandwidth at a often lower cost.
Ethernet services are significantly less expensive than DS3 in some markets, costing up to 50% less. However, in areas where Ethernet isn&amp;rsquo;t widely available, prices may be comparable to DS3.</description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers.</description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance.</description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband.</description></item></channel></rss>