<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Biometrics on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/biometrics/</link><description>Recent content in Biometrics on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 23:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/biometrics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it necessary for the EU to prohibit the real-time use of remote biometric identification systems for law enforcement purposes?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-for-the-eu-to-prohibit-the-real-time-use-of-remote-biometric-identification-systems-for-law-enforcement-purposes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 23:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-for-the-eu-to-prohibit-the-real-time-use-of-remote-biometric-identification-systems-for-law-enforcement-purposes/</guid><description>Asress Adimi Gikay (PhD)
Senior Lecturer in AI, Disruptive Innovation, and Law
Brunel Law School &amp;amp; Brunel Centre for AI(London, UK)
Twitter: @DrAsressGikay
Photo credit: Irbsas, via Wikimedia commons
Why a Complete Ban on Real-Time Remote Biometric Identification Systems Is Not the Answer
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposed Artificial Intelligence Act (EU-AIA), intended to regulate AI use, has faced criticism since its introduction two years ago. A key point of contention is the regulation&amp;rsquo;s stance on law enforcement&amp;rsquo;s use of Real-Time Remote Biometric Identification Systems (RT-RBIS) in public spaces.</description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience.</description></item></channel></rss>