<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ooredoo on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ooredoo/</link><description>Recent content in Ooredoo on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ooredoo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Indosat Ooredoo introduces nationwide 4G-LTE service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo.
Indosat Ooredoo has introduced its high-speed 4G-LTE service across Indonesia. The company stated that the improved connectivity and call clarity offered by its new 4Gplus data network come at the same cost as its existing 3G services.
In the last two years, Indosat Ooredoo has doubled its network speeds, achieving the fastest 3G internet speeds available. Independent tests show its 4Gplus service can reach download speeds of up to 185Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy the first 15 minutes of free Wi-Fi on Qatar Airways, courtesy of Ooredoo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo. The MoU was signed by (from left) Waleed Al Sayed, CEO, Ooredoo Qatar and Qatar Airways Group Chief Executive, His Excellency Akbar Al Baker.
Ooredoo and Qatar Airways have established a partnership where Ooredoo will sponsor Qatar Airways&amp;rsquo; in-flight Wi-Fi for the next three years. This agreement will make Ooredoo the sole sponsor for Wi-Fi on all Qatar Airways flights equipped with the service.
This sponsorship allows passengers to use their personal electronic devices to connect to the internet, check emails, and send SMS/MMS messages once the service is active during their flight.</description></item></channel></rss>