<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Presumption of Innocence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/presumption-of-innocence/</link><description>Recent content in Presumption of Innocence on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/presumption-of-innocence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Court of Justice reconsidering the European equivalent of the 'fifth amendment'? The CJEU makes a decision on the right to remain silent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</guid><description>Inês Pereira de Sousa, Lecturer and PhD candidate at Porto Faculty of Law, Universidade Católica Portuguesa; Researcher at CEID – Católica Research Centre for the Future of Law; Member of ANESC – Academic Network on the European Social Charter and Social Rights; Member of EUCRIM –European Criminal Law Associations’ Forum - isousa@porto.ucp.pt
On February 2, 2021, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) had the chance to reexamine the right to remain silent and the right against self-incrimination in a case originating from the Italian Constitutional Court...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pilate cleanses his hands. The CJEU's stance on pre-trial detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</guid><description>By Adriano Martufi (Assistant Professor, Leiden University) and Christina Peristeridou (Assistant Professor, Maastricht University)
Introduction
The recent judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of DK (C-653/19 PPU, 28 November 2019) has validated two concerning observations about the state of European criminal law. Firstly, Directive 2016/343 on the presumption of innocence has limited practical application, particularly regarding pre-trial detention. Secondly, pre-trial detention is a contentious subject, with both the CJEU and the EU legislator hesitant to establish common standards despite their absence negatively impacting mutual trust between Member States&amp;rsquo; judicial systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>