<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Country on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/country/</link><description>Recent content in Country on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/country/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The MyNumber service from Hashtag assists businesses in reducing their hotline expenses in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>PLDT, through its corporate business group PLDT ALPHA Enterprise, has launched the PLDT #MyNumber service. This service streamlines a business&amp;rsquo;s hotline system into a memorable four to eight-digit contact number that starts with the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; symbol (for example, #8888). This single number can be reached by consumers nationwide using PLDT landlines, Smart, Talk N’ Text, and Sun mobile phones.
This service is designed for businesses that currently advertise different hotline numbers for different regions.</description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations.</description></item><item><title>Facebook introduces a user-friendly, streamlined video advertising format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</guid><description>Over one-third of mobile internet users in Saudi Arabia are receptive to video advertisements, exceeding the global average of 22%.
Facebook is introducing &amp;ldquo;Slideshow,&amp;rdquo; a new, user-friendly video ad format designed to increase reach across various devices and connection speeds.
In a blog post announcing Slideshow, Facebook highlights a recent report indicating that people in regions like the Philippines, where connectivity can be slow, costly, or both, and where feature phones are common, are even more receptive to video ads.</description></item></channel></rss>