<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Travel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/travel/</link><description>Recent content in Travel on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates reveals updated interiors for its Boeing 777 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced redesigned interiors for its Boeing 777 fleet, featuring upgraded seats and entertainment systems across all cabins. This multi-million dollar investment reflects the airline&amp;rsquo;s focus on enhancing the customer experience.
The new First Class cabins, designed in collaboration with several firms, offer private suites with sliding doors inspired by Mercedes-Benz S-Class. These suites prioritize comfort and luxury with features like soft leather seats, mood lighting, and ample storage. Retained features include personal minibars and wireless controls for seat adjustment and entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The launch of Fairfield by Marriott Belitung has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its Fairfield by Marriott brand with the opening of a new hotel in Belitung, Indonesia.
Source: Fairfield by Marriott Belitung website. The Fairfield by Marriott Belitung.
Mike Fulkerson, Vice President of Brand &amp;amp; Marketing for Marriott International Asia Pacific, stated that Fairfield by Marriott is experiencing rapid growth in the region, with 47 properties in development in Asia Pacific and over 400 globally. He highlighted the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing a relaxing and dependable experience at a good value, enhanced by Indonesian hospitality, making the Belitung location an ideal retreat for travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two JW Marriott hotels have been ranked in the top 10 TripAdvisor Travelers' Choices for Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Lotte Hotel Seoul.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for hotels in Korea ranked the following as the top ten:
Lotte Hotel Seoul, with a rating of 4.5 out of 5 from 1,849 reviews. The Plaza Conrad Seoul JW Marriott Dongdaemun Square Seoul Park Hyatt Seoul The Shilla Seoul Sheraton Seoul D Cube City Hotel The Westin Chosun Seoul The Ritz-Carlton, Seoul The JW Marriott Seoul Curious?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Azerai offers affordable luxury in Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Azerai invites discerning travelers to experience attainable luxury in Vietnam through a collection of acclaimed boutique resorts. Founded by Adrian Zecha, the visionary behind Aman Resorts, the Azerai concept is already present in the culturally rich destinations of Ke Ga, Can Tho, and Hue.
Source: Azerai. Each Azerai resort is designed to envelop guests in sophisticated, understated luxury.
Every Azerai resort aims to immerse guests in refined yet understated luxury. At Azerai Can Tho, this translates to seclusion within low-rise structures on a private islet in the Hau River, reachable only by boat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bleisure app emerged as the winner of the Sabre hackathon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</guid><description>Source: Sabre. From left: Isolda Josy and Pranay Roy, Moments; Mendis from Sabre Travel Network Asia Pacific; and Marco Angeles, Moments.
A team from Singapore won the 24-hour Destination Hack: Singapore, Sabre&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Asia Pacific hackathon. Participants were tasked with designing a new technology app that could revolutionize travel – from planning and booking to the overall experience.
The winning app, Moments, caters to the increasing demand for &amp;ldquo;bleisure&amp;rdquo; travel in the Asia Pacific region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new, healthier menu choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has partnered with the Department of Health – Abu Dhabi to introduce Weqaya, a selection of healthy food choices, on flights and in its Abu Dhabi lounges.
Weqaya, meaning &amp;ldquo;prevention&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, is a program created by the Department of Health - Abu Dhabi to encourage healthy and balanced eating habits for improved health and well-being.
Etihad now offers several Weqaya dishes on First and Business Class long-haul and ultra-long-haul flights departing from Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Access free Wi-Fi at more than 200,000 hotspots throughout Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 21:28:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</guid><description>Source: Wire and Wireless Company. The logo displays the Wi-Fi symbol superimposed on an image of Mt Fuji.
Wire and Wireless Company, a Japanese telecommunications provider, is celebrating the second anniversary of its free TRAVEL JAPAN Wi-Fi app. The latest update includes enhanced features and a wider range of free Wi-Fi access points.
The app provides travelers with details about nearby stores, restaurants, and attractions, along with numerous discount coupons...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-free-wi-fi-at-more-than-200-000-hotspots-throughout-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines introduces direct flight between Shenzhen and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Pictured at the Auckland welcoming ceremony are the Consulate General of China in Auckland, Acting Consul General Luo Binhui, Auckland Airport CEO Adrian Littlewood, Hainan Airlines President Sun Jianfeng, and Hainan Airlines&amp;rsquo; VIP customers.
On December 30, 2016, Hainan Airlines launched its inaugural non-stop flight between Shenzhen, China, and Auckland, New Zealand. The new route connects the two cities with an 11-hour flight.
Hainan Airlines will service the Shenzhen-Auckland route with wide-body Airbus A330s, known for their spacious cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now includes Melbourne as a destination for its A380 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched a new era of luxury air travel between Melbourne and Abu Dhabi with the introduction of the A380 superjumbo. This flagship aircraft, which features luxurious amenities like The Residence and next-generation cabins, will operate on one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily flights between the cities, replacing a three-class Boeing 777-300ER. Passengers can enjoy innovative hospitality services during their flight, including a dedicated Butler, Inflight Chef, Flying Nanny, and Food and Beverage Managers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel expands ReadyRoam data roaming service to include additional destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</guid><description>Singtel has improved its ReadyRoam 1GB for 30 days service, making it the first to provide comprehensive multi-destination data roaming across Asia, Europe, the US, and Canada. This enhanced service, which covers 26 countries for S$35 and 11 countries for S$20, offers travelers a convenient way to stay connected.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, highlights that this enhancement caters to the holiday season when many customers travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural commercial flight of the Etihad Boeing 787 Dreamliner is headed to Germany</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways, the flag carrier of the UAE, launched its inaugural Boeing 787 Dreamliner commercial flight. The first flight, a Boeing 787-9, flew from Abu Dhabi to Düsseldorf, Germany. Departing at 2:15 a.m. as flight EY23, the seven-hour, 25-minute journey landed at 6:40 a.m. The return leg from Düsseldorf departs at 10:20 a.m., arriving in Abu Dhabi at 7:50 p.m.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and CEO, stated that the Boeing 787 is a significant achievement for the airline, calling it the most technologically sophisticated aircraft in its class...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces three new exclusive routes with a 20% discount on all flights until February 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</guid><description>AirAsia is the sole airline offering flights for three new routes: Johor Bahru to Tawau, Singapore to Kota Bharu, and Singapore to Terengganu. The airline is currently promoting these routes with fares as low as RM69* for travel between Johor Bahru and Tawau. This offer is valid for bookings made before February 16th, 2014, for travel dates between April 18th, 2014 and January 31st, 2015.
Welcome banners at Changi Airport..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates is offering reduced fares to more than 70 locations. Bookings must be made by August 20, 2018, for travel dates between September 1, 2018, and March 31, 2019.
Economy Class fares start at AED945 to Beirut, Lebanon, AED995 to Mumbai, India, and AED2,345 to Bangkok, Thailand. Business Class fares to these destinations cost AED5,245, AED2,795, and AED9,795, respectively.
Travelers can enhance their experience with Emirates Holidays, adding a five-star hotel stay to their trip...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wanda Vista brand expands globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</guid><description>Qian Jin, the head of the upscale hotel group Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has revealed the global growth plan for their Wanda Vista brand.
Wanda Vista represents the top tier of luxury within Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, designed specifically for guests who appreciate art and culture. Situated in major international cities and drawing inspiration from Eastern aesthetics, the brand focuses on providing personalized service catered to each guest&amp;rsquo;s individual requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is continuing its guest outreach program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas.
Since late March 2020, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has been offering its guests and followers daily live chats, cooking demonstrations, and meditation and yoga sessions.
Recognizing that many people are hesitant to resume travel despite the easing of COVID-19 restrictions, the company introduced six new themes for its #AtHomeWithSixSenses campaign.
These themes - Wellness, Eat, Grow, Sustainability, Sleep and From the Heart of Six Senses - will continue to be explored through content on the Six Senses website (sixsenses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Abu Dhabi International Airport has increased its summer flights by 18% compared to 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi International Airport&amp;rsquo;s summer 2014 flight schedule is its busiest ever, featuring six new destinations and 71 additional weekly flights to India.
Airport authorities reported an 18% increase in weekly flights compared to the previous summer, rising from 1,052 to 1,242, catering to both business and leisure travelers.
New nonstop routes debuting this summer include flights from Abu Dhabi to Los Angeles, Zurich, Belgrade (Serbia), Perth, Jaipur, and Yerevan (Armenia)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KKday has launched in Singapore and is introducing the #taiwantrippin promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</guid><description>Source: KKday. Ming Chen, CEO of Asia’s leading travel experience e-commerce platform KKday celebrates Singapore launch, and the #taiwantrippin digital campaign.
KKday, an Asian e-commerce platform specializing in travel experiences, has launched in Singapore. Based in Taiwan, KKday links users with local tours globally. Following its 2014 debut, KKday expanded to Hong Kong, Korea, and Japan, with Singapore as its fourth market.
“Establishing a presence in Singapore was a logical step...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkday-has-launched-in-singapore-and-is-introducing-the-taiwantrippin-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi First Class Lounge &amp; Spa has been opened by Etihad Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has opened a new flagship First Class Lounge &amp;amp; Spa in Terminal 3 of Abu Dhabi International Airport. This space highlights the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to offering exceptional and desirable hospitality.
Inspired by top-tier hotels, private clubs, and fine dining establishments, the lounge provides an exclusive environment. It features unmatched design, style, comfort, world-class dining, and personalized beauty and relaxation services.
The lounge offers 16 distinct zones for guests to unwind, recharge, and enjoy entertainment in complete luxury before their flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reserve a magical Disney experience aboard the Disney Adventure through Traveloka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</guid><description>Starting in the fourth quarter of 2024, travelers can book voyages with Disney Cruise Lines departing from Singapore through the Traveloka app, according to an announcement from the Southeast Asian travel platform. This addition to Traveloka&amp;rsquo;s offerings reinforces the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to showcasing the diverse experiences and attractions available in Singapore.
Launching in late 2025, the Disney Adventure will call Singapore its home port. The ship boasts seven themed areas with Disney-themed dining and exciting onboard activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IHG will no longer provide mini toiletries as bathroom amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</guid><description>Source: IHG. A shower with sink showing miniatures as amenities.
The InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) is transitioning from small, individual toiletry bottles to larger, bulk amenity dispensers in all 843,000 rooms across its portfolio of hotels. This change, to be fully implemented by 2021, is part of a larger sustainability initiative and establishes IHG as the first global hotel company to entirely eliminate miniature bathroom products in favor of bulk-sized options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates has prohibited hoverboards and reminds passengers of the approved items for carry-on luggage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates reminds passengers to check before packing, for hassle-free travel this holiday season.
Emirates Airlines is reminding travelers to review the allowed carry-on and checked baggage items for a smooth and secure journey during this holiday period.
To maintain the safety of everyone onboard, loose lithium batteries used in devices like cameras, cell phones, and laptops are not allowed in checked luggage. This includes &amp;ldquo;hoverboards&amp;rdquo; or self-balancing scooters, whether or not the batteries have been removed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ascott's latest brand, Lyf, is aimed at Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</guid><description>Source: Capitaland. CapitaLand’s President &amp;amp; Group CEO, Lim Ming Yan (left) and Ascott’s CEO, Lee Chee Koon (right) try their hand at baking at Lyf’s ‘Bond’ social kitchen.
CapitaLand&amp;rsquo;s serviced residence branch, The Ascott Limited (Ascott), is launching Lyf, a new brand designed for Millennials who want to experience travel like locals.
Lyf goes beyond typical hospitality models by creating a community where guests can connect with fellow travelers and innovators to live and collaborate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now offers Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner on flights from Abu Dhabi to Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has upgraded its Abu Dhabi to Shanghai route, now offering flights on the Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner. This change increases capacity by 14%, offering 28 business class and 271 economy seats.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Peter Baumgartner, highlighted the significance of the Chinese market, particularly the rising demand from business and leisure travelers. The decision to utilize the Dreamliner reflects Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s status as a major global hub and its importance in Etihad&amp;rsquo;s network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Business Plan package at The Shilla Seoul includes access to The Executive Lounge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. The Executive Lounge.
Through June 30, 2019, The Shilla Seoul is offering its Business Plan package, which gives guests the opportunity to experience The Executive Lounge.
Guests selecting the Executive Business Deluxe option receive exclusive access to The Executive Lounge, complimentary breakfast at The Parkview, and access to both the gym and indoor swimming pool.
The Executive Lounge at The Shilla Seoul, situated on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s top floor, is designed as a luxurious penthouse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor Plus is the latest paid loyalty program offered by Accor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</guid><description>Source: Accor.
Accor Advantage Plus, the paid loyalty program from Accor with more than 350,000 members in 17 countries, has been renamed and enhanced. Now known as Accor Plus, this 21-year-old program allows members to enjoy enhanced experiences at over 600 Accor properties in the Asia Pacific region. The company stated that members can benefit from substantial discounts on accommodations, dining at over 800 restaurants, and access to various VIP events and partner offers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the hallyu wave with Viator tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</guid><description>Viator, a popular tour booking platform, has noticed a surge in demand for tours featuring filming locations from the hit Korean drama &amp;ldquo;Descendants of the Sun.&amp;rdquo;
Besides tours to Greece, Viator offers the &amp;ldquo;Yongin MBC Dramia TV Set Tour&amp;rdquo; in Korea. This half-day tour takes fans behind the scenes at Yongin MBC TV studios, showcasing sets used in Korea&amp;rsquo;s most popular historical dramas.
For K-drama music enthusiasts, Viator has curated the &amp;ldquo;K Pop Tour&amp;rdquo; in Seoul...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Azerai reveals special promotions for Chinese New Year in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:43:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</guid><description>Source: Azerai. Exterior, Hue. Constructed in 1930 as the residence of the French Resident Superieure, this colonial mansion forms the hotel&amp;rsquo;s heart. The mansion&amp;rsquo;s noticeable facade, characterized by its elongated horizontal lines and nautical motifs, is a testament to Art Deco architectural style. Its two harmonious wings, home to a vast tropical garden and a saltwater pool, were constructed in 2005, reflecting a modern take on Art Deco.
Azerai has unveiled special offers and activities for Chinese New Year at its Vietnamese properties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take a virtual tour of Emaar hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Using panoramic photography and videography, each virtual tour showcases the hotel&amp;rsquo;s features in detail.
Emaar Hospitality Group, the hospitality and leisure branch of Emaar Properties, has launched 360-degree virtual tours of its hotels in Dubai, UAE. These tours, created with high-definition photos and videos, allow potential guests to experience each hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique offerings, explore its various aspects, and make well-informed booking decisions.
The virtual tours encompass properties under the luxury Address Hotels + Resorts brand, the upscale lifestyle Vida Hotels and Resorts brand, and the new contemporary mid-scale Rove Hotels brand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery is poised to transform into a secret retreat in Kyoto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Interior, Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery.
Accor has expanded its presence in Japan with the launch of its second MGallery Hotel, the Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery.
This Kyoto-based hotel, designed by architect Yukio Hashimoto, centers around a Japanese garden, providing a sophisticated experience of the changing seasons. Hashimoto&amp;rsquo;s design prioritizes creating a specific atmosphere over focusing solely on materials, resulting in a minimalist and timeless aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Gold Coast, Australia will be home to the first Hyde location outside of the US</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</guid><description>Accor is expanding its partnership with sbe beyond the US, selecting Australia as the first Asia Pacific location. Hyde, their luxury lifestyle brand known for its Los Angeles Sunset Strip inspiration, will debut Hyde Paradiso on the Gold Coast in March 2019. This venue promises an all-day experience, transforming into a sophisticated lounge and dining destination in the evening.
Simon McGrath, COO of Accor Pacific, highlights the partnership&amp;rsquo;s goal to deliver unique lifestyle experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Artyzen Singapore will be launched in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</guid><description>Preferred Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, boasting a global network of over 650 hotels, resorts, and residences in 80 countries, is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the upcoming October debut of Artyzen Singapore.
This 20-story establishment occupies the former site of the Marie Villa mansion, conveniently situated near Orchard Road and the Singapore Botanic Gardens. The hotel features 142 generously sized rooms and suites, each spanning at least 42 square meters and offering either a balcony or terraced Sky Gardens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enjoy a complimentary stay at a luxurious hotel in Doha when you transit overnight with Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:42:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Doha skyline.
Qatar Airways has teamed up with Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA) to launch a stopover package, aiming to highlight Qatar as a top destination for travelers.
The package allows transit passengers to explore Doha with complimentary luxury hotel stays and transit visas. This unique deal is part of their larger &amp;ldquo;+Qatar&amp;rdquo; campaign, encouraging those passing through to consider extending their trip.
The promotion invites all Qatar Airways transit passengers to include Doha in their travel plans by offering a free one-night stay at some of the country’s top four- and five-star hotels in the capital...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways introduces more flights on the Abu Dhabi to Doha route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is commemorating a decade of service to Qatar this year by adding nine weekly flights to its Abu Dhabi-Doha route, strengthening its dedication to this important Gulf market.
Starting August 1, 2016, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s national airline will boost its weekly service to Qatar&amp;rsquo;s capital to 37 flights. These new daily morning and early evening departures on Thursdays and Saturdays offer more flexibility and convenience, catering to business travelers in both Abu Dhabi and Doha...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Katamama will be opening its doors to guests in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</guid><description>Source: Katamama. A rooftop suite at dusk.
Katamama, a 58-suite boutique hotel in Seminyak, Bali&amp;rsquo;s prime oceanfront area, is set to open in late March 2016.
The hotel emphasizes &amp;ldquo;handcrafted hospitality,&amp;rdquo; with every detail meticulously designed and executed by skilled Indonesian artisans. Katamama is a project by PTT Family, known for acclaimed restaurants, bars, and the Potato Head Beach Club in Bali. This 20-villa estate is famous for its innovative environmental design and a prominent contemporary Indonesian art gallery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Yokohama Convention &amp; Visitors Bureau extends a warm welcome to Muslim travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 12:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</guid><description>Source: Yokohama Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau
The Yokohama Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau (YCVB) reports that its specialized Muslim Tourist Information microsite, part of the official Yokohama Visitors&amp;rsquo; Guide website, is gaining traction with Muslims in Southeast Asia.
Launched in December 2013, the Muslim Tourist Information website highlights tourist attractions, dining, halal shops, and mosques, all recommended by Yokohama&amp;rsquo;s Muslim residents. A survey of Southeast Asian Muslims revealed that over 90% found the information on restaurants, mosques, and recommended itineraries helpful...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yokohama-convention-visitors-bureau-extends-a-warm-welcome-to-muslim-travelers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will begin flying between Okinawa and Japan in January 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will launch its inaugural charter flights between Singapore and Okinawa, Japan.
Operated in partnership with Okinawa Tourist Service (OTS) and Jumbo Tours Okinawa, these monthly charters will run from September 9, 2014, to January 3, 2015. Utilizing Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both business and economy class seating, these direct flights aim to provide travelers with a convenient option to visit Okinawa.
From September to October 2014, flights will depart Singapore Changi Airport Terminal 2 at 10:00 am and arrive at Okinawa Naha Airport at 4:15 pm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escape to Bintan Lagoon Resort for a Global Wellness Day retreat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</guid><description>Bintan Lagoon Resort (BLR) is commemorating this year&amp;rsquo;s Global Wellness Day with a special getaway package full of wellness activities on June 10th and 11th.
A quick 75-minute ferry trip from Singapore, BLR is nestled on 300 hectares of lush land, boasting a private 1.5km beach. With a wide range of over 50 indoor and outdoor activities, from adventurous to relaxing, and delicious, healthy culinary options, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The groundbreaking ceremony for Jewel has been successfully completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Changi Airport.
Jewel Changi Airport Trustee (JCAT), a collaboration between Changi Airport Group (CAG) and CapitaMalls Asia (the shopping mall branch of CapitaLand), has initiated the construction of Jewel Changi Airport. This mixed-use development, situated in front of Terminal 1 (T1), will feature attractions, retail spaces, a hotel, and airport operational facilities.
Strategically placed at the airport&amp;rsquo;s core, Jewel aims to be a premier lifestyle destination enhancing Changi Airport&amp;rsquo;s global standing and solidifying Singapore&amp;rsquo;s attractiveness as a layover spot for travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air Arabia has opened a new sales office in Dubai and has also introduced city check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</guid><description>Air Arabia, a leading low-cost carrier in the Middle East and North Africa, has expanded its presence in Dubai, UAE, by opening a new sales office and city terminal check-in facility.
Adel Al Ali, Group CEO of Air Arabia, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to enhancing customer experience and convenience across its network. He emphasized the significance of the new sales office in strengthening their services in Dubai and the UAE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a Jumeirah City Break</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah website.
City Breaks at Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Jumeirah Creekside Hotel, and Jumeirah Living World Trade Centre Residences come with perks like free entry to Wild Wadi Waterpark and Zero Gravity Private Beach.
Jumeirah Emirates Towers boasts shopping at the Boulevard, various dining and nightlife options, and a convenient location just five minutes from Dubai Mall, accessible via the hotel&amp;rsquo;s complimentary shuttle service.
Reserve a room for three or more nights at participating Jumeirah hotels in Dubai with the Jumeirah City Break promotion and enjoy a 20% discount on the best available rates, along with:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to Henley &amp; Partners, APAC passports provide greater international travel opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:41:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</guid><description>The 2021 Henley Passport Index, which ranks global passports based on the number of destinations accessible without a prior visa, places Japan in first place when disregarding temporary restrictions. This is the third year in a row that Japan has achieved the top spot, independently or tied with Singapore. The index, which uses exclusive data from the International Air Transport Association (IATA), demonstrates the Asia Pacific (APAC) region&amp;rsquo;s dominance, a trend experts predict will continue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels establishes a high-end presence in the Maldives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</guid><description>AccorHotels is entering the Maldives market with its first luxury resort there, the Dhevanafushi Maldives Luxury Resort. Located on the private island of Meradhoo, the resort will undergo improvements in late 2018 and subsequently become part of the prestigious Raffles brand.
Currently, the resort offers 21 island villas and 16 ocean villas, all with private pools. Guests can enjoy three restaurants and a variety of amenities and activities for relaxation and rejuvenation, such as a luxurious spa, an overwater fitness center, yoga classes, watersports, and private dining options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The fourth akyra hotel in Sukhumvit, Bangkok has been launched by Akaryn</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</guid><description>Akaryn Hotel Group, a Thai hospitality company known for its luxurious hotels and resorts, will open its fourth akyra property, akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok, in December 2017.
The upscale boutique hotel is situated on Sukhumvit Soi 20, a vibrant area in the heart of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s main tourist zone, known for its excellent dining, lively nightlife, high-end shopping malls, spas, and green spaces.
akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok offers 50 rooms, ranging from 30 to 60 square meters, with city views...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir expands its route network to include Laos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, has started its first flights to Vientiane and Luang Prabang in Laos. This addition expands SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s network to 51 destinations across 14 countries.
The inaugural flight left Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport at 1:20 PM on October 31st and arrived at Vientiane’s Wattay International Airport at 3:15 PM. The same flight continued on to Luang Prabang International Airport at 4:05 PM, landing at 5:00 PM. The return flight from Luang Prabang departed at 5:50 PM and arrived back in Singapore at 10:05 PM (all times local)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gulf Air reveals its summer 2018 schedule</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air. Plane in Gulf Air livery.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has launched its Summer 2018 schedule, increasing both flight frequency and passenger capacity to popular destinations for the peak travel season between mid-June and mid-September 2018.
Flights to Amman, Jordan, will increase to three times daily, while flights to Beirut, Lebanon, will increase to twice daily. Istanbul, Turkey, a popular summer destination, will have 12 weekly flights during peak season, and flights to Baghdad, Iraq, will permanently increase to five times per week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its 200th property in Greater China, located in Chengdu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Fairmont Chengdu lobby.
The Fairmont Chengdu marks the 200th property for AccorHotels in Greater China and is the first Fairmont Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts establishment in Western China. This opening is a key part of AccorHotels’ expansion within the luxury market.
Situated on Tianfu Middle Avenue in Chengdu&amp;rsquo;s high-tech zone, the hotel provides 336 guest rooms and suites, each offering impressive views of the city skyline. Shuangliu International Airport is easily accessible at just a 25-minute drive away, and the nearby metro station provides convenient access to Tianfu Square, the forthcoming Tianfu International Airport, and the South CBD zone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has reopened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has finished renovating all guest rooms, bathrooms, and suites, offering visitors a revitalized stay in the heart of the city.
Source: Holiday Inn website. The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders.
Every room was completely emptied to give the architect a fresh start in designing a space with the modern traveler&amp;rsquo;s needs in mind. Striking new interiors are highlighted by floor-to-ceiling windows, equipped with electronically controlled blackout blinds that can be adjusted from the bedside...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens promotion is now available at the Grand Hyatt Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Hong Kong. Poster for the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens 2023.
To celebrate the return of the Cathay/HSBC Hong Kong Sevens from March 31st to April 2nd, 2023, Grand Hyatt Hong Kong, an official supplier and package provider, is offering special deals for a complete Sevens experience.
Exclusive packages combining accommodation and Sevens tickets are available starting from HK$3,900. Options include one- or three-night stays, paired with a choice of Friday, weekend, or three-day event tickets to suit every fan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cathay-hsbc-hong-kong-sevens-promotion-is-now-available-at-the-grand-hyatt-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new flights to Istanbul's Sabiha Gokcen Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</guid><description>Emirates now offers 18 flights to Istanbul every week, including a new daily service to Sabiha Gökçen Airport in addition to its existing flights to Istanbul Atatürk Airport. This makes Istanbul the third city after London and Tokyo to be served by Emirates from two airports. The new daily flight is operated with an Airbus A330-200, offering 12 First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 183 Economy Class seats, and also provides up to 12 tonnes of cargo capacity each way...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simplified travel policy implemented globally for consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-travel-policy-implemented-globally-for-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 09:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-travel-policy-implemented-globally-for-consolidation/</guid><description>Source: General Authority of
Civil Aviation, KSA. Global
policy, launched at the Future
Aviation Forum, will eliminate
difficulties in international
travel.
The General Authority of Civil Aviation (GACA) of Saudi Arabia has introduced the Harmonising Air Travel policy. This framework aims to simplify international travel and enhance the passenger experience by addressing the confusion surrounding varying travel requirements that currently discourage many from booking flights.
Developed collaboratively with the UN&amp;rsquo;s International Civil Aviation Organisation (ICAO), this proposed framework aims to create a single, accessible, and regularly updated online platform outlining entry requirements for all participating nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-travel-policy-implemented-globally-for-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-travel-policy-implemented-globally-for-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses becomes a part of the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</guid><description>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is among the first to sign the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative. This initiative, spearheaded by the UN Environment Programme and UN World Tourism Organization with the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, aims to tackle plastic waste in the tourism sector.
By signing the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative, Six Senses reinforces its commitment to eliminate, innovate, and circulate its plastic use by 2025, aiming to be plastic-free as early as 2022...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces WeChat SIM card for tourists from China visiting Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced two new prepaid SIM cards, named &amp;ldquo;StarHub WeChat Go SIM&amp;rdquo;, specifically designed for Chinese tourists visiting Singapore. This launch is a collaboration between StarHub and WeChat.
The StarHub WeChat Go SIM aims to meet the connectivity needs of the increasing number of Chinese tourists. Data from the Singapore Tourism Board shows a 36% rise in tourists from China in 2016 compared to the previous year. A 2017 Hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting from December 21, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM for Japan will be available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</guid><description>Source: Plus One Marketing.
Plus One Marketing, a Japanese company known for its FREETEL brand of mobile devices, is launching a prepaid data SIM card specifically for travelers in Japan. Starting December 21, 2015, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM will be available for purchase.
The SIM card is designed with tourists in mind, allowing unlimited access to popular social media platforms like Facebook, Kakao Talk, WeChat, LINE, and WhatsApp for seven days...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cathay Pacific has chosen Hertz as its sole car rental service provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</guid><description>Hertz Global is now the sole car rental provider for Cathay Pacific, an international airline based in Hong Kong. To streamline the rental process, Hertz created a dedicated website for Cathay Pacific travelers, offering a wide array of vehicles and deals at approximately 10,000 global locations. Furthermore, Cathay Pacific passengers will automatically receive a 5% discount on Hertz car rentals worldwide.
This agreement expands on the existing partnership between Hertz and Asia Miles, Cathay Pacific&amp;rsquo;s frequent flyer program...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad is providing selected transit passengers with a complimentary night's stay in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is offering a free overnight stay in Abu Dhabi to Economy Class travelers flying from specific locations, including Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Jordan, Kuwait, Bahrain, Oman, and Lebanon, whose journeys connect through the UAE&amp;rsquo;s capital.
This offer is valid for travel dates up to September 30, 2018, with bookings available from May 1 to September 15, 2018. Accommodation choices include the Radisson Blu on Yas Island and the Yas Island Rotana...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Le Meridien Seoul combines traditional Korean elements with French sophistication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 07:40:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</guid><description>Source: Le Meridien, Seoul website. Hub lobby.
The Le Meridien, Seoul, the first of its brand in Korea, introduces the renowned London-based David Collins Studio to the country. Conveniently located in the upscale Gangnam district, the hotel is a short walk from the Sinnonhyeon and Gangnam subway stations and easily accessible from both Gimpo (GMP) and Incheon (ICN) International Airports.
Tasked with designing the hotel&amp;rsquo;s public spaces and rooms, the studio has crafted a sophisticated blend of Parisian elegance with mid-century modern influences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>23 lessons I picked up during my Royal Caribbean voyage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 03:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</guid><description>Tips for Enjoying Your Royal Caribbean Cruise Here&amp;rsquo;s a view from the Viking Crown Lounge on Deck 14.
And here are some tips for your cruise:
Pack light on sunscreen, heavier on cleanser. Remember that everything onboard caters to US standards: food portions, electrical outlets, and currency. Your daily cruise newsletter is your best friend. Delivered to your room every afternoon, it highlights all activities and indicates which ones require payment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will enhance Singapore Airlines' offerings to Male</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</guid><description>Source: SilkAir. Male.
Starting October 25, 2015, SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will introduce four weekly flights to Male, Maldives. Previously, Singapore Airlines operated between 10 and 14 flights per week to Male. With the addition of SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s new flights, the two airlines will jointly offer two daily round trips, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, highlighted the benefits of this collaboration: “By coordinating the networks of both carriers, we can provide our customers with more choices and flexibility when planning their travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China have partnered on a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China, China&amp;rsquo;s national airline, have partnered to provide travelers with expanded options and easier connections. This agreement comes after Hawaiian launched its new non-stop service to Beijing, operating three times a week.
&amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to collaborate with Air China to expand our reach beyond Beijing, allowing our customers to conveniently explore more Chinese cities with a single ticket from Honolulu,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Dunkerley, Hawaiian Airlines President and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Adya Hotel Langkawi provides meeting rooms and a ballroom for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: Adya Hotel Langkawi website. Interior of a junior suite.
The four-star Adya Hotel Langkawi, situated in the Kuah town center on Langkawi Island in Malaysia, is marketed as a perfect starting point for exploring the natural wonders and rich culture of Langkawi, a designated UNESCO Global Geopark.
The hotel boasts 207 rooms and suites, each featuring a private bathroom with a bath and shower, along with a balcony that offers scenic views of the sea and town...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay offers a competitive advantage for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay website. The Grand Ballroom, theatre-style.
The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, a premier five-star resort in Phu Quoc and a flagship property in Vietnam, provides a range of meeting spaces suitable for various event sizes.
The resort is committed to crafting unforgettable events and immersive experiences for all attendees. Phu Quoc is an up-and-coming destination, now linked by direct flights to major cities like Ho Chi Minh City, Bangkok, and Guangzhou...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 will commence operations on January 1, 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</guid><description>Source: Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 website.
Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20, a lifestyle hotel focused on health and wellness, will softly open its doors on January 1, 2016. The hotel provides tailored food and drinks, spa treatments, fitness facilities, and wellness activities.
Conveniently situated on Sukhumvit 20, the hotel is a short walk from the BTS Asok Skytrain, MRT Sukhumvit Subway, Terminal 21 Mall, The EmQuartier, and the Emporium...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Sydney celebrates its first anniversary with joy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</guid><description>Source: Capella Sydney. To celebrate its one-year anniversary, Capella Sydney is providing a special deal with a A$365 credit applicable throughout the hotel and breakfast for two. The offer encompasses:
- Daily breakfast at Brasserie 1930
- Exclusive access to The Living Room, a shared area present in every Capella establishment. This space allows guests to participate in daily Capella customs and experience Sydney&amp;rsquo;s heritage through a curated display of local historical items and art...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury hotel to cater to Sydney airport guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</guid><description>Accor, the largest hotel operator in Australia, will be a part of a new multi-use development project in Mascot, near the Sydney Airport. The project will include a hotel, commercial space, and retail areas.
Accor signed an agreement with Goodman to oversee a 5-star hotel, named Pullman Sydney Airport, as part of a new A$100 million development. This project will also include office and retail space. Pullman, the biggest upscale hotel network in the Asia Pacific, has over 45 hotels in the area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>US airlines may now reject your standard carry-on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</guid><description>According to George Hobica from Airfarewatchdog, several US airlines have reduced the allowed size for carry-on luggage.
Traveling Hello Kitty statue at Taoyuan Airport,
Taiwan in 2008.
American, Delta, and United Airlines now permit carry-on bags with a maximum size of 22 inches in length, 14 inches in width, and 9 inches in height. The previous allowed width was 15 inches.
A Yahoo article from March highlighted United Airlines&amp;rsquo; stricter enforcement of carry-on size regulations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Airport consolidates early check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Travelers departing from Singapore have increased access to early check-in services for various airlines at Changi Airport. Since the beginning of the year, shared early check-in counters have been established in Terminals 2 and 3. Terminal 1 features a dedicated early check-in lounge for added convenience.
Operational from 6 am to midnight, the counters and lounge offer a centralized service point for passengers flying with 23 participating airlines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces the Dreamliner to Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has started using Boeing 787-9 Dreamliners for flights to Perth, Australia. These planes provide passengers with larger windows, improved air quality, spacious storage, and advanced technology for a more comfortable journey.
Flight EY486, the first Dreamliner flight, arrived in Perth on June 2nd and was greeted with a water cannon salute. This daily service replaces the Airbus A330-200, increasing capacity by 14%, with Business Class seating up by 27%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New sculptures have been added to the Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi Coralarium</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</guid><description>The Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi resort has added new sculptures to its Coralarium, an underwater art installation that doubles as the Maldives&amp;rsquo; first and only coral regeneration project. This structure, now teeming with marine life, serves as an artificial reef.
The abstract sculptures, conceived by environmentalist and eco-artist Jason deCaires Taylor, draw inspiration from the natural beauty of coral reefs and are designed to resemble coral colonies. These ten partially submerged plinths, reaching heights of up to 5 meters, aim to raise awareness about endangered ecosystems, educate visitors about marine life, and help rehabilitate the reef...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a new prepaid SIM card that also functions as a travel card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced the hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card, a first in Asia, which combines a prepaid SIM card with a stored value travel card usable for Singapore&amp;rsquo;s public transportation.
Source: Singtel. The hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card is the first in Asia to combine travel and phone services.
Priced at S$18, this SIM card provides 100 GB of 4G data, unlimited access to social media and messaging apps, and 1 GB of roaming data for select countries in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet has teamed up with Apex Air to provide private jet travel services in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</guid><description>VistaJet, a provider of luxury long-range private jet travel, announced that Apex Air, a business jet operator authorized by the Civil Aviation Administration of China (CAAC), will oversee and operate a fleet of aircraft based in China for VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s Flight Solution Program.
VistaJet is prepared to offer point-to-point service within China as early as the third quarter of 2015 with its first Chinese-registered aircraft, a Bombardier1 Challenger 8501. Chinese customers will also have access to VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s fleet of over 50 large-cabin, long-range Bombardier Challenger and Global aircraft for international flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, Etihad will assume control of Virgin's Sydney-Abu Dhabi slots</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</guid><description>Etihad Airways will increase flights between Abu Dhabi and Sydney to twice daily starting February 6, 2017. Flights EY450 departing Abu Dhabi in the morning and EY451 departing Sydney in the afternoon will now operate seven days a week.
This schedule change coincides with strategic partner Virgin Australia&amp;rsquo;s move to shift its Abu Dhabi operations from Sydney to Perth, effective June 9, 2017. Etihad Airways will expand its current codeshare agreement with Virgin Australia to include their new tri-weekly Perth-Abu Dhabi flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anantara's Al Baleed Resort Salalah introduces new wellness program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</guid><description>Source: Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara. The Balance Wellness by Anantara program includes custom-designed vegan cuisine.
The luxurious, private pool villa resort Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara has introduced a new wellness program with an a la carte approach.
Situated between a private beach and a freshwater lagoon in Salalah, Oman, Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara provides a serene setting for guests to focus on their wellness goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get 10% off and receive gifts with the HMH summer offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</guid><description>Hospitality Management Holdings (HMH) is offering a summer deal: guests can enjoy a 10% discount on bed and breakfast rates and receive a daily voucher redeemable at any of the hotel&amp;rsquo;s restaurants or spas. This promotion is valid until September 21, 2015.
Laurent Voivenel, CEO of HMH, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s presence in 15 cities across the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. He stated, &amp;ldquo;Due to significant demand from Saudi Arabia and other GCC countries, over 70% of our rooms have been booked in advance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor simplifies the process of capturing important moments during a trip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the biggest travel website globally as of July 2015 according to comScore Media Metrix, has introduced a &amp;ldquo;Travel Timeline&amp;rdquo; feature for its mobile app. This feature allows users to record and share their travel experiences. When turned on, it automatically generates a timeline of the places visited and photos taken at each location. This timeline can be viewed chronologically or as a route on a map.
Adam Medros, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s SVP of Global Product, highlights the feature&amp;rsquo;s value in documenting and sharing travel memories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Anantara Angkor Resort is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>Source: Anantara Angkor Resort website. View of the exterior.
The luxurious Anantara Angkor Resort has reopened in Siem Reap, offering an all-suite boutique experience close to the wonders of the ancient Khmer Empire.
Just a short drive from the city center, the 5-star resort provides easy access to vibrant markets, riverside attractions, and the charming French colonial quarter. The UNESCO World Heritage Site of Angkor Archaeological Park is also conveniently located a mere 10 minutes away...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Idealo has developed a flight price comparison portal for India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</guid><description>Source: idealo India website.
Idealo, a company specializing in price comparison, has expanded its services to India. With fourteen successful price comparison websites globally, idealo already helps numerous travelers find the best flight deals. The company proudly launched its fifteenth website, flights.idealo.in, in 2015.
Indian customers can now compare prices on thousands of flights from various online travel agencies and airlines, all without any cost. Idealo&amp;rsquo;s platform features offers from both budget-friendly and high-end airlines, encompassing one-way and round-trip journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen collaborate for a flash sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 01:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</guid><description>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen have teamed up to offer the Grand Spring Voyage flash sale, featuring accommodation packages ranging from two to five nights in both cities. This convenient travel opportunity is made possible by the newly extended MTR East Rail line, which directly connects the two hotels. The journey between the nearest stations, Exhibition Centre Station in Hong Kong and Lo Wu Station in Shenzhen, is a quick 40 minutes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad updates baggage policy and fare structure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
The national airline of the United Arab Emirates, Etihad Airways, is rolling out a new, clearer fare system starting September 14, 2015. This system aims to offer travelers more choices when booking their flights.
Eight new &amp;ldquo;Fare Choices&amp;rdquo; will be introduced, allowing travelers to customize their bookings to fit their needs. These transparent Fare Choices come with different baggage allowances, levels of flexibility, and included benefits that previously needed to be purchased separately...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the VIP treatment at Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</guid><description>Source: Hard Rock Hotels. Interior, Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen.
The Hard Rock Hotel brand has debuted its first establishment in China with the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen. This new property combines pop culture with high-end hospitality to create a luxurious experience for travelers seeking a unique experience.
Opening its doors in the summer of 2017, the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen is located within Mission Hills Centreville. Situated near a golf course, the hotel also provides convenient access to a variety of leisure, wellness, and entertainment options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Six Senses Bhutan experience will be available in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. A view of Bhutan.
Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has created a unique experience by linking five distinct resorts in five separate Bhutanese locations, collectively known as Six Senses Bhutan. Bhutan is notable for its isolation, remaining cut off from the outside world until the 1950s and only welcoming its first international visitors by special invitation in 1974.
With 82 guest suites and villas spread across the five intimate lodges, visitors can immerse themselves in the rich cultural heritage and hospitality of Thimphu, Punakha, Gangtey, Bumthang, and Paro, experiencing the &amp;ldquo;Happiest Place on Earth&amp;rdquo; firsthand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The book Soirees, Sojourns &amp; Stories details the most memorable moments of the Raffles narrative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</guid><description>Raffles Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, a leader in luxury hospitality known for its iconic properties, has released Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories.
Created in partnership with Rizzoli New York, the 200-page slipcased book, Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories by Natasha Fraser-Cavassoni, explores the development of Raffles&amp;rsquo; heritage of elegance and exceptional service around the world. It covers the period from the opening of its flagship hotel in Singapore in 1887 to the recent debut of Raffles Warsaw in Poland...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels Group plans to open Holiday Inn Osaka Namba by the end of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: IHG. The Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) and Japan Hotel Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) Investment Corporation (JHR) are collaborating on the Holiday Inn Osaka Namba, marking the REIT&amp;rsquo;s first venture with IHG. Scheduled to launch by the end of 2016, the hotel, presently known as Hotel Vista Grande Osaka, will be rebranded as Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
The 314-room hotel, joining the globally recognized Holiday Inn brand, will leverage IHG&amp;rsquo;s extensive global reservation systems, sales network, and the substantial IHG Rewards Club loyalty program, boasting almost 94 million members...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ignoring preferred payment methods could result in travel companies losing customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</guid><description>Around 85% of Chinese consumers take at least one leisure trip per year.
Credit cards (36%) and debit cards (29%) are the top payment choices for travel worldwide. PayPal is also popular (17%) across various countries and age groups.
Electronic payments are prevalent in China, with 78% favoring Alipay.
Seven out of ten Chinese travelers report experiencing fraud.
A recent global survey* of 7,400 consumers by YouGov and ACI Worldwide, a provider of electronic payment solutions, found that over a third (36%) of respondents from Britain, America, China, France, and Germany are dissatisfied with limited online payment choices for booking vacations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels &amp; Resorts presents an art installation in Singapore to commemorate its 200 properties worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</guid><description>Video of Hall with the bottles shaping the number &amp;lsquo;200&amp;rsquo;.
To mark the opening of their 200th hotel, InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts commissioned contemporary British artist Alexander Hall, known professionally as Haut de Gamme, to create a commemorative installation.
The artwork features 200 champagne bottles, each hand-painted by Hall in his signature drip technique. Inspired by the unique character of each InterContinental property, the individually designed bottles collectively form the number “200”...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new route connecting Dubai with Yinchuan and Zhengzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</guid><description>Emirates airline is increasing its commitment to China by starting a new service from Dubai to Yinchuan and Zhengzhou, two rapidly developing cities in Midwest China. This addition brings Emirates&amp;rsquo; total destinations in mainland China to five, including existing service to Beijing, Shanghai, and Guangzhou.
Source; Emirates. Emirates&amp;rsquo; Chairman and Chief Executive, HH Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, along with other company executives and a delegation of UAE business leaders, were on the inaugural flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Book with ONYX in February to receive exclusive discounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</guid><description>Source: Onyx web page. Several ONYX Hospitality Group properties are offering special deals for the Chinese New Year.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, guests can enjoy up to a 20% discount at the Oriental Residence Bangkok or at one of the 25 participating Amari, OZO, Shama, and Mosaic Collection hotels. These offers are available at locations in Thailand, Sri Lanka, mainland China, Hong Kong, Qatar, and Bangladesh...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates now offers a total of seven daily flights between Dubai and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Emirates will introduce a seventh daily flight between Dubai and Bangkok to accommodate rising passenger numbers. This will make Bangkok a top destination for Emirates, equal to Kuwait and Doha.
This new Boeing 777-300ER service will bring the total weekly flights to 49, increasing weekly seat capacity by 2,520 and cargo capacity by 134 tonnes each way. This addition complements the existing four daily A380 and two daily 777 flights, boosting travel and trade between Thailand and Emirates&amp;rsquo; global network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wanda Realm Taian is now officially open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</guid><description>Source: Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
The Wanda Realm Taian.
The Wanda Realm Taian (泰安万达嘉华酒店) marks its grand opening, becoming the 77th establishment under the Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts umbrella. This addition represents the 30th Wanda Realm hotel in China and the 41st property fully owned and operated by Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
This hotel is the fourth launched by Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts under their Wanda Realm brand in Shandong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Terhal by Bank Muscat provides financing for travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</guid><description>To celebrate the summer holidays (from Q2 to Q3) and the upcoming Eid al Fitr, Bank Muscat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Terhal,&amp;rdquo; a new set of travel services combined with banking features. This initiative reflects the bank&amp;rsquo;s motto, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s do more,&amp;rdquo; and aims to offer a unique banking experience for customers who enjoy traveling.
Terhal provides customers with access to financing up to RO10,000 at a 3.5% interest rate, repayable over a year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Complimentary stopovers offered to Etihad Economy Class passengers traveling from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is offering a complimentary one-night stay at the Radisson Blu hotel on Abu Dhabi’s Yas Island. This offer is open to Economy Class passengers flying from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan who have a layover in Abu Dhabi.
Mohammad Al Bulooki, Etihad Airways Executive VP Commercial, expressed the airline&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm for showcasing Abu Dhabi to its guests. He highlighted the diverse attractions of the UAE capital, ranging from cultural landmarks and beaches to sports and adventure activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is committed to connecting with Chinese tourists through investment efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotel Resorts Spas&amp;rsquo; Chinese website.
To expand its online footprint, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has launched a website in Chinese. The new website offers the same content and features as the brand&amp;rsquo;s English website. This move is anticipated to attract more customers from China, a key growth market for Six Senses.
In addition to the website, Six Senses is connecting with Chinese customers through brand engagement on social media platforms like WeChat, Youku, and Sina Weibo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor expands its footprint in regional Queensland with the addition of Mercure Rockhampton</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</guid><description>The Travelodge Hotel in Rockhampton has transitioned to the Mercure brand as part of a new franchise agreement with Accor. This addition expands Mercure&amp;rsquo;s presence to over 50 properties in Australia and New Zealand, and more than 810 globally.
Conveniently located in the city center and a short distance from the airport, the Mercure Rockhampton underwent renovations in 2008. The eight-story hotel boasts 74 rooms, views of the Fitzroy River, six conference rooms, an outdoor pool, a fitness center, a 24-hour reception, and convenient access to attractions like Great Keppel Island...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn in Bangkok is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Bangkok has reopened with a new focus on natural elements.
The traditional lobby is gone, replaced with an open space that blends the front desk, restaurant, bar, lounge, and business center in a modern style. This design approach extends to the 379 guest rooms, each envisioned as a home away from home.
Two new dining options are available: Ginger, offering all-day dining, and Beer Republic, a bar designed to evoke a 1920s European industrial warehouse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check out Rahlat.com for the best travel prices in Arabic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</guid><description>Source: Rahlat.com website. Screen capture of the home page.
Rahlat.com is an Arabic travel search website designed by Arabs, for Arabs. Its goal is to help travelers in the Middle East and Gulf region find the best prices on flights and hotels. This free, independent metasearch engine is available in both Arabic and English, making it easy for users to compare prices from numerous travel and airline websites with just one click...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-rahlat-com-for-the-best-travel-prices-in-arabic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Citizens of Thailand holding ordinary passports can travel to Taiwan without a visa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 07:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</guid><description>Holders of regular Thai passports can now travel without a visa to 26 countries, along with Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau. Beginning August 1st, Taiwan initiated a year-long trial program waiving visa requirements for Thai citizens with regular passports visiting for tourism purposes.
This program permits eligible travelers to stay in Taiwan for a maximum of 30 days. To qualify, Thai nationals must possess a valid regular passport with at least six months of validity remaining, hold a return or onward ticket to another destination, and meet Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s entry requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citizens-of-thailand-holding-ordinary-passports-can-travel-to-taiwan-without-a-visa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Mercure makes its first appearance in Myanmar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</guid><description>AccorHotels has launched its first Grand Mercure hotel in Myanmar. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire, with its 175 guest rooms and suites, provides a view of the Schwedagon Pagoda. Local artist Pyar Dade designed the accommodations.
Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire. Patrick Basset, COO of AccorHotels, Upper Southeast and Northeast Asia and the Maldives, stated, “This is our first Grand Mercure in Myanmar and the opening of Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire reflects the cultural touchstone of the destination and heritage in bringing local stories to life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FEH has announced a partnership with SIA's HighFlyer business travel program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</guid><description>Source: FEH. The Clan Hotel Singapore lobby.
Far East Hospitality (FEH) is the first hotel group to join Singapore Airlines’ (SIA&amp;rsquo;s) corporate travel program, HighFlyer. Companies in this program receive discounted airfares and earn HighFlyer points when their staff travel for business. These points can be redeemed for future travel, benefits for their business, or rewards for their traveling employees.
Members of HighFlyer can now accumulate up to 500 points when their employees stay at participating Far East Hospitality hotels in Singapore, Japan, and Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Shunde Marriott Hotel has officially opened its doors in Foshan, China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its presence in China with the opening of the 258-room Shunde Marriott Hotel. Located in Shunde, a district of Foshan in Guangdong Province, the hotel is owned by Shunde Midea Group and managed by Marriott under a long-term agreement. This latest addition brings the Marriott Hotels brand&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in Greater China to 19 properties.
Source: Marriott. The Shunde Marriott offers guests views of either Shunfeng Mountain Park or the city skyline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wyndham brand has entered the UAE market with its presence in Dubai Marina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</guid><description>Source: The First Group. The new Wyndham
Dubai Marina.
Wyndham Dubai Marina, the first hotel solely developed by leading Dubai-based property developer, The First Group, has officially opened. This launch signifies the Wyndham brand&amp;rsquo;s entrance into the UAE market.
This four-star deluxe Wyndham Dubai Marina, managed by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, the largest hotel management company globally, represents a significant achievement for The First Group. The developer has established a strong reputation for creating high-quality serviced apartments and &amp;ldquo;aparthotels&amp;rdquo; in Dubai...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Walk Japan provides distinctive viewpoints of Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/</guid><description>Source: Walk Japan. Viewing Mount Fuji on the Izu Geo Trail.
Walk Japan tours provide travelers with the chance to experience Japan&amp;rsquo;s diverse landscapes throughout the year on a more intimate level. This independent organization offers a fresh perspective on crafting and operating tours within Japan. The company&amp;rsquo;s deep knowledge and strong local connections, cultivated over many years, guarantee guests genuine experiences everywhere they travel.
Japan boasts an abundance of seasonal views...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JAL's Japan Explorer Pass simplifies travel in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</guid><description>Japan Airlines (JAL) now offers the Japan Explorer Pass, a convenient and affordable fare option for visitors from outside Japan, as well as Japanese citizens residing abroad, to explore various destinations within the country.
Travelers can easily purchase economy class tickets online, adhering to the following guidelines:
Domestic flights operated by JAL and JTA (Japan Transocean Air) can be booked up to 72 hours before the scheduled departure, even if the traveler is already in Japan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway will be celebrating their first birthday on March 31st</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Jen Orchardgateway website.
Hotel Jen, a new brand from the Shangri-La Group, is turning one year old on March 31, 2016. To mark this milestone, the two Singapore locations, Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway, are joining their sister hotels across nine Asian-Pacific cities for a grand birthday celebration. Each location will host unique events reflecting their city&amp;rsquo;s character, from a Mad Hatter&amp;rsquo;s tea party in Beijing to street art-inspired menus in Brisbane and a pool party in the Maldives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find joy through organizing your business travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</guid><description>Source: SAP Concur. View from a plane window.
SAP Concur draws parallels between decluttering and business travel, suggesting innovative ways to improve efficiency for travelers.
Andy Watson, SVP and GM for Asia Pacific Japan and Greater China at SAP Concur, believes that just as a messy home can be transformed into a joyful space, technology can turn the often-dreaded experience of business travel into something enjoyable.
Traditionally, business travelers face several time-consuming tasks: manually searching and booking flights and accommodations, organizing multiple bookings, obtaining internal trip approvals, managing paper receipts, and manually filing expense claims upon return...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-joy-through-organizing-your-business-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A trial for FAST check-in has been introduced by Changi Airport, Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</guid><description>A new Fast and Seamless Travel (FAST) check-in trial is currently underway at Changi Airport Terminal 2 for passengers flying with Singapore Airlines and SilkAir. This collaborative effort between Changi Airport Group (CAG), Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir will gradually introduce a comprehensive suite of FAST options throughout 2016. These options aim to provide passengers with more check-in choices and potentially faster processing times through automated kiosks and bag drops. Terminal 3 will also see the addition of 24 kiosks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vietjet's SkyBoss enhances the premium customer experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet.
Vietjet now offers SkyBoss, a premium travel class. SkyBoss passengers receive priority check-in, a 20kg checked baggage allowance, priority seat selection, airport lounge access, in-flight meals, extra legroom, and flexible flight date and time changes.
Established in 2011, Vietjet Air is Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s first privately held airline. Since its inception, Vietjet has served over 12 million passengers across 32 domestic and international routes. The airline currently operates two daily flights between Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi International Airport and Ho Chi Minh City&amp;rsquo;s Tan Son Nhat International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience Silom in a whole new way at the newly elevated ibis Styles Bangkok Silom</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</guid><description>Accor Hospitality Group has launched a stylish hotel, ibis Styles Bangkok Silom, in Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s lively Silom neighborhood. The hotel boasts a playful design inspired by Thai festivals and features a vibrant mural by Thai artist Tikkywow, reflecting Silom&amp;rsquo;s rich history.
Located near Sala Daeng BTS Skytrain and Silom MRT subway stations, the hotel provides convenient access to the city. Garth Simmons, CEO of Accor Southeast Asia, Japan &amp;amp; South Korea, expressed excitement for the opening, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s fit with Silom&amp;rsquo;s dynamic atmosphere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Airport introduces a new reward for the Be a Changi Millionaire campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 03:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. This year&amp;rsquo;s Be a Changi Millionaire competition offers a chance to win a Volvo sedan as well.
Changi Airport has enhanced its well-known *Be a Changi Millionaire*_ retail promotion this year by adding a new prize: a Volvo S90 T5 luxury sedan. This is in addition to the existing S$1 million cash prize. According to Changi Airport, this is the largest retail promotion at any airport globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The doors of Wanda Realm Fuyang are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts has expanded its portfolio with the opening of Wanda Realm Fuyang in the bustling business district of Fuyang, Anhui province, China. This addition marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 78th hotel, the 42nd under its ownership and management, and the 30th property under the Wanda Realm brand.
André Liu, General Manager of Wanda Realm Fuyang, highlighted the strategic importance of the location, stating, &amp;ldquo;Fuyang city is a rapidly developing hub with the largest population and fourth-largest size in Anhui province...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bahrain becomes a member of the Cruise Arabia Alliance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</guid><description>Bahrain has joined the Cruise Arabia Alliance, solidifying the organization&amp;rsquo;s presence in the region. Other members include Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Sharjah, Qatar, and Oman. The alliance promotes collaboration among its members to maintain high standards of service for cruise lines and their passengers.
This announcement took place at the Seatrade Middle East Cruise Forum in Doha, Qatar, hosted by the Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA). Alongside this news, Bahrain also shared that the 2015/2016 cruise season will include 68,000 passengers and 32 visits from major cruise lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ANA has developed an app to assist passengers in relaxing and diverting their attention away from takeoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</guid><description>Source: App Store.
All Nippon Airways (ANA), a major Japanese airline, developed an app to alleviate stress during the most anxiety-inducing part of air travel. Based on a survey of US airline passengers revealing that takeoff causes the most anxiety (68%), ANA created &amp;ldquo;ANA Takeoff Mode.&amp;rdquo; This mobile app aims to help travelers relax and focus on something other than takeoff.
The app presents a simple puzzle accompanied by calming music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British Airways assures that flying is safe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:14:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</guid><description>Source: British Airways. Doyle.
In his initial address after becoming British Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Sean Doyle stated that the airline believes flying poses a minimal health risk. He cited data from IATA suggesting only 44 COVID-19 cases have been linked to flights since early 2020, while 1.2 billion passengers traveled during that time.
During his speech at Airlines 2050: Beyond the Crisis, Doyle emphasized, &amp;ldquo;Ensuring the safety of our customers and crew remains our top priority, and we&amp;rsquo;re implementing all necessary safety protocols to protect them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FCM has landed in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcm-has-landed-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcm-has-landed-in-japan/</guid><description>FCM, a travel management company, has partnered with NSF Engagement in Japan. This investment will strengthen FCM’s presence in Asia, supporting current customers and expanding its global reach.
Several factors motivated FCM’s expansion in Japan, including a strong business travel market, increasing customer demand in Asia, and the opportunity to offer unique services.
The company recognized a need for comprehensive business travel solutions in Japan that are both reliable and user-friendly, based on feedback from FCM customers across various markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcm-has-landed-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcm-has-landed-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Urban Island promotion has been introduced by The Shilla Seoul</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</guid><description>With the arrival of summer, The Shilla Seoul presents Urban Island, a luxurious outdoor escape for guests. This all-inclusive retreat offers relaxation, a connection with nature, and delightful poolside service.
Reopened for the season, Urban Island welcomes guests to heated outdoor pools, a jacuzzi, and a rooftop garden against a scenic backdrop of Namsan Mountain and the Seoul skyline. Intimate cabanas nestled among lush greenery provide secluded havens.
The Urban Days room rate, available until June 30, 2019, starts from KRW 320,000 per night, excluding taxes and service charges, based on double occupancy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae will be available starting in March 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:23:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</guid><description>Source: BWH Hotels. A standard room at the Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, which boasts contemporary rooms with a full range of amenities.
Starting March 13, 2024, BWH Hotels (BWH), the international hospitality group that includes WorldHotels, Best Western Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, and SureStay Hotels, will introduce a newly renovated and rebranded hotel.
The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, formerly the Best Western Nagoya, was one of the city&amp;rsquo;s most well-liked international mid-scale hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three new routes have been announced by Air Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</guid><description>AirAsia is expanding its network in Indonesia and the Philippines with three new routes starting on March 27th. The airline will now offer flights from Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia to Pontianak, Indonesia, from Johor Bahru, Malaysia to Medan, Indonesia, and from Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia to Cebu, Philippines.
The Indonesian routes will operate twice a week, while the Kota Kinabalu to Cebu route, operated by AirAsia Zest, will operate four times a week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online travel insurance offer now available from AIG Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</guid><description>AIG Singapore has introduced a new digital travel insurance product, Travel Guard Direct, designed to improve customer experience from purchase to claim. This innovative product uses data to provide travelers with valuable insights about their destinations.
Travel Guard Direct is the first of its kind in Singapore, offering real-time claims information for popular destinations in Asia Pacific, the US, and the UK. This allows customers to make more informed decisions about their coverage by understanding the risks associated with their travel destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-travel-insurance-offer-now-available-from-aig-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Club Carlson celebrates reaching one million members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s international hotel rewards program, Club Carlson, celebrated a milestone by awarding its one millionth member in the Asia Pacific region with one million Club Carlson Gold Points.
The lucky recipient, Rong Weiji, is a Sales and Marketing Division Manager at Santen Pharmaceutical. He became the millionth member upon checking in at the Radisson Blu Shanghai New World on August 22, 2014.
When asked about his hotel preferences, Mr. Weiji explained that he values brand recognition, quality, service, and location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exchange your remaining loose change for digital currency at airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</guid><description>Source: TravelersBox. A kiosk at Singapore Changi Airport (airside).
Travelers passing through Singapore Changi Airport can now utilize their leftover foreign currency or remaining Singapore dollars more effectively. This is made possible by the new TravelersBox kiosks situated within the airport.
TravelersBox, a financial technology company, assists travelers in converting their remaining foreign currency, both bills and coins, into digital money. This digital money can be redeemed online with well-known brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travel to Banwa Private Island with Ascent Flights Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</guid><description>Banwa Private Island, a secluded island in Northeast Palawan known for its pristine beaches, has joined forces with Ascent Flights Global to provide exclusive and secure travel options for its guests. This collaboration aims to create a protected travel environment through personalized on-demand flights using seaplanes, helicopters, or private jets based on individual preferences.
Source: Banwa Private Island. Banwa Private Island has partnered Ascent Flights Global to offer guests safe, private transport to their accommodation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shangri-La and Singapore Airlines campaign offers packaged deals for ASEAN destinations and hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</guid><description>To commemorate the 50th anniversary of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts and Singapore Airlines have teamed up to launch a travel campaign called &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore.&amp;rdquo;
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjJuZK2IwJjPxRmvmq0DT-MS7ZPDl5douabN-yaRNI7kSFX1RAg5n8m2LHrg030pnJcr68_qz-IujmANOlf3NTbWGRF887wfkPbFQPAn168XsbqGeH8wP90CW2_M3muXU8ABKS6E9PwtOA/s1600/Shangri+La+SIA+ASEAN+is+More.JPG)
Source: Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts. Banner for the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore&amp;rdquo; campaign.
This campaign highlights Southeast Asia as a travel destination through special offers on curated leisure trips. Flight and hotel packages are available for various properties in Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Myanmar, and Thailand, including Shangri-La hotels and resorts, Hotel Jen properties, and Traders Hotel, Kuala Lumpur...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wego collaborates with the Saudi Tourism Authority to boost tourism interest in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Wego, a leading online travel platform in the Middle East and North Africa, has partnered with the Saudi Tourism Authority to promote tourism in Saudi Arabia.
The collaboration will focus on attracting travelers from the region to destinations like Riyadh and Jeddah, showcasing Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s diverse landscapes, including deserts, mountains, and coastlines. Wego has observed significant interest in travel to Saudi Arabia, with a surge in flight and hotel bookings since travel restrictions were lifted...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International SOS advises business travelers to be mindful of the risk of malaria</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-advises-business-travelers-to-be-mindful-of-the-risk-of-malaria/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-advises-business-travelers-to-be-mindful-of-the-risk-of-malaria/</guid><description>Source: International SOS. Fogging of an area likely to harbor malaria-carrying mosquitoes.
In recognition of World Malaria Day 2023 (April 25), International SOS urged organizations to actively participate in the global push for investment, innovation, and implementation to eliminate malaria.
Malaria remains a threat in over 80 countries, leading to more than 240 million infections annually, and this number is increasing, according to International SOS. The World Health Organization reports a surge of 2 million malaria cases globally in 2021 compared to 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-advises-business-travelers-to-be-mindful-of-the-risk-of-malaria/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-advises-business-travelers-to-be-mindful-of-the-risk-of-malaria/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring new destinations in 2021: Bawah Reserve and Cedar Lodge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</guid><description>Several properties, such as Bawah Reserve in Indonesia and Cedar Lodge in New Zealand, are getting ready for the return of travel.
Bawah Reserve
Source: Bawah Reserve website. Lodges at Bawah Reserve.
Located in Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s remote Anambas Islands, Bawah Reserve encompasses six tropical islands, thirteen white sand beaches, and three lagoons. The Anambas Islands are reachable by private seaplane from Bintan Island, Indonesia.
Along with its existing 36 lodges, Bawah will debut six new cliffside lodges on Elang, a previously undeveloped island, this year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers from Singapore have a strong affinity for Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</guid><description>Source: KAYAK. Tokyo skyline.
The travel search platform, KAYAK, has identified the top five destinations Singaporeans are traveling to for the Chinese New Year (CNY) holiday. The Year of the Rooster begins with a long weekend that starts on Saturday, January 28th, and ends on Monday, January 30th, 2017.
The most popular travel destination for Singaporeans between January 28th and February 5th is Bangkok, Thailand. Tokyo, Japan, and Manila in the Philippines are the second and third most popular destinations, respectively:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-from-singapore-have-a-strong-affinity-for-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2020, Canopy Power is making Southeast Asia more environmentally friendly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</guid><description>Source: Canopy Power. This image shows solar panels installed on the roof of a beachfront pavilion at Batu Batu resort. This installation was part of a larger project by Canopy Power.
Despite the economic downturn of 2020, Canopy Power has announced several accomplishments within the Asia Pacific region.
One such accomplishment was the completion of a renewable energy microgrid in the third quarter of 2020. This microgrid, located on Batu Batu, a sustainable island resort 16 km from Mersing, Malaysia, will allow the 22-villa resort to decrease its reliance on diesel and lower carbon emissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport reveals its fresh new appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has finished renovations, adding new rooms, a new Italian restaurant called Allora, another function room, an updated Club Lounge, and a revitalized fitness center.
The new design creates a calming oceanic atmosphere. Natural wood finishes on the furniture bring a feeling of warmth and comfort. This is enhanced by a color scheme of beach tones and ocean shades. Light gray couches, navy blue, and yellow accents contribute to a modern and welcoming feel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotels.com provides exclusive information on transportation options to and from the airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</guid><description>Hotels.com, a website for booking accommodations online, has put together an insider&amp;rsquo;s guide on the top transportation choices from 29 major airports globally. This guide, called the Hotels.com Airport Transportation Insider, compares taxis, private cars, and public transportation in popular international and domestic destinations using data from the recent Hotel Price Index™. Although it&amp;rsquo;s geared towards US travelers, the infographic provides helpful information for cities like Bangkok, Beijing, Singapore, and Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China and Kunming Airlines have initiated a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Source: Air China. The image shows representatives from Air China and Kunming Airlines at a signing ceremony for a codeshare agreement on September 3.
Air China and Kunming Airlines launched a codeshare partnership on September 15, 2014.
This agreement allows the airlines to link their respective networks through the city of Kunming. Air China will place its &amp;ldquo;CA&amp;rdquo; code on 26 Kunming Airlines routes, encompassing nearly 500 weekly flights. This expands Air China&amp;rsquo;s reach to various cities within Yunnan province and its neighboring areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience sustainable dining at Avani properties in Indochina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</guid><description>Image Credit: Avani. Plant-based coconut acai bowls are available at the Avani+ Samui Resort.
To create a healthier planet and promote sustainability, Avani Hotels has introduced a variety of eco-friendly and wellness-focused programs.
Avani&amp;rsquo;s flagship hotels in Thailand, Cambodia, and Laos are increasing their efforts to support nearby communities. They are accomplishing this by showcasing regional specialties and advocating for a decrease in reliance on imported goods. They have also implemented zero-waste programs, which include composting systems to handle all organic waste and on-site organic gardens to encourage self-sufficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces new flights between Penang and Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</guid><description>AirAsia has launched direct flights connecting Penang to Yangon, Myanmar, making it the airline&amp;rsquo;s seventh international destination accessible from its northern hub. Penang also offers direct flights to other international destinations, such as Ho Chi Minh City, Singapore, Medan, Jakarta, Surabaya, and Bangkok.
This new route will operate three times a week, starting on March 22, 2016. The flight schedule for Penang, Malaysia (PEN) – Yangon, Myanmar (RGN) is as follows:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Drone Experience Program by JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp; Resorts is launching in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. View from a DJI drone.
JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and drone manufacturer DJI have partnered to introduce the brand&amp;rsquo;s first Drone Experience Program.
This program will allow guests to try out DJI&amp;rsquo;s drone technology and experience JW Marriott properties from a fresh perspective. They can also capture and share these unique moments with loved ones.
Launching on November 12, 2016, at JW Marriott Zhejiang Anji, the program will feature on-site sessions hosted by DJI experts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can have a Claire Luxton experience in Dubai this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. Visitors can enjoy a unique experience showcasing the work of artist Claire Luxton at select hotels, such as the InterContinental Dubai Festival City.
InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, part of IHG Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts Luxury and Lifestyle Collection, has partnered with British artist Claire Luxton to launch a series of immersive guest experiences. Available at various hotels, including the InterContinental Dubai Festival City, until mid-July, these experiences celebrate global travel and exploration through the artistic vision of Claire Luxton...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the new Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. This hotel, the Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel, aims to create a beach resort atmosphere.
The recently opened Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel is a 72-room boutique hotel located in the city center. Its convenient location provides guests with easy walking access to shopping, dining, and entertainment. Designed around a nautical theme, the hotel offers 60 Deluxe rooms, eight Baraquda Suites, and four Baraquda Grand Suites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir have reduced their fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir, its regional subsidiary, have reduced their fuel surcharges due to decreasing fuel prices.
These new surcharge amounts apply to flights from both airlines and range from US$5 to US$83 lower per one-way trip, depending on the flight distance and class of travel.
Route Surcharge in US$* First Class, Suites Between Singapore and South East Asian gateways[1] 50 Between Singapore and Europe/South Africa[2] 175 Between Singapore and Americas 235 Between Europe and Australia/New Zealand[3] 265 All other flights[4] 131 * Figures in US Dollars, converted into currency of sale at time of ticketing..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong is the inaugural Hyatt Place in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Hyatt and Boutique Corporation have announced the launch of the Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong in Phuket, Thailand. This 161-room beachfront property is the first Hyatt Place hotel in Southeast Asia. It embodies the Hyatt Place brand&amp;rsquo;s relaxed style and offers convenient amenities like complimentary Wi-Fi and 24/7 dining options.
&amp;ldquo;Thailand remains a crucial market for Hyatt, and Phuket is a top tourist spot in Southeast Asia with rising demand from both leisure and business travelers,&amp;rdquo; said David Udell, Group President – Asia Pacific, Hyatt Hotels Corporation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etiqa has introduced the first-ever complimentary inflight insurance for travelers from Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</guid><description>The first complimentary in-flight insurance plan in Singapore offers up to S$50,000 in personal accident coverage.
For an added S$4, travelers can purchase coverage for flights delayed by three hours or more.
Claims can be paid out instantly through PayNow.
Etiqa, an online insurance provider based in Singapore, has introduced the nation&amp;rsquo;s first complimentary in-flight insurance for travelers. The company also launched a flight delay add-on for S$4, enabling travelers to receive compensation for flights delayed by three consecutive hours, which is a lower threshold compared to the industry average of six to twelve hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover Emirates aircraft in 3D</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates pioneers VR experience on its website.
Emirates has become the first airline to use web-based virtual reality (VR) technology. They&amp;rsquo;ve added 3D seat models to emirates.com.
This 3D model shows a 360-degree view of the inside of their A380 and Boeing 777 aircraft. It allows customers to view the Economy, Business, and First Class cabins, as well as the onboard lounge and shower spa on the A380...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Post Paid Calling Card Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-post-paid-calling-card-advantage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 15:20:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-post-paid-calling-card-advantage/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are commonplace, but a more convenient and cost-effective option exists: postpaid calling cards. Unlike prepaid cards that require upfront payment for a set number of minutes, postpaid cards operate on a pay-as-you-go model.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare them using FourVoice as an example. With prepaid cards, you pay for minutes upfront, often at varying rates depending on the destination. These rates don&amp;rsquo;t include additional service, connection, and minimum call fees, which reduce your actual talk time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-post-paid-calling-card-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-post-paid-calling-card-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's top business travel destinations are Tokyo and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</guid><description>A recent Samsonite survey explored the preferences of Singaporean business travelers, revealing Tokyo and Bangkok as the top choices for both business and leisure.
The survey, conducted by YouGov, involved over 500 Singaporean respondents who travel for business frequently. It found that Tokyo was the top business destination overall, particularly favored by those aged 35 to 44. Bangkok was the preferred choice for those over 45. Among younger travelers (under 34), Tokyo and London tied for the top spot...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Four Seasons Private Jet offers a luxurious flying experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</guid><description>Source: Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts.
Luxury hospitality company Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts has launched the Four Seasons Private Jet, signifying a major shift in luxury travel. This offering highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding the evolving desires of modern luxury travelers.
Every aspect of the private jet journey, both in flight and on the ground, has been redesigned through the Four Seasons perspective to provide a fully immersive experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates provides appealing packages for stopovers in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s skyline, featuring the Burj Khalifa on the right.
Travelers flying with Emirates can benefit from appealing Dubai packages. These packages offer special prices at top-rated hotels and include access to entertainment options like city shows and attractions*.
Starting from US$49 per night, based on double occupancy, visitors can experience Dubai at the Rove Dubai Marina, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s vibrant waterfront area. This package also includes two tickets to Dubai Parks and Resorts, the region&amp;rsquo;s most extensive integrated theme park destination, encompassing MOTIONGATE Dubai, BOLLYWOOD PARKS Dubai, LEGOLAND Dubai, and LEGOLAND Water Park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad provides a wider range of choices for Mediterranean travel destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is increasing the number and capacity of flights to Athens, Greece, and Larnaca, Cyprus.
Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, stated that the new flights to Athens will offer travelers two different departure times to and from Abu Dhabi. The additional flights to Larnaca will provide more options and flexibility, as well as enhanced connectivity through Abu Dhabi.
He added that these additions will support business and leisure travel growth through Abu Dhabi and offer travelers a wider choice of destinations in the Gulf region, Indian Subcontinent, Asia, and Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air France enhances first class experience with new La Première cabins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/</guid><description>Air France launched its new La Première cabin on January 12th, debuting on flight AF254 traveling from Paris-Charles de Gaulle to Singapore and Jakarta. This move emphasizes the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing top-tier products and services to its Southeast Asian clientele. Starting in February 2015 and continuing through the winter season, these new cabins will be offered on all daily flights to Singapore and Jakarta.
Source: Air France website.
Frédéric Gagey, Air France&amp;rsquo;s Chairman and CEO, stated: &amp;ldquo;Our objective with the new La Première suites is to offer the absolute best in the market, and that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re showcasing today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers now prioritize sustainable travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 20:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</guid><description>Trip.com Group, a leading travel service company, recently published its first-ever Sustainable Travel Consumer Report to coincide with World Tourism Day. The report highlights the growing popularity of sustainable travel and its significant effects on the travel industry and the world at large.
Sustainable travel is increasingly becoming a top priority for travelers worldwide, with over 68% in Singapore and 90% in Thailand recognizing its importance.
Source: Trip.com. Despite regional variations, there is a clear upward trend of individuals adopting sustainable travel habits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-now-prioritize-sustainable-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to GfK, Singaporean travelers frequently plan their trips with less than a month's notice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</guid><description>A Jetstar aircraft at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Companies can potentially reduce travel expenses by adopting strategies used by individual travelers. A study by GfK revealed that roughly 76% of trips originating in Singapore were booked no more than one month before the travel date.
Laurens van den Oever, Global Travel Director at GfK, suggests that this trend of booking close to the travel date is likely due to airlines offering discounted fares for last-minute flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian destinations emerge victorious in the inaugural KAYAK Travel Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 10:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</guid><description>Source: KAYAK. Winners from the first-ever KAYAK Travel Awards.
The travel search engine KAYAK has revealed the winners of its first KAYAK Travel Awards. Sixteen categories, including airlines, airports, hotels, and destinations, were awarded based on public votes collected over 19 days from June 12th to June 30th, 2018.
Singaporean brands dominated the awards. Singapore Airlines received top honors in four categories: Favourite Airline (Short-haul), Favourite Airline (Long-haul), Favourite Airline Crew, and Favourite In-flight F&amp;amp;B...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Novotel hotel has opened in Cambodia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</guid><description>Source: Novotel Hotels, Suites &amp;amp; Resorts. The Novotel Phnom Penh BKK 1.
Accor brand, Novotel Hotels, Suites &amp;amp; Resorts, has opened its newest location, the Novotel Phnom Penh BKK 1, in Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
This brand-new hotel features a contemporary design, a welcoming social space, and diverse dining and wellness options. Its strategic location provides easy access to the bustling Bassac Lane and Langka Lane neighborhoods, as well as landmarks such as the Independence Monument and Wat Langka, one of the city&amp;rsquo;s oldest pagodas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hilton Singapore Orchard introduces the Smart Oasis meeting space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 22:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</guid><description>Hilton Singapore Orchard Unveils &amp;lsquo;Smart Oasis&amp;rsquo; Meeting Space
Hilton Singapore Orchard is excited to announce the opening of Smart Oasis, a new meeting space located on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fifth floor. The space features seven function rooms, two breakout areas, and incorporates advanced technology with natural elements inspired by the area&amp;rsquo;s plantation history.
Cedric Nubul, General Manager of Hilton Singapore Orchard, emphasized the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing cutting-edge meeting facilities. He believes Smart Oasis will become a leading venue in Asia, promoting sustainable and impactful event experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces a mobile site in Arabic language</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced an Arabic version of its mobile website. This platform allows customers to book flights, check in online, upgrade their travel class, and access and download Apple Passbook boarding passes directly to their smartphones, regardless of the language they use on the Emirates mobile site.
The Arabic mobile platform has been launched concurrently in 15 countries across the Middle East and North Africa, including the UAE, Bahrain, Iraq, Jordan, Kuwait, Lebanon, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Morocco, and Sudan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Journeyful has revamped its website, incorporating additional listings and enhancing rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</guid><description>Source: Journeyful. The Journeyful 2.0 website.
Journeyful, a company located in Singapore, has relaunched an updated website for its rewards-based online travel agency, Journeyful.com. The new and improved &amp;ldquo;Journeyful 2.0&amp;rdquo; website features a selection of over 200,000 hotels globally, a price-match guarantee, and Facebook integration.
The redesigned website includes Journeyful MICE, which offers comprehensive solutions for business conferences, corporate events, and incentive trips. A Journeyful representative explained that once an online inquiry is submitted, MICE consultants collaborate offline with the organization to personalize solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>