<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>City on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/city/</link><description>Recent content in City on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/city/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dubai Chamber has announced the launch of the Dubai Smartpreneur Competition for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, working with the Smart Dubai Office, launched the second annual Dubai Smartpreneur Competition. This aligns with the vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, to make Dubai a leading smart city.
Source: Dubai Chamber. The event featured a panel discussion about the UAE government&amp;rsquo;s progress on smart city and innovation initiatives, and what will drive future sustainable growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GuocoLand will be responsible for overseeing the management of both Sofitel Singapore City Centre and Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Tanjong Pagar
Centre.
GuocoLand will oversee the operation of two new AccorHotels establishments: the Sofitel Singapore City Centre at Tanjong Pagar Centre in Singapore and the Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara in Damansara City, Kuala Lumpur. These additions contribute a total of 534 rooms to AccorHotel’s luxury brand.
Raymond Choong, President and CEO of GuocoLand Group, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership with AccorHotels, highlighting the shared vision for creating modern, convenient spaces within bustling business districts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guocoland-will-be-responsible-for-overseeing-the-management-of-both-sofitel-singapore-city-centre-and-sofitel-kuala-lumpur-damansara/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Leong Group has decided to establish its global headquarters at Damansara City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</guid><description>Source: Damansara City website.
GuocoLand Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s key project, Damansara City, will soon house the Hong Leong Group&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters. The 33-story, top-tier office building, situated on the southwest side of this notable development, will be a major tenant within Damansara City when fully occupied by the second quarter of next year.
The Hong Leong Group is a prominent Malaysian conglomerate with interests in banking, financial services, manufacturing, distribution, property development, investment, hospitality, leisure, and principal investment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China has a strong presence in the new City Momentum Index by Jones Lang LaSalle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 05:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</guid><description>Five cities in Asia Pacific and the Middle East — Dubai, Wuhan, Shanghai, Hong Kong and Singapore — are among the top 10 in Jones Lang LaSalle&amp;rsquo;s new City Momentum Index (CMI). This index identifies cities worldwide with significant short-term socio-economic and commercial real estate momentum, as well as strong long-term growth potential.
Jeremy Kelly, Director of Global Research at Jones Lang LaSalle, explains that city momentum is not solely determined by GDP growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore ranked among the top five in the 2016 WE Cities Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</guid><description>Dell has identified the top 25 cities worldwide that cultivate high-potential women entrepreneurs (HPWE) for 2016 through their Women Entrepreneur Cities Index (WE Cities). This unique index assesses a city&amp;rsquo;s capacity to attract and promote the growth of women-led businesses. The study focused on cities rather than countries to highlight how local policies and initiatives impact women entrepreneurs, in addition to national legislation and norms.
The WE Cities findings will serve as a starting point for discussions at the seventh annual Dell Women’s Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sydney's Christmas programme has been officially launched by the City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</guid><description>Source: City of Sydney. Lord Mayor Clover Moore launched the Sydney Christmas program at Martin Place.
Sydney has officially begun its Christmas celebrations, featuring an array of decorations, carols, light displays, concerts, Christmas trees, and special retail events.
Lord Mayor Clover Moore expressed her enthusiasm for the festivities, stating, &amp;ldquo;Each year, we warmly welcome thousands of people from all over Sydney to the city center for our Christmas celebrations. With live concerts, vibrant light projections, excellent shopping opportunities, and the chance for kids to meet Santa, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone - visitors, shoppers, and locals alike...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangkok is the top tourist destination in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Mastercard. Report cover.
Although Bangkok, Thailand remains the top spot for visitors in the Asia Pacific, the latest Mastercard Asia Pacific Destinations Index 2017* shows that Singapore outpaces the Thai capital in total tourist spending.
Singapore experienced an 18% increase in visitor spending between 2015 and 2016. As one of just five destinations in the top 20 for overall expenditure to hit a minimum daily spend of US$200, Singapore drew in the biggest spenders at US$254 per day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangkok-is-the-top-tourist-destination-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is the third best city in APEC for living and conducting business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</guid><description>A new study presented at the APEC 2015 CEO Summit has positioned Singapore as the third most desirable city for living and conducting business within the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) region.
Conducted by PwC, the &amp;ldquo;Building Better Cities&amp;rdquo; study aims to provide city leaders with insights into their current standings and to encourage collaboration and knowledge sharing among APEC cities to tackle persistent challenges.
The study examines the role urban centers play in APEC&amp;rsquo;s economic and social progress, emphasizing their growing global influence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Wuhan and Changsha were recognized as the top sustainable cities in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</guid><description>The 2015 China Sustainable Cities Report: Measuring Ecological and Human Development reveals that 35 Chinese cities have shown progress in their sustainability performance since 2014, as indicated by their scores on the Urban Ecological Input Index (EUII). This report, which assesses the progress of Chinese cities towards sustainable development, was presented in Beijing at the 2015 International Forum on Sustainable Cities in China.
A collaboration between the United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Xinhua Oriental Outlook Weekly, and a team of experts from Tongji University, this report marks the first of its kind in China since the UN&amp;rsquo;s 193 member states adopted the 17 Sustainable Development Goals in September 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>