<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DS3 Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ds3-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in DS3 Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ds3-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>Ethernet WAN is the most significant advancement in business broadband since T1 service prices dropped. What exactly is Ethernet WAN, and why should you care?
Ethernet has become the dominant standard for Local Area Networks (LANs). You could say that Ethernet is everywhere. An RJ45 Ethernet jack is standard on every desktop and laptop computer. You might not get a CD-ROM drive, probably won&amp;rsquo;t get a floppy disc drive, and may never use the phone modem jack again...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet DS3 Bandwidth Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has grown continuously since T1 lines became the norm for dedicated internet access and private point-to-point connections. If you currently use DS3 bandwidth services or are thinking about an upgrade, comparing your wide area network (WAN) bandwidth choices is essential.
DS3, a 45 Mbps service, represents the traditional high-bandwidth network connection and is equivalent in speed to a T3 line. These days, most DS3 services are delivered via fiber optic cables, with a copper handoff point at the demarcation point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps to 6 Mbps Bonded Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</guid><description>Reliable and fast business internet access is crucial for customer interaction and order processing. While you aim for a stable connection with sufficient bandwidth, you also need a budget-friendly option. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to incrementally boost your internet speed in line with your business requirements.
](http://www.T1Rex.com/)
Dedicated internet access used to be limited to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line or a 45 Mbps T3 line (DS3 bandwidth). Shared bandwidth services offer more choices, but their performance and availability can fluctuate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Covad Lets T1 Lines Go Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 03:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</guid><description>While T1 lines are currently the standard for dedicated internet and business phone service for small and medium businesses, their future might be wireless. Similar to how wireless technology changed phone service, it is now impacting broadband data delivery.
Covad, a national provider of T1 and related services, is at the forefront of this change. While they offer traditional wired T1 service in most areas, they&amp;rsquo;ve deployed &amp;ldquo;T1-class wireless broadband&amp;rdquo; in some major cities using pre-WiMAX technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-lets-t1-lines-go-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MAN and MEN - Metropolitan Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are the solution for expanding local networks across different locations within a city. Unlike confined on-site wiring, MANs tackle the challenge of connecting across larger distances.
Traditionally, businesses leased dedicated lines like T1 or DS3 from telecom companies to link their offices. However, this method proved costly and demanded self-management. MANs offer a practical alternative by providing shared fiber optic infrastructure, leading to cost savings and scalability for businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul is Backing Things Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</guid><description>While it may seem like the world operates solely on wireless connections, especially if you rely on cell phones and mobile internet, this is only true for the link between your device and the nearest cell tower or access point. Beyond that point lies the backhaul, a crucial but often overlooked component that bridges the wireless and wired worlds. As wireless connections become faster, the limitations of traditional backhaul solutions are becoming increasingly apparent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Dedicated T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 20:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</guid><description>Although a traditional service, point-to-point dedicated T1 lines remain popular. This article examines their functionality and applications.
](http://www.t1t3today.com/) Initially designed for internal use, telephone companies used T1 lines to combine 24 individual analog phone lines into a single digital connection. Their key characteristics included serial digital transmission via a maximum of two twisted pair wires, regeneration to extend transmission distance, fixed private connections between two points, a multiplexing method to separate concurrent calls, and a 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of Bandwidth for Wide Area Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 23:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) connect your business to the outside world, encompassing private networks across various locations. These connections, often called &amp;ldquo;long haul circuits&amp;rdquo;, form the foundation of wide area networking.
Connecting your local area network (LAN) to a WAN usually involves a router and a specialized interface corresponding to the WAN circuit type.
A common WAN connection is a T1 line, terminating at a &amp;ldquo;smart jack&amp;rdquo; in your telecom closet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding An Ethernet Internet Provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</guid><description>Looking for a better alternative to traditional internet services like T1 lines? Ethernet Internet might be the answer. But finding the right provider can be tricky. That’s where the Ethernet Internet Finder comes in.
This free tool, powered by Telarus, a leading telecom brokerage firm, helps businesses easily find and compare Ethernet Internet providers. Just enter your basic business contact information, preferably your main business phone number, and let the system do the rest...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Access Wireless Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</guid><description>Wireless internet isn&amp;rsquo;t just for mobile devices. Businesses can also benefit from fixed wireless services.
One affordable option utilizes existing cell towers to provide broadband similar to a T1 line at nearly half the cost. Accel Networks, for instance, partners with major carriers to leverage their bandwidth, achieving 99.9% reliability and quick installation times. This solution is ideal for businesses requiring PCI-compliant connections, like convenience stores or gas stations, especially those in areas with limited wired options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines, a technology dating back to the telegraph, have evolved to offer businesses speeds ranging from 1.5 Mbps to 100 Gbps. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the characteristics of leased lines and how they stand apart from conventional broadband.
What is a Leased Line?
Similar to leasing a property, leased lines involve an agreement and regular payments that grant you exclusive access to a dedicated communication line.
In its simplest form, a leased line consists of a pair of copper wires, linking your location to your provider, often through a local telephone company (ILEC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Bandwidth Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</guid><description>DS3 WAN connections are a popular choice for businesses that need more bandwidth than T1 lines offer but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for a full OC-3 fiber optic SONET service. However, exploring alternative options might be beneficial due to cost or performance considerations.
There are several bandwidth options available today that might be a better fit than your existing DS3 connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some alternatives.
DS3 bridges the gap between copper wireline and fiber optic bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Point to Point Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Secure and transparent data transfer is crucial. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some popular methods to achieve this.
What Are Dedicated Private Lines?
Imagine a dedicated private line as a secure connection between two points facilitated by a carrier. It&amp;rsquo;s like having your own wiring, but provided by a third party, spanning across cities or even globally.
T1 Dedicated Lines
T1 lines are the digital version of old-school &amp;ldquo;dry loops&amp;rdquo; used by radio stations and alarm systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Center Services For You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</guid><description>Smaller companies often admire the data centers of larger organizations, but they may not realize that similar services are within their reach.
The key is to only own assets crucial to your business and lease the rest, including data center services. You don&amp;rsquo;t need a massive, secure facility with 24/7 staff, backup generators, and unlimited bandwidth. These services are available on a pay-as-you-go basis.
Two types of data centers are eager to accommodate your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will Ethernet Crush DS3?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</guid><description>Companies needing more bandwidth than a 1.5 Mbps T1 line often upgraded to DS3, but its 45 Mbps speed was often more than they needed. A newer option, Carrier Ethernet (also known as Metro Ethernet), offers a more practical solution with scalable bandwidth at a often lower cost.
Ethernet services are significantly less expensive than DS3 in some markets, costing up to 50% less. However, in areas where Ethernet isn&amp;rsquo;t widely available, prices may be comparable to DS3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>