<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Citizens' Initiative on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-citizens-initiative/</link><description>Recent content in European Citizens' Initiative on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-citizens-initiative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The European Citizens' Initiative and Greek debt: A surprising pairing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</guid><description>Anastasia Karatzia, Law Lecturer, University of Essex
Introduction
Decisions from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on the European and Monetary Union (EMU) are infrequent. Recent cases on this topic, including landmark judgments like Pringle and Gauweiler, have addressed measures enacted during the Eurozone crisis. Among these decisions is Anagnostakis v Commission, a case challenging the Commission&amp;rsquo;s refusal to register a proposed European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI) titled &amp;ldquo;One million signatures for solidarity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In order to create more responsive rules, the EU-US transatlantic trade and partnership (TTIP) negotiations are crucial.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</guid><description>Dr. Elaine Fahey, Senior Lecturer, The City Law School, City University London
The script
The EU and US have concluded six rounds of discussions on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Agreement (TTIP). This agreement aims to reduce trade barriers and other obstacles, such as differing regulations and standards, across various industries. TTIP is promoted as potentially setting a global trade standard. Some argue it&amp;rsquo;s already irrelevant, but while this downplays its potential influence, skepticism is understandable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The General Court has made a ruling on the European Citizens' Initiative, stating that the Commission must provide reasons for refusing to register proposals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 16:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/</guid><description>Anastasia Karatzia, Assistant Professor in EU law, Erasmus School of Law
Introduction
On February 3rd, the General Court (GC) overturned a European Commission decision for the first time, determining that the Commission failed to provide sufficient justification when it denied registration to a proposed European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). This concise judgment in the Minority SafePack case concerns procedural matters within the relatively new ECI, which was established in 2012. The judgment offers valuable insight to those interested in the ECI and, more broadly, in opportunities for citizens to participate in EU lawmaking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>