<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bonded T1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonded-t1/</link><description>Recent content in Bonded T1 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonded-t1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper vs Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</guid><description>T1 lines have long been considered a reliable connection option for small to medium businesses, gaining traction as prices dropped in recent years. However, a new technology called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers even greater bandwidth at a lower cost and with simpler connectivity.
EoC, like T1, uses existing twisted-pair telephone wiring commonly found in business locations. Traditional T1 lines use two twisted pairs within this wiring, allowing for simultaneous two-way data transfer at 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Beefs Up Last Mile Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</guid><description>The main obstacle for companies aiming to boost their WAN (Wide Area Network) bandwidth is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; access problem. Although network bandwidth has become more affordable and easier to access, the final connection between a business and the carrier&amp;rsquo;s network often poses a significant challenge.
Think of it this way: a superhighway might be close to your company, but if the only route to your facility is a rough, narrow road, transportation will be slow and limited...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Wireline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 23:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</guid><description>In the world of telecommunications, &amp;ldquo;wireline&amp;rdquo; traditionally refers to connections made through copper wires, while &amp;ldquo;wireless&amp;rdquo; implies no physical connections. However, &amp;ldquo;fiber optic&amp;rdquo; technology exists as a distinct category, utilizing physical cables but transmitting data through light rather than electricity. This distinction makes fiber optics a promising successor to the traditional copper wire infrastructure.
Several factors contribute to fiber optic cable&amp;rsquo;s potential to replace copper wire. Interestingly, their structures share similarities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>