<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Second on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/second/</link><description>Recent content in Second on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 12:02:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/second/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality has introduced its second Sage Hotel in Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality.
SilverNeedle Hospitality, based in Singapore, is expanding its upscale Sage Hotel brand in Perth, Western Australia, with a second location. This announcement comes just weeks after the brand launched with a hotel in Brisbane.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated that Sage Hotels are designed for a specific type of business traveler: one who wants a consistent and straightforward experience while working in new cities.</description></item><item><title>Discover more about Malaysia's demographics by reading a book on the population of Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: ISEAS website.
The second edition of The Population of Malaysia, authored by Saw Swee-Hock, former Professor of Statistics at the National University of Singapore and Chairman of the National Statistical Commission of Singapore from 1971 to 1975, has been released.
This updated analysis of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s diverse population offers valuable insights for businesses interested in the Malaysian market. Dr. Saw leverages his extensive knowledge of the country, gained through his upbringing, teaching experience at the University of Malaya, and involvement in population census planning, to provide unique perspectives.</description></item></channel></rss>