<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sale on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sale/</link><description>Recent content in Sale on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:53:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shopee Malaysia's MyCyberSale provides discounts of up to 90%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:53:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</guid><description>Source: Shopee. Part of a banner for MyCyberSale.
During Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;MyCyberSale,&amp;rdquo; which ends September 30th, shoppers on Shopee have a chance to win an iPhone 7 and other prizes. Free shipping is also offered during this period.
Featured sale items include:
Jabra SPORT CORDED Stereo Headset This black, waterproof headset is designed for athletic individuals. Offered by Jabra Malaysia, this headset comes with a two-year warranty. Shopee is offering a 69% discount on this product.</description></item><item><title>Global marketing summit for Malaysian entrepreneurs hosted by INSKEN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-marketing-summit-for-malaysian-entrepreneurs-hosted-by-insken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-marketing-summit-for-malaysian-entrepreneurs-hosted-by-insken/</guid><description>Source: INSKEN. Firdaus delivered
welcome remarks at GMS 2018.
Now in its second year, the Institut Keusahawanan Negara&amp;rsquo;s (INSKEN) annual Global Marketing Summit (GMS) seeks to cultivate innovative leaders within the Malaysian entrepreneurial landscape.
Malaysian Minister Datuk Seri Mohd Redzuan Yusof highlighted the ongoing emphasis on fostering the expansion of entrepreneurs and small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), particularly those in the B40 and M40 income brackets. He stated that the Ministry of Entrepreneur Development (MED) will leverage allocated funds to execute a targeted and comprehensive entrepreneur development strategy in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Check out Shopee Malaysia's Christmas gift ideas!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:02:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, offers a convenient way to shop for Christmas.
Here are some gift ideas available in Malaysia:
Stay Connected
[Image of PINENG PN966 power bank]
This power bank, available in blue and green, ensures you stay connected all day.
[Buy now]
Capture the Moment
[Image of OPPO F1s phone]
The OPPO F1s, dubbed &amp;ldquo;The Selfie Expert,&amp;rdquo; boasts a 5.5&amp;quot; display with 1,280 x 720 pixels resolution, a 13-megapixel rear camera, and a 16-megapixel front camera.</description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric.</description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life.</description></item><item><title>The 11.11 Shopping Festival at Lazada guarantees a more enjoyable experience for everyone involved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:40:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s Lazada 11.11 Shopping Festival is breaking records with over 50 million deals, a significant increase from last year&amp;rsquo;s 27 million. The event will involve over 400,000 sellers and brands, almost triple the number from the previous year.
Lazada, a leading e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia, organizes this yearly event to demonstrate the convenience and affordability of online shopping. For 24 hours, starting at midnight on November 11th, shoppers across six countries will have access to incredible deals on a wide range of products, with discounts of up to 90%.</description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5.</description></item><item><title>Ten million transactions during the Lazada Mid-Year Festival</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ten-million-transactions-during-the-lazada-mid-year-festival/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ten-million-transactions-during-the-lazada-mid-year-festival/</guid><description>Lazada&amp;rsquo;s first sale since its rebranding offers 10 million deals.
Lazada&amp;rsquo;s shoppertainment approach is enhanced with the first region-wide livestreamed gameshow.
LazGames now includes a leaderboard and brand customization options.
On July 12th, Lazada will host its first-ever mid-year sale event, the Lazada Mid-Year Festival, throughout six Southeast Asian countries.
Consumers will have access to product discounts ranging from well-known brands to recent releases and one-of-a-kind items from 12:00 a.</description></item><item><title>Verify the authenticity of KSA sales and promotions using this app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</guid><description>Source: MCI. HE the Minister of Commerce and Investment Dr Majid bin Abdullah Al Qasabi launched the Sales app on 31 January 2017.
The Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) in Saudi Arabia has introduced a mobile application called &amp;ldquo;Sales.&amp;rdquo; This app allows the public to access the MCI&amp;rsquo;s database of authorized sales and promotional offers. The goal is to help users find genuine deals and discounts quickly.
Through the app, consumers can browse information on more than 27,000 retail locations and over 700,000 licensed products registered with the MCI.</description></item><item><title>11 facts about 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:07:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</guid><description>Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 Global Shopping Festival, beginning on November 11, is generating excitement with its pre-launch preparations. Here are 11 key things shoppers should be aware of:
AI-Powered Multilingual Tools To enhance the shopping experience for global customers, Alibaba has introduced an AI translation tool designed to bridge language gaps between buyers and sellers.
This online chat tool, recently launched on Lazada, enables real-time translation between English and Thai, Vietnamese, and Indonesian.</description></item><item><title>Shopee reveals birthday flash sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</guid><description>Shopee, a prominent mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is marking its first anniversary. To commemorate the occasion, they are holding hourly flash sales with discounts of up to 70% on December 12, 2016.
Two products will be discounted every hour on December 12th, from 12 pm to 7 pm.
Along with the hourly flash sales on December 12th, Shopee is running a lucky draw for users who take advantage of daily category vouchers.</description></item><item><title>DEAL.com.sg is celebrating its upcoming birthday by giving away S$5 million to customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</guid><description>The flash sale website, DEAL.com.sg, is thanking its loyal customers by offering them millions of dollars in discounts. This initiative, launched after the company&amp;rsquo;s start in May 2010, also aims to draw in new customers.
Patrick Linden, the CEO of DEAL.com.sg&amp;rsquo;s parent company, iBuy Group, expressed his gratitude, stating that the company is giving back $5 million to thank customers for their support over the past three and a half years.</description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3.</description></item></channel></rss>