<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Conferencing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-conferencing/</link><description>Recent content in Video Conferencing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-conferencing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing business internet services, bandwidth is important, but understanding the difference between dedicated and shared connections is crucial.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated bandwidth is exclusively for your use. This might seem obvious, but the recent rise of shared bandwidth makes it worth clarifying. The cost-effectiveness of shared bandwidth often makes businesses reconsider their need for a dedicated line.
Cost Considerations
Shared bandwidth is significantly cheaper than dedicated bandwidth at similar speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Browser Based Video Conferencing and Webinars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</guid><description>Once restricted to businesses, video conferencing is now accessible to anyone with an internet connection and a web browser. MegaMeeting offers a suite of products for PCs, Macs, and Linux computers that don&amp;rsquo;t require typical downloads or installations. As long as you can use a web browser, you can participate in video conferences and webinars.
MegaMeeting&amp;rsquo;s web-based system utilizes the Flash Player 9 plugin, commonly found in browsers like Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10x10 Mbps Ethernet Providers in Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many believe that 10 Mbps Ethernet is replacing traditional T1 lines, and for good reason. This article will explore why that is, how this technology works, and the steps to upgrade.
Businesses have relied on T1 lines for decades due to their high reliability, guaranteed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps, and symmetrical upload and download speeds. Prices have also decreased over time, and availability is now widespread.
The main drawback of T1 lines is their limited bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Managed MPLS Networking Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</guid><description>Imagine your company with offices across the country, each operating its own independent local network for computers, phones, and video calls. While efficient individually, they lack integration. To unify your company, connecting these separate networks is key. This will boost efficiency by centralizing functions, improving collaboration among employees nationwide, and enabling specialized support centers.
Integrating your phone system with your network can lead to substantial savings on long-distance calls. Instead of relying on traditional phone lines, internal communication happens within your network, cutting toll charges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-mpls-networking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The AccuConference Cost Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s challenging economy, audio teleconferencing, video conferencing, and web conferencing are gaining popularity. These tools effectively cut costs and boost productivity without resorting to layoffs or facility closures. This demonstrates how technology is replacing outdated and unsustainable business practices. Electronic conferencing helps businesses thrive during economic slowdowns by connecting teams, accelerating progress, and eliminating costly travel expenses. A frontrunner in this domain is AccuConference.
AccuConference stands out from competitors by offering a comprehensive suite of solutions, including conventional audio conference calls, video conferencing, and web conferences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Connections Bridge The Atlantic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 05:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</guid><description>The immense volume of data flowing through global fiber optic networks highlights our interconnected world. While intercontinental cables have existed for years, low latency networks are becoming increasingly vital.
High-frequency trading, particularly the use of automated programs, drives the demand for low latency. These programs compete to execute trades milliseconds or even microseconds faster than competitors, a feat impossible for human traders. This speed makes the physical path between traders and exchanges critical, with the delay on this path known as latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A New Edge On Private IP Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</guid><description>With the increase in businesses operating from multiple locations, IP network solutions have become more affordable and accessible. New Edge Networks, a key player in this domain, specializes in private IP-based WANs, offering enhanced quality and performance for connecting multiple business sites by bypassing the public internet.
While the internet has revolutionized global communication, its ubiquity and open nature pose limitations for businesses. Network neutrality principles treat all data equally, regardless of its importance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five Years Of The Explainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 21:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</guid><description>T1 Rex’s Business Telecom Explainer turned five this month, with more than 800 posts published since its 2004 launch. Our initial goal was to clarify complex telecommunications services and provide businesses with competitive options. Over time, we&amp;rsquo;ve broadened our scope to encompass a wide range of products, services, and topics relevant to our audience. As we approach our second decade, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the &amp;ldquo;aughts&amp;rdquo; and explore potential future trends.
This explainer blog, as the name suggests, was launched alongside T1Rex...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>