<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hotel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hotel/</link><description>Recent content in Hotel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hotel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The launch of Fairfield by Marriott Belitung has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its Fairfield by Marriott brand with the opening of a new hotel in Belitung, Indonesia.
Source: Fairfield by Marriott Belitung website. The Fairfield by Marriott Belitung.
Mike Fulkerson, Vice President of Brand &amp;amp; Marketing for Marriott International Asia Pacific, stated that Fairfield by Marriott is experiencing rapid growth in the region, with 47 properties in development in Asia Pacific and over 400 globally. He highlighted the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing a relaxing and dependable experience at a good value, enhanced by Indonesian hospitality, making the Belitung location an ideal retreat for travelers.</description></item><item><title>Two JW Marriott hotels have been ranked in the top 10 TripAdvisor Travelers' Choices for Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Lotte Hotel Seoul.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for hotels in Korea ranked the following as the top ten:
Lotte Hotel Seoul, with a rating of 4.5 out of 5 from 1,849 reviews. The Plaza Conrad Seoul JW Marriott Dongdaemun Square Seoul Park Hyatt Seoul The Shilla Seoul Sheraton Seoul D Cube City Hotel The Westin Chosun Seoul The Ritz-Carlton, Seoul The JW Marriott Seoul Curious?</description></item><item><title>Azerai offers affordable luxury in Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Azerai invites discerning travelers to experience attainable luxury in Vietnam through a collection of acclaimed boutique resorts. Founded by Adrian Zecha, the visionary behind Aman Resorts, the Azerai concept is already present in the culturally rich destinations of Ke Ga, Can Tho, and Hue.
Source: Azerai. Each Azerai resort is designed to envelop guests in sophisticated, understated luxury.
Every Azerai resort aims to immerse guests in refined yet understated luxury. At Azerai Can Tho, this translates to seclusion within low-rise structures on a private islet in the Hau River, reachable only by boat.</description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub.</description></item><item><title>Starting October 14, the Coffee Lounge at Goodwood Park Hotel will be offering an expanded menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Goodwood Park Hotel, home to the Coffee Lounge known for its Taiwan porridge and local dishes, is launching a limited-time menu enhancement. From October 14th, guests can enjoy new additions to the &amp;ldquo;Design Your Own Local Degustation Set Menu&amp;rdquo; and a special dessert buffet featuring Mao Shan Wang durian.
This year, from October 14th to November 17th, Coffee Lounge&amp;rsquo;s popular dessert buffet will showcase Mao Shan Wang durian pastries alongside its regular offerings during lunch and dinner.</description></item><item><title>Carlson Rezidor has revealed plans for new hotel developments in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</guid><description>The Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group has announced new deals and hotel openings in strategic locations within India, further solidifying its position as a leading international hotel group in the country.
Thorsten Kirschke, President for Asia Pacific at Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments, stating that building upon a successful 2013, the first four months of this year have shown strong results in India and Thailand. He added that with 95 hotels currently operational, they anticipate exceeding 100 operating hotels in the Asia Pacific region by year-end.</description></item><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer.</description></item><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas.</description></item><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city.</description></item><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan.</description></item><item><title>The Wanda Vista brand expands globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</guid><description>Qian Jin, the head of the upscale hotel group Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has revealed the global growth plan for their Wanda Vista brand.
Wanda Vista represents the top tier of luxury within Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, designed specifically for guests who appreciate art and culture. Situated in major international cities and drawing inspiration from Eastern aesthetics, the brand focuses on providing personalized service catered to each guest&amp;rsquo;s individual requirements.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is continuing its guest outreach program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas.
Since late March 2020, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has been offering its guests and followers daily live chats, cooking demonstrations, and meditation and yoga sessions.
Recognizing that many people are hesitant to resume travel despite the easing of COVID-19 restrictions, the company introduced six new themes for its #AtHomeWithSixSenses campaign.
These themes - Wellness, Eat, Grow, Sustainability, Sleep and From the Heart of Six Senses - will continue to be explored through content on the Six Senses website (sixsenses.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha provides Iftar and suhoor meals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</guid><description>Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha is offering special meals for iftar and suhoor throughout Ramadan.
Source: Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha website. The Gem Garden.
George Sarkis, Director of Food and Beverage at the hotel, highlights the extensive iftar buffet, which combines Oriental and Continental cuisines with traditional Ramadan drinks.
Both iftar and suhoor are served at The Gem Garden, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s all-day dining venue. The iftar buffet, available from sunset to 10 pm, costs AED120* per person and includes live cooking stations.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations.</description></item><item><title>IHG will no longer provide mini toiletries as bathroom amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</guid><description>Source: IHG. A shower with sink showing miniatures as amenities.
The InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) is transitioning from small, individual toiletry bottles to larger, bulk amenity dispensers in all 843,000 rooms across its portfolio of hotels. This change, to be fully implemented by 2021, is part of a larger sustainability initiative and establishes IHG as the first global hotel company to entirely eliminate miniature bathroom products in favor of bulk-sized options.</description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach.</description></item><item><title>Groundbreaking ceremony finished for the Fujairah Business Centre, a mixed-use development</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/groundbreaking-ceremony-finished-for-the-fujairah-business-centre-a-mixed-use-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 04:54:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/groundbreaking-ceremony-finished-for-the-fujairah-business-centre-a-mixed-use-development/</guid><description>Al Taif Investment, a collaboration between Dubai Investments and Fujairah Investment Establishment (FIE), the investment branch of the Fujairah Government, has launched its flagship Fujairah Business Centre project.
Scheduled for completion in three years with a budget of AED400 million, the project aims to be a landmark development. Located opposite the Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, it features two towers with a total built-up area of 80,058 sq m. These towers include a 19-story office building and a 19-story Courtyard by Marriott hotel offering 228 rooms and apartment units.</description></item><item><title>Miramar Hotel Group offer now available with Asia Miles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</guid><description>Source: Miramar Hotel Taipei website.
Miramar Hotel Group is now part of the Asia Miles rewards program. This means members can earn 250 Asia Miles for every qualifying stay at either the Miramar Garden Taipei or Miramar Hotel Hsinchu.
To earn miles, members should provide their membership number during booking and show their card upon arrival. Note that this offer applies to deluxe room reservations.
For reference, the Miramar Garden Taipei first opened its doors in 2006, followed by the Miramar Hotel Hsinchu in 2013.</description></item><item><title>The Business Plan package at The Shilla Seoul includes access to The Executive Lounge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. The Executive Lounge.
Through June 30, 2019, The Shilla Seoul is offering its Business Plan package, which gives guests the opportunity to experience The Executive Lounge.
Guests selecting the Executive Business Deluxe option receive exclusive access to The Executive Lounge, complimentary breakfast at The Parkview, and access to both the gym and indoor swimming pool.
The Executive Lounge at The Shilla Seoul, situated on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s top floor, is designed as a luxurious penthouse.</description></item><item><title>Accor will assume management of the Star Convention Centre in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</guid><description>In 2020, Accor will assume management of the 571-room Star Convention Centre in Thailand, rebranding it as the Novotel Rayong Star Convention Centre. The hotel, situated in Rayong province&amp;rsquo;s city center, will undergo a significant two-year renovation. The initial phase will focus on revamping public spaces, dining establishments, and 235 guest rooms. Subsequently, the remaining 336 guest rooms will be renovated in the second phase.
Patrick Basset, COO of Accor for Upper Southeast &amp;amp; Northeast Asia and the Maldives, expressed enthusiasm about the hotel joining Accor&amp;rsquo;s network and expanding their presence in Rayong.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the end of the year with eco-friendly festivities at East, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</guid><description>The environmentally conscious EAST, Hong Kong hotel is ready to celebrate the holiday season this year with special decorations and exciting events.
Continuing a tradition that began in 2014, EAST&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Village highlights creative recycling. This year, the EAST team gathered fallen logs left behind by Typhoon Mangkhut from the city streets to create unique Christmas decorations. Students from Jockey Club Sarah Roe School (JCSRS), the only school in Hong Kong offering an English curriculum for students with additional learning needs, collaborated with the EAST team on this project.</description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is the inaugural Hyatt hotel in the Jiangsu province</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</guid><description>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou has officially opened in Suzhou, a city renowned for its historic canals, stone bridges, and UNESCO-recognized classical gardens.
Source: Hyatt. The hotel boasts a 29-floor atrium, the tallest in Suzhou.
&amp;ldquo;The launch of Hyatt Regency Suzhou is a significant move for Hyatt as we expand our brand presence in China,&amp;rdquo; stated Christopher Koehler, Vice President of Operations for Hyatt in China. &amp;ldquo;We aim to create valuable connections among global business and leisure travelers.</description></item><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home.</description></item><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout.</description></item><item><title>Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery is poised to transform into a secret retreat in Kyoto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Interior, Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery.
Accor has expanded its presence in Japan with the launch of its second MGallery Hotel, the Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery.
This Kyoto-based hotel, designed by architect Yukio Hashimoto, centers around a Japanese garden, providing a sophisticated experience of the changing seasons. Hashimoto&amp;rsquo;s design prioritizes creating a specific atmosphere over focusing solely on materials, resulting in a minimalist and timeless aesthetic.</description></item><item><title>The Gold Coast, Australia will be home to the first Hyde location outside of the US</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</guid><description>Accor is expanding its partnership with sbe beyond the US, selecting Australia as the first Asia Pacific location. Hyde, their luxury lifestyle brand known for its Los Angeles Sunset Strip inspiration, will debut Hyde Paradiso on the Gold Coast in March 2019. This venue promises an all-day experience, transforming into a sophisticated lounge and dining destination in the evening.
Simon McGrath, COO of Accor Pacific, highlights the partnership&amp;rsquo;s goal to deliver unique lifestyle experiences.</description></item><item><title>Guests are now welcomed at The Murray, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-now-welcomed-at-the-murray-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Wharf Hotels. The Murray,
Hong Kong.
Wharf Hotels is pleased to announce the launch of The Murray, Hong Kong, a new Niccolo Hotel. This addition represents the group’s newest flagship Niccolo property and joins their luxury contemporary chic collection.
The Murray boasts a rich history, standing as one of eight historic landmarks protected by the Conserving Central initiative, launched by the Hong Kong government in 2013. Situated in the city’s vibrant Central district, the building has been recognized for its pioneering approach to sustainability throughout its nearly 50 years.</description></item><item><title>Artyzen Singapore will be launched in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</guid><description>Preferred Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, boasting a global network of over 650 hotels, resorts, and residences in 80 countries, is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the upcoming October debut of Artyzen Singapore.
This 20-story establishment occupies the former site of the Marie Villa mansion, conveniently situated near Orchard Road and the Singapore Botanic Gardens. The hotel features 142 generously sized rooms and suites, each spanning at least 42 square meters and offering either a balcony or terraced Sky Gardens.</description></item><item><title>Katamama will be opening its doors to guests in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</guid><description>Source: Katamama. A rooftop suite at dusk.
Katamama, a 58-suite boutique hotel in Seminyak, Bali&amp;rsquo;s prime oceanfront area, is set to open in late March 2016.
The hotel emphasizes &amp;ldquo;handcrafted hospitality,&amp;rdquo; with every detail meticulously designed and executed by skilled Indonesian artisans. Katamama is a project by PTT Family, known for acclaimed restaurants, bars, and the Potato Head Beach Club in Bali. This 20-villa estate is famous for its innovative environmental design and a prominent contemporary Indonesian art gallery.</description></item><item><title>The Ramada Abu Dhabi introduces Lebanese fine dining for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>The Ramada Abu Dhabi, a new hotel in the city&amp;rsquo;s central business district, is now home to Karamna Beirut, an upscale Lebanese dining experience. The restaurant is the brainchild of Tony Karam, a restaurateur whose family owns and operates the Karam restaurant chain.
Source: Ramada Abu Dhabi Hotel. The Karamna Beirut restaurant.
Rene Vincent, General Manager of the Ramada Abu Dhabi, highlights the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s impressive menu, curated to delight guests seeking refined Lebanese cuisine.</description></item><item><title>Special promotions for the Fireworks Celebration at the Mandarin Oriental, Macau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Macau has special Fireworks Celebration packages perfect for corporate events, team building, or client appreciation. These packages provide a unique opportunity to experience the 26th Macau International Fireworks Display Contest.
Source: Mandarin Oriental Macau website.
Available on September 8th, 13th, 20th, 27th, and October 1st, 2014, the package starts at MOP4,388 and includes:
Overnight accommodations in a room or suite with panoramic fireworks views through expansive windows. A special four-course fireworks-themed dinner for two at the Vida Rica Restaurant, showcasing Chef Dominique Bugnand’s modern take on classic French cuisine.</description></item><item><title>Accor plans to introduce the ibis Styles brand to Singapore later this year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</guid><description>Source: Accor. The ibis Style in the Macpherson area, Singapore, will be launched this year.
Accor plans to open an ibis Styles hotel in Singapore by the last quarter of 2015, introducing a trendy, lifestyle-focused brand to the country. Situated within the same complex as the MacPherson shopping mall, the hotel is conveniently located at the intersection of MacPherson and Aljunied Roads, a short 20-minute drive from the airport.</description></item><item><title>Buffets for Iftar are available at 21 on Rajah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</guid><description>Source: 21 on Rajah.
The buffet.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a venue to hold a corporate Iftar gathering in Singapore during Ramadan, consider the halal-certified 21 On Rajah. Situated within Days Hotel Singapore at Zhongshan Park, this all-day dining restaurant is presenting a selection of Mediterranean and Asian Iftar buffets each evening.
Chef de Cuisine Faustino Picardo Ines Jr and his culinary team have crafted diverse menus throughout the week.</description></item><item><title>Discover the surrounding areas of Hotel Indigo in the new Neighbourhood 15 campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 02:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</guid><description>Hotel Indigo&amp;rsquo;s new brand campaign, &amp;ldquo;Neighbourhood 15,&amp;rdquo; highlights the unique character of each hotel&amp;rsquo;s surrounding area, specifically within a 15-minute radius. The campaign showcases local businesses and individuals who contribute to the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s vibrant atmosphere.
A two-minute video featuring the Hotel Indigo Bali Seminyak Beach, the brand&amp;rsquo;s first resort location, introduces viewers to nearby attractions like Surf School Bali, Divine Earth restaurant, and Bali Barber. Starting in October, a series of videos will delve deeper into these local businesses, offering insights and personal stories.</description></item><item><title>Sparkle under the moonlight during an afternoon tea in Hong Kong this September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</guid><description>Source: The Langham, Hong Kong. The Twinkle in the Moonlight Afternoon Tea set.
The Langham Hotel in Hong Kong is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with a special afternoon tea inspired by Eastern flavors.
Offered throughout September at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Palm Court restaurant, the menu, created by Executive Pastry Chef David Puig, features treats like &amp;ldquo;The Moon,&amp;rdquo; a lychee and raspberry mousse cake decorated with a galaxy glaze. This dessert also includes rose essence, Sacher sponge cake, and a golden crescent moon topping.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Jumeirah City Break</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah website.
City Breaks at Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Jumeirah Creekside Hotel, and Jumeirah Living World Trade Centre Residences come with perks like free entry to Wild Wadi Waterpark and Zero Gravity Private Beach.
Jumeirah Emirates Towers boasts shopping at the Boulevard, various dining and nightlife options, and a convenient location just five minutes from Dubai Mall, accessible via the hotel&amp;rsquo;s complimentary shuttle service.
Reserve a room for three or more nights at participating Jumeirah hotels in Dubai with the Jumeirah City Break promotion and enjoy a 20% discount on the best available rates, along with:</description></item><item><title>The fourth akyra hotel in Sukhumvit, Bangkok has been launched by Akaryn</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</guid><description>Akaryn Hotel Group, a Thai hospitality company known for its luxurious hotels and resorts, will open its fourth akyra property, akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok, in December 2017.
The upscale boutique hotel is situated on Sukhumvit Soi 20, a vibrant area in the heart of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s main tourist zone, known for its excellent dining, lively nightlife, high-end shopping malls, spas, and green spaces.
akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok offers 50 rooms, ranging from 30 to 60 square meters, with city views.</description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel.</description></item><item><title>NOBU presents Harvest in Aomori at InterContinental Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hong Kong. Steamed abalone, sea urchin shijimi dashi jelly, and cured mackerel sashimi with chrysanthemum dressing.
NOBU InterContinental Hong Kong presents the fifth installment of its GOURMET TOUR OF JAPAN series – Harvest in Aomori – which runs from September 12th to October 22nd.
Executive Chef Sean Mell and Executive Sushi Chef Arakai Kaazunari have crafted special lunch and dinner menus that showcase the fall bounty of Aomori Prefecture, a region in northern Japan&amp;rsquo;s Tōhoku region.</description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its 200th property in Greater China, located in Chengdu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Fairmont Chengdu lobby.
The Fairmont Chengdu marks the 200th property for AccorHotels in Greater China and is the first Fairmont Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts establishment in Western China. This opening is a key part of AccorHotels’ expansion within the luxury market.
Situated on Tianfu Middle Avenue in Chengdu&amp;rsquo;s high-tech zone, the hotel provides 336 guest rooms and suites, each offering impressive views of the city skyline. Shuangliu International Airport is easily accessible at just a 25-minute drive away, and the nearby metro station provides convenient access to Tianfu Square, the forthcoming Tianfu International Airport, and the South CBD zone.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has reopened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has finished renovating all guest rooms, bathrooms, and suites, offering visitors a revitalized stay in the heart of the city.
Source: Holiday Inn website. The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders.
Every room was completely emptied to give the architect a fresh start in designing a space with the modern traveler&amp;rsquo;s needs in mind. Striking new interiors are highlighted by floor-to-ceiling windows, equipped with electronically controlled blackout blinds that can be adjusted from the bedside.</description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF.</description></item><item><title>W Retreat &amp; Spa Bali - Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary with a month-long celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</guid><description>Source: W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali website.
The W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali in Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary on March 5, 2016. The resort will commemorate this milestone with a month-long celebration titled &amp;ldquo;FIVE ON FIVE,&amp;rdquo; showcasing five unique highlights.
WOOBAR will present special edition Paletas Wey popsicles, a Mexican-style frozen treat crafted by the Bali-based company. Meanwhile, W THE STORE will offer an exclusive, limited-edition collection of &amp;ldquo;Wanitas&amp;rdquo; décor.</description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is providing selected transit passengers with a complimentary night's stay in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is offering a free overnight stay in Abu Dhabi to Economy Class travelers flying from specific locations, including Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Jordan, Kuwait, Bahrain, Oman, and Lebanon, whose journeys connect through the UAE&amp;rsquo;s capital.
This offer is valid for travel dates up to September 30, 2018, with bookings available from May 1 to September 15, 2018. Accommodation choices include the Radisson Blu on Yas Island and the Yas Island Rotana.</description></item><item><title>Accor makes a comeback in Myanmar with The Lake Garden in Nay Pyi Taw</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw.
Accor, a leading international hotel operator in the Asia-Pacific region, has established its first hotel in Myanmar: The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw. This recently constructed, upscale establishment is part of the MGallery Collection and is conveniently located a short distance from both the Myanmar International Convention Centre (MICC) and Nay Pyi Taw International Airport.
Patrick Basset, Chief Operating Officer for Accor in multiple Southeast Asian nations, highlighted the significance of this opening as it marks Accor&amp;rsquo;s return to Myanmar.</description></item><item><title>The Adya Hotel Langkawi provides meeting rooms and a ballroom for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: Adya Hotel Langkawi website. Interior of a junior suite.
The four-star Adya Hotel Langkawi, situated in the Kuah town center on Langkawi Island in Malaysia, is marketed as a perfect starting point for exploring the natural wonders and rich culture of Langkawi, a designated UNESCO Global Geopark.
The hotel boasts 207 rooms and suites, each featuring a private bathroom with a bath and shower, along with a balcony that offers scenic views of the sea and town.</description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading.</description></item><item><title>The Pottinger Hong Kong is now open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</guid><description>Sino Group, a hospitality branch of Sino Land Company, manages various properties including hotels, a yacht club, serviced apartments, and residential dining establishments. They have recently introduced The Pottinger Hong Kong, a luxurious 68-room boutique hotel. Situated on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s oldest paved street, the hotel holds a notable position on a site recognized as a Grade I historic place by the Antiquities Advisory Board of Hong Kong.
As per the Sino Group of Hotels, The Pottinger Hong Kong features 68 upscale guestrooms and suites, with sizes varying from 23 to 68 square meters.</description></item><item><title>The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay offers a competitive advantage for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay website. The Grand Ballroom, theatre-style.
The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, a premier five-star resort in Phu Quoc and a flagship property in Vietnam, provides a range of meeting spaces suitable for various event sizes.
The resort is committed to crafting unforgettable events and immersive experiences for all attendees. Phu Quoc is an up-and-coming destination, now linked by direct flights to major cities like Ho Chi Minh City, Bangkok, and Guangzhou.</description></item><item><title>The Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 will commence operations on January 1, 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</guid><description>Source: Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 website.
Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20, a lifestyle hotel focused on health and wellness, will softly open its doors on January 1, 2016. The hotel provides tailored food and drinks, spa treatments, fitness facilities, and wellness activities.
Conveniently situated on Sukhumvit 20, the hotel is a short walk from the BTS Asok Skytrain, MRT Sukhumvit Subway, Terminal 21 Mall, The EmQuartier, and the Emporium.</description></item><item><title>Capella Sydney celebrates its first anniversary with joy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</guid><description>Source: Capella Sydney. To celebrate its one-year anniversary, Capella Sydney is providing a special deal with a A$365 credit applicable throughout the hotel and breakfast for two. The offer encompasses:
- Daily breakfast at Brasserie 1930
- Exclusive access to The Living Room, a shared area present in every Capella establishment. This space allows guests to participate in daily Capella customs and experience Sydney&amp;rsquo;s heritage through a curated display of local historical items and art.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group is celebrating the expansion of its Radisson Blu brand with the debut of its first Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok.
The Radisson Blu Plaza Hotel Bangkok, boasting 290 rooms, is strategically situated in Sukhumvit, a vibrant area known for its numerous offices, corporate headquarters, and retail outlets. This property marks Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s first Radisson Blu establishment in the city and is owned by G&amp;amp;P Asset Holding Company.</description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa.</description></item><item><title>Luxury hotel to cater to Sydney airport guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</guid><description>Accor, the largest hotel operator in Australia, will be a part of a new multi-use development project in Mascot, near the Sydney Airport. The project will include a hotel, commercial space, and retail areas.
Accor signed an agreement with Goodman to oversee a 5-star hotel, named Pullman Sydney Airport, as part of a new A$100 million development. This project will also include office and retail space. Pullman, the biggest upscale hotel network in the Asia Pacific, has over 45 hotels in the area.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its inaugural five-star international hotel in Vung Tau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The
Pullman Vung Tau.
AccorHotels is introducing the Pullman Vung Tau, the first international five-star hotel in this coastal city just a 90-minute drive from Ho Chi Minh City.
The Pullman Vung Tau offers views of both Back Beach and Front Beach and boasts the largest meeting facilities in Southern Vietnam, making it perfect for business travelers looking for a quick escape from Ho Chi Minh City.</description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort introduces its new private villas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort has introduced new villas that provide enhanced privacy and luxury for guests. These villas overlook the Gulf of Thailand and the resort&amp;rsquo;s lotus lagoon. Their spaciousness makes them perfect for hosting private events, parties, or intimate gatherings, with amenities like a private chef, outdoor barbecues, and more.
Situated in a secluded part of the resort, the four three-bedroom and one four-bedroom villas offer direct access to the Club InterContinental Lounge.</description></item><item><title>Get 10% off and receive gifts with the HMH summer offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</guid><description>Hospitality Management Holdings (HMH) is offering a summer deal: guests can enjoy a 10% discount on bed and breakfast rates and receive a daily voucher redeemable at any of the hotel&amp;rsquo;s restaurants or spas. This promotion is valid until September 21, 2015.
Laurent Voivenel, CEO of HMH, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s presence in 15 cities across the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. He stated, &amp;ldquo;Due to significant demand from Saudi Arabia and other GCC countries, over 70% of our rooms have been booked in advance.</description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine.</description></item><item><title>The Anantara Angkor Resort is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>Source: Anantara Angkor Resort website. View of the exterior.
The luxurious Anantara Angkor Resort has reopened in Siem Reap, offering an all-suite boutique experience close to the wonders of the ancient Khmer Empire.
Just a short drive from the city center, the 5-star resort provides easy access to vibrant markets, riverside attractions, and the charming French colonial quarter. The UNESCO World Heritage Site of Angkor Archaeological Park is also conveniently located a mere 10 minutes away.</description></item><item><title>Experience the VIP treatment at Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</guid><description>Source: Hard Rock Hotels. Interior, Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen.
The Hard Rock Hotel brand has debuted its first establishment in China with the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen. This new property combines pop culture with high-end hospitality to create a luxurious experience for travelers seeking a unique experience.
Opening its doors in the summer of 2017, the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen is located within Mission Hills Centreville. Situated near a golf course, the hotel also provides convenient access to a variety of leisure, wellness, and entertainment options.</description></item><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr.</description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality.</description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels Group plans to open Holiday Inn Osaka Namba by the end of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: IHG. The Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) and Japan Hotel Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) Investment Corporation (JHR) are collaborating on the Holiday Inn Osaka Namba, marking the REIT&amp;rsquo;s first venture with IHG. Scheduled to launch by the end of 2016, the hotel, presently known as Hotel Vista Grande Osaka, will be rebranded as Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
The 314-room hotel, joining the globally recognized Holiday Inn brand, will leverage IHG&amp;rsquo;s extensive global reservation systems, sales network, and the substantial IHG Rewards Club loyalty program, boasting almost 94 million members.</description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels &amp; Resorts presents an art installation in Singapore to commemorate its 200 properties worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-resorts-presents-an-art-installation-in-singapore-to-commemorate-its-200-properties-worldwide/</guid><description>Video of Hall with the bottles shaping the number &amp;lsquo;200&amp;rsquo;.
To mark the opening of their 200th hotel, InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts commissioned contemporary British artist Alexander Hall, known professionally as Haut de Gamme, to create a commemorative installation.
The artwork features 200 champagne bottles, each hand-painted by Hall in his signature drip technique. Inspired by the unique character of each InterContinental property, the individually designed bottles collectively form the number “200”.</description></item><item><title>Book with ONYX in February to receive exclusive discounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</guid><description>Source: Onyx web page. Several ONYX Hospitality Group properties are offering special deals for the Chinese New Year.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, guests can enjoy up to a 20% discount at the Oriental Residence Bangkok or at one of the 25 participating Amari, OZO, Shama, and Mosaic Collection hotels. These offers are available at locations in Thailand, Sri Lanka, mainland China, Hong Kong, Qatar, and Bangladesh.</description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is committed to connecting with Chinese tourists through investment efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotel Resorts Spas&amp;rsquo; Chinese website.
To expand its online footprint, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has launched a website in Chinese. The new website offers the same content and features as the brand&amp;rsquo;s English website. This move is anticipated to attract more customers from China, a key growth market for Six Senses.
In addition to the website, Six Senses is connecting with Chinese customers through brand engagement on social media platforms like WeChat, Youku, and Sina Weibo.</description></item><item><title>Accor expands its footprint in regional Queensland with the addition of Mercure Rockhampton</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</guid><description>The Travelodge Hotel in Rockhampton has transitioned to the Mercure brand as part of a new franchise agreement with Accor. This addition expands Mercure&amp;rsquo;s presence to over 50 properties in Australia and New Zealand, and more than 810 globally.
Conveniently located in the city center and a short distance from the airport, the Mercure Rockhampton underwent renovations in 2008. The eight-story hotel boasts 74 rooms, views of the Fitzroy River, six conference rooms, an outdoor pool, a fitness center, a 24-hour reception, and convenient access to attractions like Great Keppel Island.</description></item><item><title>The second edition of Food and Hotel Penang is back!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</guid><description>Source: FHP 2016 website.
The second Food and Hotel Penang (FHP 2016) event is poised to solidify its standing as the premier trade-only platform in Northern Malaysia. This event will host a curated buyer program, offering access to key figures in the food and hospitality sectors within Penang and nearby northern states like Kedah, Perak, and Perlis.
Supported by the Penang state government and the Malaysian Association of Hotels, FHP aims to build upon the achievements of its 2014 edition, which saw participation from 240 companies spanning 30 countries.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn in Bangkok is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Bangkok has reopened with a new focus on natural elements.
The traditional lobby is gone, replaced with an open space that blends the front desk, restaurant, bar, lounge, and business center in a modern style. This design approach extends to the 379 guest rooms, each envisioned as a home away from home.
Two new dining options are available: Ginger, offering all-day dining, and Beer Republic, a bar designed to evoke a 1920s European industrial warehouse.</description></item><item><title>Grand Mercure makes its first appearance in Myanmar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</guid><description>AccorHotels has launched its first Grand Mercure hotel in Myanmar. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire, with its 175 guest rooms and suites, provides a view of the Schwedagon Pagoda. Local artist Pyar Dade designed the accommodations.
Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire. Patrick Basset, COO of AccorHotels, Upper Southeast and Northeast Asia and the Maldives, stated, “This is our first Grand Mercure in Myanmar and the opening of Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire reflects the cultural touchstone of the destination and heritage in bringing local stories to life.</description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner.</description></item><item><title>FEH has announced a partnership with SIA's HighFlyer business travel program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</guid><description>Source: FEH. The Clan Hotel Singapore lobby.
Far East Hospitality (FEH) is the first hotel group to join Singapore Airlines’ (SIA&amp;rsquo;s) corporate travel program, HighFlyer. Companies in this program receive discounted airfares and earn HighFlyer points when their staff travel for business. These points can be redeemed for future travel, benefits for their business, or rewards for their traveling employees.
Members of HighFlyer can now accumulate up to 500 points when their employees stay at participating Far East Hospitality hotels in Singapore, Japan, and Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>The Shunde Marriott Hotel has officially opened its doors in Foshan, China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its presence in China with the opening of the 258-room Shunde Marriott Hotel. Located in Shunde, a district of Foshan in Guangdong Province, the hotel is owned by Shunde Midea Group and managed by Marriott under a long-term agreement. This latest addition brings the Marriott Hotels brand&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in Greater China to 19 properties.
Source: Marriott. The Shunde Marriott offers guests views of either Shunfeng Mountain Park or the city skyline.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers.</description></item><item><title>The Wyndham brand has entered the UAE market with its presence in Dubai Marina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</guid><description>Source: The First Group. The new Wyndham
Dubai Marina.
Wyndham Dubai Marina, the first hotel solely developed by leading Dubai-based property developer, The First Group, has officially opened. This launch signifies the Wyndham brand&amp;rsquo;s entrance into the UAE market.
This four-star deluxe Wyndham Dubai Marina, managed by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, the largest hotel management company globally, represents a significant achievement for The First Group. The developer has established a strong reputation for creating high-quality serviced apartments and &amp;ldquo;aparthotels&amp;rdquo; in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Grand Millennium Dubai is providing daily iftar buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</guid><description>During Ramadan, the Grand Millennium Dubai, located near Sheikh Zayed Road, is hosting nightly iftar buffets at their Atrium restaurant. For AED 145 per person, guests can enjoy live cooking stations, along with Arabic and international dishes.
Source: Grand Millennium Dubai website. The Atrium restaurant.
The restaurant offers special group rates for iftar. The Silver package, priced at AED 165 per person, accommodates up to 50 guests. The Gold package, for a maximum of 100 people, costs AED 155 per person.</description></item><item><title>DAMAC introduces Maison Cour Jardin in the heart of downtown Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</guid><description>At the end of December 2014, DAMAC Properties, a high-end real estate developer, launched its third luxury serviced apartment complex in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area. Located just a short distance from popular attractions like the Dubai Mall and Dubai Fountain, DAMAC Maison Cour Jardin joins the company&amp;rsquo;s growing portfolio, which includes DAMAC Maison Dubai Mall Street and DAMAC Maison Canal Views.
Source: DAMAC Properties.
“DAMAC Properties is expanding its hospitality offerings, both in terms of scale and quality, to cater to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s visitors,” stated Niall McLoughlin, Senior Vice President of DAMAC Properties.</description></item><item><title>The Wanda Reign Wuhan has now opened its doors to guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-reign-wuhan-has-now-opened-its-doors-to-guests/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts debuted its luxury brand, Wanda Reign, with the opening of Wanda Reign Wuhan on March 29th. The brand emphasizes personalized service, exemplified by its &amp;ldquo;Imperial Welcome&amp;rdquo; which includes a Bentley service, and its &amp;ldquo;Reign Butler,&amp;rdquo; offering tailored assistance like schedule management and shopping guidance.
Source: Wanda Reign website
Situated near shopping and attractions in Wuhan&amp;rsquo;s East Lake Scenic Area, the hotel is conveniently located 30 minutes from Wuhan Tianhe airport and 15 minutes from the Wuhan high-speed railway station.</description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway will be celebrating their first birthday on March 31st</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Jen Orchardgateway website.
Hotel Jen, a new brand from the Shangri-La Group, is turning one year old on March 31, 2016. To mark this milestone, the two Singapore locations, Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway, are joining their sister hotels across nine Asian-Pacific cities for a grand birthday celebration. Each location will host unique events reflecting their city&amp;rsquo;s character, from a Mad Hatter&amp;rsquo;s tea party in Beijing to street art-inspired menus in Brisbane and a pool party in the Maldives.</description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India.</description></item><item><title>Experience Silom in a whole new way at the newly elevated ibis Styles Bangkok Silom</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</guid><description>Accor Hospitality Group has launched a stylish hotel, ibis Styles Bangkok Silom, in Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s lively Silom neighborhood. The hotel boasts a playful design inspired by Thai festivals and features a vibrant mural by Thai artist Tikkywow, reflecting Silom&amp;rsquo;s rich history.
Located near Sala Daeng BTS Skytrain and Silom MRT subway stations, the hotel provides convenient access to the city. Garth Simmons, CEO of Accor Southeast Asia, Japan &amp;amp; South Korea, expressed excitement for the opening, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s fit with Silom&amp;rsquo;s dynamic atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Accor has launched the Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp; Residences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</guid><description>Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences, the largest five-star hotel in Kolkata, is now open in the city’s New Town precinct.
Source: Accor Hotels. The Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences. The hotel has 347 guest rooms and suites. It is located near the airport and offers the city&amp;rsquo;s first serviced apartments. Guests can enjoy amenities such as a flat-screen LED TV, coffee and tea maker, in-room safe, refreshment center, and complimentary internet access.</description></item><item><title>The doors of Wanda Realm Fuyang are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts has expanded its portfolio with the opening of Wanda Realm Fuyang in the bustling business district of Fuyang, Anhui province, China. This addition marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 78th hotel, the 42nd under its ownership and management, and the 30th property under the Wanda Realm brand.
André Liu, General Manager of Wanda Realm Fuyang, highlighted the strategic importance of the location, stating, &amp;ldquo;Fuyang city is a rapidly developing hub with the largest population and fourth-largest size in Anhui province.</description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is preparing for Chinese New Year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Source: The Sanya EDITION.
In anticipation of the Chinese New Year, The Sanya EDITION presents two unique offerings that provide a genuine experience of Chinese culture.
Guests can immerse themselves in culture and history through The Sanya EDITION&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with the Forbidden City. This partnership features a temporary shop and exhibit highlighting fine arts and teas. Those with a passion for cuisine will enjoy the luxurious interpretations of Chinese dishes prepared by world-renowned Michelin-starred chefs, specially invited by The Sanya EDITION for the celebratory period.</description></item><item><title>The Urban Island promotion has been introduced by The Shilla Seoul</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</guid><description>With the arrival of summer, The Shilla Seoul presents Urban Island, a luxurious outdoor escape for guests. This all-inclusive retreat offers relaxation, a connection with nature, and delightful poolside service.
Reopened for the season, Urban Island welcomes guests to heated outdoor pools, a jacuzzi, and a rooftop garden against a scenic backdrop of Namsan Mountain and the Seoul skyline. Intimate cabanas nestled among lush greenery provide secluded havens.
The Urban Days room rate, available until June 30, 2019, starts from KRW 320,000 per night, excluding taxes and service charges, based on double occupancy.</description></item><item><title>The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae will be available starting in March 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:23:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</guid><description>Source: BWH Hotels. A standard room at the Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, which boasts contemporary rooms with a full range of amenities.
Starting March 13, 2024, BWH Hotels (BWH), the international hospitality group that includes WorldHotels, Best Western Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, and SureStay Hotels, will introduce a newly renovated and rebranded hotel.
The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, formerly the Best Western Nagoya, was one of the city&amp;rsquo;s most well-liked international mid-scale hotels.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food.</description></item><item><title>Club Carlson celebrates reaching one million members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s international hotel rewards program, Club Carlson, celebrated a milestone by awarding its one millionth member in the Asia Pacific region with one million Club Carlson Gold Points.
The lucky recipient, Rong Weiji, is a Sales and Marketing Division Manager at Santen Pharmaceutical. He became the millionth member upon checking in at the Radisson Blu Shanghai New World on August 22, 2014.
When asked about his hotel preferences, Mr. Weiji explained that he values brand recognition, quality, service, and location.</description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>Shangri-La and Singapore Airlines campaign offers packaged deals for ASEAN destinations and hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</guid><description>To commemorate the 50th anniversary of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts and Singapore Airlines have teamed up to launch a travel campaign called &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore.&amp;rdquo;
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjJuZK2IwJjPxRmvmq0DT-MS7ZPDl5douabN-yaRNI7kSFX1RAg5n8m2LHrg030pnJcr68_qz-IujmANOlf3NTbWGRF887wfkPbFQPAn168XsbqGeH8wP90CW2_M3muXU8ABKS6E9PwtOA/s1600/Shangri+La+SIA+ASEAN+is+More.JPG)
Source: Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts. Banner for the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore&amp;rdquo; campaign.
This campaign highlights Southeast Asia as a travel destination through special offers on curated leisure trips. Flight and hotel packages are available for various properties in Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Myanmar, and Thailand, including Shangri-La hotels and resorts, Hotel Jen properties, and Traders Hotel, Kuala Lumpur.</description></item><item><title>Preview the SG50 National Day promotion at Fairmont Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-the-sg50-national-day-promotion-at-fairmont-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:04:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-the-sg50-national-day-promotion-at-fairmont-singapore/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 50th anniversary, the Fairmont Singapore is offering a special package. This package provides guests with a prime location to view the fireworks display during the National Day preview parade on August 1st.
Ranging from S$400++ to S$750++ for a one-night stay, the package includes a premium room with views of Marina Bay and the Padang. Guests will also enjoy complimentary breakfast for two and a 24-hour self-parking coupon at Raffles City Shopping Centre.</description></item><item><title>Festive takeaways and buffets at Hotel Jen Tanglin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 06:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</guid><description>Hotel Jen Tanglin&amp;rsquo;s popular &amp;ldquo;Fully-Loaded&amp;rdquo; holiday takeaway meal is back. This offering features a whole roasted turkey, accompanied by all the fixings, conveniently packaged in a thermal bag. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to easily serve 10 to 12 guests.
According to Vathsala Subramaniam, General Manager of Hotel Jen Tanglin Singapore, they&amp;rsquo;ve crafted a special Asian roasted turkey using the &amp;ldquo;percik&amp;rdquo; style. This approach aims to blend tradition with a distinct Asian flavor. For those with bigger parties, ordering both the Western and Asian style turkeys ensures a diverse culinary experience for everyone.</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Canopy Power is making Southeast Asia more environmentally friendly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</guid><description>Source: Canopy Power. This image shows solar panels installed on the roof of a beachfront pavilion at Batu Batu resort. This installation was part of a larger project by Canopy Power.
Despite the economic downturn of 2020, Canopy Power has announced several accomplishments within the Asia Pacific region.
One such accomplishment was the completion of a renewable energy microgrid in the third quarter of 2020. This microgrid, located on Batu Batu, a sustainable island resort 16 km from Mersing, Malaysia, will allow the 22-villa resort to decrease its reliance on diesel and lower carbon emissions.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport reveals its fresh new appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has finished renovations, adding new rooms, a new Italian restaurant called Allora, another function room, an updated Club Lounge, and a revitalized fitness center.
The new design creates a calming oceanic atmosphere. Natural wood finishes on the furniture bring a feeling of warmth and comfort. This is enhanced by a color scheme of beach tones and ocean shades. Light gray couches, navy blue, and yellow accents contribute to a modern and welcoming feel.</description></item><item><title>Experience sustainable dining at Avani properties in Indochina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</guid><description>Image Credit: Avani. Plant-based coconut acai bowls are available at the Avani+ Samui Resort.
To create a healthier planet and promote sustainability, Avani Hotels has introduced a variety of eco-friendly and wellness-focused programs.
Avani&amp;rsquo;s flagship hotels in Thailand, Cambodia, and Laos are increasing their efforts to support nearby communities. They are accomplishing this by showcasing regional specialties and advocating for a decrease in reliance on imported goods. They have also implemented zero-waste programs, which include composting systems to handle all organic waste and on-site organic gardens to encourage self-sufficiency.</description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton introduces a new MICE venue in Hainan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and its DoubleTree by Hilton brand have opened a new resort in China called the DoubleTree Resort by Hilton Hainan - Qixianling Hot Spring. Situated within the Qixianling Hot Spring National Rainforest Park, the 254-room hotel is conveniently located 50 km from Lingshui Railway Station and 90 km from Sanya Phoenix International Airport.
John Greenleaf, Global Head of DoubleTree by Hilton, emphasized the brand&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding guest expectations.</description></item><item><title>Developing mutually beneficial solutions for both vendors and clients</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/developing-mutually-beneficial-solutions-for-both-vendors-and-clients/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/developing-mutually-beneficial-solutions-for-both-vendors-and-clients/</guid><description>Source: Bloem. A flower arrangement created to complement the color palette of the room at Park Hotel, Farrer Park and reflect the elegance of the setting.
Modern customers are more challenging than ever, but expecting them to change is futile. This was the message from Sukri Kadola, founder and CEO of creative consultancy Bloem, during his presentation titled &amp;ldquo;Confessions of a Perfectionist and how he tamed the Bridezilla and other impossible customers.</description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval.</description></item><item><title>The Drone Experience Program by JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp; Resorts is launching in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-drone-experience-program-by-jw-marriott-luxury-hotels-resorts-is-launching-in-china/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. View from a DJI drone.
JW Marriott Luxury Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and drone manufacturer DJI have partnered to introduce the brand&amp;rsquo;s first Drone Experience Program.
This program will allow guests to try out DJI&amp;rsquo;s drone technology and experience JW Marriott properties from a fresh perspective. They can also capture and share these unique moments with loved ones.
Launching on November 12, 2016, at JW Marriott Zhejiang Anji, the program will feature on-site sessions hosted by DJI experts.</description></item><item><title>You can have a Claire Luxton experience in Dubai this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. Visitors can enjoy a unique experience showcasing the work of artist Claire Luxton at select hotels, such as the InterContinental Dubai Festival City.
InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, part of IHG Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts Luxury and Lifestyle Collection, has partnered with British artist Claire Luxton to launch a series of immersive guest experiences. Available at various hotels, including the InterContinental Dubai Festival City, until mid-July, these experiences celebrate global travel and exploration through the artistic vision of Claire Luxton.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the new Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. This hotel, the Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel, aims to create a beach resort atmosphere.
The recently opened Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel is a 72-room boutique hotel located in the city center. Its convenient location provides guests with easy walking access to shopping, dining, and entertainment. Designed around a nautical theme, the hotel offers 60 Deluxe rooms, eight Baraquda Suites, and four Baraquda Grand Suites.</description></item><item><title>FHA2016 ends on a positive note</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</guid><description>Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), the leading trade show for Asia&amp;rsquo;s food and hospitality sector, concluded successfully.
Source: Singapore Exhibition Services. The showfloor at FHA2016.
Lindy Wee, Chief Executive of Singapore Exhibition Services, noted that as consumer preferences change, so do buyer demands. She expressed satisfaction that FHA remains a crucial platform for exhibitors to introduce innovative products and for global buyers to source them, effectively serving the food and hospitality sectors.
FHA featured a comprehensive range of products and services, from ingredients and equipment to hotel amenities and software.</description></item><item><title>This year, Concorde Hotel is arranging mooncakes in a vertical stack</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website.
For this Mid-Autumn Festival, Concorde Hotel Singapore is offering a selection of classic baked mooncakes. Customers can choose from traditional fillings like pure lotus paste, pure lotus with single or double yolks, and a less sweet white lotus with single yolk. Prices range from S$60 to S$68 for a box of four, including GST. Additionally, they offer a &amp;ldquo;Supreme Manju&amp;rdquo; flavor at S$64 for a box of four.</description></item><item><title>Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong is the inaugural Hyatt Place in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Hyatt and Boutique Corporation have announced the launch of the Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong in Phuket, Thailand. This 161-room beachfront property is the first Hyatt Place hotel in Southeast Asia. It embodies the Hyatt Place brand&amp;rsquo;s relaxed style and offers convenient amenities like complimentary Wi-Fi and 24/7 dining options.
&amp;ldquo;Thailand remains a crucial market for Hyatt, and Phuket is a top tourist spot in Southeast Asia with rising demand from both leisure and business travelers,&amp;rdquo; said David Udell, Group President – Asia Pacific, Hyatt Hotels Corporation.</description></item><item><title>CUBE Boutique Capsule Hotels has opened a new location in Kampong Glam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cube-boutique-capsule-hotels-has-opened-a-new-location-in-kampong-glam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 21:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cube-boutique-capsule-hotels-has-opened-a-new-location-in-kampong-glam/</guid><description>From left: Supriya Ghosh, Principal Consultant at CUBE as emcee; Tay; and Choa at the launch of the CUBE Boutique Capsule Hotel at Kampong Glam.
The new CUBE Boutique Capsule Hotel in Kampong Glam increases RB Hospitality&amp;rsquo;s inventory of affordable lodging options by 56 beds. Situated within revitalized historic districts, RB Hospitality specializes in providing budget-friendly accommodations in culturally significant areas. This opening complements their existing successful capsule hotel in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown.</description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality is introducing an upgraded hotel sleep experience for travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality
SilverNeedle Hospitality, a company focused on hospitality investment, management, and development, is launching the SilverNeedle DreamWeave Sleep System to enhance the sleep quality of its guests. This system will be implemented in all new hotels joining their network across midscale to luxury categories and will be gradually introduced to existing properties in those segments over time.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director and Group CEO of SilverNeedle Hospitality, emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving business travel by acknowledging the importance of sleep for their guests.</description></item><item><title>Bay Hotel Singapore will be offering a Ramadhan buffet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</guid><description>Source: Bay Hotel Singapore. The Ramadhan buffet spread.
Bay Hotel Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Rumah Rasa restaurant will offer a special Ramadan buffet every evening from May 16th to June 14th, 2018.
Leading the culinary team, Executive Chef Esa will showcase highlights like chick kut teh, a flavorful broth simmered overnight and accompanied by taupok (fried tofu puffs), dried mushrooms, and garlic, as part of the Ramadan Iftar Menu.
Another standout dish is ayam woku belanga, featuring marinated chicken infused with a special spice blend inspired by the Manado cuisine of North Sulawesi, Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Meliá Hotels opened at least 11 new locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</guid><description>Meliá Hotels International is adding at least 11 new hotels to its portfolio in 2015, including the Sol House Kuta Bali in Indonesia.
Source: Meliá Hotels website.
The recently opened 317-room Meliá Doha, which began welcoming guests in January, is the first Spanish hotel in Qatar. Located within Bin Samikh Tower, a prominent skyscraper in Doha&amp;rsquo;s West Bay district, the hotel enjoys a prime position on the Qatari coast.
The urban German brand, Innside by Meliá, is expanding its Middle Eastern presence with the upcoming Innside Dubai, a 125-room hotel.</description></item><item><title>Guests staying at the Hyatt hotel can enjoy complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels Corporation is demonstrating its commitment to enhancing the guest experience by providing free Wi-Fi at all of its hotels globally starting in February 2015. This initiative aims to provide guests with convenient connectivity regardless of how they booked their stay or their loyalty program status.
Guests will have access to complimentary Wi-Fi on an unlimited number of devices, including laptops and mobile phones, in both guest rooms and common areas of Hyatt-branded hotels.</description></item><item><title>Emirates provides appealing packages for stopovers in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s skyline, featuring the Burj Khalifa on the right.
Travelers flying with Emirates can benefit from appealing Dubai packages. These packages offer special prices at top-rated hotels and include access to entertainment options like city shows and attractions*.
Starting from US$49 per night, based on double occupancy, visitors can experience Dubai at the Rove Dubai Marina, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s vibrant waterfront area. This package also includes two tickets to Dubai Parks and Resorts, the region&amp;rsquo;s most extensive integrated theme park destination, encompassing MOTIONGATE Dubai, BOLLYWOOD PARKS Dubai, LEGOLAND Dubai, and LEGOLAND Water Park.</description></item><item><title>Dubai hotels are at the top of the list of top meeting hotels according to Cvent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 03:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</guid><description>Dubai, UAE, boasts seven out of the top 10 hotels in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region for Meetings, Incentives, Conferences, and Exhibitions (MICE), according to a new ranking. The list was released by Cvent, a leading technology provider for meetings, events, and hospitality.
These rankings are based on data from the Cvent Supplier Network (CSN), a comprehensive database with information on over 260,000 hotels, resorts, and event spaces in more than 175 countries.</description></item><item><title>The first Novotel hotel has opened in Cambodia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</guid><description>Source: Novotel Hotels, Suites &amp;amp; Resorts. The Novotel Phnom Penh BKK 1.
Accor brand, Novotel Hotels, Suites &amp;amp; Resorts, has opened its newest location, the Novotel Phnom Penh BKK 1, in Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
This brand-new hotel features a contemporary design, a welcoming social space, and diverse dining and wellness options. Its strategic location provides easy access to the bustling Bassac Lane and Langka Lane neighborhoods, as well as landmarks such as the Independence Monument and Wat Langka, one of the city&amp;rsquo;s oldest pagodas.</description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon, the Korean fine-dining restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, has been awarded three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. Nine delicacies at La Yeon.
During the first-ever Michelin Guide Seoul launch in 2017, held at The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Dynasty Hall, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s traditional Korean fine-dining establishment, La Yeon, was granted a coveted three-star Michelin rating. Recognized for its authentic flavors, exceptional service, inviting atmosphere, and well-paired drinks, La Yeon stands as the sole Seoul restaurant within a hospitality group to achieve this three-star distinction.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches.</description></item><item><title>Guests at Emaar can customize their experience using the latest apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-emaar-can-customize-their-experience-using-the-latest-apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 10:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-emaar-can-customize-their-experience-using-the-latest-apps/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Emaar introduces custom-designed apps, linked with their internal systems, to improve the customer experience.
• Apps for Address Hotels + Resorts, Vida Hotels and Resorts, Palace Downtown, and Manzil Downtown are now available. These apps are personalized based on guest profiles and preferences. The Rove Hotels App will be launched soon.
• The apps connect with backend systems, providing management teams with important real-time data to improve the guest experience.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels expands its high-end collection in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-expands-its-high-end-collection-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 06:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-expands-its-high-end-collection-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>AccorHotels, a major player in the travel and hospitality industry, is expanding its luxury presence in the Asia Pacific region with multiple high-end hotel openings scheduled in the coming months. This initiative will primarily involve the expansion of their Sofitel and Pullman brands, which are part of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; luxury and upscale portfolio. Other prestigious brands in this collection include Raffles Hotel, Fairmont, MGallery by Sofitel, Swissôtel, and Grand Mercure.
These openings follow the successful August debut of the Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara, a 312-room establishment situated in the heart of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s capital city.</description></item><item><title>Mandarin Orchard and Marina Mandarin in Singapore are now providing free local smartphone services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 20:54:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</guid><description>The Mandarin Orchard Singapore and Marina Mandarin Singapore have added a convenient amenity to all guestrooms: &amp;ldquo;handy,&amp;rdquo; a smartphone solution. This provides registered guests with complimentary unlimited 4G data, local and international calls, online city guides, and ticket booking services for Singapore attractions. Both hotels are managed by Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
With handy now available in all 1,077 rooms at Mandarin Orchard Singapore and 575 rooms at Marina Mandarin Singapore, guests can stay connected while exploring Singapore using their own personalized smartphone outside the hotel.</description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp; Spa is offering meeting packages for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa. Executive team members at Hyatt Regegncy Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa will help event planners make any meeting a success.
Located on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Hoi An coastline and close to Danang, the Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa has announced new meeting packages for 2017.
The resort offers a wide range of event and meeting spaces, both indoors and outdoors on the beachfront. These venues can accommodate up to 250 people.</description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions.</description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments.</description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings.</description></item><item><title>Dusit Thani Bangkok will reopen in September 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</guid><description>Dusit Hotels and Resorts, a prominent Thai hotel and property development company, will reopen the famous Dusit Thani Bangkok on September 27, 2024, as a key component of Dusit Central Park.
Starting May 1, 2024, reservations for the new Dusit Thani Bangkok can be made through their website, with early birds receiving a US$75 nightly credit for dining and spa treatments, among other benefits. Rates begin at US$330++ per night. Bookings made by October 31, 2024, for stays between September 27, 2024, and March 31, 2025, are eligible for this promotion.</description></item><item><title>Everything is going well at PARKROYAL on Beach Road</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everything-is-going-well-at-parkroyal-on-beach-road/</guid><description>Beginning January 16, 2017, PARKROYAL on Beach Road will be offering a new take on Lunar New Year celebrations as Executive Chef Ken Ang introduces his culinary perspective to the dishes at Plaza Brasserie, their all-day dining restaurant.
Known for his mastery of traditional Cantonese roasting methods, Executive Chef Ang will be presenting his version of the lucky facai yusheng (发财鱼生, also called lohei), enhanced with additions like crispy salmon and chicken skin.</description></item><item><title>This year, Teardrop Hotels is introducing three new tea plantation experiences in Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Teardrop Hotels is expanding its portfolio in 2018 with the addition of three renovated tea planters&amp;rsquo; houses: Goatfell, Nine Skies, and Pekoe House. These vintage managers&amp;rsquo; bungalows, located along the tea country route, will offer a modern take on traditional tea plantation accommodations.
Opening in April 2018, Goatfell is a former superintendent’s residence situated on a working tea estate above Nuwara Eliya. This four-bedroom main house, with two additional standalone chalets, boasts living and dining rooms and a swimming pool.</description></item><item><title>The Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo has officially opened its doors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-marunouchi-tokyo-has-officially-opened-its-doors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-marunouchi-tokyo-has-officially-opened-its-doors/</guid><description>Source: The Ascott Limited. The lobby, Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo.
CapitaLand&amp;rsquo;s serviced residence branch, The Ascott Limited, opened its first high-end serviced residence in Japan on March 30, 2017, under its top brand, Ascott The Residence.
The 130-unit Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo is in the desirable Marunouchi-Otemachi district. It&amp;rsquo;s part of a mixed-use development with offices and close to notable attractions like the Imperial Palace East Gardens and the Ginza area. The residence provides convenient access to Otemachi Station, a major Tokyo subway hub served by five lines, with connections to the Shinkansen bullet train available from nearby Tokyo Station.</description></item><item><title>Sofitel Kunming provides convenient access to the city center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 07:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</guid><description>Sofitel, the luxury hotel brand under AccorHotels, has launched its newest property, Sofitel Kunming. Located in the city center, it&amp;rsquo;s the only international luxury hotel in Kunming.
Situated in Kunming&amp;rsquo;s central business district, the 400-room hotel spans the 27th to 52nd floors. It showcases a blend of French elegance and art de vivre with touches of Yunnan&amp;rsquo;s vibrant ethnic cultures and customs.
&amp;ldquo;The debut of Sofitel Kunming signifies a period of rapid growth for AccorHotels in China, as we continue to solidify our dedication to delivering world-renowned, refined French hospitality to discerning Chinese travelers,&amp;rdquo; shared Paul Richardson, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China.</description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality has introduced its second Sage Hotel in Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality.
SilverNeedle Hospitality, based in Singapore, is expanding its upscale Sage Hotel brand in Perth, Western Australia, with a second location. This announcement comes just weeks after the brand launched with a hotel in Brisbane.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated that Sage Hotels are designed for a specific type of business traveler: one who wants a consistent and straightforward experience while working in new cities.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person.</description></item><item><title>Experience the unique Kampong culinary specials at the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>This June, the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur in Malaysia is offering a special deal for gatherings with colleagues, business contacts, and potential clients. The promotion is valid in their newly renovated ballrooms and private function rooms.
Source: Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur website.
For every ten paying guests, one person can attend for free. The Selera Kampong package is priced at RM155 nett per adult, while the Kampong Boys Special is RM172 nett per adult.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the successful first year of Hyatt Regency Suzhou with our Anniversary Meeting Package</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Suzhou.
The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is commemorating its first anniversary with various special offers as a thank you to its loyal and valued guests for their support throughout the year.
Having opened its doors on August 24, 2014, in the Suzhou Industrial Park (SIP), the conveniently located Hyatt Regency Suzhou boasts 355 rooms and suites. Amenities include a Regency Club, five dining options, and over 15,000 square feet of space for events.</description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives.</description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds.</description></item><item><title>Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li blends traditional shikumen architecture with modern French elegance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</guid><description>Source: Capella Shanghai website. Villa entrance.
Located in Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French Concession, the Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li, offers a journey back to the city&amp;rsquo;s early 20th-century charm. Situated within the Jian Ye Li estate, the property is a rare surviving example of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;shikumen&amp;rdquo; townhouses, characterized by their three-story brick construction and stone accents.
The goal was to develop an ultra-luxury experience while meticulously preserving the site&amp;rsquo;s historical character. Jaya Interior Design and BLINK Design Group drew inspiration from Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s past, seamlessly integrating traditional Chinese elements with French elegance.</description></item><item><title>The Autograph Collection is ready to make its first appearance in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</guid><description>Australian companies have a new, upscale event location. Pier One Sydney Harbour is joining the Autograph Collection, a curated group of almost 60 unique hotels globally. This harborside hotel provides a picturesque setting for meetings and events, featuring eight meeting rooms with expansive water views.
Source: Marriott International. From Sydney to San Diego - Autograph Collection set to debut in three new world class destinations, including Pier One Sydney Harbour in Sydney, Australia.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life.</description></item><item><title>The Ritz-Carlton is now open in Fukuoka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-is-now-open-in-fukuoka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 06:57:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-is-now-open-in-fukuoka/</guid><description>Source: The Ritz-Carlton. Facade, The Ritz-Carlton, Fukuoka.
The Ritz-Carlton, Fukuoka, the newest addition to Marriott Bonvoy&amp;rsquo;s 31 hotel brands, has opened its doors on Japan&amp;rsquo;s Kyushu island. This hotel aims to blend the brand&amp;rsquo;s signature service and modern design with Fukuoka&amp;rsquo;s unique blend of history, tradition, culinary richness, and burgeoning startup culture.
According to Tina Edmundson, President of Luxury for Marriott International, the opening marks the brand&amp;rsquo;s seventh hotel in Japan and solidifies its presence in a new and growing market.</description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base.</description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Shanghai is set to make its debut in late 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</guid><description>Source: HKRI. The Sukhothai Shanghai.
HKR International will soon expand its Sukhothai Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts portfolio with a second hotel – The Sukhothai Shanghai. This new addition, situated in the Nanjing Road West central business district, is set to launch in late 2017.
Designed by Neri &amp;amp; Hu, The Sukhothai Shanghai is a contemporary luxury boutique hotel. It offers 168 guest rooms and 33 suites, ranging from 44 to 172 square meters in size.</description></item><item><title>Experience the Peranakan Food Festival at Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>The Peranakan* Food Festival is making a comeback at the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy! The hotel is bringing back this popular food festival with new additions to the menu, such as ayam masak rebung lemak (chicken with bamboo shoots in spicy gravy). Returning favorites include bubur cha cha (tapioca in coconut milk) and much more.
Guests can explore booths showcasing Peranakan heritage at the Feast@East Buffet Restaurant.
From June 10th to 19th, enjoy a variety of seafood at Feast@East Buffet Restaurant, featuring Chilean blue mussels, spanner crabs, and other crustacean favorites.</description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be larger and improved in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</guid><description>Ting speaking at a media preview for FHA.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), a major food and hospitality trade show in Asia, is approaching its 40th anniversary of serving the industry&amp;rsquo;s needs.
Since its 1978 inception, FHA has attracted a predominantly international exhibitor base (over 80%), underscoring its global reach. FHA provides a platform for showcasing innovative products, technologies, and solutions from around the world, facilitating connections and business opportunities for trade buyers and sellers.</description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes.</description></item><item><title>Coral Beirut Al Hamra now offers two additional Ambassador Suites as part of its room options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</guid><description>The Coral Beirut Al Hamra Hotel recently introduced a new suite category featuring expansive rooftop terraces with outdoor seating areas. Situated on the 11th floor, the 87 square meter Ambassador Suites offer fully equipped kitchens, large living rooms, and luxurious bathrooms, complete with high-end amenities.
Hartmut Grauel, General Manager of the hotel, stated that these new suites cater to the preferences of discerning travelers. He noted a consistent demand for spacious accommodations akin to full-size apartments, complete with kitchens and living rooms.</description></item><item><title>Group discounts are available for the iftar buffet at Coral Beach Resort Sharjah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 12:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</guid><description>Source: Coral Beach Resort Sharjah website.
The Coral Beach Resort Sharjah, having just finished a full update of its rooms and amenities, is offering an iftar buffet at its Al Bahar Restaurant. The buffet will feature a variety of traditional Arabic and international dishes, with options like mixed grills, shawarma, hot and cold mezze, stews and biryani, in addition to soups, salads, snacks, and customary Ramadan beverages.
Jean Pierre Simon, the Regional General Manager for Northern Emirates at Coral Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, highlighted Al Bahar restaurant as the perfect location for gatherings to break the fast, suggesting guests round off their dining experience with classic Ramadan sweets like the ever-popular umm Ali and mouhalabia.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing.</description></item><item><title>The Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong and Vistajet provide a rare and unique experience called Once in a Blue Moon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</guid><description>VistaJet, a prominent business aviation company, has partnered with the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong to create the &amp;ldquo;Once in a Blue Moon&amp;rdquo; experience. This exclusive offer celebrates the Mid-Autumn Festival with a luxurious private jet journey featuring an in-flight menu designed by Chef Wong, the Executive Chinese Chef of the Michelin-starred Man Wah restaurant at the Mandarin Oriental.
Available from September 15 to October 15, 2020, this unique offering features a customized private jet experience departing from Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson hosts its first charity event of the year-end</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</guid><description>Source: Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson. The poolside.
Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson will host its first charity event with the Friends of The Disabled Society (FDS) as part of their year-end festivities.
The public can purchase various handicrafts and accessories on November 17, 2016, at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s lounge area and poolside. All proceeds will go to FDS. The hotel will also host a dinner for FDS on December 3, 2016, as part of the holiday celebrations.</description></item><item><title>Hyatt Regency is back in Sydney and is now focusing on positioning the hotel for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels announced that a hotel situated at 161 Sussex Street, previously operating under the Four Points by Sheraton brand, will transition to Hyatt Regency Sydney starting November 30, 2016. This change signifies the return of the Hyatt Regency brand to Sydney. The company is strategically positioning the Hyatt Regency Sydney as a prime location for conferences.
The introduction of Hyatt Regency Sydney aligns with the growing demand for business, meetings, incentives, conferences and exhibitions (MICE), as well as leisure travel within the Australian market.</description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities.</description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream.</description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport is offering mooncakes in a suitcase</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has launched its 2016 mooncake collection, featuring classic baked and contemporary snowskin varieties. These halal-certified treats are packaged in a stylish metal suitcase, making them a great gift for colleagues or loved ones.
For those who prefer a traditional taste, baked mooncakes are available in three flavors: White Lotus Paste with Double Egg Yolk, White Lotus Paste with Single Egg Yolk, and White Lotus Paste with Melon Seeds.</description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high.</description></item><item><title>The Ritz-Carlton in Amman makes its first appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-in-amman-makes-its-first-appearance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 04:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-in-amman-makes-its-first-appearance/</guid><description>Marriott Bonvoy&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, The Ritz-Carlton, has opened a new hotel in Amman, Jordan, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s well-regarded Fifth Circle. The 20-story hotel boasts 228 rooms, with offerings ranging from standard guest rooms to 34 suites.
Donna McNamara, Vice President and Global Brand Leader for The Ritz-Carlton, expressed the brand&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm, stating their goal is to provide exceptional service and unique experiences in captivating destinations worldwide. She emphasized that The Ritz-Carlton, Amman, aims to immerse guests in luxury, creating memorable experiences and showcasing the city&amp;rsquo;s allure.</description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Hotels partners with Deezer to create a musical experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
Ibis Hotels, a budget-friendly option within the Accor group, has launched a new campaign in Australia. Through a partnership with Deezer, a global music streaming platform, guests can now immerse themselves in the world of music.
This collaboration gives guests staying at ibis, ibis Styles, and ibis Budget hotels access to ibis PLAY, a dedicated microsite. This platform offers a variety of music-centric content, including regularly updated local concert listings, curated playlists, music news, artist interviews, photo galleries, exclusive ibis content, and a spotlight on Australian live acts.</description></item><item><title>Sunway's Resort Cafe provides a range of dining options from breakfast to dinner, perfect for business meetings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</guid><description>Source: Sunway.
The recently opened Resort Cafe, situated on the lobby level of the luxurious Sunway Resort Hotel and Spa, accommodates 362 guests and showcases the diverse culinary heritage of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Malay, Chinese, and Indian populations.
Spanning 17,588 square feet, the restaurant presents eight distinct culinary themes: the impressive Monumental Fruit and Salad Towers, Malay Archipelago (featuring dishes from Malaysia, Singapore, and Indonesia), Indo-Chine (showcasing cuisine from Thailand and Vietnam), Oriental Far East (highlighting dishes from Japan, Korea, and China), Spices of India, Mirage of the Gulf (offering dishes from the Middle East), Best from the West (featuring Western comfort food, grills, rotisserie, and churrasco), and a dedicated dessert section.</description></item><item><title>The KL Journal provides a unique boutique option for accommodations in Kuala Lumpur, as an alternative to traditional hotel chains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 01:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</guid><description>Source: The KL Journal. This hotel blends industrial design, diverse local touches, and vintage pieces to create a stylishly modern yet retro atmosphere.
Located near Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s primary shopping and entertainment area, the Kuala Lumpur Journal (KL Journal) is a boutique hotel designed for the modern traveler seeking an alternative to large chains. It offers all the necessary modern amenities while retaining a unique sense of style and personality.</description></item><item><title>Cachet Hotel Group unveils the fresh appearance of URBN Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</guid><description>The Cachet Hotel Group (CHG) has revamped its stylish URBN Hotel in Shanghai, a former warehouse. Led by CHG&amp;rsquo;s renowned fashion designer, Jay Godfrey, the updated interiors offer guests a modern, zen-like ambiance. The use of recycled and reclaimed wood materials adds a natural touch, further enhanced by the neutral color scheme.
Source: CHG. The Jay Godfrey Courtyard Suite.
Photo - http://photos.prnasia.com/prnh/20140911/0861406560
The URBN Shanghai boasts a unique Jay Godfrey-designed suite.</description></item><item><title>The opening date for Six Senses Kaplankaya is May 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</guid><description>![Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEg6jRBaFFB8FLc8GWUouGmkRpZIrrVyWlKYCZ1pRPjPgJhTMuDR2tOLPpVhKP-eWibrLG1ZGt42dmOjjJoSeU_SwAl_HlA8BkuquNMt_lQ5P90CQTn7bDyCDPtU74R2ApXfx4oJxuNUaZo/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;Six Senses hotel in Turkey opens May 1.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.
The Six Senses Kaplankaya resort, which became part of Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas on May 1, 2017, commences its new season on May 1, 2018. The property now aligns with Six Senses&amp;rsquo; standards of design, sustainability, and wellness, offering a distinct guest experience focused on achieving equilibrium and well-being by engaging all the senses.</description></item><item><title>Embark on an artistic adventure with Hotel Indigo Singapore Katong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/embark-on-an-artistic-adventure-with-hotel-indigo-singapore-katong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/embark-on-an-artistic-adventure-with-hotel-indigo-singapore-katong/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Indigo Singapore Katong website. The rooms showcase artwork by Don Low, including this mural featuring durians.
Hotel Indigo encourages guests to embark on a journey of artistic discovery with its #staysurprised campaign. Explore some of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s most impressive street art, all within a 15-minute radius of the Katong neighborhood.
The Hotel Indigo Singapore Katong boasts 131 rooms adorned with murals created by local urban artist Don Low. His work highlights Singapore&amp;rsquo;s passion for traditional cuisine.</description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www.</description></item><item><title>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental Hong Kong has become more environmentally friendly than ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</guid><description>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong is implementing environmentally friendly practices to offer guests sustainable luxury, including producing its own eco-friendly water and starting a rooftop garden.
The hotel is the first in Hong Kong to work with Nordaq FRESH, a Swedish company, to provide filtered and purified water in reusable glass bottles. This system reduces plastic waste and carbon emissions associated with traditional bottled water. Guests can also refill BPA-free bottles at the hotel.</description></item><item><title>Details of the farewell accommodation package at The Excelsior, Hong Kong are provided below</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 13:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</guid><description>To commemorate its rich history, The Excelsior, Hong Kong is offering a special &amp;ldquo;Fond Farewell Room Package&amp;rdquo; for guests to experience the hotel one last time before its closure on March 31, 2019. Guests who book this package will also be invited to a special farewell reception in the hotel lobby.
Three package options are available, each highlighting the four-star hotel&amp;rsquo;s renowned Michelin-star cuisine and its prime location on the Victoria Harbour waterfront for the past 45 years.</description></item><item><title>Five Asian hotels are ranked in the top 25 of Expedia Insiders' Select 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</guid><description>Expedia unveiled its 2014 Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select list in early July. This list highlights the best hotels globally, as determined by almost two million verified customer reviews and Expedia&amp;rsquo;s own travel experts.
Source: Blue Karma Resort website.
Out of over 290,000 bookable properties on Expedia&amp;rsquo;s global websites, 650 hotels received the Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select designation in 2014.
Here are a few of the top 25 hotels from this year&amp;rsquo;s list:
2. Blue Karma Resort - Seminyak, Bali</description></item><item><title>Experience the Singapore F1 promotion at BIG Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-singapore-f1-promotion-at-big-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 06:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-singapore-f1-promotion-at-big-hotel/</guid><description>Source: BIG Hotel.
Travelers can take advantage of a Formula One promotion at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s BIG Hotel. Bookings made by September 12th will receive a 10% discount on room rates, complimentary Wi-Fi throughout their stay, and access to free on-demand movies. This offer is valid for stays during the F1 night race in Singapore, from September 18th to 21st.
The hotel is conveniently situated on Middle Road, a short distance from Bras Basah station.</description></item><item><title>Indulge in a luxurious 20 Carat Gold Escape with JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay and Maserati</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 14:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay.
The lobby lounge.
Upon arrival at the sports university-themed JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, guests will be greeted with a luxurious Maserati transfer*. Building on the success of the resort&amp;rsquo;s previous collaboration showcasing DMC&amp;rsquo;s SS2017 womenswear collection, this partnership with Maserati aims to captivate those passionate about sports and automobiles.
Ty Collins, General Manager at JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, states, &amp;ldquo;This collaboration amplifies the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to offering design-focused experiences.</description></item><item><title>Observe the fireworks display on February 11 at the Regent Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</guid><description>For the Lunar New Year, The Regent Hong Kong offers various culinary experiences:
Hong Kong Cuisine 1983
Celebrate with symbolic à la carte dishes (HK$468 to HK$980) like Lohei (HK$580) for prosperity, prawns in salted egg yolk (HK$580) for wealth, and braised Wagyu beef cheek (HK$980) for strength. Their HK$438 Good Fortune Turnip Cake Gift Box contains two 800g turnip cakes, one traditional and one smoked with tea leaves, sugarcane, imperatae, and brown sugar.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas in Vietnam have been recognized with accolades from TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The master bedroom of an oceanfront three-bedroom villa at Six Senses Con Dao, Vietnam.
TripAdvisor, a leading travel platform, has revealed its highest-rated properties for the fourteenth consecutive year. These rankings are determined by analyzing user reviews and feedback from travelers globally over the past year. Three properties - Evason Ana Mandara, Six Senses Ninh Van Bay, and Six Senses Con Dao - have earned the prestigious Traveler’s Choice award, signifying TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s highest honor.</description></item><item><title>Travellers are pleased to engage with hotels on social media</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</guid><description>A 2014 study by Accorhotels called the Social Media Monitor showed that hotels have a significant opportunity to connect with travelers on social media. In the Asia Pacific region, almost half of travelers follow hotel brands, more than airlines or other travel-related businesses. This trend is especially strong among travelers from China and Indonesia, as well as those between 25 and 44 years old.
Interestingly, in countries with prominent airlines such as Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, and Japan, airlines are followed most on social media.</description></item><item><title>Improve your sleep with the Sleep with Six Senses program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Better sleep with the new Sleep with Six Senses programme.
Six Senses partnered with Sleep Doctor Dr. Michael Breus to launch its improved sleep standard called Sleep With Six Senses. Currently, five resorts offer this standard, with complete implementation across all locations expected by mid-2017. All future resorts will feature this program from their opening day.
The experience begins with a pre-arrival online questionnaire. This allows a designated Sleep Ambassador to understand the guest&amp;rsquo;s relationship with sleep and tailor the room accordingly.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!</description></item><item><title>Join us at the Pullman Jakarta Indonesia to celebrate the holy month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>The Pullman Jakarta Indonesia hotel has a special offer for corporate groups during Ramadan. For groups of 50 or more, they offer a deluxe Iftar (breaking the fast) package for Rp450,000 per person. This package features a selection of traditional Iftar snacks and drinks, along with an Indonesian buffet.
To make a reservation or get more details, you can contact Ms. Sarat via email at H8491-SM4@accor.com or by phone at +62 21 3192 1111.</description></item><item><title>DAMAC Properties has revealed plans for three new serviced hotels in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 05:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</guid><description>High-end real estate company DAMAC Properties is expanding its presence in the hospitality sector with the addition of three new serviced hotels in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area.
Two of these hotels, Cour Jardin and Capital Bay, are scheduled to open within the next few months, while Canal Views is already operational and receiving guests. This initiative is part of DAMAC Properties&amp;rsquo; goal to become the leading provider of serviced hotel apartments in the Middle East by 2018.</description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality introduces the new Sage Hotel brand, catering specifically to upscale business travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</guid><description>SilverNeedle Hospitality, headquartered in Singapore, has introduced a new upscale hotel brand, Sage Hotel, tailored for business travelers. The first Sage Hotel will be located in Brisbane, Australia.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated, &amp;ldquo;We recognize a significant group of business travelers seeking a consistent and straightforward experience while working in unfamiliar cities.&amp;rdquo; He added, &amp;ldquo;Sage Hotel is designed to meet their needs and complements our existing portfolio of six brands.</description></item><item><title>The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant is launching a fresh new menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant, found within the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, has introduced a new menu to coincide with the arrival of their new head chef, Victor. The dishes are meant to complement the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s modern Eastern aesthetic and embody the Chinese principle of &amp;ldquo;家味,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;flavors of home.&amp;rdquo;
The menu features popular Eastern dishes like Chef&amp;rsquo;s superior fish maw served with seafood soup, and fresh prawns accompanied by two special sauces.</description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is offering a promotion during Golden Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</guid><description>The Sanya EDITION hotel is offering a special promotion for travelers visiting China during Golden Week, which falls on October 1st to 7th.
To celebrate, the hotel is hosting guest chef Matthew David Ona from Roof 325 Restaurant and Bar in Shanghai. Chef Ona, known for his culinary expertise at one of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s top dining destinations, will be at The Jade Egret restaurant from October 1st to 3rd. He has designed special steak and seafood tasting menus for the occasion.</description></item><item><title>Amara Signature Shanghai has been softly launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 02:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</guid><description>![Source: Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. The Amara Signature Shanghai.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgAfBJYJW9dykG8i4PiZBEX_SuEbBpNrdOHxK7OgjVsJ6TA5Nt3-In_JgJHn8Ca19sRF5j5K5W-upNOpJ4qsG-tQA9WfYeGX2oQViKTULwU3f0PwufZs6HVNmCPk3UB45hfYmL_9NVDfxE/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;The Amara Signature Shanghai is the first Amara Signature in China.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. The Amara Signature Shanghai.
The Amara Signature Shanghai, a new luxury hotel under Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has recently held its soft opening.
This 30-story, five-star hotel showcases a sleek, all-glass exterior and sits at the crossroads of Changshou Road and Jiaozhou Road in Shanghai, China.</description></item><item><title>Experience an unexpected Christmas at Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel in Singapore has designed a Christmas menu featuring new versions of classic dishes, playful food presentations, and delightful surprises. These festive meals and unique takeaway options aim to make holiday celebrations even more memorable.
This year&amp;rsquo;s new gourmet takeaway options center around turkey with unique Asian flavors for savory dishes and chocolate-focused sweet treats.
Source: Goodwood Park Hotel. The 12 Treasures turkey is available for takeaways.
12 Treasures Turkey | S$268, serves eight to 10 people - New for 2017</description></item><item><title>Robots have been introduced to the teams at Hotel Jen in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</guid><description>Hotel Jen is pioneering the use of Savioke&amp;rsquo;s Relay robots in Asian hotels. The robots, Jeno and Jena, will be stationed at Hotel Jen Orchardgateway and Tanglin Singapore, respectively. They will handle deliveries of amenities and local food selections from the in-room dining menu.
Cetin Sekercioglu, Executive VP of Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts, stated that Hotel Jen prioritizes technology that can improve efficiency and guest experiences. He believes that the robots will be valuable additions to the team and align with Hotel Jen&amp;rsquo;s playful and surprising brand identity.</description></item><item><title>Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 now accepts e-signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</guid><description>Source: Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 website.
The Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 has introduced a paperless check-in experience featuring electronic signatures. This system aims to eliminate the need for printed documents and expedite the arrival process for guests. Aloft Bangkok claims to be the first hotel within the Starwood brand to offer this service.
This innovative approach streamlines the check-in procedure by presenting all reservation details on a tablet.</description></item><item><title>The Marina Mandarin Singapore welcomes the arrival of hairy crabs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</guid><description>Peach Blossoms, the renowned Cantonese restaurant located on the 5th level of Marina Mandarin Singapore, is now offering a seasonal delicacy flown in from Shanghai, China: hairy crabs.
Also at the Marina Mandarin, on the 4th level, the AquaMarine buffet restaurant is spotlighting seafood until October 29th.
Source: Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
AquaMarine features an array of Asian dishes, including Vietnamese Braised Fish in Clay Pot, Thai Curry Mud Crab, authentic Filipino Beef Adobo, fresh Cambodian Fish Curry, and many more.</description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan.</description></item><item><title>Toyo Koda will enhance the menus at Le Passage Mohkan Shan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</guid><description>Source: Le Passage Mohkan Shan website.
Le Passage Mohkan Shan, a French-style hotel and restaurant nestled in its own private tea plantation at the base of Moganshan* mountain in China, has appointed Toyo Koda as its new head chef. This strategic hire emphasizes the hotel&amp;rsquo;s aim to become a premier culinary destination in Asia.
Chef Toyo, previously recognized as one of Asia&amp;rsquo;s top chefs by the San Pellegrino Restaurant Awards in 2013 for his role at Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French restaurant Franck, is poised to transform the hotel&amp;rsquo;s culinary offerings.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce.</description></item><item><title>The Presidential Villa is now available at Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:01:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort.
The Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort is located near Dujiangyan, a UNESCO World Heritage &amp;amp; Natural Cultural site known as the home of giant pandas.
Inspired by the region&amp;rsquo;s history as the birthplace of Taoism, Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain introduces a new Presidential Villa. This villa embodies Taoist principles of living in harmony with nature, offering a space for reconnection and self-discovery.</description></item></channel></rss>