<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fulfilment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fulfilment/</link><description>Recent content in Fulfilment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 23:58:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fulfilment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aramex logistics support is available to Shopmatic merchants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 23:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</guid><description>Shopmatic, a Singapore-based e-commerce software as a service (SaaS) provider, has partnered with Aramex, a global logistics and transportation company. This partnership aims to provide online merchants with efficient and secure delivery options.
Shopmatic offers a comprehensive, commission-free e-commerce platform for businesses to establish and manage their online presence. By integrating with Aramex&amp;rsquo;s services, Shopmatic strengthens its position as a one-stop solution for anyone looking to sell online.
Anurag Avula, CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Shopmatic Group, highlights the significant growth potential of online shopping in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zap Delivery in Singapore guarantees fast and reliable couriered deliveries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</guid><description>Source: Zap Delivery.
Zap Delivery, an on-demand courier service, promises quick, safe, and dependable deliveries of packages and documents within Singapore in two hours or less using their new mobile app. This app utilizes advanced authentication and real-time tracking to provide peace of mind for those awaiting deliveries.
“We’ve experienced our fair share of delivery issues, so we created a user-friendly app that fosters trust,&amp;quot; explained Michael Tan, Zap Delivery Co-founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singpost will collaborate with Shippit on final delivery services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</guid><description>Shippit has partnered with Singapore Post (SingPost) to offer their delivery services and special negotiated rates on its platform. This collaboration allows small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to deliver parcels throughout Singapore.
This partnership provides SMEs on Shippit&amp;rsquo;s platform with more e-commerce fulfillment options. They can now offer customers island-wide parcel collection through SingPost&amp;rsquo;s POPStation network. Additionally, Shippit will provide access to SingPost&amp;rsquo;s Speedpost Express Service and discounted, pre-negotiated rates for next-day and economy deliveries—services previously exclusive to larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia and Pos Malaysia are working together for order fulfillment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</guid><description>Shopee Malaysia has partnered with Pos Malaysia, the national courier service, to offer free shipping to all sellers on its platform.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace with a strong regional presence of over 12 million users, operates as a free online customer-to-customer (C2C) platform. Launched in December 2015, Shopee aims to empower both individual and business entrepreneurs to conduct secure buying and selling transactions on their mobile devices. In Malaysia alone, Shopee&amp;rsquo;s app has been downloaded over a million times within a six-month timeframe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL eCommerce has launched a new Fulfillment Center in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</guid><description>DHL eCommerce, a branch of the logistics giant Deutsche Post DHL Group, has opened a Fulfillment Center in Sydney, Australia. The new center will help the company meet the demands of Australia&amp;rsquo;s rapidly growing number of online shoppers buying goods from overseas.
Damien Sheehan, Managing Director for DHL eCommerce in Australia, highlighted the significance of Australian online shoppers, stating, “Australian shoppers are some of the most frequent buyers from international sellers online, and their influence will only grow as cross-border e-commerce continues to expand at an average rate of 29% annually through 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InPost has officially started its operations in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: InPost.
InPost, a global leader in automated parcel locker networks, has expanded its services to Malaysia. The launch was accompanied by a roadshow, themed &amp;ldquo;Malaysia E-commerce Day (MED) 2015,&amp;rdquo; aimed at raising awareness about the latest advancements in e-commerce, e-payments, and logistics.
According to InPost Malaysia Managing Director Rosland Mohd Jannes, the initiative seeks to connect with businesses and individuals, boosting consumer confidence in online shopping and alleviating delivery-related anxieties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopmatic has partnered with Easyship to make it easier for merchants to deliver their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</guid><description>Source: Shopmatic. Shopmatic co-founders from left: Kris Chen,
Anurag Avula, and Yen Ti Lim. Shopmatic, the Singapore-based e-commerce company, has teamed up with Easyship, a comprehensive shipping platform for global e-commerce. This partnership will enable Shopmatic merchants to streamline product delivery and expand their businesses internationally.
Easyship offers integrated shipping services from over 100 providers, including DHL, FedEx, and UPS. It allows for immediate order shipping with discounts of up to 70%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>