<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expulsion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expulsion/</link><description>Recent content in Expulsion on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expulsion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to deport and prohibit unemployed EU citizens from returning?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Germany&amp;rsquo;s recent exploration of expelling unemployed EU citizens has sparked interest among critics of EU free movement in the UK. As this topic gains traction, it&amp;rsquo;s timely to clarify the circumstances under which EU citizens can be expelled.
While the EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive empowers Member States to expel citizens for reasons related to public policy, security, or health, it explicitly prohibits using these grounds for economic reasons. Consequently, the rules for expelling unemployed EU citizens lie elsewhere within the Directive.</description></item><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections.</description></item><item><title>CS and Rendón Marín: Are Union Citizens and their Third-Country National Parents Experiencing a Revival of the Ruiz Zambrano Ruling?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</guid><description>Maria Haag, PhD Researcher, European University Institute (Florence, Italy) &amp;amp; Michigan Grotius Research Scholar, University of Michigan Law School (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
Background
Five years ago, a significant ruling in the case of C-34/09 Ruiz Zambrano was delivered by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The court found that national measures that hinder EU citizens from genuinely enjoying their rights as citizens are prohibited under Article 20 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N.</description></item><item><title>The immigration issues in the UK renegotiation deal have been finalized.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
David Cameron has successfully negotiated a deal regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the EU. This post, the first in a series about the deal, focuses on &amp;ldquo;EU immigration&amp;rdquo; or, in terms of EU law, the free movement of EU citizens. I will delve into other important matters (competitiveness, Eurozone relations, sovereignty) and the legal structure of the deal later.
The deal comprises seven legal documents: a Decision by the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government (the &amp;ldquo;Decision&amp;rdquo;); a Statement from the Heads of State and Government (an agreed Council Decision); a Declaration by the European Council (representing the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government); and four declarations by the Commission.</description></item><item><title>Following the Dano ruling, under what circumstances can unemployed EU citizens be deported?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Dano case focused on benefit applications, not deportation. Therefore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly affect deportation. However, due to the Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the EU citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive, it might indirectly impact deportation.
Earlier this year, I published a blog post about when unemployment could justify deporting or banning EU citizens. This post expands on that analysis, considering the Dano judgment.</description></item><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015.</description></item><item><title>Italian Court of Cassation: Vos Thalassa ruling clears migrants who opposed being sent back to Libya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/italian-court-of-cassation-vos-thalassa-ruling-clears-migrants-who-opposed-being-sent-back-to-libya/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/italian-court-of-cassation-vos-thalassa-ruling-clears-migrants-who-opposed-being-sent-back-to-libya/</guid><description>Yasha Maccanico, Statewatch
Photo credit: Sergio D&amp;rsquo;Afflitto, via Wikimedia commons In December 2021, Italy&amp;rsquo;s highest court overturned the convictions and prison sentences of two men who were found guilty of leading a protest on a rescue ship. The men, from Ghana and Sudan, were part of a group of 67 migrants rescued from a distressed boat in the Libyan Search and Rescue zone in July 2018. Initially, the rescue ship was instructed to take the migrants to Italy, but later received orders to return them to Libya.</description></item><item><title>Responsibility in Joint Returns after WS and Others v Frontex: Letting the Active By-Stander Off the Hook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</guid><description>A Missed Opportunity for Accountability: Examining the General Court&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in WS and others v Frontex This analysis delves into the General Court&amp;rsquo;s September 6, 2023, decision in the case of WS and others v Frontex, where a Syrian refugee family&amp;rsquo;s claim for damages against Frontex was dismissed. The family, seeking refuge in the EU during the Syrian war, was returned to Turkey under questionable circumstances involving a joint return operation between Greece and Frontex.</description></item><item><title>The EU Court of Justice has made a ruling on the Schengen Conundrum, which involves a non-EU citizen who has been ordered to leave one Member State but holds a valid residence permit in another Member State.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</guid><description>Professors Elspeth Guild, Queen Mary University of London and Kingsley Napley, and Steve Peers, University of Essex
This article examines a case presented to the Court of Justice concerning the situation of a non-EU citizen residing in one Member State while facing potential expulsion by another.
Background
This issue presents legal complexities due to the involvement of two separate EU law sources. Article 25 of the Schengen Convention, amended in 2010, dictates that a Member State considering issuing a residence permit must first check the Schengen Information System (SIS) for any entry bans (alerts) on the individual.</description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a Member State to be expelled or suspended from the EU? An updated summary of Article 7 of the Treaty on European Union.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-member-state-to-be-expelled-or-suspended-from-the-eu-an-updated-summary-of-article-7-of-the-treaty-on-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-member-state-to-be-expelled-or-suspended-from-the-eu-an-updated-summary-of-article-7-of-the-treaty-on-european-union/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The re-election of Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Orban government has led some critics to demand Hungary&amp;rsquo;s expulsion from the EU. This raises questions about the possibility of such an action and the available sanctions the EU can impose on its members.
This post revisits and updates earlier discussions on this topic, focusing on the &amp;lsquo;Article 7&amp;rsquo; process for addressing breaches of the rule of law and other EU values by Member States.</description></item></channel></rss>