<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-network/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments.</description></item><item><title>Covad Offers A Nationwide MPLS VPN Network For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:31:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</guid><description>Companies with numerous offices across the country have access to a new secure networking solution. Covad&amp;rsquo;s recently launched Intelligent Network Platform offers expanded WAN networking capabilities at a lower cost than traditional options.
Covad&amp;rsquo;s MPLS VPNs are designed for small to medium-sized businesses and larger dispersed companies needing to connect multiple locations, such as franchises, remote offices, warehouses, retail stores, factories, and hotels. Multi-location networking presents two key challenges: establishing secure and reliable connections between all sites and doing so cost-effectively.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Recovery Mirrors Your Servers and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</guid><description>Protecting valuable assets is crucial for any business, which is why backups are essential. However, backups alone can&amp;rsquo;t protect against major disasters that could damage physical infrastructure.
Having a backup located in the company safe won&amp;rsquo;t help if a catastrophic event destroys the entire building. Since many businesses heavily rely on computer systems, replicating the entire IT infrastructure is a wise decision.
You might be wondering about the cost of duplicating server rooms, applications, and data.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Ports In a Data Storm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</guid><description>Businesses are finding it increasingly challenging to forecast their WAN network needs, especially during uncertain economic times. The traditional long wait times for telecom upgrades add to this uncertainty. What&amp;rsquo;s needed is a solution that allows businesses to pay only for the bandwidth they currently use while retaining the ability to swiftly increase capacity as needed.
Ethernet service ports offer this flexibility. Service providers install these ports, often as RJ45 jacks or fiber optic connectors, on a managed router at the customer&amp;rsquo;s location.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</guid><description>Businesses can now benefit from a new, cost-effective broadband connection service: Ethernet Internet. To learn more about this exciting development, watch my concise YouTube presentation here: Ethernet Internet business presentation.
As the presentation highlights, Ethernet Internet offers a rare combination of affordability and superior performance. This cutting-edge technology is rapidly evolving and expanding beyond metropolitan areas. Soon, it will be accessible across the country, delivered wirelessly in rural regions and through copper or fiber optic connections in urban centers, with speeds reaching up to 10 Mbps or higher.</description></item><item><title>Handle Big Data With Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>The age of &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; is upon us. But what does that mean? Big data refers to massive datasets that are too large for typical database management tools. Think terabytes, petabytes, exabytes, and even zettabytes – each one thousands of times larger than the last.
This surge in data originates from sources like computer simulations, financial modeling, research projects, sensor data, and high-definition video processing, which generate terabytes of information rapidly.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile/</guid><description>Global telecommunication companies are updating their networks from circuit-based to packet-based systems. With the growth of internet-based networks, Ethernet WAN services have become more accessible and affordable. However, businesses often still rely on older technologies like T1, DS3, or SONET for connecting to these services and cloud networks.
While these older technologies are reliable and getting cheaper, using Ethernet for the initial connection, known as the &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; offers several benefits.</description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous.</description></item><item><title>Burstable Bandwidth Offers Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</guid><description>Most businesses purchase dedicated WAN bandwidth to support their voice and data services. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a more cost-effective option called burstable bandwidth.
Take business broadband service as an example. A dedicated DS3 connection provides a constant 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads. This full capacity is always available, whether you&amp;rsquo;re sending a large file or backing up data. When not fully utilized, the line remains idle.
The recent drop in DS3 prices has made it a common choice for medium to large businesses.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Speed Challenged By EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</guid><description>When a company needs more bandwidth than its T1 lines can provide, the typical upgrade has been to DS3. However, DS3 is usually delivered through fiber optic SONET connections, which can be costly to install unless a building is already equipped for fiber optic services. A new service called EoC offers a potential solution by providing DS3 speeds over existing copper telephone wiring.
EoC stands for Ethernet over Copper. It delivers high bandwidth services, up to DS3 levels of 45 Mbps, without needing fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Meshed MPLS Forms a Cloud of Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</guid><description>Modern MPLS networks are replacing outdated Frame Relay networks for connecting multiple business sites. Their ability to handle almost any protocol with high quality and reliability has driven their popularity. A long-standing desire has been the ability to use multiple carriers across locations seamlessly within a managed MPLS network. This desire has finally been fulfilled.
AireSpring, a rapidly growing and innovative carrier, now offers a &amp;ldquo;Meshed MPLS Network.&amp;rdquo; But what exactly does this entail and how does it differ from the inherent mesh capabilities of any MPLS network?</description></item></channel></rss>