<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Line Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/line-services/</link><description>Recent content in Line Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/line-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Replacements for GigaMAN and Other Discontinued Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
AT&amp;amp;T recently decided to discontinue certain line services due to a lack of demand. While this might not seem surprising, the services being phased out are not outdated copper lines, but rather relatively new, high-speed technologies: GigaMAN Gigabit Ethernet and DecaMAN 10 Gigabit Ethernet. These services are used to connect geographically dispersed Local Area Networks (LANs).
Not So Old-Timey
The discontinuation will affect customers in eleven states: Arkansas, California, Illinois, Indiana, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Ohio, Oklahoma, Texas, and Wisconsin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replacements-for-gigaman-and-other-discontinued-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Competition Is Cutting Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</guid><description>In this day and age, everyone is trying to save money. Your monthly telecom costs are a great place to start. Telecom expenses are often high and confusing, so it’s a good idea to take a close look at your bills and see if you can find ways to reduce costs or find a better deal. Keep in mind that pricing can vary significantly depending on your location.
We often assume that the cost of goods and services is relatively consistent regardless of location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>