<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Court of Human Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-court-of-human-rights/</link><description>Recent content in European Court of Human Rights on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-court-of-human-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview and analysis of the relaunched negotiations for EU accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The potential inclusion of the EU into the ECHR has been a long-awaited development. With the necessary Treaty modifications in the Lisbon Treaty and a negotiated accession treaty by 2013, it appeared that the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s December 2014 ruling would solidify this union. However, the Court&amp;rsquo;s judgment (Opinion 2/13), which was subject to criticism on this blog, unexpectedly disrupted the accession process.
However, the process was resurrected in 2019 and has advanced quickly since then...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bosphorus presumption remains in effect in EU law and the ECHR, as demonstrated in the case of Avotiņš v. Latvia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</guid><description>Stian Øby Johansen, a PhD fellow at the University of Oslo Faculty of Law*, examines a recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR). On May 23, 2016, the court delivered its judgment in the case of Avotiņš v. Latvia, marking the first detailed analysis of the &amp;ldquo;Bosphorus presumption&amp;rdquo; since the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) rejected a draft agreement for EU accession to the European Convention of Human Rights (ECHR)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bosphorus-presumption-remains-in-effect-in-eu-law-and-the-echr-as-demonstrated-in-the-case-of-avoti-v-latvia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing religious tolerance with freedom of expression in ECHR case law: Is there a right to insult?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights has reignited the debate about whether freedom of speech should have limitations, particularly when it comes to potentially offensive remarks targeting religious beliefs, such as those of the Muslim faith. This presents an opportunity to analyze the case&amp;rsquo;s background and determine what, if any, restrictions on free speech are justifiable in such instances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The potential threat to human rights protection posed by the CJEU and the EU's accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The CJEU’s Opinion on EU Accession to the ECHR: Taking the Football Home Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) finally issued its ruling on the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed accession to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). This intricate judgment brings up numerous legal points. This post will present a concise summary of the ruling, examine its implications, and offer an initial critique of the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/13 on EU accession to the ECHR: Searching for the Positive Aspect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-13-on-eu-accession-to-the-echr-searching-for-the-positive-aspect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 16:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-13-on-eu-accession-to-the-echr-searching-for-the-positive-aspect/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge
Introduction Opinion 2/13 is a legal judgment with significant political consequences. It provides a thorough examination of the Draft Accession Agreement (DAA) clauses and fundamental EU law principles. While some have offered helpful explanations of the Opinion, others have criticized it intensely. This piece aims to explore a more favorable interpretation of the Opinion, focusing on three key points: the potential oversight of the bigger picture during negotiations, whether Opinion 2/13 was an act of judicial self-importance, and its impact on the relationship between the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-13-on-eu-accession-to-the-echr-searching-for-the-positive-aspect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-13-on-eu-accession-to-the-echr-searching-for-the-positive-aspect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Human Rights highlights the significance of encryption in the case of Podchasov v. Russia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip &amp;amp; Frederik Zuiderveen Borgesius*
*Both authors work at the iHub and the Institute for Computing and Information Sciences, Radboud University, The Netherlands - mattis.vantschip[at]ru.nl &amp;amp; frederikzb[at]cs.ru.nl
Photo credit: Gzen92, on wikimedia commons A February 2024 ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Podchasov v. Russia highlighted the crucial role of encryption in safeguarding privacy rights. This judgment comes at a time when encryption is at the heart of many global legal discussions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the case of Schipani v Italy, under what circumstances is it necessary for national courts to seek guidance from the CJEU as per the ECHR?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo; (ECHR) judgment in the Schipani vs. Italy case, issued on July 21, 2015, revisited a topic of significant interest to EU legal experts: the violation of the ECHR by a national court due to its failure to request a preliminary ruling. This judgment, released just before the summer break, might have slipped under the radar for some...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>