<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dispute Settlement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dispute-settlement/</link><description>Recent content in Dispute Settlement on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dispute-settlement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The resolution of disputes and the role of the ECJ in the proposed withdrawal agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A key point of contention in post-Brexit EU/UK relations is the degree to which the UK remains bound to the EU Court of Justice (ECJ). This issue arises first in the withdrawal agreement being negotiated, a draft of which was recently proposed by the EU Commission. While it will eventually affect the future relationship between the two, this post focuses on the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 4 of the Brexit agreement: Examination of dispute resolution and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement between the EU and UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction and Overview
A crucial element of the &amp;lsquo;Brexit deal&amp;rsquo;, formally called the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA), is dispute resolution. This post provides a thorough analysis of the treaty&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution mechanisms and offers a concise summary upfront. (An update on April 29, 2021, incorporates the final TCA article numbers).
This is the fourth post in a series examining the TCA. It follows an overview of the TCA, an analysis of its social security provisions by Professor Tamara Hervey, and an exploration of the connections between the TCA and human rights.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of the Environment and Climate Provisions in the Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Introduction
The start of the new year marked a significant shift in the UK-EU relationship, ending the Brexit transition and ushering in the provisional Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). This post delves into the TCA&amp;rsquo;s environmental and climate change provisions, drawing on prior analyses of the TCA&amp;rsquo;s overview, social security provisions, human rights aspects, and dispute settlement mechanisms. (Updated as of April 28, 2021, to reflect the final TCA article numbering).</description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 3 of the updated Brexit Withdrawal Agreement focuses on dispute resolution.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
This post examines the dispute settlement mechanisms outlined in the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement, specifically addressing the role of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). It is part of a series analyzing the updated agreement, which includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship. Previous posts have provided an overview of the agreement and examined the transition period.</description></item><item><title>Dispute resolution between the EU and UK after Brexit in the context of the White Paper.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Emilija Leinarte*
*Professor of EU law, University of Cambridge and PhD student, University of Cambridge. This research has received support from the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme.
A recent publication by UK in a Changing Europe examined various governing structures that could be used to manage the UK-EU relationship following Brexit. The released White Paper offers a glimpse into the institutional structure that the UK envisions for its future dealings with the EU after withdrawal.</description></item><item><title>How can the issue of Suella be resolved? Exploring the legal implications of breaching and terminating the withdrawal agreement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent news suggests the UK may plan to violate the Brexit withdrawal agreement, with new Attorney-General Suella Braverman potentially seeking legal justification. This makes examining the repercussions of such a breach crucial. While the dispute resolution mechanisms within the agreement and the UK&amp;rsquo;s Withdrawal Agreement Act have been analyzed separately, this piece aims to provide a comprehensive overview, encompassing international law perspectives. This blog post summarizes the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution clauses and the international law principles concerning treaty termination, exploring their interplay.</description></item></channel></rss>