<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel provides leasing options for high-end smartphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first mobile phone leasing program to make high-end devices more accessible.
Subscribers with SIM Only plans can choose to pay a low monthly fee to use premium Apple and Samsung handsets instead of buying them outright. They can lease the newest Apple iPhone and Samsung Galaxy models for two years and have the option to upgrade in the twelfth month for a S$200 fee.
With prices starting at S$35 per month for a Samsung Galaxy S9 (64 GB), customers can save up to S$578 off the regular retail price if they lease the phone for a year or S$358 if they keep it for two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-leasing-options-for-high-end-smartphones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The more specific the mobile advertisement, the higher its earnings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</guid><description>Smaato, a mobile advertising company, has observed that the most successful advertising categories in China during the first quarter of the year were shopping, e-commerce, communication, and technology. These categories achieved high eCPMs (effective cost per mille), reaching up to US$0.30.
When analyzing mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad expenditures in China during the same period, entertainment (30%) and games (22%) were the top two categories.
Ajitpal Pannu, Smaato&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, noted that both monetization and brand spending increased when essential parameters were shared globally with advertising partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Styletag is known for identifying the latest fashion trends globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</guid><description>Want to stay stylish at work? South Korea&amp;rsquo;s SK Planet has refreshed its Styletag mobile app using trends from New York Fashion Week, which wrapped up on February 13th.
Source: Styletag page at the Play Store
Styletag gathers and organizes user-submitted fashion content worldwide, offering both style inspiration and shopping details. The app includes contributions from professional photographers, amateur enthusiasts, and invited fashion experts.
This free app is compatible with iOS 7 (iPad, iPhone, and iPod) via iTunes and Android devices through the Google Play store...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The handbag app reveals the newest handbag options available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 15:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</guid><description>Source: Google Play Store.
Swipe Boutique has launched a new fashion app for Android devices called &amp;ldquo;handbag swipe.&amp;rdquo;
The app allows users to explore thousands of the latest handbag designs from over a hundred popular brands, including Topshop, New Look, and Michael Kors.
With a browsing experience resembling Tinder, shoppers can swipe through various handbag options. The app enables users to curate personal wish lists, purchase desired products instantly, or save handbag details for future reference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers of Credit Suisse in Hong Kong now have access to a new digital private banking app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse e-brochure.
Credit Suisse has introduced its digital private banking platform in Hong Kong, launching an improved Private Banking Asia Pacific app.
This digital platform offers a new way to serve clients, blending digital and in-person experiences. Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s first digital private banking platform debuted in Singapore in March 2015. After analyzing client usage and conducting usability tests for over a year, the bank has introduced an enhanced app in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel will be providing the option to share up to 50GB of mobile data at the PC Show 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</guid><description>Singtel is increasing its mobile data offerings with the launch of &amp;ldquo;DataMore,&amp;rdquo; a new plan featuring larger data bundles. This launch comes less than a month after Circles.Life entered the market with a focus on data options. DataMore is designed for users who need a lot of data and is shareable with multiple users, making it perfect for families.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Mobile Marketing, highlights that this plan caters to customer demand for larger data packages at affordable prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-be-providing-the-option-to-share-up-to-50gb-of-mobile-data-at-the-pc-show-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xperience the Sony Ericsson Xperia X10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</guid><description>The Xperia X10 might be the perfect smartphone you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for. It boasts an 8.1 Megapixel camera and a 4-inch touchscreen, which begs the question: do you really need to carry a separate camera?
The Xperia&amp;rsquo;s camera eliminates that need with features like flash, 16x zoom, touch focus, geo-tagging, smile detection, and a &amp;lsquo;send to web&amp;rsquo; option. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable for landscape, portrait, night, beach, and various other settings. You can even edit photos directly on the phone using apps from the Android Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guvera introduces support for Apple TV and updates its product</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</guid><description>Source: Guvera.
Guvera, a music streaming service supported by brand funding, has announced significant upgrades to its product and compatibility with Apple TV.
The updated Guvera 3.0 app introduces music channels and a variety of new editorial features. These include artist interviews, news articles, reviews, photo galleries, brand competitions, and product promotions.
Hazel Savage, Head of Marketing and Operations for Guvera Asia, stated that the company recognizes that music is more than just individual tracks; it represents a whole culture and way of life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG Electronics has introduced a new website dedicated to product security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</guid><description>LG Electronics has launched a dedicated website to address security concerns related to their mobile products. The website, managed by LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security Response Team (PSRT), will serve as a central hub for security announcements, updates, and a platform for reporting vulnerabilities.
LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security website will feature regular updates and bulletins on security matters concerning their mobile products, aiming to provide a secure and safe user experience. The website will prioritize vulnerabilities based on their severity, starting with the most critical ones, followed by high, moderate, and low-risk threats, including those identified by Google for the Android operating system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Plethora of Free Android Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</guid><description>This Christmas, give the gift of a cutting-edge Android phone without breaking the bank. Although these devices boast advanced technology and typically come with a high price tag (often $500-$600), it&amp;rsquo;s possible to get one for free.
Android smartphones are essentially pocket computers, running on 3G and 4G networks and offering similar functionality to desktops and laptops. They&amp;rsquo;re capable of web browsing, social networking, email, video streaming, and more. While $500-$600 might be reasonable for such a device, why pay when you can get one for free?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new laptops and monitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</guid><description>Dell Singapore has launched new laptops and a monitor for consumers.
The XPS 12 is the first 2-in-1 laptop with a 4K Ultra HD display. The Inspiron 11 3000 series offers an affordable and portable laptop option available in three colors. Dell also released their first 4K consumer monitor, the Dell 28 Ultra HD 4K Monitor.
&amp;ldquo;Consumers have increasingly diverse needs. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a student or a professional, size, power, design, and price all matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kodak Alaris unveils new wireless scanners with network connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</guid><description>Kodak Alaris&amp;rsquo; latest desktop scanners, the Kodak ScanMate i1150WN and Kodak i1190WN, offer wireless and network connectivity and are compatible with mobile apps. These features support bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policies and workplace mobility.
Source: Kodak Alaris. The Kodak ScanMate i1150WN.
The i1150WN and i1190WN scanners can connect through an office network or Wi-Fi, making them adaptable to various office settings. Standard drivers (TWAIN, ISIS) allow integration with new and existing business applications, streamlining the capture process and simplifying software installation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-alaris-unveils-new-wireless-scanners-with-network-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Nanu, the free calling app, provides a fresh approach to connecting with customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</guid><description>Source: nanu website.
Nanu, the first entirely free mobile calling app, is experiencing rapid growth in its monthly and daily active users. Based in Singapore, the startup claims its app&amp;rsquo;s active user rates are almost twice the industry standard, with 56% monthly active users and 19% daily active users.
CEO Martin Nygate points out that many tech startups avoid disclosing these figures due to poor performance. He&amp;rsquo;s pleased to share nanu&amp;rsquo;s positive data, reflecting both strong download numbers and increasing app usage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Activpass provides discounted rates for wellness activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</guid><description>Source: Activpass. Activpass is a mobile-based marketplace for booking lifestyle activities.
The team behind Activpass, a platform designed for businesses and professionals in fitness, wellness, and beauty, believes in living life to the fullest. Their mobile platform gives users access to over 1,000 services like yoga, training sessions, golf, massages, and beauty treatments, all without requiring a long-term commitment.
Users can easily book and pay for services on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC has unveiled the Desire 620 and 620G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC Desire 620 dual sim, the successor to the HTC Desire 610.
Source: HTC. The 620G in Milkyway gray.
Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia, stated that the new HTC Desire model provides a balance of modern design, strong processing, and fast connectivity, making it a suitable option for budget-conscious entertainment enthusiasts.
The Desire 620 dual sim is equipped with a Snapdragon 410 Qualcomm processor, Android 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China's unicorn company has revealed the top 10 rankings in the Google Play store for its Wi-Fi crowdsourcing app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</guid><description>Source: Play Store.
The free app WiFi Master Key, which helps users find and connect to crowdsourced Wi-Fi hotspots, is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia. It helps people access the internet in a region where connectivity is rapidly expanding.
The app lets users share Wi-Fi hotspot information with the community. While this information allows others to connect for free, the app prioritizes privacy and security by encrypting and storing shared Wi-Fi passwords in its cloud database instead of revealing them directly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo emphasizes that e-commerce must be integrated into the retail strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, predicts that mobile will play an even greater role in the e-commerce industry this quarter.
Eric Eichmann, President and COO of Criteo, believes that 2015 will be a year of significant change for e-commerce as consumer online shopping habits continue to evolve rapidly. The increased use of multiple devices presents a challenge for marketers targeting consumers. Eichmann suggests that advertisers who adapt quickly by investing wisely in solutions such as cross-device targeting and mobile-optimized websites and apps will be best equipped to meet consumer demand and boost sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are You A Sentio Being?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re someone who likes to stay ahead of the curve in technology without breaking the bank, now is the time to make a move. The LG Sentio, a free high-quality smartphone, is a prime example of getting significant value without spending a lot.
You might be wondering how a high-value phone can be free. It&amp;rsquo;s a combination of taking advantage of technological advancements at the right moment and knowing where to find the best deals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circles.Life introduces a range of new services centered around unlimited usage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</guid><description>For S$3, enjoy unlimited on-demand data at 4G+ speeds.
For the first time, get unlimited WhatsApp roaming in 18 countries for S$1 per day.
Source: Circles.Life. Poster for Unlimited
Data on Demand. Circles.Life, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fourth mobile operator, argues that the current unlimited data plans are actually quite restrictive. They believe that these plans should not be limited to weekends, slowed down after a small data limit, or tied to yearly contracts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check Point has discovered a vulnerability in a preinstalled app on Xiaomi devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</guid><description>Slava Makkaveev, a researcher from cybersecurity firm Check Point Software, recently discovered a concerning security flaw in Xiaomi phones.
This vulnerability was found within the pre-installed &amp;ldquo;Guard Provider&amp;rdquo; app (com.miui.guardprovider), designed to identify malware. Ironically, this app could allow attackers on the same Wi-Fi network to perform a man-in-the-middle (MiTM) attack. This type of attack enables the interception and copying of data transmitted between the phone and online services.
Furthermore, by exploiting a third-party software development kit (SDK) update mechanism, attackers could potentially disable malware protection and inject malicious code...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LifeProof has unveiled new cases designed specifically for the latest iPhones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 11:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/</guid><description>LifeProof has introduced the FLiP, their first iPhone case to include built-in storage.
“Our iPhones are essential for capturing photos and videos, providing long-lasting battery life, and keeping us connected,” stated Jim Parke, LifeProof&amp;rsquo;s CEO.
Source: LifeProof.
“Apple is known for its continuous innovation, and LifeProof aims to complement the phone&amp;rsquo;s sleek design with cases that maintain optimal performance.”
Engineered to withstand drops from 2 meters, the single-piece FLiP case incorporates a wallet-like panel on the back, providing storage for cards and cash...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lifeproof-has-unveiled-new-cases-designed-specifically-for-the-latest-iphones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verizon Goes After Blue Collar Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</guid><description>When picturing someone in a hard hat using a cell phone, most people think of a Nextel phone, known for their walkie-talkie feature and durability. However, Verizon is now entering this market, aiming to capture the construction and outdoor enthusiast demographics.
Verizon has the advantage of being a larger company with a wider customer base and a broader phone selection. They have leveled the playing field by adding push-to-talk (PTT) functionality and introducing tougher phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wacom introduces the Wacom MobileStudio Pro, designed for demanding creative tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wacom-introduces-the-wacom-mobilestudio-pro-designed-for-demanding-creative-tasks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wacom-introduces-the-wacom-mobilestudio-pro-designed-for-demanding-creative-tasks/</guid><description>Wacom is launching the Wacom MobileStudio Pro, a new line of mobile computers designed for professional creatives who work on the go. These lightweight computers feature Wacom&amp;rsquo;s latest pen technology, including the new Wacom Pro Pen 2. With four times the accuracy and pressure sensitivity of its predecessor, the Wacom Pro Pen 2 makes the MobileStudio Pro a powerful tool for 2D, 3D, and CAD artists and designers.
The MobileStudio Pro family includes both 13...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wacom-introduces-the-wacom-mobilestudio-pro-designed-for-demanding-creative-tasks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wacom-introduces-the-wacom-mobilestudio-pro-designed-for-demanding-creative-tasks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is your company using mobile for recruiting?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</guid><description>Mobile interaction is crucial for successful recruitment in India. In 2014-15, almost half of companies surveyed by TimesJobs reported receiving 10-20% of job applications via mobile phones, significantly up from the previous year.
With mobile phones widespread, 65% of organizations in India now have mobile recruitment strategies, a 10% increase from the previous year, according to a TimesJobs.com survey.
Jobseeker behavior has shifted dramatically, with 85% of online job searching now done on smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Intercept Brings Free Android Smartphone to Sprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 05:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</guid><description>A popular new smartphone design combines a 3-inch touchscreen, a slide-out QWERTY keyboard, and the Android operating system. Sprint offers this package in their Samsung Intercept model. Amazingly, you can get this phone for free when you order it online with a new Sprint PCS service plan. There are no additional costs; even shipping is free, and the plans are the same price as in stores.
The Samsung Intercept M910 is a fantastic deal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can now pre-order the new Microsoft Surface 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</guid><description>At an event in Singapore in April, bloggers were given the opportunity to test out the Surface 3, as well as the Lumia 640 and 640 XL.
The Surface Pro was a hit, but some users desired more. Ian Tan, the Surface Lead for Consumer at Microsoft Singapore, revealed during a media event that certain customers requested a lighter, more budget-friendly device, a request to which Microsoft paid attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DIB Mobile app has been enhanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</guid><description>Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has launched an upgraded version of its mobile banking app for iOS and Android devices. This enhanced app offers access to over 60 services, including features designed to help users manage their personal finances effectively.
With smartphone usage on the rise and Nielsen reporting that 78% of the UAE population owns at least one such device, DIB&amp;rsquo;s mobile app caters to this growing trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Altec Lansing introduces durable mobile accessories at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</guid><description>Altec Lansing is launching new lines of durable chargers, power banks, cables, and cases for smartphones and tablets. Expected to be available around the second quarter of 2016, these accessories will have rugged features like IP67-rated, military-grade construction for waterproof, dustproof, and shock-resistant functionality and device protection.
The new products will include:
Altec Lansing Everything Proof Power Packs (3,000, 6,000, and 10,000 mAh): These power banks are designed for smartphones, tablets, and MP3 players, offering up to 100 hours of talk time, 75 hours of music, 50 hours of video, or 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lonliness of the Long Distance Landline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</guid><description>Recent data shows people are rapidly ditching landlines. If Alexander Graham Bell were alive today, he&amp;rsquo;d have trouble reaching anyone on his original invention. Instead, he&amp;rsquo;d have much better luck using a cell phone, just like everyone else.
It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that most people own a cell phone, or even multiple old ones. People want to be constantly connected, even when they perhaps shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be. Observe drivers at a stoplight, and you&amp;rsquo;ll likely spot several talking on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhance car safety with 360-degree hands-free device viewing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</guid><description>Sprint-Cass, the sole distributor of Taiwanese brand Digidock in Singapore, is introducing a new line of Digidock mobile device holders for vehicles at IT Show 2015, happening from March 19th to 22nd at the Suntec Convention Centre. These holders are designed for cars, motorcycles, and bicycles.
Every Digidock holder features a 360-degree swivel joint, allowing users to securely position their smartphones or tablets at any desired angle. Engineered for simple attachment and removal, the holders come with interchangeable cradles and universal mounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub is offering a deal of 3GB for S$3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</guid><description>StarHub is offering a new &amp;ldquo;3GB-for-$3&amp;rdquo; data upsize option for its mobile postpaid customers. For a limited time, customers who sign up for or renew their StarHub 4G plans can get an extra 3GB of data for S$3 per month. This promotional price will increase to S$6 per month for customers who sign up on or after April 1, 2016.
Here are the details for StarHub&amp;rsquo;s two-year mobile postpaid plans:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HandySpeech app, which converts handwriting to speech, is now available on Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</guid><description>iSpeak4U, a company known for developing mobile apps for individuals with speech and hearing impairments, has launched an Android version of their app HandySpeech. This app offers a simple and efficient communication tool for those with speech difficulties.
Source: iSpeak4U. HandySpeech running on various devices.
With HandySpeech, users can input text on a device screen using their finger or a stylus, and the device will then vocalize the written words. The app is designed to store frequently used phrases and adapt to the user&amp;rsquo;s handwriting style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the ability to hail a cab using Hailo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</guid><description>Hailo, a highly-rated taxi app boasting more five-star reviews than any other similar service, launched in Singapore on October 29th. With a global network of over 60,000 drivers and a strong user base exceeding 1.4 million, Hailo reports a ride request every two seconds somewhere in the world.
Source: Hailo. From left: Benny Lim, Managing Director, SMRT Road Holdings; Ron Zeghibe, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Executive Chairman, Hailo Global, and Yu Hsiang Wong, General Manager, Hailo Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Impressive Samsung Impression Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</guid><description>Get ready to be amazed by a groundbreaking cell phone display technology called AMOLED, short for Active Matrix Organic Light Emitting Diode. This technology delivers a sharper, more vibrant display that is also slimmer, lighter, and more energy-efficient. While it will soon be widely used in various mobile devices, you can currently experience AMOLED technology in the Samsung Impression A877 Blue cell phone.
As cell phones continue to replace laptops, the demand for larger screens has increased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It's Pink Cell Phone Season Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/</guid><description>Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day kicks off the season for pink cell phones, a trend that lasts until Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. This convergence of technology and pink offers a stylish option for yourself or your significant other.
This year, the Samsung Instinct Pink for Sprint PCS is a top pick. Though usually a pricey phone, it&amp;rsquo;s available at a significant discount with an Everything Plan or Talk/Message/Data Share Plan from Sprint PCS. Families can even get two discounted phones with the right family plan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drowning In A Sea Of Free Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 22:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/</guid><description>Your cell phone contract ends every two years, allowing you to explore new options. Many people take advantage of this because they&amp;rsquo;re unhappy with their current provider or want to upgrade to the latest technology. While constantly upgrading your phone can be expensive, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get the newest models without breaking the bank.
You can find the most recent phones for little to no cost if you know where to look...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Stay away from Pokemon Go scams and malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</guid><description>Source: Niantic blog.
The augmented reality game Pokémon Go, highly popular since its July launch, has attracted scammers and cybercriminals. While the game hasn&amp;rsquo;t officially launched in all of Asia, Symantec warns of potential risks for players.
Symantec&amp;rsquo;s blog post details several Pokémon Go scams, from fake PokeCoins to privacy concerns.
Free PokeCoin scams
Pokémon Go offers in-app purchases using real money to buy PokeCoins, a virtual currency. Players use these coins to purchase items like incense to attract Pokémon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zap Delivery in Singapore guarantees fast and reliable couriered deliveries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</guid><description>Source: Zap Delivery.
Zap Delivery, an on-demand courier service, promises quick, safe, and dependable deliveries of packages and documents within Singapore in two hours or less using their new mobile app. This app utilizes advanced authentication and real-time tracking to provide peace of mind for those awaiting deliveries.
“We’ve experienced our fair share of delivery issues, so we created a user-friendly app that fosters trust,&amp;quot; explained Michael Tan, Zap Delivery Co-founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get double the mobile data for just a small increase with Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Coinciding with the start of IT Show 2016, Singtel is introducing DataX2, a new service that doubles customers&amp;rsquo; monthly mobile data for a fixed price of S$5.90. This new option reflects Singtel&amp;rsquo;s focus on data-driven services, building on the success of last year&amp;rsquo;s SIM Only Plan.
DataX2 lets customers double their data when they sign up for or renew a Combo Mobile Plan (Combo 2 or higher)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the second quarter of 2014, China's RTB ad spending increased by 616% compared to the previous quarter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</guid><description>Smaato, a company specializing in mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad exchange (SMX) and supply side platform (SSP), has reported significant growth in mobile RTB in its Q2 2014 Global Mobile RTB Insights Report.
Source: The Smaato RTB Insights Report for Q2 2014. RTB spending in the APAC region for the top five countries.
Smaato&amp;rsquo;s findings show a 69% increase in RTB spending in the second quarter of 2014 compared to the first quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recharge your prepaid mobile accounts using du's mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</guid><description>For the first time in the UAE, du customers can now top up their prepaid mobile phones using mPay. This new service was unveiled today at GITEX Technology Week 2015.
Fahad Al Hassawi, Chief Commercial Officer at du, stated, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to be the first operator offering prepaid recharge via mPay, making it easier for our customers to top up their prepaid du lines conveniently. We believe this will be highly popular among our users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Captivated By Samsung’s Android Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</guid><description>Ready for the newest smartphones? Check out the Samsung Captivate, available through AT&amp;amp;T. It&amp;rsquo;s a fast, sleek, and runs on the Android operating system – specifically, the Galaxy Android version.
The Samsung Galaxy series is creating a lot of excitement. These phones will have different names depending on the carrier. The Captivate is specifically designed for AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network, and it lives up to its name!
This phone pushes the boundaries of slimness, measuring a mere 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor simplifies the process of capturing important moments during a trip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the biggest travel website globally as of July 2015 according to comScore Media Metrix, has introduced a &amp;ldquo;Travel Timeline&amp;rdquo; feature for its mobile app. This feature allows users to record and share their travel experiences. When turned on, it automatically generates a timeline of the places visited and photos taken at each location. This timeline can be viewed chronologically or as a route on a map.
Adam Medros, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s SVP of Global Product, highlights the feature&amp;rsquo;s value in documenting and sharing travel memories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Someline Apple Tree app will produce apples for charity as long as you refrain from using your phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</guid><description>Source: Google Play.
Libern Lin, a student entrepreneur attending Republic Polytechnic in Singapore, has expanded his app, Someline Apple Tree, with financial support from the Singapore Computer Society (SCS).
The app incentivizes real-life interactions by rewarding users with digital apples for reducing phone usage. Lin, the app&amp;rsquo;s creator, explained that they wanted to use the app&amp;rsquo;s concept for a good cause. So, they used the S$30,000 grant from SCS to add a charitable component to the app in line with IDA&amp;rsquo;s Code for Charity*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How BlackBerry Touch Screen Technology Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</guid><description>The BlackBerry Storm is a unique addition to the BlackBerry lineup, featuring a touch screen instead of the traditional physical QWERTY keyboard. Though the keyboard is now virtual, it still aims to provide a tactile experience.
Why this change? Primarily, to accommodate a larger display screen without increasing the phone&amp;rsquo;s overall size. To achieve this, the physical keyboard was removed, leaving only essential call, menu, and navigation buttons below the screen...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BlackBerry Storm Just Blew In at a Lower Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:51:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on getting a BlackBerry Storm in stores. You can buy one online from Cell Phone Plans Finder with free shipping.
Although I can&amp;rsquo;t disclose the price here, you can easily find it on the cellphone special offers page. You can then order the phone with your preferred Verizon Wireless service package, all delivered directly to you without shipping fees.
The BlackBerry Storm 9530 Black, the first BlackBerry with a touch keyboard, offers a unique experience for those accustomed to physical keys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi cab booking app is now available in Kuala Lumpur and will soon be expanding to more countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a cab booking app, has expanded its reach to Malaysia and will be pre-installed on Celkon phones in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal.
Developed by India-based On Time Technologies, TaxiPixi launched in Malaysia this week. Celkon, a mobile phone manufacturer, will pre-install the app on its devices in several countries. Pradeep Yerraguntla, Celkon&amp;rsquo;s Head of Digital, stated that Celkon will promote the app through its app store and website, targeting consumers in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new NYNJA app allows you to communicate, make purchases, and utilize cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: NYNJA Group. Screen captures of the NYNJA app, currently in beta.
NYNJA Group, a Hong Kong-based communications and mobile technology firm, has introduced NYNJA, a new communications app with a built-in digital marketplace and cryptocurrency wallet.
The NYNJA app works across multiple platforms and integrates voice, text, and visual messaging with business management and e-commerce tools. Its features are powered by its own financial ecosystem and cryptocurrency, NYNJACoin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia honors female entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, marked International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day on March 8, 2017, by recognizing the achievements of women.
This year&amp;rsquo;s International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day centers around empowering women globally and inspiring them to make bold moves. Shopee Malaysia honored this theme by highlighting the stories of women entrepreneurs who took a leap of faith to launch their own ventures. The platform&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly design, free nationwide shipping, and zero-commission fees are designed to encourage more women to tap into their potential as leaders and business owners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Obtain a prepaid virtual Visa account through Singtel Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one mobile payments app, Dash, now features Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first virtual Visa account. All Dash users, new and existing, will automatically receive a Dash Visa Virtual Account. This account can be used for mobile payments at over 50,000 merchant locations in Singapore.
To use the mobile payment feature, customers sign in to the Dash app, add funds to their Dash Visa accounts, and make purchases at Dash merchants and participating e-commerce websites like Qoo10, Zalora, and HungryGoWhere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub reintroduces 12GB mobile data bundles and additional features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced a new, budget-friendly package called SurfHub, combining mobile and home internet services.
For a starting price of S$96.56 per month on a 24-month contract, SurfHub customers receive a 4G mobile plan with a minimum of 12GB of data and a 1Gbps fiber broadband connection for their homes. This combined offer costs roughly half the price of a standalone 12GB mobile plan. SurfHub also includes generous benefits like up to 700 minutes of local calls, 1,500 local SMS/MMS messages, and a subsidy for a new mobile phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maybank customers in Malaysia can now access Western Union remittances digitally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</guid><description>Maybank and Western Union have partnered to introduce the first digital remittance service in Malaysia. This service, accessible through the Maybank2u (M2u) mobile app and website, allows Maybank customers to send money to over 500,000 Western Union agent locations in more than 200 countries and territories. Available 24/7, the service facilitates transfers up to RM10,000 daily, with recipients typically receiving funds faster than traditional methods.
Datuk Lim Hong Tat, Maybank&amp;rsquo;s Group Head of Community Financial Services, highlighted that this launch strengthens Maybank&amp;rsquo;s online presence and promotes digital transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry 8830 is World Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</guid><description>Verizon Wireless has engineered a BlackBerry that functions domestically and internationally. This is notable because Verizon uses the CDMA network in the US, while the rest of the world primarily uses GSM.
Previously, this difference prevented Verizon phones from roaming internationally. To solve this, Verizon created a device with both CDMA and GSM capabilities. In the US, the CDMA component accesses the 800 and 1900 MHz bands, including EV-DO broadband. Outside the US, the GSM component accesses the 900 and 1800 MHz bands, including GPRS broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</a></p></description></item><item><title>iOS 9 has been released by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple has announced that its latest mobile operating system, iOS 9, will launch on September 16th. This free update for iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch users boasts enhanced search capabilities and improved Siri functionality.
One of the standout features of iOS 9 is its new multitasking capabilities for iPad. Users can now work with two apps concurrently, viewing them side-by-side. A Picture-in-Picture feature also allows for video playback while using other apps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ios-9-has-been-released-by-apple/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV Envy Touch Phone Messaging Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</guid><description>Do you find yourself desiring a modern touchscreen phone but also require a physical QWERTY keyboard? The new LG enV Touch eliminates this dilemma by offering both!
When closed, the &amp;ldquo;enV Touch&amp;rdquo; resembles a typical touchscreen smartphone. The exterior features a 3-inch, 800x480 pixel color TFT touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable shortcuts. However, a hidden surprise awaits inside: a second 3-inch, 800x400 pixel color display. This internal screen, paired with a spacious QWERTY keyboard, prioritizes efficient typing over touch input...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson's portable projectors are designed for on-the-go presentations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</guid><description>Source: Epson website. The EB-1780W.
Epson has introduced the EB-1700 series, its lightest line of 3LCD projectors yet. This series prioritizes portability without sacrificing image quality or connectivity options, making it ideal for business presentations on the go.
The projectors in the EB-1700 series weigh under 4 pounds and are less than 2 inches thick, making them easy to carry in a laptop bag. Grip lines on the sides add to their portability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-portable-projectors-are-designed-for-on-the-go-presentations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Airtel to launch hi!India plans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:05:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</guid><description>Singtel and Airtel have partnered to provide Singtel prepaid mobile customers with access to high-quality calls to India through the Airtel Talk app. This service was previously only available to credit card holders.
Now, Singtel prepaid customers can utilize Airtel Talk by purchasing hi!India plans using their prepaid credits. Calls made through Airtel Talk are transmitted via standard IDD lines, resulting in enhanced call clarity.
Hi!India plans start at S$5 for 100 minutes (S$0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Tencent collaborate to simplify gifting and payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Wong.
Starbucks Coffee Company and Tencent Holdings, a Chinese provider of online services, are collaborating. In early 2017, they plan to launch a new social gifting feature within WeChat, a popular mobile communications service in China. Additionally, Starbucks customers at nearly 2,500 stores across mainland China can now use WeChat Pay for their purchases.
This partnership makes Starbucks the first retailer in China to provide an integrated, locally relevant social gifting and digital payment experience within WeChat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces the thinnest laptop in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</guid><description>Every Spectre accessory has been designed to provide a luxurious experience.
The CNC machined aluminum body is as sleek as an AAA battery at a mere 10.4mm. Enjoy exceptional performance with Intel Core i5 and i7 processors. Immerse yourself in the vibrant visuals of a full HD 13.3&amp;quot; edge-to-edge display complemented by Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen sound. HP claims to have developed the slimmest laptop globally, meticulously refining every detail to provide an unmatched user experience and peak performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adyen predicts that smartphones will soon surpass tablets as the primary device for mobile payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 22:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</guid><description>Source: Adyen. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Adyen, a global payments technology provider, recently released its quarterly Mobile Payments Index for Q3. This report analyzes mobile payment data from web-based transactions across Adyen&amp;rsquo;s customer base between July and September. Notably, the Index reveals that nearly half of online transactions using specific payment methods are now conducted on mobile devices.
The Index shows that 47% of payments made with JCB, a Japanese card, were completed on mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces Malaysia's tonton to its CAST app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</guid><description>Singtel has added Media Prima&amp;rsquo;s tonton, a popular Malaysian streaming platform, to its CAST video streaming app. This partnership, along with existing offerings on Singtel TV, makes Singtel a leading provider of Malay entertainment content in Singapore.
This is the first time tonton is available outside of Malaysia. Through CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus pack, subscribers will have access to over 23,000 hours of Malay entertainment, including content from TV3, TV9, and tonton originals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is a region where digital marketing is effective</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</guid><description>Source: Adobe website.
Recent research from Adobe highlights the growing importance of mobile devices for marketers in Southeast Asia, emphasizing its effectiveness in customer interaction and engagement. This shift toward mobile-first business strategies is particularly prominent in the Asia Pacific region.
Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Digital Index &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Benchmark&amp;rdquo; for 2015 analyzed website performance across eight regions, including Southeast Asia. By comparing the top 20% of websites (&amp;ldquo;best of the best&amp;rdquo;) with the overall average across six key performance indicators, the research provides valuable insights into the strategies of high-performing digital marketing organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Bill Shock Is So Easy To Avoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission is looking into new regulations due to a high volume of complaints regarding unexpected cell phone charges. While this intervention is welcomed by those who have faced this issue, understanding how to avoid such situations is key.
&amp;ldquo;Bill shock&amp;rdquo; refers to the unpleasant surprise of discovering unexpectedly high charges on your cell phone bill, often leaving you in disbelief and frantically searching for errors. While billing mistakes can occur, these charges are typically accurate, stemming from a lack of awareness regarding contract details or exceeding usage limits, often unknowingly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP updates Pavilion features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pavilion PCs, including convertibles and notebooks, designed to be stylish and powerful. The company aims to provide customers with a range of options to suit their needs and budgets.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that HP understands customers&amp;rsquo; diverse needs, with some prioritizing portability and others seeking performance. The redesigned Pavilion PCs cater to both, offering affordability and style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Aneka Plus pack on Singtel CAST now features Tribe from Astro</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The show &amp;ldquo;Qadr&amp;rdquo; from Tribe is now available through CAST.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CAST platform now includes Tribe, a regional video service by Astro. Showcasing content from Astro&amp;rsquo;s Malay channels, like Astro Ria and Astro Prima, Tribe will be part of CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus package.
For the first time in Singapore, viewers can access Astro&amp;rsquo;s premium on-demand Malay programs anywhere. Tribe offers complete seasons of drama series, variety shows, movies, and award shows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indosat Ooredoo introduces nationwide 4G-LTE service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo.
Indosat Ooredoo has introduced its high-speed 4G-LTE service across Indonesia. The company stated that the improved connectivity and call clarity offered by its new 4Gplus data network come at the same cost as its existing 3G services.
In the last two years, Indosat Ooredoo has doubled its network speeds, achieving the fastest 3G internet speeds available. Independent tests show its 4Gplus service can reach download speeds of up to 185Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accessories After The Fact</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve either already purchased your dream phone or are seriously considering your wireless choices. However, the box might not include every accessory you desire. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we offer a wide variety of accessories at significantly discounted prices (up to 80% off).
For instance, car chargers are essential for professionals on the go. Your device might run low on battery before you can reach an outlet. Even with an AC charger, finding a power source isn&amp;rsquo;t always easy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/</a></p></description></item><item><title>du offers corporate mobile plans for SMEs in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Du offers five corporate mobile plans designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These plans include data and free calls to colleagues within the business.
Ranging from AED 50 to AED 450 per month, the plans provide data, national calling minutes, national text messages, and free calls to numbers within a designated &amp;lsquo;business calling circle&amp;rsquo;. Three of the plans also include free international minutes and texts. Businesses can purchase additional &amp;lsquo;packs&amp;rsquo; to add more minutes, texts, or members to their calling circle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verify the authenticity of KSA sales and promotions using this app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</guid><description>Source: MCI. HE the Minister of Commerce and Investment Dr Majid bin Abdullah Al Qasabi launched the Sales app on 31 January 2017.
The Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) in Saudi Arabia has introduced a mobile application called &amp;ldquo;Sales.&amp;rdquo; This app allows the public to access the MCI&amp;rsquo;s database of authorized sales and promotional offers. The goal is to help users find genuine deals and discounts quickly.
Through the app, consumers can browse information on more than 27,000 retail locations and over 700,000 licensed products registered with the MCI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inexpensive cellphone you recently purchased may be counterfeit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 02:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</guid><description>The global black market for counterfeit and substandard cell phones is a significant issue, costing the industry an estimated US$6 billion each year, as reported in a recent study by the Mobile Manufacturers Forum (MMF). This comprehensive analysis, &amp;ldquo;Counterfeit/Substandard Mobile Phones - A Resource Guide for Governments&amp;rdquo;, examines the prevalence of these phones across all major brands.
According to MMF Secretary General Michael Milligan, research suggests approximately 148 million counterfeit or substandard cell phones were sold in 2013 alone, primarily through established retail channels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inexpensive-cellphone-you-recently-purchased-may-be-counterfeit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Lotus is Square to Be Hip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:19:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</guid><description>The LG Lotus LX600, a new and innovative phone in the mobile market, boasts a unique square design. Don&amp;rsquo;t let its shape fool you; this phone is powerful and designed for messaging.
The LG Lotus LX600 is slim, lightweight, and square. It flips open to reveal a full, backlit QWERTY keyboard. Despite this feature, it remains compact, even compared to typical messaging smartphones.
The LG Lotus has a lot to offer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel will provide ZoneAlarm Mobile Security protection from Check Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:16:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</guid><description>Singtel has partnered with Check Point Software Technologies to launch ZoneAlarm Mobile Security. This mobile security app offers extensive protection against digital threats like malware, hacking attempts, and Wi-Fi attacks.
ZoneAlarm, available for both iOS and Android devices, conducts thorough risk evaluations. It scans installed applications, identifies unsafe Wi-Fi networks, and suggests the safest Wi-Fi hotspot choices. Additionally, it alerts users of any questionable processes running on their phones and safeguards their operating systems from attacks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The intelligent coach for individuals with diabetes is designed to improve long-term quality of life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</guid><description>A new &amp;ldquo;smart coach&amp;rdquo; service aims to assist individuals with type 2 diabetes in developing healthier lifestyle choices for improved long-term well-being. Diabetes, particularly when poorly managed, can result in complications such as vision loss, kidney issues, and nerve damage. It has also been linked to Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease, sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;type 3 diabetes.&amp;rdquo;
The global rise of diabetes presents significant healthcare cost concerns. Holmusk, a digital health and data analytics company, highlights that over 415 million people worldwide have diabetes, a figure that continues to grow annually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel announces pricing for iPhone SE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Singtel has revealed its plans to offer Apple&amp;rsquo;s 4-inch iPhone SE starting March 31, 2016. Customers can pre-order the device now. A 16 GB model with the most affordable plan, costing S$27.90 per month for two years, is priced at S$350.
The telecom provider recently conducted a crowdsourced study, highlighting its superior 4G network speed and coverage in Singapore. The study, based on data from IDA&amp;rsquo;s MyConnection SG crowdsourced survey and 4G Mobile Service Coverage results, positioned Singtel as a frontrunner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Deep linking achieves a significant milestone in mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</guid><description>Instead of relying on traditional search engine strategies, using deep links to guide potential customers straight to the point of sale might be more effective at boosting conversion rates for e-commerce.
A recent study by Lotlinx, a company specializing in deep-linking inventory platforms for the auto industry, reveals that deep-linking attracts double the number of genuine shoppers and doubles their engagement compared to conventional search engine marketing approaches.
Criteo, TapCommerce, and ActionX have recently collaborated to introduce a standardized specification and best practice guide for deep-linking within mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G2 With Google is 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</guid><description>T-Mobile is raising the bar for smartphones with its new G2, a Google phone that seamlessly integrates with Google Voice. This allows for voicemails to be converted to text and read like emails or texts.
Powered by Android 2.2, the G2 boasts a 3.7-inch full touch screen with seven customizable home panels. Users can personalize their experience with thousands of apps and widgets from the Android Market.
One of the G2&amp;rsquo;s standout features is its Adobe Flash Player, unlike a well-known competitor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Booqed offers a selection of workspaces available for rent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</guid><description>Booqed, an online marketplace for booking meeting rooms and workspaces, has introduced its mobile app on the Apple App Store. This app offers a convenient way to find and reserve available spaces in a city, allowing users to book instantly or in advance and make payments directly from their smartphones or tablets.
Businesses can also benefit from this service by monetizing their underutilized meeting or conference rooms. Booqed provides a platform for them to list and rent out these spaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The market welcomes four new Surfaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</guid><description>Microsoft has introduced four new Surface products designed for the modern world.
Source: Microsoft website. The Surface Pro 6.
&amp;ldquo;Today, people need devices and technology that move with them and are ready whenever and wherever inspiration strikes,&amp;rdquo; stated Microsoft Chief Product Officer, Panos Panay, in a blog post.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the power of Surface, Windows, and Office working together through the cloud to provide the perfect tool. We designed these products together, optimizing every detail to empower your productivity and creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub now offers mobile phone aftersales care to customers who have SIM-only plans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced SmartSupport Lite, a new mobile phone aftersales service designed to be incredibly user-friendly. This service is specifically for customers with SIM Only plans, allowing them to quickly address any unexpected issues with their phones.
Source: StarHub SmartSupport Lite offers mobile phone aftersales care to SIM Only customers.
Signing up is simple - customers can register their existing phones digitally using the My StarHub app without needing any paperwork or activation fees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-now-offers-mobile-phone-aftersales-care-to-customers-who-have-sim-only-plans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Motorola ROKR Rocks On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</guid><description>The first iTunes phone, the Motorola ROKR, was a huge success. But instead of fading away, it has evolved into the modern ROKR E8 for T-Mobile. Is it still a great phone? You be the judge.
The sleek black design with red accents makes the Motorola ROKR E8 a striking multimedia phone. It&amp;rsquo;s actually three devices in one: a cell phone, music player, and digital camera. The touch-sensitive keypad adapts to the function you&amp;rsquo;re using...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID is the Woid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</guid><description>Motorola and Verizon have partnered to challenge the dominant Apple iPhone with their highly anticipated DROID phone. Powered by the Google Android 2.0 operating system, the DROID promises exceptional functionality. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore its features.
A key distinction between the iPhone and most other smartphones, aside from the BlackBerry Storm, is the inclusion of a physical keyboard. For those accustomed to texting on physical keys, transitioning to a touchscreen keyboard can be challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is encouraging subscribers to use their phones for payment at the supermarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</guid><description>A picture of a Dash payment reader at a FairPrice checkout.
Starting November 17th, shoppers can use Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash mobile payment app at over 200 NTUC FairPrice locations, including their supermarkets, Xtra hypermarkets, and standalone Cheers stores.
Gan Siok Hoon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of mCommerce, Consumer Singapore, stated that as a major fintech provider, they were excited to partner with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer, FairPrice, to offer this fast and secure payment option to their over half a million daily shoppers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC reveals the preferences of APAC consumers when it comes to mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 05:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</guid><description>The International Data Corporation (IDC) has released an infographic that reveals how consumers in the Asia Pacific region make decisions about mobile devices. Key findings from the Essential Guide to Device Decisions of a Connected Consumer in Asia Pacific report include:
Source: IDC infographic. What consumers like about bigger phone screens.
77% of surveyed consumers reported having a larger smartphone now than their previous device, while only 8% opted for a smaller one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel customers enjoy the top roaming experience in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Opensignal. 4G download speed experience in Mbps for Singapore roamers in Malaysia compared to the experience for Malaysian mobile users.
A 2019 Opensignal study on Singaporean 4G users roaming in Malaysia revealed that Singtel subscribers had the best download speeds, upload speeds, and latency.
M1 and StarHub users experienced comparable download and upload speeds while in Malaysia. However, StarHub users enjoyed better latency compared to M1. Although both StarHub and M1 users faced significantly slower latency than Malaysian domestic users, indicating a poorer experience, Singtel users only lagged behind domestic Maxis users by 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Save the Cell Phone, Save the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</guid><description>Cell phones are frequently overlooked as a source of environmental concern, valuable resources, and potential income. While seemingly harmless, these devices contain toxic materials and represent a significant waste problem due to their short lifespans and frequent replacement.
A cell phone&amp;rsquo;s small size and durable exterior might make it seem environmentally benign, but the internal components tell a different story. Lead, cadmium, arsenic, mercury, plastics, and glass are all found within these devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Omnia Smartphone for Smart People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Omnia&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; in Latin, a fitting name for a high-tech wireless device designed for mobile professionals.
The Samsung Omnia is a cutting-edge smartphone using the Windows Mobile 6.1 Pro operating system. It boasts a complete HTML web browser, Opera Mobile, on a 3.2-inch LCD touchscreen enhanced with Samsung TouchWiz technology. This technology provides tactile feedback through slight vibrations, while an accelerometer automatically adjusts the display based on the phone&amp;rsquo;s orientation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Flickr App for iPad has been optimized for iOS 8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a new Flickr app designed for iPads, allowing users seamless photo management across all devices. Yahoo claims the app is optimized for iOS 8, providing an enhanced experience for capturing, editing, and browsing images.
Source: Yahoo.
Current iPad users can update their existing Flickr app, while new users can download it from the App Store. The app supports multiple languages, including English, French, Indonesian, Korean, Chinese, and Vietnamese...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Doing BACKFLIPs with MOTOBLUR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 10:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</guid><description>Would you do a backflip for your current cell phone? Probably not, but Motorola&amp;rsquo;s BACKFLIP might just change your mind.
This phone&amp;rsquo;s unique feature is its reverse hinge. Unlike most phones where the keyboard is hidden beneath the screen, the BACKFLIP&amp;rsquo;s keyboard is located on the exterior, flipping open to reveal a full-size touchscreen. This design eliminates the need for a smaller internal screen, offering a more spacious keyboard and a high-resolution touchscreen experience comparable to a small computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Participate in the Singapore Mother's Day contest for a chance to win a Huawei P20 in Pink Gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</guid><description>Source: Huawei Mobile Singapore
Facebook page. Watch the video
In Singapore, Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group is holding a contest in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day (May 13th), ending on May 24th.
To participate, Singaporean residents simply need to comment on the contest video found on the Huawei Mobile Singapore Facebook page. The comment should answer the question: &amp;ldquo;What lengths would your mother go to for you?&amp;rdquo; and include the hashtag #SeeMooore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash is running a flash campaign offering mystery cashback for purchases made on Lazada.SG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment app, Dash, is holding a short promotional campaign with online store Lazada.SG. From October 2nd to 9th, 2015, shoppers can receive a surprise cashback reward of 15% to 50%*.
Each day of the campaign features a &amp;ldquo;Dash Happy Hour.&amp;rdquo; During this limited time frame, which lasts up to two hours, customers using Dash to pay for purchases on Lazada.SG can earn cashback. The specific cashback amount won&amp;rsquo;t be disclosed until the end of each day and will be added to customer accounts within three business days...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acer introduces new convertible notebooks, the Aspire R 13 and R 14</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</guid><description>Acer has introduced two new convertible notebook lines, the Aspire R 13 and Aspire R 14 Series, both capable of transitioning between various notebook and tablet modes. These notebooks are designed for users seeking the functionality of a traditional notebook with added flexibility.
Source: Acer. The R 13 in one mode.
Acer&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Jason Chen, stated that their objective is to exceed expectations with their products at every price point. He believes these Aspire convertibles are ideal for users who require both portability and productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces a mobile site in Arabic language</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced an Arabic version of its mobile website. This platform allows customers to book flights, check in online, upgrade their travel class, and access and download Apple Passbook boarding passes directly to their smartphones, regardless of the language they use on the Emirates mobile site.
The Arabic mobile platform has been launched concurrently in 15 countries across the Middle East and North Africa, including the UAE, Bahrain, Iraq, Jordan, Kuwait, Lebanon, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Morocco, and Sudan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AsiaKredit has introduced a consumer lending platform in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>AsiaKredit&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make financial services more accessible in the Philippines. They aim to achieve this by making credit easier to obtain and improving the approval rates for individuals with limited or no credit history.
Source: pera247 website. Screenshot of the pera247 app.
Pera247 is a completely digital platform offering short-term loans, up to 90 days, through a mobile wallet. These loans are typically small, unsecured, and target consumers with limited financial history...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepaid Cell Phones Are Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/</guid><description>Are you tired of feeling locked into long, expensive cell phone contracts? While those &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; phones and big discounts might sound appealing, the high cost of multi-year service plans can be daunting. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve even avoided getting a cell phone to escape that commitment. There&amp;rsquo;s another option: a pay-as-you-go service that lets you pay only for what you use.
With Net10, you&amp;rsquo;ll always know exactly what you owe. This service offers a straightforward plan: 10 cents per minute for local, long-distance, and roaming calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Galaxy A53 5G and Galaxy A33 5G are both awesome options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</guid><description>Source: Samsung. The new Galaxy A series handsets.
Samsung Electronics has released the Galaxy A53 5G and Galaxy A33 5G, incorporating the latest technology to provide a comprehensive mobile experience at an affordable price. These new Galaxy A series phones boast 5G connectivity, robust security features, and a sleek, eco-conscious design. They&amp;rsquo;re powered by a new processor, include Samsung&amp;rsquo;s AI camera, a large, responsive display, and a long-lasting battery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XOHM, XOHM's Got The Range</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</guid><description>Sprint&amp;rsquo;s XOHM (pronounced &amp;ldquo;zome,&amp;rdquo; like &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;) wireless broadband service has launched in Baltimore, marking the start of the highly anticipated rollout of WiMAX as the next generation of high-speed internet. If Sprint successfully implements its 4G vision, WiFi hotspots could become obsolete. DSL? Cable? Why bother with wires when you can have the freedom of wireless connectivity?
This vision relies on a new wireless technology standardized for global use in both fixed and mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xohm-xohms-got-the-range/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub, offering the quickest 3G and 4G network in Singapore, introduces the World's Fastest Band</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</guid><description>StarHub, a telecommunications company, has unveiled the &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Fastest Band&amp;rdquo; to celebrate its recognition in OpenSignal&amp;rsquo;s Speed Awards 2018 for having Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fastest 4G and 3G speeds. OpenSignal, a global wireless coverage mapping specialist, awarded StarHub based on network quality. StarHub&amp;rsquo;s VP of Segment &amp;amp; Marketing, Donovan Kik, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to network quality and customer satisfaction. He stated their dedication to meeting customer needs and expectations despite achieving this recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-offering-the-quickest-3g-and-4g-network-in-singapore-introduces-the-world-s-fastest-band/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive outfits for My Omamori will be available to Huawei mobile gamers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. My Omamori offers perks for Huawei users.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s mobile services branch has teamed up with Original Workshop, the creators of the female-oriented game My Omamori, to give special prizes to mobile players.
Omamori means lucky charm in Japanese. In the game, an ancient warrior, Toki Mamoru, travels to the present to become the player’s guardian angel. Mamoru, who is voiced by Japanese voice actor Yuki Ono, was developed by Taiwanese novelist Deer Li...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Top-paying technology jobs for 2014 - for those in the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</guid><description>The 2014 Salary Guides published by Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group identify six technology and digital jobs experiencing high demand in the US. This demand may also be reflected in the Asia Pacific region.
Companies are specifically seeking professionals skilled in information and network security, data analysis for business intelligence, and mobile development.
&amp;ldquo;Building a strong online presence and engaging customers through mobile platforms is crucial for businesses today,&amp;rdquo; says John Reed, Senior Executive Director of Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel now offers budget-friendly roaming options for Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
Singtel is introducing a new &amp;ldquo;Roam Like Home&amp;rdquo; DataRoam Saver plan for customers traveling to Australia. The DataRoam Saver Australia (Monthly) 1 GB plan is currently offered at a promotional price of S$10 for the first gigabyte of data. After exceeding this limit, users will be charged S$0.10 per megabyte.
Singtel claims this plan is the most budget-friendly option available and builds upon the success of the DataRoam Saver Malaysia (Monthly) 1 GB plan launched last October...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel has launched new mobile plans that include HBO content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</guid><description>Singtel has launched three innovative &amp;ldquo;XO&amp;rdquo; postpaid mobile plans, the first to offer premium entertainment as part of the package.
These new XO plans are designed to provide both generous data allowances and significant handset discounts, offering customers the best of both worlds. Additionally, XO plans include an HBO GO subscription, giving customers access to top-tier video entertainment.
The XO 78 Plan provides customers with 30 GB of data, 300 minutes of talk time, 300 SMS messages, and a 24-month HBO GO subscription for S$78 per month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-launched-new-mobile-plans-that-include-hbo-content/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google prefers websites that are optimized for mobile devices. Have you taken any steps to ensure your site is mobile-friendly?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</guid><description>World Markets Korea, a Seoul-based online marketing firm, has outlined some of the factors Google now considers when evaluating websites for mobile friendliness. These include text size, spacing between links, and whether the content fits comfortably on a mobile screen. Google uses these criteria to determine if a website is &amp;ldquo;Mobile Friendly.&amp;rdquo;
The company recommends that businesses engage their web designers to update their sites accordingly. World Markets Korea also provides services to optimize websites for mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sophos has simplified the process of securing corporate information on mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Source: Sophos website.
Sophos recently launched Sophos Mobile Control 5 (SMC 5), a software solution designed to differentiate personal and company data on devices to enhance corporate data security.
Managing devices like laptops, tablets, and smartphones often involves individual configuration, updates, and management. SMC 5 simplifies this process for IT administrators by allowing them to establish user-specific rules once to protect company data stored on the device or in personal cloud storage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV2 Sparks Envy Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</guid><description>The LG enV, nicknamed the &amp;ldquo;envy phone,&amp;rdquo; certainly attracted attention. Its successor, the enV2 VX9100, takes it up a notch, especially for those who love texting, gaming, and enjoying media on their phone.
The standout feature of the enV2 is its hidden full QWERTY keyboard. No need to fumble with a virtual keyboard on this phone! It boasts a real keyboard with comfortably sized keys. Keep your enV2 closed for calls, just like any other standard phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei has released the schedule for the EMUI10 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</guid><description>Huawei has released the global update schedule for EMUI 10. This latest version features an updated interface, a &amp;ldquo;Dark Mode&amp;rdquo; setting, performance and security improvements, and &amp;ldquo;Multi-screen Collaboration&amp;rdquo; which allows Huawei PCs and Android devices to seamlessly connect.
Starting this month, users with the HUAWEI P30 Pro, HUAWEI P30, HUAWEI Mate 20 Pro, HUAWEI Mate 20, HUAWEI Mate 20 X (4G) and HUAWEI nova 5T will get push notifications to install the EMUI 10 update...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Have SIM, Will Travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</guid><description>SIM Simminy, SIM Simminy, SIM SIM Siree
Having the right phone is essential for international travel.
Traveling to a foreign country can be exciting, but discovering your cell phone is unusable can put a damper on your trip. Without a working phone, you&amp;rsquo;ll be stuck using expensive hotel phones to stay in touch.
Fortunately, with a little planning, you can avoid this problem. The key is to ensure your cell phone is compatible with the network used in your destination country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepaid Business Calling Controls Phone Expense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 17:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/</guid><description>Your business phone costs are becoming unmanageable, especially in today&amp;rsquo;s economic climate. While unlimited calling might have been acceptable in the past, now it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to minimize expenses. This year, prioritize controlling calling habits and securing the most cost-effective rates for both domestic and international calls.
TEL3Business offers tools to manage your business calls, whether from landlines or mobile phones. Their strategy combines technology with competitive rates, empowering managers to optimize their telephone budgets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-business-calling-controls-phone-expense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2015 Vuclip Global Video Insights reveals that Malaysian consumers are seeking uncomplicated entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Vuclip, a leading mobile video-on-demand (VOD) service in emerging markets, has published its Global Video Insights (GVI) 2015 Survey. The study examines video consumption trends and device preferences among Malaysian consumers.
Source: Vuclip. Prakash.
Malaysian consumers value several features in an over-the-top (OTT) content player. The most important are a seamless user interface (61%), uninterrupted viewing experience (58%), high-definition video quality (56%), and access to the newest videos (54%). Other desirable features include adjustable streaming quality (47%), video downloads (46%), and simultaneous multiple video downloads (45%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Support World Vision in the Philippines by using the Gift It app to make a contribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</guid><description>World Vision, a charitable organization, has teamed up with Gift It, a crowdgifting platform. Gift It allows users to create personalized campaigns to fund gifts from various stores or support charitable causes through foundation partners.
Jun Godornes, World Vision&amp;rsquo;s Director for National Resources and Development, highlights the app&amp;rsquo;s convenience, stating it simplifies giving while raising awareness for their programs that support children through education, disaster relief, and economic development. Gift It also features a social aspect, enabling friends to contribute collaboratively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Have The Instinct For Covert Ops?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</guid><description>Ever imagine yourself as a secret agent like Jack Bauer from the show &amp;ldquo;24&amp;rdquo;? The Samsung Instinct phone, especially in sleek black, is your gateway to that world. Packed with features, it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate device for any aspiring operative.
The large, high-resolution touchscreen provides crystal-clear visuals and even vibrates slightly when you touch it, ensuring precise navigation. Its powerful 2.0 Megapixel camera captures high-quality photos and videos suitable for sharing or printing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There are many options to choose from when it comes to Intel mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Thinking about buying a new PC? A laptop might be a better choice than a desktop, or maybe even a tablet. Intel powers a wider variety of devices than ever before.
Sumner Lemon, Country Manager for Intel Singapore &amp;amp; Malaysia, points out that &amp;ldquo;2015 is the Year of the Goat - an animal known for being curious, clever, and ambitious,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;Intel shares these values as we continue to innovate and push the limits of computing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-are-many-options-to-choose-from-when-it-comes-to-intel-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The key to e-commerce success according to Akamai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</guid><description>Akamai, a content delivery network (CDN) provider, emphasizes the importance of speed in e-commerce, stating that slow loading times can lead to customer loss. They suggest two key ways online retailers can improve their businesses: by understanding modern customer behavior and by prioritizing speed, intelligence, and security in their online operations.
Mobile shopping is a growing trend. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s data shows that mobile and tablet shoppers make purchases 20% more often and spend US$500 more than desktop users in the same timeframe, highlighting the need for strong mobile optimization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Shows its Curve in Pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</guid><description>Who says productivity can&amp;rsquo;t be stylish? Why not combine technology and beauty in the business world? It&amp;rsquo;s definitely possible!
The BlackBerry Curve 8330 Pink for Verizon Wireless is a perfect example. This device deserves a spot in a movie, maybe titled &amp;ldquo;Pretty in Pink&amp;rdquo;—although that title is already taken, it perfectly captures the essence of this phone. This classic BlackBerry delivers on productivity while boasting an elegant curved design and a lovely pink exterior...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank has enhanced its mobile application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</guid><description>Source: Alizz Islamic Bank. The app.
Alizz Islamic Bank has introduced a redesigned mobile banking app and online platform to solidify its position as a customer experience frontrunner in Oman.
The dual-language app, compatible with both Android and iOS devices, boasts high-level security features and a self-registration option. Users can conveniently manage web banking logins, money transfers, bill payments, and other transactions using QR codes. The app is compatible with 3D Touch technology and is the first of its kind in Oman to provide in-app alerts for new transactions and payment reminders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is debate over whether mobile phones can cause cancer, with some believing they can and others disagreeing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</guid><description>There have been many concerns about mobile phones and cancer risks. Since the first mobile phone&amp;rsquo;s debut in 1984 and their rise in popularity in the 1990s, it&amp;rsquo;s taken time to study the long-term effects of mobile phone radiation, as some cancers take years to manifest. We might only now be starting to see the impact.
A recent study in Pathophysiology suggests that radiation from mobile and cordless phones could contribute to a specific brain tumor called glioma...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-debate-over-whether-mobile-phones-can-cause-cancer-with-some-believing-they-can-and-others-disagreeing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Insurance is now available through Singtel's Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash app is launching Dash EasyEarn, a new financial product offering a 2% annual return. This insurance savings plan is available exclusively through the Dash app and is backed by Etiqa Insurance.
Source: Singtel. Dash EasyEarn is a fully digital insurance product, allowing users to manage their plans entirely through the Singtel Dash app.
This innovative addition to the Dash app, which already provides various services like payments and mobile top-ups, aims to make saving simple and accessible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Optimize marketing tactics with native mobile strategies tailored for the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 15:56:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Sinead Woodley, Managing Director UK at April Six, a digital marketing agency, emphasizes that the right marketing approach can significantly enhance early buyer engagement for tech companies. Speaking at the Asia Pacific launch of April Six in Singapore, she highlighted how technology can be leveraged to achieve this.
Woodley cited EMEA-wide campaigns for VMware as a prime example, where April Six successfully reached IT professionals who are typically averse to marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new version of McAfee Mobile Security has been launched by Intel Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</guid><description>Intel Security has released the newest version of McAfee Mobile Security (MMS) for Android devices. This updated software offers enhanced security and improved device performance.
As people increasingly rely on their mobile devices for personal and sensitive tasks, MMS provides protection and addresses the need for faster speeds, longer battery life, and secure browsing on Android phones and tablets.
This new version of MMS allows users to maximize their Android device performance with features that optimize speed and battery life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces two phablets in the Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 05:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new mobile devices to their collection: the 6-inch HP Slate6 VoiceTab and the 7-inch HP Slate7 VoiceTab. These &amp;ldquo;voice tablets&amp;rdquo; will be released in India this February*.
These devices combine the functions of a phone and a tablet into one portable design. “The voice tablet market is growing because consumers want to combine their phones and tablets into one device,” said Ron Coughlin, Senior VP of HP&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Personal Systems Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year in the Philippines, the focus is on mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</guid><description>In the Philippines, technology is synonymous with mobile technology.
According to Jubert Alberto, Research Manager at IDC Philippines, &amp;ldquo;The younger generation is entering the workforce, and they have a strong desire to be connected, informed, and entertained. They also tend to have fewer dependents. These factors indicate a growing demand for all things mobile, including devices, services, and applications.&amp;rdquo; IDC predicts that the Philippines will experience a 22% rise in smartphone spending and a 40% increase in tablet expenditure in 2014, fueled by a positive economic outlook...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New touchless camera app is now accessible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:22:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/</guid><description>Source: Crunchfish.
Crunchfish, in partnership with MOMAX, has introduced MOMAX cam, a hands-free camera application for selfie sticks.
MOMAX cam allows users to take pictures using gestures, touch, and Bluetooth.
Here are some of its key features:
Snap photos with a simple V-sign gesture. Use a touchless grab gesture to set the timer for capturing photos from up to 3 meters away. Switch between the front and rear cameras, as well as zoom in and out, using the Bluetooth trigger to get the perfect shot...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The enhanced Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB from ALE simplifies collaboration and boosts productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</guid><description>Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise, operating under the Alcatel-Lucent Enterprise brand, helps small and medium businesses provide a streamlined user experience and enhanced onsite mobility for their employees, while ensuring business continuity. This is achieved through the latest update of their product, Alcatel-Lucent OpenTouch Suite for SMB.
The latest improvements to OpenTouch Suite for SMB focus on increasing productivity and efficiency. This is achieved through expanded communication and collaborative tools, as well as enabling employees to access the company environment from any location, at any time, using mobile applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-enhanced-alcatel-lucent-opentouch-suite-for-smb-from-ale-simplifies-collaboration-and-boosts-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC has launched the HTC Desire 826 dual sim, promising an exceptional mobile audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The Blue Lagoon version.
HTC is enhancing the mobile audio experience with its Desire 826 dual sim phone, featuring HTC BoomSound and Dolby Audio surround sound. This makes HTC the first smartphone manufacturer to integrate dual front-facing stereo speakers, a precisely adjusted sound profile, and Dolby&amp;rsquo;s decoding technology for a comprehensive multi-channel audio solution.
This combination provides listeners with a level of audio depth and range not typically found in mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drowning in a Sea of Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 10:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</guid><description>Current estimations show approximately three billion mobile phone users globally, with a billion new devices sold annually. Given that phones are typically replaced every two to three years, this equates to roughly one billion phones becoming obsolete yearly. The question then arises: where do these discarded devices end up?
Contrary to assumptions that they are forgotten in drawers, a recent study revealed that only 44% of old phones remain unused at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evernote introduces a new and improved app with a redesigned interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</guid><description>Evernote has announced three updates: a brand new app, a significantly enhanced feature, and a major app redesign.
As detailed in a recent blog post, the company will introduce &amp;ldquo;Scannable,&amp;rdquo; a mobile scanning app. Scannable can transform physical items like business cards and receipts into digital content that can be easily shared and acted upon. It also integrates with the ScanSnap Evernote Edition desktop scanner, enabling shared scanning across a user&amp;rsquo;s network and essentially turning it into a shared office resource...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For Free Phone Aficionados Only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</guid><description>Looking for a free cell phone? Look no further than Cell Phone Plan Finder&amp;rsquo;s free phones section. This site is completely dedicated to showcasing free phones available when you sign up for a service contract.
This screenshot only displays a limited selection. As of today, there are 23 free phone models from leading carriers such as Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, AT&amp;amp;T, and Sprint.
The selection includes various BlackBerry models like the Bold, Curve, Storm, and Tour...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks Indonesia has launched the Starbucks Mobile App</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Use the mobile app to make purchases at Starbucks.
Starbucks Indonesia has launched its mobile app, offering customers a quick and easy way to pay at over 260 stores across the country.
Expanding upon the cashless Starbucks Card system introduced in 2013, the Starbucks Indonesia mobile app (available on iPhone and Android) allows customers to pay for purchases by scanning a barcode linked to their registered Starbucks Card...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avast Wi-Fi Finder helps you find trustworthy Wi-Fi connections globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</guid><description>Avast has released Avast Wi-Fi Finder, an Android app that helps users locate trustworthy, fast, and secure Wi-Fi connections no matter where they are. The app uses a map interface to display recommended and crowdsourced hotspots.
&amp;ldquo;Many of us, whether traveling or working remotely, have struggled to find dependable and secure Wi-Fi,&amp;rdquo; said Gagan Singh, President of mobile at Avast. &amp;ldquo;With Avast Wi-Fi Finder, consumers can now easily locate a safe and fast Wi-Fi connection at the gym, hotel, airport, bus station, library, or café...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Traveloka will introduce awards based on audience participation for Asia's Got Talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 13:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</guid><description>Traveloka, a popular Southeast Asian travel app, is sponsoring the second season of AXN&amp;rsquo;s Asia&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent and introducing the Traveloka Awards.
The Traveloka Awards will recognize the contestant with the most compelling background, emphasizing unique talents and strong family and friend connections.
Premiering this October, Asia’s Got Talent on AXN will feature ten episodes, including auditions, semifinals, a finale, and a results show revealing the winner of a $100,000 prize from Traveloka...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoPhones For Hurricane Gustav</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 08:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/</guid><description>During the preparations for Hurricane Gustav, AT&amp;amp;T gave out over 2,000 GoPhones with $15 of pre-loaded airtime to Gulf Coast evacuees. This act of generosity brought attention to the GoPhone and its potential use as an emergency phone.
AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s GoPhone isn&amp;rsquo;t a specific phone model but a prepaid cellular service. Unlike traditional cell phone plans that require contracts and monthly fees regardless of usage, GoPhone lets you pay for airtime in advance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gophones-for-hurricane-gustav/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new version of Flickr is now available for iOS 9</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 02:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s Flickr app for iOS 9 now includes features designed for the updated operating system.
Source: Yahoo.
The app utilizes 3D Touch on the latest iPhones. This allows users to preview content by pressing lightly on the screen. For example, in the Camera Roll, lightly pressing a photo shows a preview, while a harder press expands it to full screen.
Another 3D Touch feature, &amp;ldquo;Quick Actions,&amp;rdquo; lets users perform certain tasks directly from the app icon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ally In The Android vs iPhone Battle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 20:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s initial Android offering, the LG Ally for Verizon Wireless, is a remarkable device. It boasts a range of features and access to a vast library of apps on the Android Market.
If you prioritize texting and email, you&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the tactile feedback of real keys. The LG Ally features a 3.2-inch touchscreen and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with well-sized keys. With five customizable home screens, you can personalize it with numerous Android apps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing complimentary content and data to commemorate Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 51st birthday on August 9th, Singtel is offering customers complimentary mobile data, alongside free access to Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO.
Postpaid mobile users will enjoy free data from 12:01 am to 11:59 pm on August 9th, allowing them to connect with family and friends on social media, stream music, and watch videos.
From August 5th to 9th, Singtel TV subscribers will have free access to over 140 channels, including popular options like Disney Channel, National Geographic Channel HD, FOX Movie Premium HD, KBS World HD, Astro Ria, and Sun TV...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo measures the passion for travel among Singaporeans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</guid><description>Mobile travel purchases saw a 35% surge between 2011 and 2016, a trend predicted to continue its upward trajectory. Accessibility (74%) and convenience (69%) are the primary motivators for respondents&amp;rsquo; preference to browse travel products online. A significant 78% choose smartphones over desktops/laptops for browsing due to their on-the-go functionality.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology firm, highlights the continuous growth of mobile travel sales, emphasizing it as a prime growth avenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub simplifies mobile customers' ability to browse and travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile postpaid customers can now subscribe to a Mobile DataTravel plan for S$15. This plan offers 2GB of data valid for 30 days, usable in a single country or across multiple destinations.
DataTravel eliminates the need to manually select or lock phones to specific mobile networks, unlike traditional roaming plans. StarHub highlights this as a unique advantage among Singaporean telcos and plans to expand its list of supported destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red, Red, LG Vu Wine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 22:49:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</guid><description>Everyone enjoys a nice wine with dinner, but what about in business or on the go? It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly acceptable when that &amp;ldquo;wine&amp;rdquo; is the new touchscreen phone available from AT&amp;amp;T.
This &amp;ldquo;red wine&amp;rdquo; phone boasts more features than a full-bodied Cabernet. Its compact size of 4.3 x 2.1 x 0.5 inches makes it easy to carry in your pocket or bag. You read that correctly – this device is only half an inch thin!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean banks are getting their customers ready for Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 09:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s website in Singapore now features a dedicated page for Apple Pay, which includes a list of participating banks and retailers. Among the banks listed, DBS and POSB have almost identical images on their websites, and UOB also has a dedicated page. Standard Chartered currently does not have any information available. DBS clarifies that Apple Pay offers a fast and secure payment method compatible with a user&amp;rsquo;s preferred DBS card. Contactless payments are also supported for iPhone and Apple Watch users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SmartUp introduces the Digital Readiness Experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</guid><description>Source: SmartUp website.
Screen capture of the SmartUp
platform.
SmartUp, a mobile-first knowledge-sharing platform, has introduced a Digital Readiness Experience. This offering utilizes microlearning modules to educate the workforce on trending technology topics.
This multi-week Digital Readiness Experience is available for purchase by SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s corporate clients for their employees, as explained by Deborah Tan-Pink, SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s Global Head of Marketing.
&amp;ldquo;The Digital Readiness Experience is a four-to-six-week program designed to shift attitudes and knowledge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides triple the mobile data for a low price, along with Wi-Fi calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</guid><description>Singtel launched a new mobile data add-on called DataX3 at their iPhone 7 event held at Marina Bay Sands Convention Centre. For S$9.90 per month, DataX3 allows customers to triple their mobile data limit. This add-on is available to Singtel Combo Plan customers (Combo 2 and above). It follows the successful launch of the DataX2 add-on earlier this year.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, highlighted the importance of affordable mobile data for communication, shopping, banking, and entertainment in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-triple-the-mobile-data-for-a-low-price-along-with-wi-fi-calling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Subscribe to Grabz for exclusive insider privileges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</guid><description>Source: Grabz website.
Grabz is a subscription service that provides its members with exclusive benefits and special offers. Using location-based alerts and a wide range of affiliated businesses, the app connects its subscribers with exclusive deals and privileges in their city.
For a monthly fee of S$15.98, premium members enjoy invitations to events and promotions such as discounted business class airfare and exclusive access to limited-edition luxury watches.
Premium members also get access to the Grabz Concierge, a personalized booking service that assists members with securing reservations at clubs and getting on guest lists for exclusive parties in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>