<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PDF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pdf/</link><description>Recent content in PDF on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 23:21:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pdf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Textbooks Move To The iPad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/textbooks-move-to-the-ipad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 23:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/textbooks-move-to-the-ipad/</guid><description>College students are familiar with the weight and cost of traditional textbooks. However, eTextbooks offer a significantly cheaper and lighter alternative, available at a 30-50% discount compared to physical books. The future of education is digital, and eTextbooks are leading the way.
Electronic textbooks offer several advantages over print. Firstly, the cost is significantly lower. Physical textbooks are expensive to produce due to their size and durable materials, which aren’t as necessary since students often don’t keep their books long-term.</description></item><item><title>Adobe improves the functionality of the PDF format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-improves-the-functionality-of-the-pdf-format/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-improves-the-functionality-of-the-pdf-format/</guid><description>Adobe has introduced new features for Adobe Document Cloud, providing user-friendly mobile experiences. Document Cloud enables users to work seamlessly across integrated cloud services, mobile, and desktop applications. Leading this update are enhancements to Adobe Sign for increased usability and accessibility, and Adobe Scan, a new complimentary app that transforms mobile devices into smart scanning and text recognition tools.
&amp;ldquo;Documents are fundamental to society, conveying information from contracts and textbooks to financial statements and everything in between,&amp;rdquo; stated Abhay Parasnis, CTO of Adobe.</description></item></channel></rss>