<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MWC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mwc/</link><description>Recent content in MWC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mwc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LG Stylus 2 will make its first appearance at MWC 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</guid><description>LG will introduce the LG Stylus 2 at the upcoming Mobile World Congress 2016 in Barcelona, Spain.
Source: LG. The LG Stylus 2.
The LG Stylus 2 is slimmer and lighter than its predecessor, measuring 7.4mm thick and weighing 145g. This follow-up to the G4 Stylus boasts a 5.7&amp;quot; HD display for an enhanced viewing experience.
Using the LG Stylus 2 mimics the experience of writing with a traditional pen and notepad.</description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day.</description></item><item><title>The Alcatel IDOL 4 Series offers enhanced multimedia features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-idol-4-series-offers-enhanced-multimedia-features/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-idol-4-series-offers-enhanced-multimedia-features/</guid><description>Boom Key provides personalized features for taking pictures, enjoying music, and improving user experience.
Audio experience powered by Waves and JBL, including high-quality JBL headphones included in the box.
Three-way reversibility: sound travels from left to right or front to back, and the user interface adapts when flipped upside down.
VR-in-the-box: VR goggles create an immersive virtual reality experience anywhere, anytime*
ALCATEL has introduced its premium IDOL 4 and IDOL 4S smartphones, offering an enhanced multimedia experience.</description></item><item><title>HTC and holoride introduce glasses that are ready for a ride</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-and-holoride-introduce-glasses-that-are-ready-for-a-ride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 07:07:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-and-holoride-introduce-glasses-that-are-ready-for-a-ride/</guid><description>HTC VIVE, a leading virtual reality platform, is teaming up with holoride, an innovative in-car entertainment company, to bring XR experiences to passengers. Launching in the latter half of 2022, holoride&amp;rsquo;s technology blends extended reality content with real-time car data, such as motion and location, to craft immersive adventures synchronized with the journey.
HTC&amp;rsquo;s VIVE Flow, a lightweight and portable VR headset, will be the first to integrate holoride&amp;rsquo;s technology for in-car use.</description></item></channel></rss>