<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Laptop on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/laptop/</link><description>Recent content in Laptop on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/laptop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Preorder the HUAWEI Matebook X Pro now in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</guid><description>Huawei Consumer Business Group is introducing the HUAWEI MateBook X Pro to its Singapore laptop collection. Until August 16, 2020, customers can take advantage of special gift packages worth S$250 to S$1,200 when they purchase select laptops.
The premium MateBook X Pro boasts a sleek, metallic design with a sandblasted finish. At just 14.6 mm thick and 1.33 kg, it prioritizes portability without sacrificing a truly immersive viewing experience.
Source: Huawei.</description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new laptops and monitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-laptops-and-monitors/</guid><description>Dell Singapore has launched new laptops and a monitor for consumers.
The XPS 12 is the first 2-in-1 laptop with a 4K Ultra HD display. The Inspiron 11 3000 series offers an affordable and portable laptop option available in three colors. Dell also released their first 4K consumer monitor, the Dell 28 Ultra HD 4K Monitor.
&amp;ldquo;Consumers have increasingly diverse needs. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a student or a professional, size, power, design, and price all matter.</description></item><item><title>Targus introduces the T-1211 line of laptop and tablet cases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/targus-introduces-the-t-1211-line-of-laptop-and-tablet-cases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 04:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/targus-introduces-the-t-1211-line-of-laptop-and-tablet-cases/</guid><description>Targus, a company known for its laptop cases and accessories, has introduced the T-1211 collection, a new line of laptop and tablet cases designed for both work and everyday commutes.
The T-1211 cases have a sleek, minimalist design accented by a subtle crosshatch pattern. Every case in the collection features a water-resistant exterior and a scratch-resistant interior lining.
The T-1211 13.3”-17” Backpack offers a spacious yet streamlined design with multiple compartments for organization.</description></item><item><title>You can now pre-order the new Microsoft Surface 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-pre-order-the-new-microsoft-surface-3/</guid><description>At an event in Singapore in April, bloggers were given the opportunity to test out the Surface 3, as well as the Lumia 640 and 640 XL.
The Surface Pro was a hit, but some users desired more. Ian Tan, the Surface Lead for Consumer at Microsoft Singapore, revealed during a media event that certain customers requested a lighter, more budget-friendly device, a request to which Microsoft paid attention.</description></item><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series.</description></item><item><title>Promotions for Dell at CEE 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</guid><description>Dell is promoting several products at the Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) 2017. These products, equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors, are designed for an excellent visual experience and enhanced gameplay.
Here are some of the featured products:
Inspiron 13 5000 2-in-1
Original Price: Starting from S$1,699 Show Price: Starting from S$1,299 Features:
Latest 7th Gen Intel Core processor 13.3&amp;quot; FHD (1,920 x 1,080) IPS Truelife LED-backlit touchscreen with wide viewing angles and an infrared (IR) camera Four versatile modes: tent, stand, laptop, and tablet XPS 13 2-in-1</description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life.</description></item><item><title>HP's Elite business PCs excel in performance, productivity, and security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 22:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</guid><description>HP has introduced its latest Elite business PCs, including the exceptionally thin and light HP EliteBook 705 series, an all-in-one (AiO) model, and a refreshed desktop lineup featuring the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest business-class desktop.
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the demand for high-end Elite notebook innovation to be extended to a wider range of employees and devices. HP&amp;rsquo;s response is the Elite 705 and 800 Series PCs, which bring sleek design, enhanced collaboration features, and robust security to mainstream business devices.</description></item><item><title>Dell unveils CES award-winning products at IT Show 2017 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-unveils-ces-award-winning-products-at-it-show-2017-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:19:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-unveils-ces-award-winning-products-at-it-show-2017-in-singapore/</guid><description>Dell unveiled new personal computing products at the IT Show 2017 in Singapore. First shown at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in January 2017, these products are equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors to create an enhanced visual and gaming experience.
[Image of Dell Inspiron 15 Gaming series]
Source: Dell website. The Dell Inspiron 15 Gaming series.
Inspiron 15 Gaming (CES Industry Awards Honoree, Gaming category) Features like strategically placed thermal outlets, dual fans, and large pipes and heat exchangers work together to prevent overheating during extended gaming.</description></item><item><title>HP introduces the thinnest laptop in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-the-thinnest-laptop-in-the-world/</guid><description>Every Spectre accessory has been designed to provide a luxurious experience.
The CNC machined aluminum body is as sleek as an AAA battery at a mere 10.4mm. Enjoy exceptional performance with Intel Core i5 and i7 processors. Immerse yourself in the vibrant visuals of a full HD 13.3&amp;quot; edge-to-edge display complemented by Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen sound. HP claims to have developed the slimmest laptop globally, meticulously refining every detail to provide an unmatched user experience and peak performance.</description></item><item><title>HP updates Pavilion features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-updates-pavilion-features/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pavilion PCs, including convertibles and notebooks, designed to be stylish and powerful. The company aims to provide customers with a range of options to suit their needs and budgets.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that HP understands customers&amp;rsquo; diverse needs, with some prioritizing portability and others seeking performance. The redesigned Pavilion PCs cater to both, offering affordability and style.</description></item><item><title>Huawei will be offering laptops for sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore customers can purchase the HUAWEI MateBook 13 and MateBook X Pro starting May 30, 2019.
The HUAWEI P30 Pro in Amber Sunrise will be offered for models with 512 GB of storage.
The Huawei Consumer Business Group Singapore has revealed its plan to expand its product lineup in Singapore beyond smartphones and smartwatches to include laptops. This new laptop selection features the latest HUAWEI MateBook 13 and MateBook X Pro.</description></item><item><title>Aftershock introduces the new Apex 15X EVO hybrid performance laptop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aftershock-introduces-the-new-apex-15x-evo-hybrid-performance-laptop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 23:40:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aftershock-introduces-the-new-apex-15x-evo-hybrid-performance-laptop/</guid><description>Source: Aftershock PC. The new Apex 15x EVO takes over as a flagship model.
Aftershock PC, a leading custom PC builder in Singapore, has introduced the Apex 15X EVO. This laptop is among the first to use a hybrid cooling system with both liquid and air cooling, pushing the boundaries of portable computer performance.
The Apex 15X EVO represents a new class of laptops. It combines a redesigned internal structure with an external liquid-cooling device, the Aftershock Glacier Core, to achieve exceptional processing power in a portable design.</description></item><item><title>The market welcomes four new Surfaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</guid><description>Microsoft has introduced four new Surface products designed for the modern world.
Source: Microsoft website. The Surface Pro 6.
&amp;ldquo;Today, people need devices and technology that move with them and are ready whenever and wherever inspiration strikes,&amp;rdquo; stated Microsoft Chief Product Officer, Panos Panay, in a blog post.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the power of Surface, Windows, and Office working together through the cloud to provide the perfect tool. We designed these products together, optimizing every detail to empower your productivity and creativity.</description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure.</description></item><item><title>Acer introduces new convertible notebooks, the Aspire R 13 and R 14</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</guid><description>Acer has introduced two new convertible notebook lines, the Aspire R 13 and Aspire R 14 Series, both capable of transitioning between various notebook and tablet modes. These notebooks are designed for users seeking the functionality of a traditional notebook with added flexibility.
Source: Acer. The R 13 in one mode.
Acer&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Jason Chen, stated that their objective is to exceed expectations with their products at every price point. He believes these Aspire convertibles are ideal for users who require both portability and productivity.</description></item><item><title>Fujitsu introduces new mobile products in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujitsu-introduces-new-mobile-products-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 13:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujitsu-introduces-new-mobile-products-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Fujitsu. The LIFEBOOK U7310/D.
Fujitsu and its subsidiary, Fujitsu Client Computing, have introduced new mobile devices designed to support the changing workstyles of their customers, particularly in remote work environments.
The new product lineup consists of nine FUJITSU Notebook LIFEBOOK models, four Fujitsu Tablet ARROWS Tab models (running on Windows), and a Fujitsu Workstation CELSIUS model. These devices are equipped with the latest CPUs and operating systems, with the exception of the CELSIUS model*.</description></item><item><title>Dell introduces an improved range of PCs for both consumer and commercial markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</guid><description>Dell debuted groundbreaking personal computing innovations at the annual Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in the US. They also updated their XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware consumer lines. Their OptiPlex, Latitude, and Precision commercial products received upgrades to 7th Gen Intel Core processors, USB-C with Thunderbolt 3 connectivity, and new professional graphics from NVIDIA and AMD. Dell&amp;rsquo;s monitor lineup also saw a refresh. The new Dell PC portfolio is equipped with Windows 10 and 7th Gen Intel Core processors, designed to maximize user productivity and creativity.</description></item><item><title>LG will be unveiling its 2020 laptops at CES 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-unveiling-its-2020-laptops-at-ces-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:23:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-unveiling-its-2020-laptops-at-ces-2020/</guid><description>Source: LG. The LG gram 14T90N in action.
LG&amp;rsquo;s 2020 gram laptops maintain their focus on lightweight, compact design and long battery life, with the added benefit of improved performance. This refreshed lineup boasts a sleek, minimalist aesthetic and enhanced features.
Leading LG&amp;rsquo;s new gram series are the LG gram 17 (model 17Z90N), LG gram 15 (model 15Z90N), LG gram 14 (model 14Z90N), and the 14&amp;quot; LG gram 2-in-1 (model 14T90N).</description></item><item><title>The Apple Macbook is revolutionizing the laptop industry with its numerous innovative features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apple-macbook-is-revolutionizing-the-laptop-industry-with-its-numerous-innovative-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 02:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apple-macbook-is-revolutionizing-the-laptop-industry-with-its-numerous-innovative-features/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The new MacBook is offered in three aluminum finishes—gold, silver, and space gray. Its thickest point measures 13.1 mm.
Apple has introduced the redesigned MacBook, a new notebook lineup representing the thinnest and lightest Macs to date. Every aspect of the new MacBook has been meticulously redesigned to achieve a remarkably thin and light profile, weighing a mere two pounds and measuring a mere 13.1 mm thick.</description></item><item><title>Dell updates its Inspiron laptop lineup and unveils new business devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-its-inspiron-laptop-lineup-and-unveils-new-business-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 03:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-its-inspiron-laptop-lineup-and-unveils-new-business-devices/</guid><description>Check out the Inspiron 7000 series unveiling on Instagram.
- Dell introduces a new collection of business devices including the Inspiron 7000 series and Alienware&amp;rsquo;s latest gaming accessories at their updated Dell Exclusive Store located in Singapore
- The latest Inspiron 13 7000 2-in-1 packs impressive visuals and robust performance into a compact design - Experience heightened gaming immersion with the Inspiron 15 Gaming Laptop, equipped with NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060 discrete graphics - The award-winning XPS 13 is now up to 44% more potent thanks to the integration of new 8th Generation Intel Core i7 processors</description></item><item><title>Acer unveils three convertible notebooks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-unveils-three-convertible-notebooks/</guid><description>Acer has expanded its line of 2-in-1 notebooks with the new 11.6&amp;quot; Aspire Switch 11 series and a new Switch 10 featuring a 1080p Full HD 10.1&amp;quot; display. The Aspire Switch 2-in-1 series combines a Microsoft Windows notebook and tablet in one device.
Source: Acer. The Aspire Switch 10.
The Aspire Switch series is thin, lightweight, and durable, designed for work and travel. It supports four modes: touch, typing, viewing, and sharing.</description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights.</description></item><item><title>Computer Recycling Easier Than Ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-recycling-easier-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 02:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-recycling-easier-than-ever/</guid><description>Most people own several computers at home, but many go unused due to outdated specifications. Instead of letting them gather dust, have you considered selling or recycling them for cash?
Computer recycling is a relatively new concept. Previously, old computers were relegated to storage or landfills. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing concern about the environmental impact of discarded electronics. Many communities now organize recycling events, offering a responsible disposal method. But instead of giving away your old computers, you can sell them for profit.</description></item><item><title>HP introduces a limited edition notebook featuring a Star Wars theme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</guid><description>In anticipation of the release of Star Wars: &amp;ldquo;The Force Awakens,&amp;rdquo; HP has launched a special edition notebook.
“As the only PC vendor collaborating with Disney and Lucasfilm, HP is providing an incredible Star Wars experience by creating a truly unique notebook,&amp;quot; shared Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore. &amp;ldquo;This collaboration granted us access to Lucasfilm’s media archives, which we used to create customizable screen savers, desktop backgrounds, and sound profiles.</description></item></channel></rss>