<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>White Paper on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/white-paper/</link><description>Recent content in White Paper on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/white-paper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The guidelines for using YouTube have been published by the UAE's Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</guid><description>The Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA) of the UAE has introduced guidelines for using YouTube as part of its UAE Social Media White Papers series.
The TRA highlights the immense popularity of YouTube, with over a billion unique monthly users and over 100 hours of video uploaded every minute. They emphasize that UAE law forbids publishing content that violates public morals, Islamic principles, and the social and moral well-being of the UAE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A white paper providing solutions for talent management in the Chinese hospitality industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</guid><description>Florida International University&amp;rsquo;s Chaplin School of Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Management (CSHTM) and its Institute for Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Education &amp;amp; Research (IHTER) have published a new resource for HR professionals and hospitality businesses, particularly those working with Chinese markets. The white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Managing Growing Pains of China’s Relentless Hotel Development Pipeline,&amp;rdquo; examines the significant lack of qualified talent within China&amp;rsquo;s rapidly expanding hotel industry. The paper offers practical solutions such as professional development programs, conflict resolution strategies, and clearly defined career paths to attract and retain skilled employees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dispute resolution between the EU and UK after Brexit in the context of the White Paper.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Emilija Leinarte*
*Professor of EU law, University of Cambridge and PhD student, University of Cambridge. This research has received support from the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme.
A recent publication by UK in a Changing Europe examined various governing structures that could be used to manage the UK-EU relationship following Brexit. The released White Paper offers a glimpse into the institutional structure that the UK envisions for its future dealings with the EU after withdrawal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>