<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HubSpot on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hubspot/</link><description>Recent content in HubSpot on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:31:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hubspot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HubSpot reveals the secrets of inbound marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot presentation. A higher volume of content leads to increased lead generation.
Ryan Bonnici, HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan, argues that traditional methods of customer acquisition are no longer effective. During the launch of HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Singapore office, which also serves as the company&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters, Bonnici explained the effectiveness of inbound marketing compared to outbound marketing.
Traditionally, marketing involved bombarding consumers with advertisements and flyers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hubspot's new, modern Asia Pacific headquarters in Singapore is designed with Millennials in mind</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot. Pictured at the official opening ceremony, from left: Jeetu Mahtani and JD Sherman.
HubSpot has officially launched its Singapore office and revealed plans to add 150 employees to its Singapore-based team over the next three years. Currently, HubSpot Singapore has 30 employees.
The Singapore office, warmly referred to as SingSpot, joins the Sydney, Australia office as HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s second location in the Asia Pacific region and will serve as the company’s Asia Pacific headquarters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HubSpot uncovers the true desires of buyers when it comes to salespeople</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</guid><description>HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s recent report, Asia Pacific Buyers Have Spoken: Sales Needs to Evolve, reveals what Asia Pacific buyers desire in a sales experience, from initial call topics to the best time for sales interactions.
The report suggests that sales isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily becoming more challenging, but rather traditional sales strategies are losing their effectiveness. The mismatch between current sales tactics and buyer expectations is the root of the problem. HubSpot asserts that conversions will increase if salespeople align their approach with buyer preferences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>