<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accommodation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accommodation/</link><description>Recent content in Accommodation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accommodation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The launch of Fairfield by Marriott Belitung has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its Fairfield by Marriott brand with the opening of a new hotel in Belitung, Indonesia.
Source: Fairfield by Marriott Belitung website. The Fairfield by Marriott Belitung.
Mike Fulkerson, Vice President of Brand &amp;amp; Marketing for Marriott International Asia Pacific, stated that Fairfield by Marriott is experiencing rapid growth in the region, with 47 properties in development in Asia Pacific and over 400 globally. He highlighted the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing a relaxing and dependable experience at a good value, enhanced by Indonesian hospitality, making the Belitung location an ideal retreat for travelers.</description></item><item><title>Azerai offers affordable luxury in Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Azerai invites discerning travelers to experience attainable luxury in Vietnam through a collection of acclaimed boutique resorts. Founded by Adrian Zecha, the visionary behind Aman Resorts, the Azerai concept is already present in the culturally rich destinations of Ke Ga, Can Tho, and Hue.
Source: Azerai. Each Azerai resort is designed to envelop guests in sophisticated, understated luxury.
Every Azerai resort aims to immerse guests in refined yet understated luxury. At Azerai Can Tho, this translates to seclusion within low-rise structures on a private islet in the Hau River, reachable only by boat.</description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub.</description></item><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer.</description></item><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas.</description></item><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city.</description></item><item><title>The Wanda Vista brand expands globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</guid><description>Qian Jin, the head of the upscale hotel group Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has revealed the global growth plan for their Wanda Vista brand.
Wanda Vista represents the top tier of luxury within Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, designed specifically for guests who appreciate art and culture. Situated in major international cities and drawing inspiration from Eastern aesthetics, the brand focuses on providing personalized service catered to each guest&amp;rsquo;s individual requirements.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is continuing its guest outreach program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas.
Since late March 2020, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has been offering its guests and followers daily live chats, cooking demonstrations, and meditation and yoga sessions.
Recognizing that many people are hesitant to resume travel despite the easing of COVID-19 restrictions, the company introduced six new themes for its #AtHomeWithSixSenses campaign.
These themes - Wellness, Eat, Grow, Sustainability, Sleep and From the Heart of Six Senses - will continue to be explored through content on the Six Senses website (sixsenses.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations.</description></item><item><title>IHG will no longer provide mini toiletries as bathroom amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</guid><description>Source: IHG. A shower with sink showing miniatures as amenities.
The InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) is transitioning from small, individual toiletry bottles to larger, bulk amenity dispensers in all 843,000 rooms across its portfolio of hotels. This change, to be fully implemented by 2021, is part of a larger sustainability initiative and establishes IHG as the first global hotel company to entirely eliminate miniature bathroom products in favor of bulk-sized options.</description></item><item><title>The Ascott's latest brand, Lyf, is aimed at Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-s-latest-brand-lyf-is-aimed-at-millennials/</guid><description>Source: Capitaland. CapitaLand’s President &amp;amp; Group CEO, Lim Ming Yan (left) and Ascott’s CEO, Lee Chee Koon (right) try their hand at baking at Lyf’s ‘Bond’ social kitchen.
CapitaLand&amp;rsquo;s serviced residence branch, The Ascott Limited (Ascott), is launching Lyf, a new brand designed for Millennials who want to experience travel like locals.
Lyf goes beyond typical hospitality models by creating a community where guests can connect with fellow travelers and innovators to live and collaborate.</description></item><item><title>The Business Plan package at The Shilla Seoul includes access to The Executive Lounge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. The Executive Lounge.
Through June 30, 2019, The Shilla Seoul is offering its Business Plan package, which gives guests the opportunity to experience The Executive Lounge.
Guests selecting the Executive Business Deluxe option receive exclusive access to The Executive Lounge, complimentary breakfast at The Parkview, and access to both the gym and indoor swimming pool.
The Executive Lounge at The Shilla Seoul, situated on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s top floor, is designed as a luxurious penthouse.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the end of the year with eco-friendly festivities at East, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</guid><description>The environmentally conscious EAST, Hong Kong hotel is ready to celebrate the holiday season this year with special decorations and exciting events.
Continuing a tradition that began in 2014, EAST&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Village highlights creative recycling. This year, the EAST team gathered fallen logs left behind by Typhoon Mangkhut from the city streets to create unique Christmas decorations. Students from Jockey Club Sarah Roe School (JCSRS), the only school in Hong Kong offering an English curriculum for students with additional learning needs, collaborated with the EAST team on this project.</description></item><item><title>Azerai reveals special promotions for Chinese New Year in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:43:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</guid><description>Source: Azerai. Exterior, Hue. Constructed in 1930 as the residence of the French Resident Superieure, this colonial mansion forms the hotel&amp;rsquo;s heart. The mansion&amp;rsquo;s noticeable facade, characterized by its elongated horizontal lines and nautical motifs, is a testament to Art Deco architectural style. Its two harmonious wings, home to a vast tropical garden and a saltwater pool, were constructed in 2005, reflecting a modern take on Art Deco.
Azerai has unveiled special offers and activities for Chinese New Year at its Vietnamese properties.</description></item><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home.</description></item><item><title>Take a virtual tour of Emaar hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Using panoramic photography and videography, each virtual tour showcases the hotel&amp;rsquo;s features in detail.
Emaar Hospitality Group, the hospitality and leisure branch of Emaar Properties, has launched 360-degree virtual tours of its hotels in Dubai, UAE. These tours, created with high-definition photos and videos, allow potential guests to experience each hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique offerings, explore its various aspects, and make well-informed booking decisions.
The virtual tours encompass properties under the luxury Address Hotels + Resorts brand, the upscale lifestyle Vida Hotels and Resorts brand, and the new contemporary mid-scale Rove Hotels brand.</description></item><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout.</description></item><item><title>Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery is poised to transform into a secret retreat in Kyoto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kyoto-yura-hotel-nijo-jo-bettei-mgallery-is-poised-to-transform-into-a-secret-retreat-in-kyoto/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Interior, Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery.
Accor has expanded its presence in Japan with the launch of its second MGallery Hotel, the Kyoto Yura Hotel Nijo Jo Bettei MGallery.
This Kyoto-based hotel, designed by architect Yukio Hashimoto, centers around a Japanese garden, providing a sophisticated experience of the changing seasons. Hashimoto&amp;rsquo;s design prioritizes creating a specific atmosphere over focusing solely on materials, resulting in a minimalist and timeless aesthetic.</description></item><item><title>The Gold Coast, Australia will be home to the first Hyde location outside of the US</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</guid><description>Accor is expanding its partnership with sbe beyond the US, selecting Australia as the first Asia Pacific location. Hyde, their luxury lifestyle brand known for its Los Angeles Sunset Strip inspiration, will debut Hyde Paradiso on the Gold Coast in March 2019. This venue promises an all-day experience, transforming into a sophisticated lounge and dining destination in the evening.
Simon McGrath, COO of Accor Pacific, highlights the partnership&amp;rsquo;s goal to deliver unique lifestyle experiences.</description></item><item><title>Artyzen Singapore will be launched in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artyzen-singapore-will-be-launched-in-october/</guid><description>Preferred Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, boasting a global network of over 650 hotels, resorts, and residences in 80 countries, is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the upcoming October debut of Artyzen Singapore.
This 20-story establishment occupies the former site of the Marie Villa mansion, conveniently situated near Orchard Road and the Singapore Botanic Gardens. The hotel features 142 generously sized rooms and suites, each spanning at least 42 square meters and offering either a balcony or terraced Sky Gardens.</description></item><item><title>Katamama will be opening its doors to guests in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</guid><description>Source: Katamama. A rooftop suite at dusk.
Katamama, a 58-suite boutique hotel in Seminyak, Bali&amp;rsquo;s prime oceanfront area, is set to open in late March 2016.
The hotel emphasizes &amp;ldquo;handcrafted hospitality,&amp;rdquo; with every detail meticulously designed and executed by skilled Indonesian artisans. Katamama is a project by PTT Family, known for acclaimed restaurants, bars, and the Potato Head Beach Club in Bali. This 20-villa estate is famous for its innovative environmental design and a prominent contemporary Indonesian art gallery.</description></item><item><title>Escape to Bintan Lagoon Resort for a Global Wellness Day retreat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</guid><description>Bintan Lagoon Resort (BLR) is commemorating this year&amp;rsquo;s Global Wellness Day with a special getaway package full of wellness activities on June 10th and 11th.
A quick 75-minute ferry trip from Singapore, BLR is nestled on 300 hectares of lush land, boasting a private 1.5km beach. With a wide range of over 50 indoor and outdoor activities, from adventurous to relaxing, and delicious, healthy culinary options, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Discover the surrounding areas of Hotel Indigo in the new Neighbourhood 15 campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 02:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</guid><description>Hotel Indigo&amp;rsquo;s new brand campaign, &amp;ldquo;Neighbourhood 15,&amp;rdquo; highlights the unique character of each hotel&amp;rsquo;s surrounding area, specifically within a 15-minute radius. The campaign showcases local businesses and individuals who contribute to the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s vibrant atmosphere.
A two-minute video featuring the Hotel Indigo Bali Seminyak Beach, the brand&amp;rsquo;s first resort location, introduces viewers to nearby attractions like Surf School Bali, Divine Earth restaurant, and Bali Barber. Starting in October, a series of videos will delve deeper into these local businesses, offering insights and personal stories.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Jumeirah City Break</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah website.
City Breaks at Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Jumeirah Creekside Hotel, and Jumeirah Living World Trade Centre Residences come with perks like free entry to Wild Wadi Waterpark and Zero Gravity Private Beach.
Jumeirah Emirates Towers boasts shopping at the Boulevard, various dining and nightlife options, and a convenient location just five minutes from Dubai Mall, accessible via the hotel&amp;rsquo;s complimentary shuttle service.
Reserve a room for three or more nights at participating Jumeirah hotels in Dubai with the Jumeirah City Break promotion and enjoy a 20% discount on the best available rates, along with:</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels establishes a high-end presence in the Maldives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</guid><description>AccorHotels is entering the Maldives market with its first luxury resort there, the Dhevanafushi Maldives Luxury Resort. Located on the private island of Meradhoo, the resort will undergo improvements in late 2018 and subsequently become part of the prestigious Raffles brand.
Currently, the resort offers 21 island villas and 16 ocean villas, all with private pools. Guests can enjoy three restaurants and a variety of amenities and activities for relaxation and rejuvenation, such as a luxurious spa, an overwater fitness center, yoga classes, watersports, and private dining options.</description></item><item><title>The fourth akyra hotel in Sukhumvit, Bangkok has been launched by Akaryn</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</guid><description>Akaryn Hotel Group, a Thai hospitality company known for its luxurious hotels and resorts, will open its fourth akyra property, akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok, in December 2017.
The upscale boutique hotel is situated on Sukhumvit Soi 20, a vibrant area in the heart of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s main tourist zone, known for its excellent dining, lively nightlife, high-end shopping malls, spas, and green spaces.
akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok offers 50 rooms, ranging from 30 to 60 square meters, with city views.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its 200th property in Greater China, located in Chengdu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-200th-property-in-greater-china-located-in-chengdu/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Fairmont Chengdu lobby.
The Fairmont Chengdu marks the 200th property for AccorHotels in Greater China and is the first Fairmont Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts establishment in Western China. This opening is a key part of AccorHotels’ expansion within the luxury market.
Situated on Tianfu Middle Avenue in Chengdu&amp;rsquo;s high-tech zone, the hotel provides 336 guest rooms and suites, each offering impressive views of the city skyline. Shuangliu International Airport is easily accessible at just a 25-minute drive away, and the nearby metro station provides convenient access to Tianfu Square, the forthcoming Tianfu International Airport, and the South CBD zone.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has reopened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has finished renovating all guest rooms, bathrooms, and suites, offering visitors a revitalized stay in the heart of the city.
Source: Holiday Inn website. The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders.
Every room was completely emptied to give the architect a fresh start in designing a space with the modern traveler&amp;rsquo;s needs in mind. Striking new interiors are highlighted by floor-to-ceiling windows, equipped with electronically controlled blackout blinds that can be adjusted from the bedside.</description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses becomes a part of the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-becomes-a-part-of-the-global-tourism-plastics-initiative/</guid><description>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is among the first to sign the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative. This initiative, spearheaded by the UN Environment Programme and UN World Tourism Organization with the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, aims to tackle plastic waste in the tourism sector.
By signing the Global Tourism Plastics Initiative, Six Senses reinforces its commitment to eliminate, innovate, and circulate its plastic use by 2025, aiming to be plastic-free as early as 2022.</description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is providing selected transit passengers with a complimentary night's stay in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is offering a free overnight stay in Abu Dhabi to Economy Class travelers flying from specific locations, including Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Jordan, Kuwait, Bahrain, Oman, and Lebanon, whose journeys connect through the UAE&amp;rsquo;s capital.
This offer is valid for travel dates up to September 30, 2018, with bookings available from May 1 to September 15, 2018. Accommodation choices include the Radisson Blu on Yas Island and the Yas Island Rotana.</description></item><item><title>Le Meridien Seoul combines traditional Korean elements with French sophistication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 07:40:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/le-meridien-seoul-combines-traditional-korean-elements-with-french-sophistication/</guid><description>Source: Le Meridien, Seoul website. Hub lobby.
The Le Meridien, Seoul, the first of its brand in Korea, introduces the renowned London-based David Collins Studio to the country. Conveniently located in the upscale Gangnam district, the hotel is a short walk from the Sinnonhyeon and Gangnam subway stations and easily accessible from both Gimpo (GMP) and Incheon (ICN) International Airports.
Tasked with designing the hotel&amp;rsquo;s public spaces and rooms, the studio has crafted a sophisticated blend of Parisian elegance with mid-century modern influences.</description></item><item><title>23 lessons I picked up during my Royal Caribbean voyage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 03:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/23-lessons-i-picked-up-during-my-royal-caribbean-voyage/</guid><description>Tips for Enjoying Your Royal Caribbean Cruise Here&amp;rsquo;s a view from the Viking Crown Lounge on Deck 14.
And here are some tips for your cruise:
Pack light on sunscreen, heavier on cleanser. Remember that everything onboard caters to US standards: food portions, electrical outlets, and currency. Your daily cruise newsletter is your best friend. Delivered to your room every afternoon, it highlights all activities and indicates which ones require payment.</description></item><item><title>The Adya Hotel Langkawi provides meeting rooms and a ballroom for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adya-hotel-langkawi-provides-meeting-rooms-and-a-ballroom-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: Adya Hotel Langkawi website. Interior of a junior suite.
The four-star Adya Hotel Langkawi, situated in the Kuah town center on Langkawi Island in Malaysia, is marketed as a perfect starting point for exploring the natural wonders and rich culture of Langkawi, a designated UNESCO Global Geopark.
The hotel boasts 207 rooms and suites, each featuring a private bathroom with a bath and shower, along with a balcony that offers scenic views of the sea and town.</description></item><item><title>The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay offers a competitive advantage for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay website. The Grand Ballroom, theatre-style.
The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, a premier five-star resort in Phu Quoc and a flagship property in Vietnam, provides a range of meeting spaces suitable for various event sizes.
The resort is committed to crafting unforgettable events and immersive experiences for all attendees. Phu Quoc is an up-and-coming destination, now linked by direct flights to major cities like Ho Chi Minh City, Bangkok, and Guangzhou.</description></item><item><title>The Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 will commence operations on January 1, 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</guid><description>Source: Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 website.
Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20, a lifestyle hotel focused on health and wellness, will softly open its doors on January 1, 2016. The hotel provides tailored food and drinks, spa treatments, fitness facilities, and wellness activities.
Conveniently situated on Sukhumvit 20, the hotel is a short walk from the BTS Asok Skytrain, MRT Sukhumvit Subway, Terminal 21 Mall, The EmQuartier, and the Emporium.</description></item><item><title>Capella Sydney celebrates its first anniversary with joy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</guid><description>Source: Capella Sydney. To celebrate its one-year anniversary, Capella Sydney is providing a special deal with a A$365 credit applicable throughout the hotel and breakfast for two. The offer encompasses:
- Daily breakfast at Brasserie 1930
- Exclusive access to The Living Room, a shared area present in every Capella establishment. This space allows guests to participate in daily Capella customs and experience Sydney&amp;rsquo;s heritage through a curated display of local historical items and art.</description></item><item><title>New sculptures have been added to the Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi Coralarium</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</guid><description>The Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi resort has added new sculptures to its Coralarium, an underwater art installation that doubles as the Maldives&amp;rsquo; first and only coral regeneration project. This structure, now teeming with marine life, serves as an artificial reef.
The abstract sculptures, conceived by environmentalist and eco-artist Jason deCaires Taylor, draw inspiration from the natural beauty of coral reefs and are designed to resemble coral colonies. These ten partially submerged plinths, reaching heights of up to 5 meters, aim to raise awareness about endangered ecosystems, educate visitors about marine life, and help rehabilitate the reef.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its inaugural five-star international hotel in Vung Tau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The
Pullman Vung Tau.
AccorHotels is introducing the Pullman Vung Tau, the first international five-star hotel in this coastal city just a 90-minute drive from Ho Chi Minh City.
The Pullman Vung Tau offers views of both Back Beach and Front Beach and boasts the largest meeting facilities in Southern Vietnam, making it perfect for business travelers looking for a quick escape from Ho Chi Minh City.</description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center.</description></item><item><title>Anantara's Al Baleed Resort Salalah introduces new wellness program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</guid><description>Source: Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara. The Balance Wellness by Anantara program includes custom-designed vegan cuisine.
The luxurious, private pool villa resort Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara has introduced a new wellness program with an a la carte approach.
Situated between a private beach and a freshwater lagoon in Salalah, Oman, Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara provides a serene setting for guests to focus on their wellness goals.</description></item><item><title>Get 10% off and receive gifts with the HMH summer offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</guid><description>Hospitality Management Holdings (HMH) is offering a summer deal: guests can enjoy a 10% discount on bed and breakfast rates and receive a daily voucher redeemable at any of the hotel&amp;rsquo;s restaurants or spas. This promotion is valid until September 21, 2015.
Laurent Voivenel, CEO of HMH, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s presence in 15 cities across the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. He stated, &amp;ldquo;Due to significant demand from Saudi Arabia and other GCC countries, over 70% of our rooms have been booked in advance.</description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country.</description></item><item><title>The Anantara Angkor Resort is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>Source: Anantara Angkor Resort website. View of the exterior.
The luxurious Anantara Angkor Resort has reopened in Siem Reap, offering an all-suite boutique experience close to the wonders of the ancient Khmer Empire.
Just a short drive from the city center, the 5-star resort provides easy access to vibrant markets, riverside attractions, and the charming French colonial quarter. The UNESCO World Heritage Site of Angkor Archaeological Park is also conveniently located a mere 10 minutes away.</description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen collaborate for a flash sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 01:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</guid><description>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen have teamed up to offer the Grand Spring Voyage flash sale, featuring accommodation packages ranging from two to five nights in both cities. This convenient travel opportunity is made possible by the newly extended MTR East Rail line, which directly connects the two hotels. The journey between the nearest stations, Exhibition Centre Station in Hong Kong and Lo Wu Station in Shenzhen, is a quick 40 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Experience the VIP treatment at Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-vip-treatment-at-hard-rock-hotel-shenzhen/</guid><description>Source: Hard Rock Hotels. Interior, Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen.
The Hard Rock Hotel brand has debuted its first establishment in China with the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen. This new property combines pop culture with high-end hospitality to create a luxurious experience for travelers seeking a unique experience.
Opening its doors in the summer of 2017, the Hard Rock Hotel Shenzhen is located within Mission Hills Centreville. Situated near a golf course, the hotel also provides convenient access to a variety of leisure, wellness, and entertainment options.</description></item><item><title>The Six Senses Bhutan experience will be available in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-senses-bhutan-experience-will-be-available-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. A view of Bhutan.
Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has created a unique experience by linking five distinct resorts in five separate Bhutanese locations, collectively known as Six Senses Bhutan. Bhutan is notable for its isolation, remaining cut off from the outside world until the 1950s and only welcoming its first international visitors by special invitation in 1974.
With 82 guest suites and villas spread across the five intimate lodges, visitors can immerse themselves in the rich cultural heritage and hospitality of Thimphu, Punakha, Gangtey, Bumthang, and Paro, experiencing the &amp;ldquo;Happiest Place on Earth&amp;rdquo; firsthand.</description></item><item><title>The St Regis Macao, Cotai Central has now been officially opened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-st-regis-macao-cotai-central-has-now-been-officially-opened/</guid><description>Source: Sands China. High-ranking officials inaugurated The St. Regis Macao, Cotai Central on Friday during a ribbon-cutting ceremony. The ceremony was attended by dignitaries such as Chui Sai On, the Chief Executive of Macau; Edmund Ho Hau Wah, Vice Chairman of the National Committee of the Chinese People&amp;rsquo;s Political Consultative Conference; and representatives from the Liaison Office, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Macau SAR government. Key figures from Las Vegas Sands and Sands China, including Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson and President Dr.</description></item><item><title>The book Soirees, Sojourns &amp; Stories details the most memorable moments of the Raffles narrative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</guid><description>Raffles Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, a leader in luxury hospitality known for its iconic properties, has released Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories.
Created in partnership with Rizzoli New York, the 200-page slipcased book, Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories by Natasha Fraser-Cavassoni, explores the development of Raffles&amp;rsquo; heritage of elegance and exceptional service around the world. It covers the period from the opening of its flagship hotel in Singapore in 1887 to the recent debut of Raffles Warsaw in Poland.</description></item><item><title>InterContinental Hotels Group plans to open Holiday Inn Osaka Namba by the end of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intercontinental-hotels-group-plans-to-open-holiday-inn-osaka-namba-by-the-end-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: IHG. The Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) and Japan Hotel Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT) Investment Corporation (JHR) are collaborating on the Holiday Inn Osaka Namba, marking the REIT&amp;rsquo;s first venture with IHG. Scheduled to launch by the end of 2016, the hotel, presently known as Hotel Vista Grande Osaka, will be rebranded as Holiday Inn Osaka Namba.
The 314-room hotel, joining the globally recognized Holiday Inn brand, will leverage IHG&amp;rsquo;s extensive global reservation systems, sales network, and the substantial IHG Rewards Club loyalty program, boasting almost 94 million members.</description></item><item><title>Book with ONYX in February to receive exclusive discounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</guid><description>Source: Onyx web page. Several ONYX Hospitality Group properties are offering special deals for the Chinese New Year.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, guests can enjoy up to a 20% discount at the Oriental Residence Bangkok or at one of the 25 participating Amari, OZO, Shama, and Mosaic Collection hotels. These offers are available at locations in Thailand, Sri Lanka, mainland China, Hong Kong, Qatar, and Bangladesh.</description></item><item><title>Wanda Realm Taian is now officially open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wanda-realm-taian-is-now-officially-open-for-business/</guid><description>Source: Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
The Wanda Realm Taian.
The Wanda Realm Taian (泰安万达嘉华酒店) marks its grand opening, becoming the 77th establishment under the Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts umbrella. This addition represents the 30th Wanda Realm hotel in China and the 41st property fully owned and operated by Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
This hotel is the fourth launched by Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts under their Wanda Realm brand in Shandong.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is committed to connecting with Chinese tourists through investment efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-committed-to-connecting-with-chinese-tourists-through-investment-efforts/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotel Resorts Spas&amp;rsquo; Chinese website.
To expand its online footprint, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has launched a website in Chinese. The new website offers the same content and features as the brand&amp;rsquo;s English website. This move is anticipated to attract more customers from China, a key growth market for Six Senses.
In addition to the website, Six Senses is connecting with Chinese customers through brand engagement on social media platforms like WeChat, Youku, and Sina Weibo.</description></item><item><title>Accor expands its footprint in regional Queensland with the addition of Mercure Rockhampton</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</guid><description>The Travelodge Hotel in Rockhampton has transitioned to the Mercure brand as part of a new franchise agreement with Accor. This addition expands Mercure&amp;rsquo;s presence to over 50 properties in Australia and New Zealand, and more than 810 globally.
Conveniently located in the city center and a short distance from the airport, the Mercure Rockhampton underwent renovations in 2008. The eight-story hotel boasts 74 rooms, views of the Fitzroy River, six conference rooms, an outdoor pool, a fitness center, a 24-hour reception, and convenient access to attractions like Great Keppel Island.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn in Bangkok is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Bangkok has reopened with a new focus on natural elements.
The traditional lobby is gone, replaced with an open space that blends the front desk, restaurant, bar, lounge, and business center in a modern style. This design approach extends to the 379 guest rooms, each envisioned as a home away from home.
Two new dining options are available: Ginger, offering all-day dining, and Beer Republic, a bar designed to evoke a 1920s European industrial warehouse.</description></item><item><title>Grand Mercure makes its first appearance in Myanmar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</guid><description>AccorHotels has launched its first Grand Mercure hotel in Myanmar. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire, with its 175 guest rooms and suites, provides a view of the Schwedagon Pagoda. Local artist Pyar Dade designed the accommodations.
Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire. Patrick Basset, COO of AccorHotels, Upper Southeast and Northeast Asia and the Maldives, stated, “This is our first Grand Mercure in Myanmar and the opening of Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire reflects the cultural touchstone of the destination and heritage in bringing local stories to life.</description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner.</description></item><item><title>FEH has announced a partnership with SIA's HighFlyer business travel program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</guid><description>Source: FEH. The Clan Hotel Singapore lobby.
Far East Hospitality (FEH) is the first hotel group to join Singapore Airlines’ (SIA&amp;rsquo;s) corporate travel program, HighFlyer. Companies in this program receive discounted airfares and earn HighFlyer points when their staff travel for business. These points can be redeemed for future travel, benefits for their business, or rewards for their traveling employees.
Members of HighFlyer can now accumulate up to 500 points when their employees stay at participating Far East Hospitality hotels in Singapore, Japan, and Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers.</description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist.</description></item><item><title>The Wyndham brand has entered the UAE market with its presence in Dubai Marina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</guid><description>Source: The First Group. The new Wyndham
Dubai Marina.
Wyndham Dubai Marina, the first hotel solely developed by leading Dubai-based property developer, The First Group, has officially opened. This launch signifies the Wyndham brand&amp;rsquo;s entrance into the UAE market.
This four-star deluxe Wyndham Dubai Marina, managed by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, the largest hotel management company globally, represents a significant achievement for The First Group. The developer has established a strong reputation for creating high-quality serviced apartments and &amp;ldquo;aparthotels&amp;rdquo; in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway will be celebrating their first birthday on March 31st</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Jen Orchardgateway website.
Hotel Jen, a new brand from the Shangri-La Group, is turning one year old on March 31, 2016. To mark this milestone, the two Singapore locations, Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway, are joining their sister hotels across nine Asian-Pacific cities for a grand birthday celebration. Each location will host unique events reflecting their city&amp;rsquo;s character, from a Mad Hatter&amp;rsquo;s tea party in Beijing to street art-inspired menus in Brisbane and a pool party in the Maldives.</description></item><item><title>Experience Silom in a whole new way at the newly elevated ibis Styles Bangkok Silom</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</guid><description>Accor Hospitality Group has launched a stylish hotel, ibis Styles Bangkok Silom, in Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s lively Silom neighborhood. The hotel boasts a playful design inspired by Thai festivals and features a vibrant mural by Thai artist Tikkywow, reflecting Silom&amp;rsquo;s rich history.
Located near Sala Daeng BTS Skytrain and Silom MRT subway stations, the hotel provides convenient access to the city. Garth Simmons, CEO of Accor Southeast Asia, Japan &amp;amp; South Korea, expressed excitement for the opening, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s fit with Silom&amp;rsquo;s dynamic atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>The doors of Wanda Realm Fuyang are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-wanda-realm-fuyang-are-now-open/</guid><description>Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts has expanded its portfolio with the opening of Wanda Realm Fuyang in the bustling business district of Fuyang, Anhui province, China. This addition marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 78th hotel, the 42nd under its ownership and management, and the 30th property under the Wanda Realm brand.
André Liu, General Manager of Wanda Realm Fuyang, highlighted the strategic importance of the location, stating, &amp;ldquo;Fuyang city is a rapidly developing hub with the largest population and fourth-largest size in Anhui province.</description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is preparing for Chinese New Year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Source: The Sanya EDITION.
In anticipation of the Chinese New Year, The Sanya EDITION presents two unique offerings that provide a genuine experience of Chinese culture.
Guests can immerse themselves in culture and history through The Sanya EDITION&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with the Forbidden City. This partnership features a temporary shop and exhibit highlighting fine arts and teas. Those with a passion for cuisine will enjoy the luxurious interpretations of Chinese dishes prepared by world-renowned Michelin-starred chefs, specially invited by The Sanya EDITION for the celebratory period.</description></item><item><title>The Urban Island promotion has been introduced by The Shilla Seoul</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-urban-island-promotion-has-been-introduced-by-the-shilla-seoul/</guid><description>With the arrival of summer, The Shilla Seoul presents Urban Island, a luxurious outdoor escape for guests. This all-inclusive retreat offers relaxation, a connection with nature, and delightful poolside service.
Reopened for the season, Urban Island welcomes guests to heated outdoor pools, a jacuzzi, and a rooftop garden against a scenic backdrop of Namsan Mountain and the Seoul skyline. Intimate cabanas nestled among lush greenery provide secluded havens.
The Urban Days room rate, available until June 30, 2019, starts from KRW 320,000 per night, excluding taxes and service charges, based on double occupancy.</description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia.</description></item><item><title>The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae will be available starting in March 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:23:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-western-plus-hotel-nagoya-sakae-will-be-available-starting-in-march-2024/</guid><description>Source: BWH Hotels. A standard room at the Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, which boasts contemporary rooms with a full range of amenities.
Starting March 13, 2024, BWH Hotels (BWH), the international hospitality group that includes WorldHotels, Best Western Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, and SureStay Hotels, will introduce a newly renovated and rebranded hotel.
The Best Western Plus Hotel Nagoya Sakae, formerly the Best Western Nagoya, was one of the city&amp;rsquo;s most well-liked international mid-scale hotels.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food.</description></item><item><title>Shangri-La and Singapore Airlines campaign offers packaged deals for ASEAN destinations and hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</guid><description>To commemorate the 50th anniversary of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts and Singapore Airlines have teamed up to launch a travel campaign called &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore.&amp;rdquo;
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjJuZK2IwJjPxRmvmq0DT-MS7ZPDl5douabN-yaRNI7kSFX1RAg5n8m2LHrg030pnJcr68_qz-IujmANOlf3NTbWGRF887wfkPbFQPAn168XsbqGeH8wP90CW2_M3muXU8ABKS6E9PwtOA/s1600/Shangri+La+SIA+ASEAN+is+More.JPG)
Source: Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts. Banner for the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore&amp;rdquo; campaign.
This campaign highlights Southeast Asia as a travel destination through special offers on curated leisure trips. Flight and hotel packages are available for various properties in Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Myanmar, and Thailand, including Shangri-La hotels and resorts, Hotel Jen properties, and Traders Hotel, Kuala Lumpur.</description></item><item><title>Exploring new destinations in 2021: Bawah Reserve and Cedar Lodge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-new-destinations-in-2021-bawah-reserve-and-cedar-lodge/</guid><description>Several properties, such as Bawah Reserve in Indonesia and Cedar Lodge in New Zealand, are getting ready for the return of travel.
Bawah Reserve
Source: Bawah Reserve website. Lodges at Bawah Reserve.
Located in Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s remote Anambas Islands, Bawah Reserve encompasses six tropical islands, thirteen white sand beaches, and three lagoons. The Anambas Islands are reachable by private seaplane from Bintan Island, Indonesia.
Along with its existing 36 lodges, Bawah will debut six new cliffside lodges on Elang, a previously undeveloped island, this year.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Canopy Power is making Southeast Asia more environmentally friendly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</guid><description>Source: Canopy Power. This image shows solar panels installed on the roof of a beachfront pavilion at Batu Batu resort. This installation was part of a larger project by Canopy Power.
Despite the economic downturn of 2020, Canopy Power has announced several accomplishments within the Asia Pacific region.
One such accomplishment was the completion of a renewable energy microgrid in the third quarter of 2020. This microgrid, located on Batu Batu, a sustainable island resort 16 km from Mersing, Malaysia, will allow the 22-villa resort to decrease its reliance on diesel and lower carbon emissions.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport reveals its fresh new appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has finished renovations, adding new rooms, a new Italian restaurant called Allora, another function room, an updated Club Lounge, and a revitalized fitness center.
The new design creates a calming oceanic atmosphere. Natural wood finishes on the furniture bring a feeling of warmth and comfort. This is enhanced by a color scheme of beach tones and ocean shades. Light gray couches, navy blue, and yellow accents contribute to a modern and welcoming feel.</description></item><item><title>Experience sustainable dining at Avani properties in Indochina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</guid><description>Image Credit: Avani. Plant-based coconut acai bowls are available at the Avani+ Samui Resort.
To create a healthier planet and promote sustainability, Avani Hotels has introduced a variety of eco-friendly and wellness-focused programs.
Avani&amp;rsquo;s flagship hotels in Thailand, Cambodia, and Laos are increasing their efforts to support nearby communities. They are accomplishing this by showcasing regional specialties and advocating for a decrease in reliance on imported goods. They have also implemented zero-waste programs, which include composting systems to handle all organic waste and on-site organic gardens to encourage self-sufficiency.</description></item><item><title>You can have a Claire Luxton experience in Dubai this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-have-a-claire-luxton-experience-in-dubai-this-july/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. Visitors can enjoy a unique experience showcasing the work of artist Claire Luxton at select hotels, such as the InterContinental Dubai Festival City.
InterContinental Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, part of IHG Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts Luxury and Lifestyle Collection, has partnered with British artist Claire Luxton to launch a series of immersive guest experiences. Available at various hotels, including the InterContinental Dubai Festival City, until mid-July, these experiences celebrate global travel and exploration through the artistic vision of Claire Luxton.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the new Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. This hotel, the Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel, aims to create a beach resort atmosphere.
The recently opened Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel is a 72-room boutique hotel located in the city center. Its convenient location provides guests with easy walking access to shopping, dining, and entertainment. Designed around a nautical theme, the hotel offers 60 Deluxe rooms, eight Baraquda Suites, and four Baraquda Grand Suites.</description></item><item><title>Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong is the inaugural Hyatt Place in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Hyatt and Boutique Corporation have announced the launch of the Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong in Phuket, Thailand. This 161-room beachfront property is the first Hyatt Place hotel in Southeast Asia. It embodies the Hyatt Place brand&amp;rsquo;s relaxed style and offers convenient amenities like complimentary Wi-Fi and 24/7 dining options.
&amp;ldquo;Thailand remains a crucial market for Hyatt, and Phuket is a top tourist spot in Southeast Asia with rising demand from both leisure and business travelers,&amp;rdquo; said David Udell, Group President – Asia Pacific, Hyatt Hotels Corporation.</description></item><item><title>Emirates provides appealing packages for stopovers in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s skyline, featuring the Burj Khalifa on the right.
Travelers flying with Emirates can benefit from appealing Dubai packages. These packages offer special prices at top-rated hotels and include access to entertainment options like city shows and attractions*.
Starting from US$49 per night, based on double occupancy, visitors can experience Dubai at the Rove Dubai Marina, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s vibrant waterfront area. This package also includes two tickets to Dubai Parks and Resorts, the region&amp;rsquo;s most extensive integrated theme park destination, encompassing MOTIONGATE Dubai, BOLLYWOOD PARKS Dubai, LEGOLAND Dubai, and LEGOLAND Water Park.</description></item><item><title>The first Novotel hotel has opened in Cambodia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-novotel-hotel-has-opened-in-cambodia/</guid><description>Source: Novotel Hotels, Suites &amp;amp; Resorts. The Novotel Phnom Penh BKK 1.
Accor brand, Novotel Hotels, Suites &amp;amp; Resorts, has opened its newest location, the Novotel Phnom Penh BKK 1, in Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
This brand-new hotel features a contemporary design, a welcoming social space, and diverse dining and wellness options. Its strategic location provides easy access to the bustling Bassac Lane and Langka Lane neighborhoods, as well as landmarks such as the Independence Monument and Wat Langka, one of the city&amp;rsquo;s oldest pagodas.</description></item><item><title>Hilton Singapore Orchard introduces the Smart Oasis meeting space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 22:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-singapore-orchard-introduces-the-smart-oasis-meeting-space/</guid><description>Hilton Singapore Orchard Unveils &amp;lsquo;Smart Oasis&amp;rsquo; Meeting Space
Hilton Singapore Orchard is excited to announce the opening of Smart Oasis, a new meeting space located on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fifth floor. The space features seven function rooms, two breakout areas, and incorporates advanced technology with natural elements inspired by the area&amp;rsquo;s plantation history.
Cedric Nubul, General Manager of Hilton Singapore Orchard, emphasized the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing cutting-edge meeting facilities. He believes Smart Oasis will become a leading venue in Asia, promoting sustainable and impactful event experiences.</description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels expands its high-end collection in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-expands-its-high-end-collection-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 06:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-expands-its-high-end-collection-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>AccorHotels, a major player in the travel and hospitality industry, is expanding its luxury presence in the Asia Pacific region with multiple high-end hotel openings scheduled in the coming months. This initiative will primarily involve the expansion of their Sofitel and Pullman brands, which are part of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; luxury and upscale portfolio. Other prestigious brands in this collection include Raffles Hotel, Fairmont, MGallery by Sofitel, Swissôtel, and Grand Mercure.
These openings follow the successful August debut of the Sofitel Kuala Lumpur Damansara, a 312-room establishment situated in the heart of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s capital city.</description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp; Spa is offering meeting packages for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa. Executive team members at Hyatt Regegncy Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa will help event planners make any meeting a success.
Located on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Hoi An coastline and close to Danang, the Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa has announced new meeting packages for 2017.
The resort offers a wide range of event and meeting spaces, both indoors and outdoors on the beachfront. These venues can accommodate up to 250 people.</description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions.</description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments.</description></item><item><title>Dusit Thani Bangkok will reopen in September 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</guid><description>Dusit Hotels and Resorts, a prominent Thai hotel and property development company, will reopen the famous Dusit Thani Bangkok on September 27, 2024, as a key component of Dusit Central Park.
Starting May 1, 2024, reservations for the new Dusit Thani Bangkok can be made through their website, with early birds receiving a US$75 nightly credit for dining and spa treatments, among other benefits. Rates begin at US$330++ per night. Bookings made by October 31, 2024, for stays between September 27, 2024, and March 31, 2025, are eligible for this promotion.</description></item><item><title>This year, Teardrop Hotels is introducing three new tea plantation experiences in Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-teardrop-hotels-is-introducing-three-new-tea-plantation-experiences-in-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Teardrop Hotels is expanding its portfolio in 2018 with the addition of three renovated tea planters&amp;rsquo; houses: Goatfell, Nine Skies, and Pekoe House. These vintage managers&amp;rsquo; bungalows, located along the tea country route, will offer a modern take on traditional tea plantation accommodations.
Opening in April 2018, Goatfell is a former superintendent’s residence situated on a working tea estate above Nuwara Eliya. This four-bedroom main house, with two additional standalone chalets, boasts living and dining rooms and a swimming pool.</description></item><item><title>SiteMinder: Travelers are projected to spend in 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/siteminder-travelers-are-projected-to-spend-in-2022/</guid><description>A recent global survey of over 8,000 travelers reveals a growing desire for international travel, even with increasing living expenses.
Source: SiteMinder Changing Traveller Report 2022. Global accommodation momentum from 2020 to 2022.
The report identified five key travel trends:
Macro-travel: The desire to travel outweighs concerns about inflation.
Digital influence: Travelers are currently the most receptive to marketing efforts.
Bleisure: Business travelers seek modern hotel amenities.
Trust: Digital interactions are crucial for building trust with travelers.</description></item><item><title>The Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo has officially opened its doors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-marunouchi-tokyo-has-officially-opened-its-doors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ascott-marunouchi-tokyo-has-officially-opened-its-doors/</guid><description>Source: The Ascott Limited. The lobby, Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo.
CapitaLand&amp;rsquo;s serviced residence branch, The Ascott Limited, opened its first high-end serviced residence in Japan on March 30, 2017, under its top brand, Ascott The Residence.
The 130-unit Ascott Marunouchi Tokyo is in the desirable Marunouchi-Otemachi district. It&amp;rsquo;s part of a mixed-use development with offices and close to notable attractions like the Imperial Palace East Gardens and the Ginza area. The residence provides convenient access to Otemachi Station, a major Tokyo subway hub served by five lines, with connections to the Shinkansen bullet train available from nearby Tokyo Station.</description></item><item><title>Sofitel Kunming provides convenient access to the city center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 07:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</guid><description>Sofitel, the luxury hotel brand under AccorHotels, has launched its newest property, Sofitel Kunming. Located in the city center, it&amp;rsquo;s the only international luxury hotel in Kunming.
Situated in Kunming&amp;rsquo;s central business district, the 400-room hotel spans the 27th to 52nd floors. It showcases a blend of French elegance and art de vivre with touches of Yunnan&amp;rsquo;s vibrant ethnic cultures and customs.
&amp;ldquo;The debut of Sofitel Kunming signifies a period of rapid growth for AccorHotels in China, as we continue to solidify our dedication to delivering world-renowned, refined French hospitality to discerning Chinese travelers,&amp;rdquo; shared Paul Richardson, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China.</description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds.</description></item><item><title>Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li blends traditional shikumen architecture with modern French elegance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</guid><description>Source: Capella Shanghai website. Villa entrance.
Located in Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French Concession, the Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li, offers a journey back to the city&amp;rsquo;s early 20th-century charm. Situated within the Jian Ye Li estate, the property is a rare surviving example of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;shikumen&amp;rdquo; townhouses, characterized by their three-story brick construction and stone accents.
The goal was to develop an ultra-luxury experience while meticulously preserving the site&amp;rsquo;s historical character. Jaya Interior Design and BLINK Design Group drew inspiration from Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s past, seamlessly integrating traditional Chinese elements with French elegance.</description></item><item><title>The Ritz-Carlton is now open in Fukuoka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-is-now-open-in-fukuoka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 06:57:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-is-now-open-in-fukuoka/</guid><description>Source: The Ritz-Carlton. Facade, The Ritz-Carlton, Fukuoka.
The Ritz-Carlton, Fukuoka, the newest addition to Marriott Bonvoy&amp;rsquo;s 31 hotel brands, has opened its doors on Japan&amp;rsquo;s Kyushu island. This hotel aims to blend the brand&amp;rsquo;s signature service and modern design with Fukuoka&amp;rsquo;s unique blend of history, tradition, culinary richness, and burgeoning startup culture.
According to Tina Edmundson, President of Luxury for Marriott International, the opening marks the brand&amp;rsquo;s seventh hotel in Japan and solidifies its presence in a new and growing market.</description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Shanghai is set to make its debut in late 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</guid><description>Source: HKRI. The Sukhothai Shanghai.
HKR International will soon expand its Sukhothai Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts portfolio with a second hotel – The Sukhothai Shanghai. This new addition, situated in the Nanjing Road West central business district, is set to launch in late 2017.
Designed by Neri &amp;amp; Hu, The Sukhothai Shanghai is a contemporary luxury boutique hotel. It offers 168 guest rooms and 33 suites, ranging from 44 to 172 square meters in size.</description></item><item><title>The Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong and Vistajet provide a rare and unique experience called Once in a Blue Moon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</guid><description>VistaJet, a prominent business aviation company, has partnered with the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong to create the &amp;ldquo;Once in a Blue Moon&amp;rdquo; experience. This exclusive offer celebrates the Mid-Autumn Festival with a luxurious private jet journey featuring an in-flight menu designed by Chef Wong, the Executive Chinese Chef of the Michelin-starred Man Wah restaurant at the Mandarin Oriental.
Available from September 15 to October 15, 2020, this unique offering features a customized private jet experience departing from Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson hosts its first charity event of the year-end</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</guid><description>Source: Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson. The poolside.
Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson will host its first charity event with the Friends of The Disabled Society (FDS) as part of their year-end festivities.
The public can purchase various handicrafts and accessories on November 17, 2016, at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s lounge area and poolside. All proceeds will go to FDS. The hotel will also host a dinner for FDS on December 3, 2016, as part of the holiday celebrations.</description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities.</description></item><item><title>The Ritz-Carlton in Amman makes its first appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-in-amman-makes-its-first-appearance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 04:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ritz-carlton-in-amman-makes-its-first-appearance/</guid><description>Marriott Bonvoy&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, The Ritz-Carlton, has opened a new hotel in Amman, Jordan, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s well-regarded Fifth Circle. The 20-story hotel boasts 228 rooms, with offerings ranging from standard guest rooms to 34 suites.
Donna McNamara, Vice President and Global Brand Leader for The Ritz-Carlton, expressed the brand&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm, stating their goal is to provide exceptional service and unique experiences in captivating destinations worldwide. She emphasized that The Ritz-Carlton, Amman, aims to immerse guests in luxury, creating memorable experiences and showcasing the city&amp;rsquo;s allure.</description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Citadines OMR serviced apartments are now available in Chennai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</guid><description>The Ascott Limited, a fully owned subsidiary of CapitaLand specializing in serviced residences, has expanded its presence in India with the opening of Citadines OMR in Chennai. This 269-unit property marks Ascott&amp;rsquo;s second serviced residence in India, further solidifying its position as a leading international serviced residence operator in the country.
With this addition, Ascott&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in India now encompasses over 1,600 units across nine properties, including those currently operational and under development.</description></item><item><title>The KL Journal provides a unique boutique option for accommodations in Kuala Lumpur, as an alternative to traditional hotel chains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 01:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</guid><description>Source: The KL Journal. This hotel blends industrial design, diverse local touches, and vintage pieces to create a stylishly modern yet retro atmosphere.
Located near Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s primary shopping and entertainment area, the Kuala Lumpur Journal (KL Journal) is a boutique hotel designed for the modern traveler seeking an alternative to large chains. It offers all the necessary modern amenities while retaining a unique sense of style and personality.</description></item><item><title>The opening date for Six Senses Kaplankaya is May 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</guid><description>![Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEg6jRBaFFB8FLc8GWUouGmkRpZIrrVyWlKYCZ1pRPjPgJhTMuDR2tOLPpVhKP-eWibrLG1ZGt42dmOjjJoSeU_SwAl_HlA8BkuquNMt_lQ5P90CQTn7bDyCDPtU74R2ApXfx4oJxuNUaZo/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;Six Senses hotel in Turkey opens May 1.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.
The Six Senses Kaplankaya resort, which became part of Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas on May 1, 2017, commences its new season on May 1, 2018. The property now aligns with Six Senses&amp;rsquo; standards of design, sustainability, and wellness, offering a distinct guest experience focused on achieving equilibrium and well-being by engaging all the senses.</description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www.</description></item><item><title>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental Hong Kong has become more environmentally friendly than ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-landmark-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-has-become-more-environmentally-friendly-than-ever/</guid><description>The Landmark Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong is implementing environmentally friendly practices to offer guests sustainable luxury, including producing its own eco-friendly water and starting a rooftop garden.
The hotel is the first in Hong Kong to work with Nordaq FRESH, a Swedish company, to provide filtered and purified water in reusable glass bottles. This system reduces plastic waste and carbon emissions associated with traditional bottled water. Guests can also refill BPA-free bottles at the hotel.</description></item><item><title>Details of the farewell accommodation package at The Excelsior, Hong Kong are provided below</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 13:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-farewell-accommodation-package-at-the-excelsior-hong-kong-are-provided-below/</guid><description>To commemorate its rich history, The Excelsior, Hong Kong is offering a special &amp;ldquo;Fond Farewell Room Package&amp;rdquo; for guests to experience the hotel one last time before its closure on March 31, 2019. Guests who book this package will also be invited to a special farewell reception in the hotel lobby.
Three package options are available, each highlighting the four-star hotel&amp;rsquo;s renowned Michelin-star cuisine and its prime location on the Victoria Harbour waterfront for the past 45 years.</description></item><item><title>Indulge in a luxurious 20 Carat Gold Escape with JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay and Maserati</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 14:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay.
The lobby lounge.
Upon arrival at the sports university-themed JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, guests will be greeted with a luxurious Maserati transfer*. Building on the success of the resort&amp;rsquo;s previous collaboration showcasing DMC&amp;rsquo;s SS2017 womenswear collection, this partnership with Maserati aims to captivate those passionate about sports and automobiles.
Ty Collins, General Manager at JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, states, &amp;ldquo;This collaboration amplifies the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to offering design-focused experiences.</description></item><item><title>Improve your sleep with the Sleep with Six Senses program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Better sleep with the new Sleep with Six Senses programme.
Six Senses partnered with Sleep Doctor Dr. Michael Breus to launch its improved sleep standard called Sleep With Six Senses. Currently, five resorts offer this standard, with complete implementation across all locations expected by mid-2017. All future resorts will feature this program from their opening day.
The experience begins with a pre-arrival online questionnaire. This allows a designated Sleep Ambassador to understand the guest&amp;rsquo;s relationship with sleep and tailor the room accordingly.</description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is offering a promotion during Golden Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</guid><description>The Sanya EDITION hotel is offering a special promotion for travelers visiting China during Golden Week, which falls on October 1st to 7th.
To celebrate, the hotel is hosting guest chef Matthew David Ona from Roof 325 Restaurant and Bar in Shanghai. Chef Ona, known for his culinary expertise at one of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s top dining destinations, will be at The Jade Egret restaurant from October 1st to 3rd. He has designed special steak and seafood tasting menus for the occasion.</description></item><item><title>Robots have been introduced to the teams at Hotel Jen in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</guid><description>Hotel Jen is pioneering the use of Savioke&amp;rsquo;s Relay robots in Asian hotels. The robots, Jeno and Jena, will be stationed at Hotel Jen Orchardgateway and Tanglin Singapore, respectively. They will handle deliveries of amenities and local food selections from the in-room dining menu.
Cetin Sekercioglu, Executive VP of Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts, stated that Hotel Jen prioritizes technology that can improve efficiency and guest experiences. He believes that the robots will be valuable additions to the team and align with Hotel Jen&amp;rsquo;s playful and surprising brand identity.</description></item><item><title>Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 now accepts e-signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</guid><description>Source: Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 website.
The Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 has introduced a paperless check-in experience featuring electronic signatures. This system aims to eliminate the need for printed documents and expedite the arrival process for guests. Aloft Bangkok claims to be the first hotel within the Starwood brand to offer this service.
This innovative approach streamlines the check-in procedure by presenting all reservation details on a tablet.</description></item><item><title>The Presidential Villa is now available at Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:01:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort.
The Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort is located near Dujiangyan, a UNESCO World Heritage &amp;amp; Natural Cultural site known as the home of giant pandas.
Inspired by the region&amp;rsquo;s history as the birthplace of Taoism, Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain introduces a new Presidential Villa. This villa embodies Taoist principles of living in harmony with nature, offering a space for reconnection and self-discovery.</description></item></channel></rss>