<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Donations on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/donations/</link><description>Recent content in Donations on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/donations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Last Minute Online Gifts For Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</guid><description>_On Christmas Eve, instead of the typical peaceful house,
your home is filled with stress as you realize you forgot a gift.
Despite your best efforts, you overlooked someone on your list.
The pressure is on to find a solution quickly.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that can save your holiday!
Search online and find the K.I.N.D site for the perfect gift.
You&amp;rsquo;ll not only deliver a thoughtful present but also make a difference.</description></item><item><title>Widgets for Charity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/widgets-for-charity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:49:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/widgets-for-charity/</guid><description>The holiday season is a time for giving, and this year, technology is making it easier than ever to support causes we care about. &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Giving Challenge,&amp;rdquo; a contest using &amp;ldquo;charity badges,&amp;rdquo; harnesses the power of social networks and the internet to raise money for charities.
The contest is backed by Kevin Bacon, who is known for his association with the &amp;ldquo;six degrees of separation&amp;rdquo; concept. His website, SixDegrees.org, supports celebrity charities and promotes the Charity Badge.</description></item><item><title>Get Paid To Celebrate National Cell Phone Recycling Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-celebrate-national-cell-phone-recycling-week/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s National Cell Phone Recycling Week, and there&amp;rsquo;s a way to make some money while participating! This initiative, spearheaded by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), highlights the importance of recycling valuable and potentially harmful materials found in cell phones.
Wireless carriers and various retailers are accepting old cell phones to ensure these devices are properly processed and their components are reused in new products. By taking part, you contribute to environmental protection by preventing hazardous materials from ending up in landfills.</description></item></channel></rss>