<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Protocol on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-protocol/</link><description>Recent content in Network Protocol on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-protocol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet is Cheaper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</guid><description>You probably know that T1 and DS3 lines have become much cheaper in recent years. But for those who need bandwidth of 10 Mbps or more, there&amp;rsquo;s an even better deal: Ethernet.
While you might know Ethernet as a local area network protocol, it&amp;rsquo;s now a wide area network protocol too. This means your carrier can provide an Ethernet connection that plugs directly into your existing network router or switch. You might see it called Ethernet WAN, Metro Ethernet, Carrier Ethernet, or Ethernet Transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-is-cheaper/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>