<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Capacitor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/capacitor/</link><description>Recent content in Capacitor on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/capacitor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Next Battery Is a Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</guid><description>Benjamin Franklin&amp;rsquo;s experiment with capturing electricity in Leyden Jars, glass jars with foil conductors that store electric charge, laid the groundwork for modern battery technology.
Today, researchers have developed ultracapacitors, like the Graphene Ultracapacitor from the University of Texas at Austin, which are essentially very small but powerful capacitors. These ultracapacitors use nanometer-thin dielectrics instead of bulky glass jars, allowing them to achieve farad-level capacitance, much higher than the picofarad capacity of a Leyden Jar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and one of the challenges is finding modern replacements for the large capacitors used in the 1970s. I received a 3D-printed adapter that allows me to neatly install smaller, current-generation capacitors.
These photos show the adapter with the new capacitors in place:
For reliability, I used two 300uF capacitors wired together to replace the original 150uF motor capacitor. The remaining capacitors are high-quality Rubycon, Panasonic, and Multicomp components chosen for their longevity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Power Supply and Replacing the Reservoir Capacitors with a 3D Printed Fixture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</guid><description>It seems Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen made two versions of the Beogram 4002 (5513) with different power supply setups, both designed with a possible CD4 upgrade in mind. The output board could be swapped for one with a pre-amplifier and CD4 decoder. One version powers the CD4 board directly from the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s 30V rail and uses a single 4000uF capacitor.
My Beogram 4002 uses a separate power supply for the CD4 board, with its own transformer winding, bridge rectifier, and 1000uF capacitor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Total Recap - Replacement of all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 10:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>This article revisits a complete restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, focusing on the replacement of electrolytic capacitors for improved long-term reliability. While not as crucial as with amplifiers due to lower operating temperatures, capacitor replacement is recommended for optimal performance.
The Beocord 9000, designed for serviceability, allows access to its numerous electrolytic capacitors. Unlike its predecessors, it offers easier access by removing the front and back panels instead of extracting the main circuit boards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Preamplifier and the Radio Amplifier Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s review the Beocord 5000! This model contains many tantalum capacitors that, due to their age (around 35 years), should be replaced. Tantalum capacitors pose a fire risk if they short circuit because of the intense heat released when tantalum reacts with oxygen. While tantalum capacitors were favored in the 1970s due to their smaller size compared to aluminum electrolytic capacitors, advancements in manufacturing have closed the size gap. Today, modern aluminum capacitors can be just as small as the older tantalum ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of New Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 and it was time to replace the large capacitors. This is a process I enjoy, made easier with a 3D printed adapter I designed. This adapter allows for the use of smaller, modern capacitors while maintaining a neat and organized appearance. I have a previous post detailing the connections for anyone who might find it helpful, as there are several jumpers that require re-soldering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration involved replacing the motor phase capacitor and reservoir. I used a 3D-printed adapter I designed, which allows for secure mounting of modern, smaller capacitors in the original location using the factory bracket. This post provides a closer look at the replacement process and includes a comprehensive wiring diagram for the capacitors. This can be particularly helpful for those tackling this task for the first time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Power Supply, Motor Control, Electronic Switch and Operational Control Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</guid><description>The restoration continues! Today, I replaced the remaining electrolytic capacitors on my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716). New electrolytics bring peace of mind!
The power supply board, including its reservoir and AC motor capacitors, along with the motor control, electronic switch, and operational control boards, were all addressed:
The Motor Control board, responsible for the take-up motor, had only one Tantalum capacitor that needed replacement:
Here it is after the replacement:
Next is the Electronic Switch board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating Recording Current and Bias</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</guid><description>Pleased with the seemingly functional Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape mechanism, an initial test recording was conducted using a waveform generator. Playback revealed a 3 dB channel imbalance on the Peak Program Meter (PPM), indicating a calibration issue. This was unsurprising given the deck&amp;rsquo;s age and highlighted the fortunate performance of a previously rebuilt Beocord 5000 in a Beolab 6000 setup, which operated well without calibration. To establish a solid calibration baseline, a reliable frequency response measurement was deemed essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Pulse Found...Beocord has life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-pulse-foundbeocord-has-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 16:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-pulse-foundbeocord-has-life/</guid><description>My examination of the Beocord power system continued with the regulator and power supply boards.
The regulator board houses the +5 VDC and ±15 VDC regulators, all situated on the large rear heatsink. I always inspect the heatsink compound and mica insulators for dryness, and thankfully, this Beocord appears to be in good condition.
I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered instances where these components showed deterioration, but not in this case.
With the regulator board cleared, I shifted focus to the power supply board&amp;rsquo;s voltages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-pulse-foundbeocord-has-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-pulse-foundbeocord-has-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor and Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</guid><description>I recently obtained a main PCB and DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002. I began with the motor refurbishment, a process that often requires several days for the bearings to become saturated with oil.
The motor is depicted here:
Disassembly was necessary to access the bearings, visible as two small rings on the black component in the front:
The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was noticeably oily, suggesting prior tampering. This was supported by a damaged commutator brush that was bent out of its intended form:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-and-main-pcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Recapping the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 restoration, I replaced all electrolytic capacitors as a preventative measure, opting for durable 105C types from reputable Japanese brands. Tantalum capacitors, particularly in older equipment, can fail dramatically, even catching fire.
On the power supply board, I discovered a missing screw and a loose one, potentially creating a dangerous short circuit scenario. Thankfully, no damage was evident. I replaced the tantalum capacitors and secured the board with a new stainless steel M3 screw...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating the Peak Program Meters (VU Meters)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</guid><description>After reassembling and successfully testing a Beocord 5000 tape deck, I decided to calibrate its Peak Program Meters (PPMs) according to the service manual.
Instead of directly inputting a 300 Hz signal into the Dolby B ICs as the manual suggested, I opted to feed a 25 mV, 300 Hz signal into the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inputs while in record mode (paused). Using a multimeter, I adjusted the recording levels to achieve the specified 740 mV RMS output at the Dolby B ICs (pin 7), allowing for the calibration of the PPMs&amp;rsquo; 0 dB level...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 551x: Exciting!! Replica DC Motor Bearing Prototypes from Beoparts Successfully Tested</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</guid><description>I received another set of Beogram 4002 platter motor components and an RPM panel from a customer in the Netherlands to restore. My work started with the motor, as it usually does.
I disassembled the motor to get to the bearings.
Typically, I would show a picture of the bearings being oiled in a vacuum chamber, but I received new Oilite bearings from www.beoparts-shop.com specifically for these DC motors, which I am testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-551x-exciting-replica-dc-motor-bearing-prototypes-from-beoparts-successfully-tested/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</guid><description>I recently provided a customer with replacement capacitors for his Beogram 4000 turntable, along with a 3D-printed adapter I designed.
He had been experiencing problems with the motor, as it was only displaying half waveforms. This suggested an issue with either the phase capacitor or the power supply reservoir capacitors. After installing the new components, the problem was completely resolved. You can find more details about this process in my original post here: link to my original post about this procedure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Platter Motor, Main PCB and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 18:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, experiencing RPM fluctuations, recently arrived from a customer for repair. The restoration process involved addressing issues with the DC platter motor, the main PCB, and the RPM adjustment panel.
The platter motor was disassembled to lubricate the bearings. After immersing them in oil and applying a vacuum, the bearings were left undisturbed for two days to ensure proper saturation. Once the bubbling ceased, indicating full replenishment, the bearings were extracted and the motor was reassembled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board and Adding a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>During the Beogram 4002 restoration, I took the opportunity to rebuild the output board while cleaning the keypad contacts. A common issue with these units is low or absent volume in one or both channels, often caused by the output relay. To address this, I replaced it with a modern, durable Japanese relay designed to last for many years. The original output board is shown here:
The old Siemens relay was swapped out for a custom-designed SMD relay assembly, pictured below:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>