<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>F1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/f1/</link><description>Recent content in F1 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/f1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monitoring social media shows the sentiments towards Formula One in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>In July, Microsoft launched Microsoft Social Listening in eight Asia Pacific markets. This service is designed to help professionals in sales, marketing, and customer care understand and engage with customers on social media more effectively. Microsoft Social Listening provides tools for analyzing market intelligence from social conversations, including sentiment analysis across multiple platforms. It also allows users to monitor products, brands, competitors, and campaigns globally in real time to gain a comprehensive understanding of their customers and their business in the social media landscape.</description></item><item><title>Tata Communications announces Global Scrapbook Challenge ahead of upcoming Formula 1 race</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications company, has launched its second technology challenge offering US$50,000 in prizes. This challenge focuses on harnessing innovative connectivity solutions, a key aspect of Formula 1 racing.
Leading up to the FORMULA 1 GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2014, Tata Communications is challenging the public to create a digital scrapbook celebrating the history of the Mercedes-Benz Silver Arrows in Formula 1. This Global Scrapbook Challenge aims to build a virtual museum, a captivating online archive of stories, memories, and intrigue for fans of the sport.</description></item><item><title>Experience the Singapore F1 promotion at BIG Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-singapore-f1-promotion-at-big-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 06:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-singapore-f1-promotion-at-big-hotel/</guid><description>Source: BIG Hotel.
Travelers can take advantage of a Formula One promotion at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s BIG Hotel. Bookings made by September 12th will receive a 10% discount on room rates, complimentary Wi-Fi throughout their stay, and access to free on-demand movies. This offer is valid for stays during the F1 night race in Singapore, from September 18th to 21st.
The hotel is conveniently situated on Middle Road, a short distance from Bras Basah station.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay to celebrate F1 with special meal promotions and parties at Attica</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 18:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay website.
Clarke Quay is celebrating the Singapore Grand Prix season with special offers and events for both racing fans and those just looking to enjoy the festivities.
Everyone can take advantage of dining deals like buy-one-get-one-free offers at District 10, special Grand Prix menu items at Hooters, and a free meal for every four diners at Peony Jade.
Those with Grand Prix tickets can also enjoy discounts of 10% to 20% at participating restaurants.</description></item></channel></rss>