<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Hosted PBX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-hosted-pbx/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Hosted PBX on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-hosted-pbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking Providers Want Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 12:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>The telephone industry is undergoing a transformation. Previously, businesses typically relied on in-house PBX systems to manage their phone networks and utilized ISDN PRI trunk lines for external calls. However, this is changing rapidly.
Two significant trends are emerging: cloud-based hosted PBX telephone systems and SIP trunking. While these technologies complement each other, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to implement SIP trunking without cloud services.
A telephone trunk consists of multiple phone lines grouped together, either physically or electronically...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rise Of The Cloud Hosted PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</guid><description>Traditional, in-house PBX systems might be nearing obsolescence with the emergence of cloud-hosted solutions like AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s AirePBX. This innovation signifies a return to an older model where the service provider manages the switching system, but with modern technological advancements.
This shift back to provider-managed systems, reminiscent of early telephone networks, offers significant cost advantages due to increased competition and the use of existing network infrastructure for VoIP services. Businesses no longer need to invest in separate wiring or proprietary equipment, leading to more competitive offerings and feature-rich options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>