<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>University on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/university/</link><description>Recent content in University on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:05:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zhaopin reveals changes in the entry-level job market in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</guid><description>Zhaopin, a Chinese career platform that connects users with job opportunities, conducted a 2017 career survey of college graduates in China, revealing notable trends. The survey indicated that graduates faced a more challenging job market and lower average salaries, presenting a difficult situation for the 7.95 million graduates entering the workforce.
2017 Labor Market for College Graduates Difficult and very challenging: 40.8% Difficult, but acceptable: 47.0% The market was OK: 9...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-reveals-changes-in-the-entry-level-job-market-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that students from third countries have the right to enter school.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the new academic year begins, students across the EU are met with a mix of anticipation and anxiety. Juggling academics, finances, personal life, and social activities is a universal experience for students, and those from outside the EU face the added pressure of meeting immigration requirements.
These requirements are standardized by the EU&amp;rsquo;s 2004 Students’ Directive. However, the degree of uniformity across member states remains unclear. Do individual countries retain the right to impose additional entry prerequisites?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on immigration for students and researchers a minor advancement or a significant stride?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU has been working for many years to attract highly skilled individuals from non-EU countries. However, the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s reports indicate that the existing legislation, specifically the 2005 Researchers&amp;rsquo; Directive and the 2004 Students&amp;rsquo; Directive, have not significantly increased the number of students and researchers coming to the EU.
As a result, in 2013, the Commission recommended a complete overhaul of these laws. The European Parliament (EP) and the Council recently reached an agreement on the content of this proposal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is making strides towards achieving global recognition for its universities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</guid><description>Indian educational institutions are increasingly recognizing the value of global university rankings, according to Quacquarelli Symonds (QS), the organization behind the recently released Asian Universities Ranking for 2014. This year&amp;rsquo;s list features 17 Indian universities, a significant increase from the 11 included in the previous year.
Source: QS website.
While the latest rankings show a slight dip in rankings for most of India&amp;rsquo;s top universities, the substantial increase in the number of represented institutions suggests a positive trajectory for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vitamin D does not increase longevity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 23:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</guid><description>While some believe vitamin D is a miracle cure, new research from the University of Cambridge, which analyzed data from almost 100 studies, indicates that vitamin D supplementation alone doesn&amp;rsquo;t decrease mortality rates in older adults.
Past research connected low vitamin D levels with illnesses like multiple sclerosis, cancer, and cardiovascular disease. To clarify if vitamin D supplementation by itself (without calcium or other interventions) impacts death from various causes, researchers examined 73 observational cohort studies and 22 randomized trials on naturally occurring vitamin D and supplements (D2 or D3)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>