<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IMF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/imf/</link><description>Recent content in IMF on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:56:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/imf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IMF is analyzing the economy of the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) mission, headed by Chikahisa Sumi, has assessed the Philippine economy&amp;rsquo;s performance as positive but believes there&amp;rsquo;s room for improvement.
During their visit to Davao and Manila from June 28 to July 12, the mission engaged with various stakeholders, including the Governor of the Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP), economic ministers, high-ranking government representatives, private sector leaders, and financial experts. Sumi&amp;rsquo;s post-mission statement highlighted the following:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF has finished its 2017 Article IV consultation with Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its regular economic review of Vietnam, finding that the country&amp;rsquo;s economy remains in good shape, supported by strong underlying economic conditions. Despite a slowdown in 2016 to 6.2% growth due to agricultural challenges from drought and saltwater intrusion, as well as reduced oil production, Vietnam’s economy has shown resilience.
While the oil sector continued to struggle in early 2017, strong manufacturing and foreign direct investment, healthy domestic demand, and a resurgence in agriculture are driving overall economic momentum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF reports that Armenia's economy is improving</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-reports-that-armenia-s-economy-is-improving/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:30:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-reports-that-armenia-s-economy-is-improving/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) concluded its regular economic assessment of Armenia on June 23, 2017. The IMF noted Armenia&amp;rsquo;s satisfactory economic growth with controlled inflation, generally well-managed government finances, and increased foreign currency reserves.
The IMF observed that in 2016, Armenia&amp;rsquo;s economic output grew by a minimal 0.2%, prices continued to fall, and the budget deficit reached 5.6% of GDP. However, in 2017, economic activity showed signs of recovery, with a rise in inflation and business loans, supported by relaxed monetary policies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-reports-that-armenia-s-economy-is-improving/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-reports-that-armenia-s-economy-is-improving/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhancing financial inclusion has the potential to boost economic growth in the Arab region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) is advocating for the development of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and greater financial inclusion in the Arab world.
During the World Government Summit in Dubai, UAE, IMF Managing Director Christine Lagarde emphasized the need for Arab countries to prioritize growth and job creation. She highlighted the significant role of SMEs in generating employment, diversifying economies, and driving overall economic growth.
Lagarde pointed out that while SMEs make up 96% of registered companies and employ half of the workforce in the Arab region, they face significant challenges in accessing finance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhancing-financial-inclusion-has-the-potential-to-boost-economic-growth-in-the-arab-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF has identified key policy priorities for Cambodia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) team, led by Sonali Jain-Chandra, visited Cambodia from July 6 to July 20, 2016, for their yearly review of Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s economy. The team analyzed economic data and discussed policies with Cambodian government officials, business leaders, and other stakeholders. They concluded that Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s economy is strong, with high growth projected to continue due to exports, real estate, and construction. However, they cautioned that this growth could slow in the long term and emphasized the risk of financial instability from rapid credit growth, particularly in real estate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMF provides feedback on the economy of Laos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-feedback-on-the-economy-of-laos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-feedback-on-the-economy-of-laos/</guid><description>At the end of January, the Executive Board of the International Monetary Fund (IMF) concluded its annual Article IV consultation with the Lao People&amp;rsquo;s Democratic Republic.
The IMF reported that real GDP growth is anticipated to decrease from 7.5% in 2015 to 7% in 2016. This moderation is attributed to a less favorable external environment leading to slower domestic activity, and a reduction in credit growth from its previous high levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-feedback-on-the-economy-of-laos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-feedback-on-the-economy-of-laos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF predicts a positive outcome for Pakistan's economic growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</guid><description>The IMF Executive Board finalized its regular economic assessment of Pakistan on June 14, 2017.
The IMF determined that Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic outlook is positive, with real GDP expected to reach 5.3% in FY2016/17 and rise to 6% in the medium term. This growth is attributed to increased investments from the China Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), greater energy availability, and structural reforms that support economic expansion. While inflation has gradually risen, the IMF team stated it remains manageable, and the financial sector is stable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-predicts-a-positive-outcome-for-pakistan-s-economic-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF mission has stated that Pakistan's economic reform efforts must extend beyond the EFF program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</guid><description>An IMF team, led by Harald Finger, visited Dubai between July 26th and August 4th, 2016, to discuss the final review of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic program supported by a three-year IMF Extended Fund Facility (EFF). The team met with key officials, including Finance Minister Ishaq Dar and State Bank of Pakistan Governor Ashraf Wathra.
The mission concluded with a staff-level agreement on the completion of the twelfth and final review under the EFF, subject to approval by IMF management and the Executive Board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should legitimacy be prioritized in the further development of the EMU, or should it be considered as a secondary concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</guid><description>Päivi Leino-Sandberg: Adjunct Professor of EU Law, Academy of Finland Research Fellow, University of Helsinki
In June 2012, the European Council outlined &amp;ldquo;four essential building blocks&amp;rdquo; for the future of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU): integrated frameworks for finance, budget, and economic policy, and enhanced democratic legitimacy and accountability. The European Council emphasized ensuring democratic legitimacy and accountability at all levels of decision-making and implementation, stating that stronger economic governance requires stronger legitimacy and accountability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF anticipates that the Kyrgyz Republic's economy will grow by 2.2% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) team, headed by Edward Gemayel, visited Bishkek, Kyrgyz Republic from July 8th to 14th. The purpose of the visit was to assess the country&amp;rsquo;s recent economic performance and lay the groundwork for the third review mission under the Extended Credit Facility (ECF), tentatively planned for late September.
Preliminary findings from the visit were presented by Gemayel, noting that these do not necessarily reflect the views of the IMF’s Executive Board:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMF approves of Singapore's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its yearly assessment of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy. The IMF noted that while Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy remains strong, it is facing challenges from both global and domestic factors.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economic growth slowed to 2% in 2015, down from 3.3% in 2014, and was 2.2% in the first half of 2016. While unemployment is still low, job creation slowed significantly in 2015, and inflation has remained negative since late 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF emphasizes the importance of AML/CFT for maintaining stability in the financial sector of the Kyrgyz Republic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</guid><description>Despite external pressures decreasing and some positive economic signs, the recovery has been modest. Economic growth sped up towards the end of 2016, hitting 3.8% with 0.5% deflation, partly due to a currency appreciation of about 9%. The 2016 deficit was kept to 4.5% of GDP due to controlled spending on less critical items and the rescheduling of some investment projects, even though tax revenue fell short of expectations. Efforts to consolidate the budget should continue to achieve the 2017 fiscal deficit target of 3% of GDP...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-emphasizes-the-importance-of-aml-cft-for-maintaining-stability-in-the-financial-sector-of-the-kyrgyz-republic/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>