<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spark on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spark/</link><description>Recent content in Spark on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:03:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor: Spark Snubber Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</guid><description>I recently had a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor on my workbench that I had previously worked on in November 2016 due to a broken brush and a severed pickup coil lead.
The motor recently began experiencing RPM fluctuations again.
This pointed to a problem with the spark snubbers. To access the rotor, I opened the motor:
The spark snubbers, marked with red dots, are located around the commutator. The replacements are on the black pad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and RPM Stability Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor from France was received for restoration.
As is typical, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite brass bearings needed fresh oil. This requires disassembling the motor and extracting the bearings for a vacuum oiling process.
The bearings were submerged in motor oil under vacuum, forcing air out of the porous material and drawing oil in. This process generally takes about 24 hours.
This shows the bearings after the oil infusion.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of DC Motor and a Dead TR2 Transistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</guid><description>After refreshing the PCBs and the RPM trimmer scale backlighting on a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, I turned my attention to its DC motor. Most DC motors in these models need their Oilite brass bearings replenished with oil, as the oil tends to seep out over time, leading to RPM instability. To do this, the motor needs to be disassembled.
The bearings sit on a black pad within the motor. I noticed the motor had been previously repaired, evident in the bent brushes, which would have hindered its performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Replacement of Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) DC platter motor, previously restored in 2016, displayed RPM fluctuations and required attention. Although the motor&amp;rsquo;s bearings had been treated with oil at that time, the spark snubbers were not replaced. The motor had functioned correctly following the initial restoration.
Initial testing involved installing the motor in a 4002 turntable and monitoring its RPM stability over 24 hours. The results are represented by the blue line in the provided graph.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and Dependence of RPM Performance on the Value of C10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</guid><description>I recently obtained two DC motors from Beogram 4002 turntables that are being refurbished. One of the motors is pictured here.
The first step in restoring these motors is addressing the brass sleeve bearings, which are often dry after more than 35 years of use. I do this through an oil infusion process, which requires complete disassembly, as shown.
The bearings, visible on the black pad in the front, are submerged in oil and placed under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: A New Tool on the Bench and the Importance of the Orientation of the Top Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was acquired for restoration. Evidence suggested prior repair attempts on the motor, including scratches on the bearing assembly and damaged brushes.
Upon disassembly, it was clear the bearings hadn&amp;rsquo;t been properly oiled. A vacuum oil infusion process was conducted on both the top and bottom bearings. After cleaning and reassembly, a short circuit was detected, pointing to faulty spark snubbers.
The old spark snubbers were replaced with modern TVS devices.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion, New Spark Snubbers and an Ultrasonic Cleaning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was recently sent in for repair. Initial testing showed the motor was barely functional. To address this, the motor was disassembled, and the bearings were removed for lubrication.
The bearings, designed to be porous and oil-filled, were treated with a vacuum oil infusion process. This process, evidenced by vigorous bubbling, helps to replenish the oil within the bearings over time. After a few days, the bubbling subsided, indicating the bearings were adequately filled with oil, and they were removed from the oil bath.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion of Bearings and New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A DC motor, removed from a Beogram 4002 in Arlington, VA, was sent in for repair.
The initial step involved taking the motor apart and extracting its bearings for lubrication.
The bearings, resembling small rings, were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied. This process causes air bubbles to emerge from the bearing material, indicating oil infusion.
After a day, the bubbling stopped, signifying that the bearings were saturated with oil.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Very Oily DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:44:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from Berlin, Germany, for restoration. The motor&amp;rsquo;s exterior was noticeably oily, likely due to an attempt to improve its RPM stability through lubrication.
Disassembly was necessary to access and treat the bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was also oil-coated. However, this is ineffective for the bearings, as they require vacuum oil infusion. This process removes air trapped within the porous Oilite brass material, enabling new oil to penetrate the bearing effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor, sent from Pennsylvania for repair, showed typical signs of needing lubrication, emitting a high-pitched noise when first turned on.
The motor was taken apart to access the bearings for oil treatment.
The bearings were placed in oil and a vacuum was applied. The appearance of bubbles showed air being pulled from the bearings, making room for oil to enter. After two days, the bubbles ceased, signaling the completion of the oil infusion process.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of DC Motor: A New Tool and a New Spark Suppressor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-motor-a-new-tool-and-a-new-spark-suppressor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 21:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-dc-motor-a-new-tool-and-a-new-spark-suppressor/</guid><description>I worked on restoring a Beogram 4002 DC motor, a process that unveiled a new and interesting failure point for these motors. This experience further refines the restoration process for these motors.
The motor needed its usual oil infusion for the porous brass bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s rough operation when powered confirmed this need.
Upon disassembly, I found this motor had the older brush carrier design, notorious for being glued to the alignment posts and feedback coils.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from the Netherlands, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t use it. The top bearing suspension was damaged beyond repair.
As a result, I refurbished a different motor I had on hand.
To lubricate the bearings, I took the motor apart and submerged them in oil.
A vacuum was applied to the oil-submerged bearings. This caused significant bubbling, signifying air escaping from the bearing material and creating space for oil to enter.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Bearings and Installation of New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 06:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor arrived from New Zealand for restoration. The upside-down pulley suggested prior repairs. Disassembly revealed a bent brush, a possible cause for the motor&amp;rsquo;s poor performance.
[Image of motor with bent brush]
The motor was fully disassembled, and the bearings underwent an oil infusion process to address potential RPM instability, a common issue.
[Image of disassembled motor] [Image of bearings in oil]
After the infusion, the bent brush was straightened.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the DC motor required attention. The bearings were making noise, indicating a need for lubrication. This is a common issue in Beogram DC motors of this age, often requiring oil replenishment for stable performance.
The motor was removed from the turntable for servicing.
The bearings, identified as two ring-shaped components, were taken out of the motor.
To lubricate them, the bearings were submerged in motor oil, and a vacuum was applied to remove trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Oil Infusion of Bearings, Replacement of Spark Snubbers, and Repair of a Disconnected Pickup Coil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-replacement-of-spark-snubbers-and-repair-of-a-disconnected-pickup-coil/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-replacement-of-spark-snubbers-and-repair-of-a-disconnected-pickup-coil/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor arrived from Michigan. Initial inspection showed no obvious external issues.
However, a bench test revealed the rotor was blocked, preventing the motor from spinning.
Upon disassembly, it was evident that someone had previously attempted a repair: the brushes were deformed and a pickup coil pin was broken. Further disassembly revealed a loose and disconnected coil near the missing pin.
To address potential bearing issues, the bearings were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied.</description></item><item><title>TomTom's latest Spark GPS fitness watches also have the capability to play music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. TomTom has introduced the Spark GPS fitness watch line. These new watches include a 3GB music player, making it simpler for fitness enthusiasts to enhance their workouts by listening to music directly from their wrist.
The TomTom Spark GPS fitness watch can stream music to a variety of Bluetooth headphones. It also includes a preloaded thirty-minute Running Trax curated by Ministry of Sound. Users can easily download playlists to the TomTom Spark from iTunes or Windows Media Player.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Some Microsurgery on Disconnected Pickup Coils</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-some-microsurgery-on-disconnected-pickup-coils/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 10:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-some-microsurgery-on-disconnected-pickup-coils/</guid><description>I recently obtained a DC platter motor from a Beogram 4002 located in Norway. The motor required repair. The owner had already performed the &amp;lsquo;oil infusion&amp;rsquo; procedure for the Oilite bearings. However, after reassembling and reinstalling the motor into the Beogram, the platter&amp;rsquo;s speed was excessively high and could not be adjusted.
This image displays the motor, without the pulley, in the condition I received it:
Uncontrollably high speed in a DC platter motor usually indicates a problem with one or both of the RPM feedback pickup coils within the motor, assuming the motor control circuit is functioning correctly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 and 4004 DC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-and-4004-dc-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 01:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-and-4004-dc-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently acquired two DC motors from Beogram 4002 and 4004 turntables located in Denmark. My typical first step is an oil infusion process to address RPM fluctuations, a common issue.
The 4002 motor arrived in this condition:
Disassembly revealed the following:
The two small, donut-shaped brass bearings, visible on the black pad, were submerged in motor oil under a vacuum. Bubbles appeared immediately, indicating the oil infusion process was working.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Repair of a Damaged Pickup Coil and Oil Infusion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-repair-of-a-damaged-pickup-coil-and-oil-infusion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 14:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-repair-of-a-damaged-pickup-coil-and-oil-infusion/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from Australia was sent in for repair. The owner reported the motor always ran at high speed, suggesting a broken RPM feedback coil. Without this feedback, the motor receives maximum power and spins as fast as possible.
Disassembly revealed the motor&amp;rsquo;s brushes were improperly installed and a solder burn marked one terminal. The small pickup coils, responsible for sending an AC voltage proportional to motor RPM, were also examined.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - The Influence of C10 on RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-the-influence-of-c10-on-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 10:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-the-influence-of-c10-on-rpm-stability/</guid><description>Another Beogram 4002 DC motor was prepped for restoration.
The process began by removing the bearings for an oil infusion.
The small brass bearings were submerged in motor oil, and a vacuum was applied.
Bubbling indicated that the oil was being drawn into the bearings. These bearings took longer than usual, approximately 48 hours, for the bubbling to cease.
After the bubbling stopped, the bearings were taken out of the oil</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4002 DC motor from France that needed some repair. My typical first step is to rejuvenate the oil-impregnated brass bearings by submerging them in oil. This process is usually successful in restoring motor function. This image displays the motor in its initial condition upon arrival:
To access the bearings, I took the motor apart:
The bearings are the two small ring-shaped components on the black surface.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: Oil Infusion of Bearings and Installation of New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 01:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-installation-of-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor, in need of restoration, arrived from Washington state. Initial examination showed it needed some work.
A bench test confirmed the bearings were squeaking, a common issue. The motor was disassembled to remove the bearings for lubrication.
The bearings were placed in motor oil under a vacuum. This process forces air out of the bearing material and allows oil to penetrate it. After a few days, the bearings were removed from the oil.</description></item></channel></rss>