<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smaato on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smaato/</link><description>Recent content in Smaato on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smaato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The more specific the mobile advertisement, the higher its earnings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</guid><description>Smaato, a mobile advertising company, has observed that the most successful advertising categories in China during the first quarter of the year were shopping, e-commerce, communication, and technology. These categories achieved high eCPMs (effective cost per mille), reaching up to US$0.30.
When analyzing mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad expenditures in China during the same period, entertainment (30%) and games (22%) were the top two categories.
Ajitpal Pannu, Smaato&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, noted that both monetization and brand spending increased when essential parameters were shared globally with advertising partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-more-specific-the-mobile-advertisement-the-higher-its-earnings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the second quarter of 2014, China's RTB ad spending increased by 616% compared to the previous quarter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</guid><description>Smaato, a company specializing in mobile real-time bidding (RTB) ad exchange (SMX) and supply side platform (SSP), has reported significant growth in mobile RTB in its Q2 2014 Global Mobile RTB Insights Report.
Source: The Smaato RTB Insights Report for Q2 2014. RTB spending in the APAC region for the top five countries.
Smaato&amp;rsquo;s findings show a 69% increase in RTB spending in the second quarter of 2014 compared to the first quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-second-quarter-of-2014-china-s-rtb-ad-spending-increased-by-616-compared-to-the-previous-quarter/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>