<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advice on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advice/</link><description>Recent content in Advice on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India has implemented measures to prepare for Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</guid><description>India is actively monitoring the situation to prevent the Ebola virus disease (EVD) from entering the country. Three dedicated helplines (2306 3205, 2306 1469, and 2306 1302) were set up at the Health Ministry on August 9th to address public inquiries.
While India has no confirmed or suspected Ebola cases, the World Health Organization (WHO) alerted the government about an Indian passenger who shared a flight with an Ebola patient traveling from Monrovia (Liberia) to Lagos (Nigeria), both experiencing outbreaks.</description></item><item><title>The most effective productivity hacks for Microsoft Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</guid><description>Microsoft Office 2013 offers several improvements over previous versions, but long-time users may not be aware of these useful additions. At the Singapore launch of Office 365 Personal, Elsie Chong, Marketing Manager for Microsoft Singapore, highlighted her favorite new features:
PDF Reflow in Word 2013 allows users to open PDF files as editable Word documents, retaining the original formatting as much as possible. The modified document can be saved as a PDF or a Word file.</description></item><item><title>CrowdsUnite offers convenient crowdsourcing updates all in one location</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 22:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</guid><description>CrowdsUnite (crowdsunite.com) aims to be the &amp;ldquo;Yelp&amp;rdquo; for crowdfunding, featuring over 800 platforms in its database. The website provides guidance on crowdfunding and helps startups find the best platforms for their needs.
Alex Feldman, CEO of CrowdsUnite, points out that crowdfunding sites vary in features, customer support, and transparency. He emphasizes the risk of fraudulent campaigns that disappear with investors&amp;rsquo; money.
Source: CrowdsUnite blog. Feldman presents crowdfunding at a July 2014 talk in New York, US.</description></item></channel></rss>