<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tip on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tip/</link><description>Recent content in Tip on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 23:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Criteo provides three suggestions for increasing sales conversions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 23:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance display advertising, offers advice based on its collaborations within the travel industry on converting leads into customers. This guidance is relevant across all sectors.
Tip #1: Strategically Time Your User Acquisition
Travel app downloads peak during summer (June-September), providing a window before peak season to engage a larger active user base*. Capitalize on your customers&amp;rsquo; planning and buying cycles by aligning download promotions for optimal new customer acquisition, Criteo recommends.</description></item><item><title>The most effective productivity hacks for Microsoft Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</guid><description>Microsoft Office 2013 offers several improvements over previous versions, but long-time users may not be aware of these useful additions. At the Singapore launch of Office 365 Personal, Elsie Chong, Marketing Manager for Microsoft Singapore, highlighted her favorite new features:
PDF Reflow in Word 2013 allows users to open PDF files as editable Word documents, retaining the original formatting as much as possible. The modified document can be saved as a PDF or a Word file.</description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question.</description></item></channel></rss>