<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cashless Transactions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cashless-transactions/</link><description>Recent content in Cashless Transactions on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cashless-transactions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wireless Business Broadband Available In A Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</guid><description>Imagine this: your new store is ready to open, everything is in place, but you can&amp;rsquo;t start selling because your internet service isn&amp;rsquo;t working. This is where Accel Networks comes in, offering a wireless solution that can get you online in just a few days.
Why choose Accel Networks? Traditional broadband often involves time-consuming installations. Accel Networks bypasses this by using existing cell tower infrastructure. Their service is secure, meets payment industry standards, and covers most of the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>POS For Temporary Store Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</guid><description>A common sight during the holidays is the &amp;ldquo;pop-up shop.&amp;rdquo; These temporary stores occupy vacant spaces in malls and shopping centers, offering seasonal goods like decorations, costumes, and calendars. Once the season ends, so do their operations. Despite their temporary nature, these businesses require robust point-of-sale (POS) systems, even more so than traditional stores.
The need for efficient POS systems stems from the concentrated bursts of customer traffic these stores experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath’s Black Friday Strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</guid><description>Black Friday, the day following Thanksgiving, is the traditional kickoff for Christmas shopping. Its success is crucial for retailers, as it can significantly impact their yearly profitability.
The term &amp;ldquo;Black Friday&amp;rdquo; is believed to originate from the accounting practice of using red ink for losses and black ink for profits. Many retailers struggle throughout the year, making the holiday shopping season, especially Black Friday, vital for their financial stability.
Black Friday, along with its online counterpart Cyber Monday (the Monday after Thanksgiving), initiates the busiest and most demanding sales period for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-s-black-friday-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Includes Canada &amp; Puerto Rico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 09:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</guid><description>People often associate broadband with wired connections, like T1 lines commonly used by small to medium businesses, or the increasingly popular Ethernet option known for its speed and affordability. While satellite is vital for many chain stores, there&amp;rsquo;s another reliable broadband solution that avoids construction costs and high monthly fees: fixed wireless broadband, now available across the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Accel Networks, a leading provider of fixed wireless broadband, leverages existing 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>