<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UK Nationality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-nationality/</link><description>Recent content in UK Nationality on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-nationality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Does Rottmann Rule apply in the UK? Can British citizenship be revoked without consideration of EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-rottmann-rule-apply-in-the-uk-can-british-citizenship-be-revoked-without-consideration-of-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-rottmann-rule-apply-in-the-uk-can-british-citizenship-be-revoked-without-consideration-of-eu-law/</guid><description>Simon Cox*
The UK Supreme Court recently examined the meaning and implications of the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s Rottmann judgment, which deals with EU law limitations on the revocation of national citizenship. The British Home Secretary&amp;rsquo;s legal representative contended that interpreting the judgment beyond cross-border situations would exceed the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s authority. The Court questioned if it could rule on the application of Rottmann before consulting the CJEU, a proposal the Government did not strongly contest.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of an Advocate-General's opinion reveals that Brexit will result in the end of EU citizenship for UK nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 11:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-an-advocate-general-s-opinion-reveals-that-brexit-will-result-in-the-end-of-eu-citizenship-for-uk-nationals/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The question of whether British citizens retained their EU citizenship after Brexit is disputed. While the EU and UK governments assert that they did not, some British individuals disagree.
This issue has been raised before EU courts through various avenues. Three cases directly appealed to the EU General Court, contesting the EU Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to finalize the withdrawal agreement. These appeals argued that the agreement improperly revoked their EU citizenship.</description></item></channel></rss>