<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Career on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/career/</link><description>Recent content in Career on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:08:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Swag employment superapp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises as well as job seekers in Singapore and Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</guid><description>Employment Hero, a company specializing in HR, payroll, and employee engagement, is launching Swag, an employment superapp designed to modernize the employer-employee relationship.
Building on its existing platform that streamlines HR and payroll processes for SMEs, Employment Hero is shifting its focus to enhance the job hunting experience for both employers and job seekers. Swag utilizes AI-powered recruitment tools to simplify and expedite the process of finding, onboarding, and rewarding talent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-swag-employment-superapp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-as-well-as-job-seekers-in-singapore-and-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Supporting mothers returning to work and mom entrepreneurs in advancing their careers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 10:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</guid><description>For more details, scan the QR code.
Among the nearly 40,000 members of Mums@Work, common challenges faced when rejoining the workforce include age, keeping up with technology and necessary skills, a lack of confidence, anxieties about new work environments, and generational differences.
This is despite over 80% of members having more than eight years of professional experience, primarily in white-collar roles within banking and finance, media and entertainment, and human resources...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supporting-mothers-returning-to-work-and-mom-entrepreneurs-in-advancing-their-careers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the corporate hierarchy, creative roles are gaining prominence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-corporate-hierarchy-creative-roles-are-gaining-prominence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 20:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-corporate-hierarchy-creative-roles-are-gaining-prominence/</guid><description>The increasing prominence of design-led thinking in business and strategic problem-solving is benefiting creatives&amp;rsquo; careers globally.
A 2016 Adobe survey of over 1,700 creatives, including graphic and web designers and artists, revealed that these professionals feel they are making a bigger impact within their organizations. Over half of respondents in the Asia Pacific region (56%) reported a greater impact compared to two years prior, with 89% stating that their companies now place more emphasis on creativity and design thinking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-corporate-hierarchy-creative-roles-are-gaining-prominence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-corporate-hierarchy-creative-roles-are-gaining-prominence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to LinkedIn, 65% of employees in Singapore are planning to change jobs in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</guid><description>Although hiring in Singapore experienced a significant drop of 34% in December 2022 compared to the previous year, and despite economic uncertainties, professionals are adopting a forward-thinking approach to their careers. They are investing in skill development and actively pursuing opportunities for advancement. LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s research indicates that a considerable 65% of professionals are contemplating job changes in 2023.
The desire for enhanced financial stability amidst rising living costs is a primary driver behind this job search trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is showcasing career opportunities in the field of cyber security to the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 23:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</guid><description>Singtel launched the Singtel Cyber Security Experience (CSX), an interactive online platform, to bolster Singapore&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity workforce. This portal aims to attract students and career changers to the field.
CSX showcases cybersecurity career paths through profiles of professionals from Singtel, Trustwave (its US-based subsidiary), and the Cyber Security Agency of Singapore (CSA). The platform features interactive simulations that mimic real-world scenarios, illustrating the skills needed for various roles.
Visitors can test their knowledge through challenges focused on fundamental cybersecurity concepts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-showcasing-career-opportunities-in-the-field-of-cyber-security-to-the-public/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>