<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expense on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expense/</link><description>Recent content in Expense on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 19:05:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/expense/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intuit Singapore is set to release a popular expense management application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 19:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/</guid><description>Intuit, a leading provider of accounting software for small businesses worldwide, is getting ready to introduce QuickBooks Self-Employed in Singapore. This software helps users efficiently monitor their business expenditures. Launched in the US back in 2015, QuickBooks Self-Employed has gained significant traction, boasting a global customer base of 180,000, a considerable increase from 50,000 just a year ago, including users in Australia.
The QuickBooks Self-Employed mobile app, expected to be released later this month, aims to support the expanding freelance workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grab for Work assists businesses in managing transportation costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</guid><description>Grab, a Southeast Asian ride-hailing company, has introduced Grab for Work, a complimentary transport expense management tool for businesses in Southeast Asia. Designed for business leaders, managers, HR, and finance professionals in both SMEs and MNCs, Grab for Work provides a streamlined approach to handling company transportation costs.
Developed with feedback from over 150 companies in the region during its beta phase, Grab for Work is currently utilized by a similar number of businesses across Southeast Asia, including notable names such as Chope Group (Singapore), Park Hotel Group (Singapore), Rainmaker Labs (Singapore), Yesboss (Indonesia), and Malaysian Airlines (Malaysia)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>