<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Connectivity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-connectivity/</link><description>Recent content in Network Connectivity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-connectivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>