<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Loss on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/loss/</link><description>Recent content in Loss on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/loss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Today is World Backup Day. Have you ensured the safety of your data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</guid><description>A recent worldwide study funded by Acronis, a prominent name in hybrid cloud data protection, highlights a rising awareness of the importance of safeguarding personal data on computers, mobile phones, and tablets.
Almost half of the surveyed individuals possess more than four devices per household requiring protection, and 45% are most afraid of misplacing photos and videos. Security and privacy were identified as crucial factors in data backup.
Evolving Concerns in Personal Data Security The traditional worries of hardware malfunctions and accidental deletions are no longer the sole reasons for data loss apprehension...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies that experience data breaches in the Asia Pacific region are unlikely to be forgiven</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 02:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</guid><description>New research from SafeNet reveals that data breaches significantly influence customer trust. The global study, including participants from Japan and Australia, found that 65% wouldn&amp;rsquo;t patronize a business that experienced a financial data breach, compromising credit card details, bank accounts, or login credentials.
SafeNet&amp;rsquo;s Q2 Breach Level Index reported 237 data breaches from April to June 2014, exposing over 175 million records globally. These findings highlight the impact of data breaches on customer loyalty and revenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consuming a balanced amount of protein helps dieters maintain muscle mass at a slower rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</guid><description>Source: Nestlé.
Nestlé Research Center collaborated with global scientists and found that consistent protein intake throughout the day might reduce muscle loss during weight loss attempts.
Published in the American Journal of Physiology - Endocrinology and Metabolism, the study explored ways to promote weight loss in obese older men while preventing muscle loss. Muscle loss can hinder weight loss, decrease strength and functional capacity, and heighten the risk of disability and mortality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>