<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Walk on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/walk/</link><description>Recent content in Walk on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:40:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/walk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jane's Walk Singapore offers a blend of classic and innovative walking tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Peatix page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk logo.
The annual Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore, a series of free walking tours led by community members, will take place from May 4th to 6th. Inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, these walks encourage participants to share local stories, discover the city, and connect with their neighbors.
While many tours are already at capacity, new spots may open up, so interested individuals are encouraged to check back.</description></item><item><title>Register for a Jane's Walk (if possible)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/register-for-a-jane-s-walk-if-possible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:32:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/register-for-a-jane-s-walk-if-possible/</guid><description>](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjjjftL3eBnpoP9-lZPIx2FBUIjixQblEemCMYjK1fsqWMFAnV2mbG6iaAU305MtXqwpzxONmNTYc8Z02crj7dnUv-D5-CAAuQb0naLfJdJRIYhUsM2hARYEEShQ8L3TaCSNH0-kREbc6cU/s1600/20180505_150031.jpg)
This image showcases an overseas Chinese support organization, 武裕平民互助会, with Lee Huat Motoring located just beyond the tree.
As expected, spots for Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walks are quickly filling up. Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk is a yearly event featuring free walks led by volunteers. These walks pay tribute to Jane Jacobs (May 4, 1916 - April 25, 2006), an urbanist, writer, and activist who tirelessly advocated for community involvement in urban design.
This coming May marks the 7th anniversary of Jane’s Walk Singapore.</description></item><item><title>There is something for everyone on Jane's Walks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 02:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global initiative of free walking tours led by community members, is making a comeback from May 6th to 8th. The walks are inspired by Jane Jacobs (1916-2006), an urban planner and advocate who championed community-driven city development. Grounded in the belief that everyone possesses knowledge about their surroundings, these walks celebrate Jacobs&amp;rsquo; ideas worldwide. Participants share stories about their neighborhoods, discover hidden gems, and connect with their neighbors.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the history of Bukit Panjang, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</guid><description>Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global movement of free walking tours inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, continues to thrive in Singapore, with tours often fully booked within hours of being announced. This enthusiastic response highlights the movement&amp;rsquo;s ability to connect people with their communities and explore urban landscapes.
This year, on May 5th, a sold-out walk titled &amp;ldquo;At the Crossroads: Bukit Panjang&amp;rdquo; offered participants a unique opportunity to delve into the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s rich history.</description></item><item><title>Digi is sponsoring customers to participate in the Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</guid><description>Source: Digi Telecommunications.
Digi Telecommunications is sponsoring 200 customers to join the WWF-Malaysia Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk in Penang and Sunway Pyramid. This event coincides with the Earth Hour 2015 celebration on March 28, 2015.
As the Night Walk@Sunway&amp;rsquo;s corporate sponsor, Digi has donated RM35,000 to support WWF-Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s environmental conservation efforts.
Digi is sponsoring 200 walk packs, costing RM60 each, for its customers. 100 packs are designated for Night Walk@Sunway and 100 for Night Walk@Penang.</description></item><item><title>Join Jane's Walk for free guided tours around Singapore from May 1 to 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 04:42:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk website.
Gather your coworkers and spend the first weekend of May discovering Singapore with Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a worldwide initiative of free walking tours led by locals and inspired by Jane Jacobs. The walks encourage people to share their community stories, explore their cities, and connect with their neighbors.
&amp;ldquo;Jane Jacobs, an advocate for walkability, vibrant communities, and citizen involvement in urban development, would be proud! She believed understanding a city requires observation, inquiry, and exploration, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to do just that during the weekend of May 1-3,&amp;rdquo; stated Mai Tatoy, Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk City Organizer in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>