<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Returns Directive on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/returns-directive/</link><description>Recent content in Returns Directive on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/returns-directive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU's Returns Directive beneficial or detrimental to the well-being of undocumented migrants?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-returns-directive-beneficial-or-detrimental-to-the-well-being-of-undocumented-migrants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at the EU Returns Directive: Five Years On Many EU citizens are worried about the impact of immigration, especially when it comes to unauthorized migrants without legal status. Others, however, prioritize humane treatment for these individuals. To manage this challenge, the EU created the &amp;ldquo;Returns Directive&amp;rdquo; in 2008, outlining procedures for returning unauthorized migrants, including detention rules and procedural rights.
Upon its introduction, the Directive faced criticism from NGOs and academics who felt it was overly harsh.</description></item><item><title>Europe's Immigration Detention: Uncovering the Truth - A Recent Study by the European Migration Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
In November, the European Migration Network (EMN) published a Focused Study entitled “The use of detention and alternatives to detention in the context of immigration policies.” The study is a synthesis report drawn from national reports from 26 countries, compiled by the EMN National Contact Points (NCPs).</description></item><item><title>The Utilization of Prisons for Detaining Migrants in Europe and the EU Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, a researcher at the Global Detention Project and the Global Migration Centre, and a PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies in Geneva, examines a legal question: can immigration detainees be held in prisons alongside ordinary prisoners?
On July 17, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this question in its decisions regarding the combined cases of Bero and Bouzalmate and the separate case of Pham.</description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law.</description></item><item><title>Comparing Celaj and Vélez Loor: The implications of Latin American immigrants' detention in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</guid><description>Dr Andrea Romano, Research assistant, “Sapienza” University of Rome
Introduction
The recent Celaj judgment and its debatable connection to past rulings of the Court of Justice concerning the Returns Directive has been the subject of much discussion. This analysis will provide a concise comparison between this judgment and the Vélez Loor case, which was decided by the Inter-American Court of Human Rights (IACtHR) in 2010.
The Court of Justice of the European Union’s judgment in the Celaj case stemmed from various preliminary rulings brought forth by Italian judicial bodies regarding the Returns Directive.</description></item><item><title>Is the non-refoulement principle in the EU's qualification Directive considered invalid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 14:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</guid><description>By Pieter Boeles, visiting professor migration law, VU University Amsterdam, emeritus professor University Leiden
Introduction
The principle of non-refoulement, which forbids returning individuals to unsafe nations, is generally considered absolute. However, ambiguity persists concerning its application within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, which governs the determination of refugee or subsidiary protection status. The Czech Nejvyšší správní soud inquired with the Court of Justice of the European Union on July 14, 2016, about the potential conflict between Article 14(4) of the Qualification Directive and the principle of non-refoulement (Case C-391/16).</description></item><item><title>EU leaders are avoiding taking significant action to address the migrant crisis.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU leaders convened yesterday and agreed on a policy to handle the escalating migrant death toll in the Mediterranean Sea. This new policy expands on the recently implemented 10-point plan established by ministers. Notably, some significant last-minute revisions to the initial draft highlight the leaders&amp;rsquo; priorities.
Detailed comments
The leaders&amp;rsquo; statement appears to demonstrate more empathy than the prior 10-point plan. It acknowledges the immense loss of life as a tragedy and prioritizes the prevention of further deaths at sea.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N.</description></item><item><title>Comments on the outcomes of the most recent European Council meeting regarding EU migration policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU faces another crisis alongside &amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;: a surge in immigration. Initial EU responses culminated in an emergency summit in April. I previously discussed the outcomes of that summit. Subsequently, the Commission released its EU migration &amp;ldquo;Agenda&amp;rdquo; in mid-May, followed by detailed proposals. Last week, the European Council revisited immigration, reaching several conclusions. This post outlines those conclusions and offers my commentary. The third part of the conclusions, which vaguely promises increased cooperation with third countries, is omitted.</description></item><item><title>Responsibility in Joint Returns after WS and Others v Frontex: Letting the Active By-Stander Off the Hook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</guid><description>A Missed Opportunity for Accountability: Examining the General Court&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in WS and others v Frontex This analysis delves into the General Court&amp;rsquo;s September 6, 2023, decision in the case of WS and others v Frontex, where a Syrian refugee family&amp;rsquo;s claim for damages against Frontex was dismissed. The family, seeking refuge in the EU during the Syrian war, was returned to Turkey under questionable circumstances involving a joint return operation between Greece and Frontex.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the voluntary departure of irregular migrants: Act before you are forced to leave.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued its first ruling on &amp;ldquo;voluntary departure&amp;rdquo; provisions within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, which governs the deportation of undocumented non-EU migrants. While technically still an obligation to leave under threat of force, &amp;ldquo;voluntary departure&amp;rdquo; offers a more humane alternative to forced removal.
Typically, migrants are given 7 to 30 days for voluntary departure, extendable in specific cases. However, this period can be denied or shortened to less than seven days if the migrant is deemed a flight risk, if their application for legal stay was rejected as unfounded or fraudulent, or if they pose a risk to public safety, security, or national interests.</description></item><item><title>The decision in Celaj by the CJEU: Implications of criminal penalties, entry bans, and the Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</guid><description>By Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a decision on October 1, 2015, in the case of Skerdjan Celaj (C-290/14) that once again addressed the relationship between immigration and criminal law. Specifically, the court examined whether national criminal penalties for unlawful migration align with the EU Returns Directive.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees.</description></item><item><title>The EU Court of Justice has made a ruling on the Schengen Conundrum, which involves a non-EU citizen who has been ordered to leave one Member State but holds a valid residence permit in another Member State.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-court-of-justice-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-schengen-conundrum-which-involves-a-non-eu-citizen-who-has-been-ordered-to-leave-one-member-state-but-holds-a-valid-residence-permit-in-another-member-state/</guid><description>Professors Elspeth Guild, Queen Mary University of London and Kingsley Napley, and Steve Peers, University of Essex
This article examines a case presented to the Court of Justice concerning the situation of a non-EU citizen residing in one Member State while facing potential expulsion by another.
Background
This issue presents legal complexities due to the involvement of two separate EU law sources. Article 25 of the Schengen Convention, amended in 2010, dictates that a Member State considering issuing a residence permit must first check the Schengen Information System (SIS) for any entry bans (alerts) on the individual.</description></item><item><title>Is the judicial oversight of detention a misleading disruption?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III
Member of the Institut Universitaire de France
On June 5, 2014, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) issued a decision in the Mahdi case, providing further interpretation of the Return Directive. This directive, formally known as Directive 2008/115/EC, establishes common standards for EU Member States regarding the return of illegally staying third-country nationals. The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s judgment builds upon its prior rulings concerning this directive.</description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly.</description></item><item><title>Imprison them: the suggestion to revise the EU's Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, established to manage irregular migration by non-EU citizens, mandates that Member States issue return decisions to unauthorized individuals and enforce their removal. While the Directive allows for voluntary departure periods, it also outlines rules for detention and entry bans. Initially considered lenient by migrant support groups, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has since interpreted the Directive more broadly.</description></item></channel></rss>