<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Managed IT Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-it-services/</link><description>Recent content in Managed IT Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-it-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A New Cloud In IT Managed Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</guid><description>Many businesses are seriously considering migrating their IT infrastructure to cloud-based managed solutions. The key question then becomes: which cloud platform is the right fit? One compelling option is the &amp;ldquo;new cloud.&amp;rdquo;
NewCloud Networks, a managed service provider established in 1988, offers comprehensive solutions ranging from voice and data services for small businesses to intricate national and international networking solutions.
NewCloud differentiates itself by providing bespoke solutions tailored to specific client needs, rather than forcing a one-size-fits-all approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Network Provider Can Help Keep You Secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large and small companies alike are constantly facing major cyberattacks. While these attacks used to be more of a nuisance carried out by tech enthusiasts, they now pose a serious threat to businesses, causing disruptions and even irreparable damage.
Taking All Necessary Precautions
You might believe you&amp;rsquo;re protected from cyberattacks, but there&amp;rsquo;s always a chance that you&amp;rsquo;re still vulnerable. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some fundamental cybersecurity practices, as advised by Level 3 Communications, to ensure we&amp;rsquo;re taking all necessary precautions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-network-provider-can-help-keep-you-secure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Colocate To An Omaha Data Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</guid><description>While major corporations might associate colocation data centers with locations like 60 Hudson St in New York City or One Wilshire in Los Angeles, Omaha, Nebraska, presents a compelling alternative.
Beyond being home to Warren Buffett and Berkshire Hathaway, Omaha boasts a robust business environment, earning recognition from Forbes magazine as the nation&amp;rsquo;s top &amp;ldquo;Best-Bang-For-The-Buck City.&amp;rdquo; Crucially, Omaha houses the Scott Data Center complex.
The Scott Data Center offers over 110,000 square feet of data storage, boasting continuous operation since 2006...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why The Smart WAN Beats A Dumb Pipe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 16:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) are traditionally built using &amp;ldquo;dumb pipes,&amp;rdquo; which are simple bandwidth connections between two points. These connections are efficient at their primary function: transferring data packets. However, as IT requirements become more complex, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing need for more intelligent solutions. This can be achieved by either enhancing your internal IT capabilities or outsourcing these needs as a service.
Level 3 Communications, a leading provider of fiber network services, recognizes this shift from basic to high-performance networking demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Meshed MPLS Forms a Cloud of Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</guid><description>Modern MPLS networks are replacing outdated Frame Relay networks for connecting multiple business sites. Their ability to handle almost any protocol with high quality and reliability has driven their popularity. A long-standing desire has been the ability to use multiple carriers across locations seamlessly within a managed MPLS network. This desire has finally been fulfilled.
AireSpring, a rapidly growing and innovative carrier, now offers a &amp;ldquo;Meshed MPLS Network.&amp;rdquo; But what exactly does this entail and how does it differ from the inherent mesh capabilities of any MPLS network?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>