<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP VPN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-vpn/</link><description>Recent content in IP VPN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-vpn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet VPLS Extends Your LAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</guid><description>Traditional methods of connecting multiple business locations, such as Frame Relay, VSAT satellite terminals, internet-based VPNs, and dedicated T1 lines, have been around for a while. However, a new technology called Ethernet VPLS offers superior performance and cost advantages, making it a compelling option for businesses with multiple locations, including branch offices, retail franchises, and medical clinics.
Ethernet VPLS, which stands for Virtual Private LAN service, essentially functions as a carrier-managed local area network that can span across cities, states, or even the entire country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Networking Services Extend Business Footprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 20:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</guid><description>For businesses with a single office in one city, cloud computing or hosted PBX might suffice, as their communication needs are primarily about connecting to a provider&amp;rsquo;s cloud. However, companies with multiple locations require cloud networking services to link these sites seamlessly.
Cloud networking utilizes public or private networks to connect geographically dispersed locations in various configurations. Examples include the internet, privately managed MPLS networks, and even custom-built networks using leased lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TelePacific Takes Business Continuity Seriously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications, a telecommunications company serving California and Nevada, emphasizes a thorough approach to disaster preparedness and business continuity.
Their Business Continuity Services aim to keep your voice and data operational, even if a trunk line or your entire facility goes down. But how is this achieved?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with telephone service. Many businesses utilize digital trunk lines like T1 PRI and SIP Trunks, which offer cost savings compared to individual lines but pose a single point of failure risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>