<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Border and Coast Guard on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-border-and-coast-guard/</link><description>Recent content in European Border and Coast Guard on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-border-and-coast-guard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Border and Coast Guard a completely new entity or just a revamped version of Frontex?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</guid><description>Herbert Rosenfeldt, Research Assistant and PhD candidate, University of Passau
Introduction
Celebrating the new European Border and Coast Guard Agency, also known as Frontex, at the Bulgarian external border with Turkey might seem like an odd festivity. However, last Thursday, high-ranking EU and Member State officials gathered at Bulgaria&amp;rsquo;s Kapitan Andreevo Border Checkpoint for this inauguration. This event marked the implementation of the European Border and Coast Guard Regulation, a significant step towards strengthening external border control in the wake of recent migration challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accountability of Frontex: a challenging journey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 22:27:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</guid><description>Laura Salzano, PhD student in Constitutional Law, Barcelona University
Since its establishment in 2004, Frontex&amp;rsquo;s role and duties have been heavily scrutinized by the EU and human rights advocates. This attention stems from various concerns, including allegations of power abuse, opacity, and lack of cooperation. These concerns have been raised by diverse voices, such as policy experts, legal professionals, academics, activists, and NGOs.
Critiques of Frontex originate from both within and outside the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Union Migration Agencies: Frontex, EASO, and Europol's Operations and Collaborations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</guid><description>Dr. David Fernández-Rojo, Universidad de Deusto - davidfrojo@deusto.es
The recent surge in migration, often called the “refugee crisis,” highlighted the urgent need to strengthen both the Schengen area and the Common European Asylum System (CEAS). It also underscored the need to support EU member states dealing with large numbers of migrants and to consistently apply EU policies on migration, asylum, and border control. EU agencies such as Frontex, EASO, and Europol have become central to these efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>