<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Payment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-payment/</link><description>Recent content in E-Payment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-payment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recharge your prepaid mobile accounts using du's mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</guid><description>For the first time in the UAE, du customers can now top up their prepaid mobile phones using mPay. This new service was unveiled today at GITEX Technology Week 2015.
Fahad Al Hassawi, Chief Commercial Officer at du, stated, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to be the first operator offering prepaid recharge via mPay, making it easier for our customers to top up their prepaid du lines conveniently. We believe this will be highly popular among our users.</description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides.</description></item><item><title>Maybank customers in Malaysia can now access Western Union remittances digitally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</guid><description>Maybank and Western Union have partnered to introduce the first digital remittance service in Malaysia. This service, accessible through the Maybank2u (M2u) mobile app and website, allows Maybank customers to send money to over 500,000 Western Union agent locations in more than 200 countries and territories. Available 24/7, the service facilitates transfers up to RM10,000 daily, with recipients typically receiving funds faster than traditional methods.
Datuk Lim Hong Tat, Maybank&amp;rsquo;s Group Head of Community Financial Services, highlighted that this launch strengthens Maybank&amp;rsquo;s online presence and promotes digital transactions.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Tencent collaborate to simplify gifting and payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Wong.
Starbucks Coffee Company and Tencent Holdings, a Chinese provider of online services, are collaborating. In early 2017, they plan to launch a new social gifting feature within WeChat, a popular mobile communications service in China. Additionally, Starbucks customers at nearly 2,500 stores across mainland China can now use WeChat Pay for their purchases.
This partnership makes Starbucks the first retailer in China to provide an integrated, locally relevant social gifting and digital payment experience within WeChat.</description></item><item><title>Adyen predicts that smartphones will soon surpass tablets as the primary device for mobile payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 22:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</guid><description>Source: Adyen. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Adyen, a global payments technology provider, recently released its quarterly Mobile Payments Index for Q3. This report analyzes mobile payment data from web-based transactions across Adyen&amp;rsquo;s customer base between July and September. Notably, the Index reveals that nearly half of online transactions using specific payment methods are now conducted on mobile devices.
The Index shows that 47% of payments made with JCB, a Japanese card, were completed on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is encouraging subscribers to use their phones for payment at the supermarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</guid><description>A picture of a Dash payment reader at a FairPrice checkout.
Starting November 17th, shoppers can use Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash mobile payment app at over 200 NTUC FairPrice locations, including their supermarkets, Xtra hypermarkets, and standalone Cheers stores.
Gan Siok Hoon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of mCommerce, Consumer Singapore, stated that as a major fintech provider, they were excited to partner with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer, FairPrice, to offer this fast and secure payment option to their over half a million daily shoppers.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash is running a flash campaign offering mystery cashback for purchases made on Lazada.SG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment app, Dash, is holding a short promotional campaign with online store Lazada.SG. From October 2nd to 9th, 2015, shoppers can receive a surprise cashback reward of 15% to 50%*.
Each day of the campaign features a &amp;ldquo;Dash Happy Hour.&amp;rdquo; During this limited time frame, which lasts up to two hours, customers using Dash to pay for purchases on Lazada.SG can earn cashback. The specific cashback amount won&amp;rsquo;t be disclosed until the end of each day and will be added to customer accounts within three business days.</description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide.</description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally.</description></item><item><title>Fishbat provides commentary on the latest developments in iOS8 and the introduction of Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple, the tech giant, recently launched the first beta version of iOS 8.1. This upgrade comes shortly after the release of iOS 8.0.2, which was itself a fix for a bug found in the recently launched iOS 8.0.1.
This new beta version offers several new features:
A redesigned icon for iBooks. An option to enable dictation within the keyboard settings. Updated application permission settings. Larger application icons specifically designed for the new widgets in the notification center.</description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave.</description></item><item><title>The Double 12 Global Shopping Festival aims to attract Alipay users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 09:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</guid><description>Source: Alipay Facebook page. Flag advertising the Double 12 Global Shopping Festival.
Alipay, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading online and mobile payment and lifestyle platform operated by Ant Financial Services Group, launched its 2017 Double 12 Global Shopping Festival in Southeast Asia. The festival includes Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, and the Philippines.
Double 12 is a global event spanning 15 countries and territories across four continents. Over 500 brands and 100,000 merchants worldwide participate, offering Alipay users exclusive promotions throughout December.</description></item><item><title>Card-not-present fraud is on the rise, leaving two-thirds of credit card issuers in the Asia-Pacific region vulnerable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 11:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</guid><description>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing a surge in e-commerce, but this growth is accompanied by an increase in online fraud. A survey of fraud professionals in the region, conducted by predictive analytics firm FICO, revealed that card-not-present (CNP) fraud is the fastest-growing type of fraud. Nearly all (94%) of the survey respondents reported an increase in CNP fraud.
eMarketer, a research firm, projects that B2C e-commerce sales in the Asia Pacific region will reach US$525.</description></item><item><title>Global Payout expands MoneyTrac assistance to the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 12:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</guid><description>Global Payout, a company that offers business-to-business electronic payment solutions, has expanded its proprietary MoneyTrac consolidated payment gateway (CPG) platform to the Philippines.
MoneyTrac allows users to make secure payments to employees and business partners. Users can configure virtual accounts to meet specific payment needs, sending funds to bank accounts in supported countries, debit cards, credit cards, or even other users on the system.
Bill Rochfort, President and VP of Sales, highlighted the significant opportunity in providing financial services to the Philippines&amp;rsquo; large population, including millions of Filipinos working abroad (OFWs).</description></item><item><title>Singaporean banks are getting their customers ready for Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 09:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s website in Singapore now features a dedicated page for Apple Pay, which includes a list of participating banks and retailers. Among the banks listed, DBS and POSB have almost identical images on their websites, and UOB also has a dedicated page. Standard Chartered currently does not have any information available. DBS clarifies that Apple Pay offers a fast and secure payment method compatible with a user&amp;rsquo;s preferred DBS card. Contactless payments are also supported for iPhone and Apple Watch users.</description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app.</description></item></channel></rss>