<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Violence Against Women on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/violence-against-women/</link><description>Recent content in Violence Against Women on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/violence-against-women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Opinion of AG de la Tour in C-621/21: Is it a helpful clarification or an unnecessary hindrance to women seeking international protection from gender-based violence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Grundler, a Lecturer in Law at the Department of Law and Criminology, Royal Holloway, University of London, examines a recent legal opinion concerning refugee and subsidiary protection eligibility for women at risk of violence within their families.
Advocate General (AG) de la Tour&amp;rsquo;s Opinion in case C-621/21 tackles the scope of the refugee definition within Article 2(d) of the Qualification Directive and the definition of subsidiary protection beneficiaries in Article 2(g) concerning women facing potential violence within a family setting.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Complex Legal Issues from a Legal Standpoint with Partiality and Passion, or The European Union's Approval of the Istanbul Convention: Jurisdiction, Foundations, and Consensus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - @CateBriddick*
On March 11, 2021, Advocate General Hogan of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) presented his legal opinion on the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s inquiry regarding the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) potential membership in the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Istanbul Convention).</description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU truly dedicated to addressing violence against women, or is it just empty words?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre of the University of Oxford - @CateBriddick
Background
The European Union (EU) has a core legal commitment to fight discrimination, including sex-based discrimination, and to promote gender equality. However, it has faced ongoing and valid criticism for not upholding these commitments, especially regarding its treatment of female migrants and refugees. Therefore, the Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2016 announcement that the EU would sign and ratify the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women (the Istanbul Convention) was welcomed by activists and academics.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on domestic violence and the free movement of EU citizens is disgraceful.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU freedom of movement laws don&amp;rsquo;t directly apply to non-EU citizens. Instead, they gain rights through family ties with EU citizens. This poses a problem in domestic violence situations where the abuser is an EU citizen and the victim is not. Leaving the abuser could lead to expulsion, forcing victims to choose between their safety and remaining in the country, potentially separated from their children.
EU law attempts to mitigate this risk.</description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles.</description></item><item><title>The EU's groundbreaking Directive 2024/1385 on Violence Against Women is a significant step forward in promoting gender equality.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</guid><description>Dr. Ceren Kasım, Postdoctoral Research and Teaching Fellow, University of Hildesheim, Germany
Photo credit: MesserWoland, via Wikimedia Commons
INTRODUCTION
May 14, 2024, marked a pivotal moment for the European Union (EU) as it unveiled its first legally binding instrument to combat violence against women and domestic violence. This Directive, officially known as Directive 2024/1385, signifies the EU&amp;rsquo;s strong commitment to achieving genuine equality for women.
Gender-based violence is a pervasive issue across the EU.</description></item></channel></rss>