<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Right to Family Life on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-family-life/</link><description>Recent content in Right to Family Life on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-family-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Integration requirements for family reunification: the CJEU restricts the autonomy of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In recent times, many EU member states have started requiring non-EU citizens to pass an integration test before they can be reunited with their families in the EU. The EU&amp;rsquo;s family reunification rules allow for this, stating that family members joining non-EU citizens &amp;ldquo;may be required to comply with integration measures.&amp;rdquo; However, for family members of refugees and highly skilled migrants with EU Blue Cards, these tests can only be applied after they arrive.</description></item><item><title>Love triumphs in the CJEU: Equal Marriage and EU Freedom of Movement Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling on same-sex marriage within the framework of EU free movement law in the case of Coman. This case involved a Romanian citizen, Mr. Coman, who married his American husband in Belgium while residing there. When they attempted to return to Romania, the Romanian government, which does not legally acknowledge same-sex marriage, refused residency to Mr.</description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood.</description></item><item><title>Guardianship, freedom of movement, and child rights: the SM ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*This blog post expands on research that informed the upcoming revised edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Defining a &amp;ldquo;family member&amp;rdquo; legally can be complex, especially when it comes to immigration law and child welfare. The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment in the SM case highlights these complexities, particularly where EU free movement law intersects with the family law of non-EU nations.</description></item></channel></rss>