<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UAE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uae/</link><description>Recent content in UAE on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uae/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The success of Dubai as a business hub will depend on talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-success-of-dubai-as-a-business-hub-will-depend-on-talent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-success-of-dubai-as-a-business-hub-will-depend-on-talent/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Crown Prince and Chairman of The Executive Council, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, emphasized the importance of skill development, talent discovery, and attracting skilled professionals to establish Dubai as a future-forward city during his visit to LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s regional headquarters.
He attributed Dubai&amp;rsquo;s success in drawing entrepreneurs and multinational corporations to its conducive investment climate, fostering a hub of exceptional talent. This aligns with the vision of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister and Ruler of Dubai, to shape Dubai into a knowledge-based, innovation-driven economy.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber has announced the launch of the Dubai Smartpreneur Competition for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, working with the Smart Dubai Office, launched the second annual Dubai Smartpreneur Competition. This aligns with the vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, to make Dubai a leading smart city.
Source: Dubai Chamber. The event featured a panel discussion about the UAE government&amp;rsquo;s progress on smart city and innovation initiatives, and what will drive future sustainable growth.</description></item><item><title>DED allows for the licensing of eight additional business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</guid><description>Source: DED. Bushahab.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Economic Development (DED) has expanded its list of permissible business activities, increasing the total to 2,133. This decision stems from regular feedback gathered from various industry sectors regarding local market needs and the balance of supply and demand. The goal is to simplify business operations and offer essential resources for growth.
The new additions encompass several specialized activities. These include assembling industrial robots, providing tax consultancy services, printing secure documents, manufacturing scanners, collecting and transporting hazardous waste, offering health consultancy, brokering financing deals, and developing and managing applications for social media.</description></item><item><title>Consumer Card achieves outstanding success, according to DIB's report</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</guid><description>Source: DIB website. Banner for the Consumer Card page.
The Consumer Card, a collaboration between the Department of Economic Development (DED) in Dubai and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the largest Islamic bank in the UAE, has surpassed expectations in a very competitive market by the close of 2016. This success highlights how much customers value the card&amp;rsquo;s transparency and customer-centric approach.
Customers appreciate the card&amp;rsquo;s straightforward rewards system, which focuses on everyday transactions rather than requiring increased spending.</description></item><item><title>The Al Ain Cultural Programme for 2017/2018 is currently in full swing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</guid><description>The Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi recently held three events showcasing Emirati culture and heritage as part of the annual Al Ain Cultural Programme.
On October 19th, Qasr Al Muwaiji (Al Muwaiji Palace) hosted the Bisht Workshop, which delved into the history of the traditional garment worn by UAE rulers and the unique patterns associated with each ruler. Attendees also participated in a hands-on workshop, learning to create their own bisht.</description></item><item><title>Dubai World Central is pleased to welcome partnerships between the UAE and Japan through the Japan Trade Centre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</guid><description>Source: Dubai World Central. Khalid Abdulla, Vice President, Licensing, Registration &amp;amp; Permits Approval, Dubai World Central, Usama Saleh, Vice President, Land Planning and Development, Dubai World Central, with Shogo Ishida, Director, JTC DWC LLC, during the inauguration of the Japan Trade Centre at Dubai World Central in January 2015.
The Japan Trade Centre (JTC), a private business-to-business platform promoting Japanese small and medium enterprises (SMEs) internationally, is now operational at Dubai World Central (DWC)&amp;rsquo;s Business Park.</description></item><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Chamber partners with Souq.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry and Souq.com, the leading online retail and marketplace platform in the Middle East, have partnered to boost Chamber members’ participation in regional e-commerce.
The agreement grants Dubai Chamber members exclusive benefits from Souq.com, including complimentary access to its Fulfilled by SOUQ services for three months and specialized onboarding training. These benefits also encompass enhanced search visibility, customer support, and promotional opportunities.
In turn, Souq.</description></item><item><title>The perspectives of Gen Z differ from those of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</guid><description>A panel discussion at the Global Islamic Economy Summit focused on the characteristics of Generation Z, the generation following Millennials. Growing up with the internet and mobile phones, Gen Z is not only tech-savvy but also possesses a distinct perspective.
Sunil John, CEO of ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller, pointed out that governments are increasingly paying attention to this generation, questioning if current education and employment systems meet their needs. Citing the ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey 2016, John highlighted that 58% of young Arabs desire higher education, and 36% aim to start businesses, a departure from the traditional reliance on government jobs.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural commercial flight of the Etihad Boeing 787 Dreamliner is headed to Germany</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways, the flag carrier of the UAE, launched its inaugural Boeing 787 Dreamliner commercial flight. The first flight, a Boeing 787-9, flew from Abu Dhabi to Düsseldorf, Germany. Departing at 2:15 a.m. as flight EY23, the seven-hour, 25-minute journey landed at 6:40 a.m. The return leg from Düsseldorf departs at 10:20 a.m., arriving in Abu Dhabi at 7:50 p.m.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and CEO, stated that the Boeing 787 is a significant achievement for the airline, calling it the most technologically sophisticated aircraft in its class.</description></item><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC).</description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule.</description></item><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile.</description></item><item><title>The flag-carrier airline of Dubai is the most popular brand among women in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. 2019 Women&amp;rsquo;s Choice Rankings, top 10 for the UAE.
For the third consecutive year, Emirates secured the top spot in the UAE YouGov BrandIndex Women&amp;rsquo;s Rankings. The airline achieved the highest positive &amp;ldquo;Impression&amp;rdquo; score, reaching +70.0 among women in the UAE. WhatsApp maintained its second-place position, while Carrefour climbed to third place, surpassing Apple, which descended to fourth.
These rankings were determined using data from YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex, a daily brand tracker.</description></item><item><title>Abu Dhabi International Airport has increased its summer flights by 18% compared to 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi International Airport&amp;rsquo;s summer 2014 flight schedule is its busiest ever, featuring six new destinations and 71 additional weekly flights to India.
Airport authorities reported an 18% increase in weekly flights compared to the previous summer, rising from 1,052 to 1,242, catering to both business and leisure travelers.
New nonstop routes debuting this summer include flights from Abu Dhabi to Los Angeles, Zurich, Belgrade (Serbia), Perth, Jaipur, and Yerevan (Armenia).</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha provides Iftar and suhoor meals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</guid><description>Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha is offering special meals for iftar and suhoor throughout Ramadan.
Source: Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha website. The Gem Garden.
George Sarkis, Director of Food and Beverage at the hotel, highlights the extensive iftar buffet, which combines Oriental and Continental cuisines with traditional Ramadan drinks.
Both iftar and suhoor are served at The Gem Garden, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s all-day dining venue. The iftar buffet, available from sunset to 10 pm, costs AED120* per person and includes live cooking stations.</description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi First Class Lounge &amp; Spa has been opened by Etihad Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has opened a new flagship First Class Lounge &amp;amp; Spa in Terminal 3 of Abu Dhabi International Airport. This space highlights the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to offering exceptional and desirable hospitality.
Inspired by top-tier hotels, private clubs, and fine dining establishments, the lounge provides an exclusive environment. It features unmatched design, style, comfort, world-class dining, and personalized beauty and relaxation services.
The lounge offers 16 distinct zones for guests to unwind, recharge, and enjoy entertainment in complete luxury before their flights.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th).</description></item><item><title>Groundbreaking ceremony finished for the Fujairah Business Centre, a mixed-use development</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/groundbreaking-ceremony-finished-for-the-fujairah-business-centre-a-mixed-use-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 04:54:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/groundbreaking-ceremony-finished-for-the-fujairah-business-centre-a-mixed-use-development/</guid><description>Al Taif Investment, a collaboration between Dubai Investments and Fujairah Investment Establishment (FIE), the investment branch of the Fujairah Government, has launched its flagship Fujairah Business Centre project.
Scheduled for completion in three years with a budget of AED400 million, the project aims to be a landmark development. Located opposite the Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, it features two towers with a total built-up area of 80,058 sq m. These towers include a 19-story office building and a 19-story Courtyard by Marriott hotel offering 228 rooms and apartment units.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now offers Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner on flights from Abu Dhabi to Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has upgraded its Abu Dhabi to Shanghai route, now offering flights on the Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner. This change increases capacity by 14%, offering 28 business class and 271 economy seats.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Peter Baumgartner, highlighted the significance of the Chinese market, particularly the rising demand from business and leisure travelers. The decision to utilize the Dreamliner reflects Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s status as a major global hub and its importance in Etihad&amp;rsquo;s network.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Volvo is offering special deals on their cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. The Volvo XC60.
Trading Enterprises – Volvo, the sole distributor of Volvo cars in the UAE and a member of the Al-Futtaim Group, has revealed its Ramadan promotional offers for several popular models.
The Volvo XC90 and XC60, both luxury SUVs, come with a 20% dealer contribution towards the down payment through the Volvo Selection program. This offer also includes a two-year buyback guarantee and monthly payments starting at AED 2,999 for the XC90 and AED 1,999 for the XC60.</description></item><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No.</description></item><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home.</description></item><item><title>Take a virtual tour of Emaar hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Using panoramic photography and videography, each virtual tour showcases the hotel&amp;rsquo;s features in detail.
Emaar Hospitality Group, the hospitality and leisure branch of Emaar Properties, has launched 360-degree virtual tours of its hotels in Dubai, UAE. These tours, created with high-definition photos and videos, allow potential guests to experience each hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique offerings, explore its various aspects, and make well-informed booking decisions.
The virtual tours encompass properties under the luxury Address Hotels + Resorts brand, the upscale lifestyle Vida Hotels and Resorts brand, and the new contemporary mid-scale Rove Hotels brand.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways introduces more flights on the Abu Dhabi to Doha route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is commemorating a decade of service to Qatar this year by adding nine weekly flights to its Abu Dhabi-Doha route, strengthening its dedication to this important Gulf market.
Starting August 1, 2016, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s national airline will boost its weekly service to Qatar&amp;rsquo;s capital to 37 flights. These new daily morning and early evening departures on Thursdays and Saturdays offer more flexibility and convenience, catering to business travelers in both Abu Dhabi and Doha.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA announces transport service timings for Eid al Fitr holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) has released the operating schedules for its services during the Eid al-Fitr holidays. The schedule covers various services, including customer service centers, parking, public buses, Dubai Metro and Tram, marine transit, driving institutes, and vehicle testing and registration centers.
Source: RTA. Al Marri.
Moaza Al Marri, RTA&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communication, stated that Customer Service Centers will be closed for the Eid al-Fitr holiday from Sunday, July 3rd, 2016, and will reopen on Sunday, July 10th, 2016.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has welcomed three new celebrity chefs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. From left: Costa, Joinie-Maurin, Kurdahl, Semblat and Silva.
The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has added three new chefs to its roster of acclaimed restaurants, aiming to elevate the dining experience for their guests.
Jose Silva, CEO of Jumeirah Group, stated that the addition of these culinary experts to their flagship Dubai hotel signifies the beginning of a more diverse and innovative culinary program. He emphasized their dedication to guest experiences as a crucial aspect of luxury hospitality.</description></item><item><title>The UAE Central Bank has introduced raised marks on certain currency notes to assist individuals with visual impairments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</guid><description>The Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates has introduced new AED1,000, AED20, and AED10 banknotes featuring raised tactile marks designed to assist people with visual impairments, according to the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
These new banknotes incorporate tactile elements created using the intaglio printing method on their widths. The AED1,000 note now includes two sets of four horizontal lines, evenly spaced, on both the left and right edges.
Similarly, the AED20 denomination features three distinct horizontal lines in the same position, while the AED10 denomination has two.</description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre now offers complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-national-exhibition-centre-now-offers-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Guests at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) can enjoy free Wi-Fi access through the &amp;lsquo;ADNEC Free Wi-Fi&amp;rsquo; network.
Humaid Matar Al Dhaheri, Acting Group CEO of Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company, stated that providing complimentary Wi-Fi highlights ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s focus on using technology to improve visitor experiences. This service eliminates the need for visitors to seek out basic internet access, aligning with ADNEC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing its technological infrastructure and enhancing service offerings to meet the changing needs of its stakeholders.</description></item><item><title>Air Arabia has opened a new sales office in Dubai and has also introduced city check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</guid><description>Air Arabia, a leading low-cost carrier in the Middle East and North Africa, has expanded its presence in Dubai, UAE, by opening a new sales office and city terminal check-in facility.
Adel Al Ali, Group CEO of Air Arabia, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to enhancing customer experience and convenience across its network. He emphasized the significance of the new sales office in strengthening their services in Dubai and the UAE.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Jumeirah City Break</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah website.
City Breaks at Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Jumeirah Creekside Hotel, and Jumeirah Living World Trade Centre Residences come with perks like free entry to Wild Wadi Waterpark and Zero Gravity Private Beach.
Jumeirah Emirates Towers boasts shopping at the Boulevard, various dining and nightlife options, and a convenient location just five minutes from Dubai Mall, accessible via the hotel&amp;rsquo;s complimentary shuttle service.
Reserve a room for three or more nights at participating Jumeirah hotels in Dubai with the Jumeirah City Break promotion and enjoy a 20% discount on the best available rates, along with:</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new flights to Istanbul's Sabiha Gokcen Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</guid><description>Emirates now offers 18 flights to Istanbul every week, including a new daily service to Sabiha Gökçen Airport in addition to its existing flights to Istanbul Atatürk Airport. This makes Istanbul the third city after London and Tokyo to be served by Emirates from two airports. The new daily flight is operated with an Airbus A330-200, offering 12 First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 183 Economy Class seats, and also provides up to 12 tonnes of cargo capacity each way.</description></item><item><title>The DIB Mobile app has been enhanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</guid><description>Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has launched an upgraded version of its mobile banking app for iOS and Android devices. This enhanced app offers access to over 60 services, including features designed to help users manage their personal finances effectively.
With smartphone usage on the rise and Nielsen reporting that 78% of the UAE population owns at least one such device, DIB&amp;rsquo;s mobile app caters to this growing trend.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank ranks the UAE in the top 10 for enhancing the business environment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-ranks-the-uae-in-the-top-10-for-enhancing-the-business-environment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:35:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-ranks-the-uae-in-the-top-10-for-enhancing-the-business-environment/</guid><description>A new World Bank Group study reveals that local businesses in the Middle East have faced difficulties over the past year. While some economies, such as the UAE—one of the top 10 global improvers—enhanced their business environments, the Middle East and North Africa region saw relatively slow regulatory reform.
According to Doing Business 2015: Going Beyond Efficiency, 55% of economies in the region implemented business regulatory reforms. This is comparable to 60% in East Asia and the Pacific but indicates that the reforms were limited in scope.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways is the designated airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</guid><description>The image showcases young people at work, sourced from the WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017 website.
Etihad Airways is the official airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017, a major international event focusing on vocational education and skills excellence. Taking place at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) from October 14th to 17th, 2017, the event will host over 3,000 participants and experts representing approximately 75 countries.
WorldSkills encompasses a variety of industries, from construction and creative fields like arts and fashion to technology, manufacturing, engineering, social services, and transport.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is providing selected transit passengers with a complimentary night's stay in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is offering a free overnight stay in Abu Dhabi to Economy Class travelers flying from specific locations, including Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Jordan, Kuwait, Bahrain, Oman, and Lebanon, whose journeys connect through the UAE&amp;rsquo;s capital.
This offer is valid for travel dates up to September 30, 2018, with bookings available from May 1 to September 15, 2018. Accommodation choices include the Radisson Blu on Yas Island and the Yas Island Rotana.</description></item><item><title>The Lexus LC performance coupe has been introduced in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lexus-lc-performance-coupe-has-been-introduced-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lexus-lc-performance-coupe-has-been-introduced-in-the-uae/</guid><description>The 2018 Lexus LC, a flagship performance coupe now available from Al-Futtaim Motors, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s exclusive Lexus distributor, seamlessly blends striking aesthetics, exhilarating performance, long-distance comfort, and superior craftsmanship.
This production coupe embodies the essence of the handcrafted Lexus LFA supercar and visually echoes the Lexus LF-LC concept. Christopher Buxton, Managing Director of Lexus at Al-Futtaim Motors, highlights the brand&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the UAE, particularly its leadership in luxury hybrid vehicles over the past seven years.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Golf introduces special promotions for Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Golf website.
During Ramadan, Dubai Golf has several special iftar and suhoor packages perfect for corporate events.
QD&amp;rsquo;s
QD&amp;rsquo;s has a special Ramadan tent where they serve both iftar and suhoor. The daily iftar buffet features a variety of traditional hot and cold Arabic mezze, soups, Middle Eastern and international main dishes, and desserts. This comes with your choice of juice and traditional Arabic sweets and dates.</description></item><item><title>Art covering Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 08:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-covering-dubai/</guid><description>Brand Dubai, the creative branch of the Government of Dubai Media Office (GDMO), and the Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) have joined forces to enhance the city&amp;rsquo;s aesthetics. This three-year partnership will involve a series of city beautification projects.
Their first initiative, the Dubai Metro Murals Project, will feature artwork on the pillars of the Dubai Metro line along Sheikh Zayed Road. Renowned artists Daniel Cortez from Peru and Evoca1 (Elio Mercado) from the Dominican Republic will create murals between the Dubai International Financial Centre and Emirates Towers stations.</description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi.</description></item><item><title>Numerous methods to ignite internal innovation at TRA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-methods-to-ignite-internal-innovation-at-tra/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 06:35:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-methods-to-ignite-internal-innovation-at-tra/</guid><description>Source: TRA.
The Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA) has implemented new programs to encourage internal innovation. Employees now have expanded opportunities to share their insights and actively participate in the TRA&amp;rsquo;s development.
The Idea for Tomorrow initiative, implemented at both TRA’s Abu Dhabi and Dubai locations, features idea boards on each floor. This allows employees a convenient method for sharing suggestions. TRA’s Innovation Committee will then select ideas with the most potential to improve TRA&amp;rsquo;s services, work environment, and the telecommunications sector as a whole.</description></item><item><title>In 2018, Dubai drew in more than 1,000 residents with a net worth of over a million dollars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</guid><description>Hamdan bin Mohammed: &amp;ldquo;The UAE&amp;rsquo;s forward-looking leadership has made it a top global destination for living and business.&amp;rdquo;
Over 1,000 millionaires relocated to Dubai in 2018.
Crown Prince of Dubai, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, credits the UAE&amp;rsquo;s robust investment and economic landscape to its leadership&amp;rsquo;s visionary approach. He highlights their commitment to the well-being of residents, visitors, and investors, along with fostering innovation, as key factors in establishing the UAE as a premier lifestyle and business hub.</description></item><item><title>Recharge your prepaid mobile accounts using du's mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</guid><description>For the first time in the UAE, du customers can now top up their prepaid mobile phones using mPay. This new service was unveiled today at GITEX Technology Week 2015.
Fahad Al Hassawi, Chief Commercial Officer at du, stated, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to be the first operator offering prepaid recharge via mPay, making it easier for our customers to top up their prepaid du lines conveniently. We believe this will be highly popular among our users.</description></item><item><title>Etihad updates baggage policy and fare structure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
The national airline of the United Arab Emirates, Etihad Airways, is rolling out a new, clearer fare system starting September 14, 2015. This system aims to offer travelers more choices when booking their flights.
Eight new &amp;ldquo;Fare Choices&amp;rdquo; will be introduced, allowing travelers to customize their bookings to fit their needs. These transparent Fare Choices come with different baggage allowances, levels of flexibility, and included benefits that previously needed to be purchased separately.</description></item><item><title>Kinoya in Dubai has been awarded the One to Watch Award for 2022 by MENA's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Kinoya restaurant has been awarded the One To Watch Award 2022 by Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. This recognition is given to up-and-coming restaurants in the region that have the potential to earn a spot on the 50 Best list in future years.
Kinoya&amp;rsquo;s founder, Neha Mishra, also known as the Ramen Queen, opened the restaurant after the success of her home-based supper club, A Story of Food.</description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www.</description></item><item><title>Emirates now offers a total of seven daily flights between Dubai and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Emirates will introduce a seventh daily flight between Dubai and Bangkok to accommodate rising passenger numbers. This will make Bangkok a top destination for Emirates, equal to Kuwait and Doha.
This new Boeing 777-300ER service will bring the total weekly flights to 49, increasing weekly seat capacity by 2,520 and cargo capacity by 134 tonnes each way. This addition complements the existing four daily A380 and two daily 777 flights, boosting travel and trade between Thailand and Emirates&amp;rsquo; global network.</description></item><item><title>Compass Offices has launched a new business center at Oberoi Centre in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</guid><description>Compass Offices, a leading provider of serviced offices in the Asia Pacific region, is expanding its presence to the United Arab Emirates with the inauguration of its first business center in Dubai in July 2014. This strategic move comes on the heels of the company&amp;rsquo;s recent expansion into Australia and Kazakhstan, as well as the establishment of new business centers in Hong Kong.
Alexander Passler, Vice President of Business Development at Compass Offices, highlighted Dubai&amp;rsquo;s growing appeal for businesses, stating, &amp;ldquo;Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation for economic stability and its thriving financial hub status are attracting a growing number of companies.</description></item><item><title>Dubai ranks in the middle of the global innovation push, according to the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 03:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has published the findings from the inaugural Dubai Innovation Index. Introduced last year, this index is part of the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s plan to encourage innovation and global best practices in the private sector. The index identified medical care, media, marketing, IT, and retail industrial sectors as the most innovative, while professional services, agriculture, fisheries, construction, and energy were identified as the least innovative in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>Complimentary stopovers offered to Etihad Economy Class passengers traveling from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is offering a complimentary one-night stay at the Radisson Blu hotel on Abu Dhabi’s Yas Island. This offer is open to Economy Class passengers flying from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan who have a layover in Abu Dhabi.
Mohammad Al Bulooki, Etihad Airways Executive VP Commercial, expressed the airline&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm for showcasing Abu Dhabi to its guests. He highlighted the diverse attractions of the UAE capital, ranging from cultural landmarks and beaches to sports and adventure activities.</description></item><item><title>The recipients of the MRM Business Award and MRM Business Innovation Award have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. HH Sheikh Ahmed Al Maktoum acknowledged the recipients of the 10th Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (MRM) Business Award and the 2nd MRM Business Innovation Award in Dubai, UAE.
Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, President of Dubai Civil Aviation Authority, as well as Chairman &amp;amp; Chief Executive of the Emirates Airline &amp;amp; Group, presided over the ceremony, which was held under the patronage of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Vice-President and Prime Minister of the UAE and Ruler of Dubai, and organized by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions.</description></item><item><title>The Wyndham brand has entered the UAE market with its presence in Dubai Marina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wyndham-brand-has-entered-the-uae-market-with-its-presence-in-dubai-marina/</guid><description>Source: The First Group. The new Wyndham
Dubai Marina.
Wyndham Dubai Marina, the first hotel solely developed by leading Dubai-based property developer, The First Group, has officially opened. This launch signifies the Wyndham brand&amp;rsquo;s entrance into the UAE market.
This four-star deluxe Wyndham Dubai Marina, managed by Wyndham Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, the largest hotel management company globally, represents a significant achievement for The First Group. The developer has established a strong reputation for creating high-quality serviced apartments and &amp;ldquo;aparthotels&amp;rdquo; in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Grand Millennium Dubai is providing daily iftar buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</guid><description>During Ramadan, the Grand Millennium Dubai, located near Sheikh Zayed Road, is hosting nightly iftar buffets at their Atrium restaurant. For AED 145 per person, guests can enjoy live cooking stations, along with Arabic and international dishes.
Source: Grand Millennium Dubai website. The Atrium restaurant.
The restaurant offers special group rates for iftar. The Silver package, priced at AED 165 per person, accommodates up to 50 guests. The Gold package, for a maximum of 100 people, costs AED 155 per person.</description></item><item><title>Australia, Singapore, and the UAE are among the top 10 destinations on people's relocation wishlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</guid><description>A recent report by Hydrogen Group, a global recruitment firm, reveals a growing trend of professionals seeking international work opportunities. The study found that the number of individuals open to working abroad doubled over a five-year period, rising from 16% in 2010 to 35% in 2014. Furthermore, 40% of respondents believe there are no obstacles to relocating for work.
While the US and UK were the most popular destinations, followed by Australia, Singapore ranked as the most preferred Asian country at seventh place.</description></item><item><title>DAMAC introduces Maison Cour Jardin in the heart of downtown Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</guid><description>At the end of December 2014, DAMAC Properties, a high-end real estate developer, launched its third luxury serviced apartment complex in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area. Located just a short distance from popular attractions like the Dubai Mall and Dubai Fountain, DAMAC Maison Cour Jardin joins the company&amp;rsquo;s growing portfolio, which includes DAMAC Maison Dubai Mall Street and DAMAC Maison Canal Views.
Source: DAMAC Properties.
“DAMAC Properties is expanding its hospitality offerings, both in terms of scale and quality, to cater to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s visitors,” stated Niall McLoughlin, Senior Vice President of DAMAC Properties.</description></item><item><title>Fireworks will be held at Al Majaz Waterfront to celebrate Eid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fireworks-will-be-held-at-al-majaz-waterfront-to-celebrate-eid/</guid><description>Al Majaz Waterfront, a popular destination located in Sharjah, UAE, will be hosting a fireworks show to celebrate the beginning of Eid al-Adha.
As reported by the Emirates News Agency (WAM), a three-minute fireworks display will take place at 9pm on the first and second days of Eid. The fireworks will be launched above the Sharjah Musical Fountain, and additional entertainment will be offered.
Source: Al Majaz Waterfront website. Fireworks on Marwa Obaid Al Shamsi, the Manager of Al Majaz Waterfront, emphasized that Eid al-Adha is a joyous celebration for families and especially children.</description></item><item><title>The First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport Terminal 1 has been reopened by Etihad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has officially reopened its First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport’s Terminal 1 after a complete renovation.
The improved lounge, open around the clock, spans over 1,044 square meters and can accommodate 134 guests. This updated space in Terminal 1 provides a variety of amenities to meet the needs of modern business and leisure travelers. Mirroring the lounge in Terminal 3, the refurbished facility features comfortable seating, a designated dining area, modern business facilities, complimentary Wi-Fi, USB charging ports, restrooms with shower facilities, and a children&amp;rsquo;s play area.</description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>du offers corporate mobile plans for SMEs in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Du offers five corporate mobile plans designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These plans include data and free calls to colleagues within the business.
Ranging from AED 50 to AED 450 per month, the plans provide data, national calling minutes, national text messages, and free calls to numbers within a designated &amp;lsquo;business calling circle&amp;rsquo;. Three of the plans also include free international minutes and texts. Businesses can purchase additional &amp;lsquo;packs&amp;rsquo; to add more minutes, texts, or members to their calling circle.</description></item><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories.</description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers.</description></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Information System for sharing insights on businesses in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced the Business Intelligence Information System (BIIS), a new digital platform designed to revolutionize how business information is accessed and utilized.
This initiative aligns with the UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, HH Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum&amp;rsquo;s vision of transforming Dubai into a smart city. BIIS provides a centralized hub for users to obtain crucial information about local and international businesses, empowering companies to identify potential partners and make well-informed decisions.</description></item><item><title>Special discounts are available for group bookings for iftar and suhoor at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp; Hotel in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Source: Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is offering special group rates for iftar and suhoor.
The iftar buffet, which includes Ramadan juices, is priced at AED 180*, with a discounted rate of AED 170 per person for groups of 10 or more. Using the coupon system**, the price drops to AED 150 per person. The suhoor buffet, also with Ramadan juices, costs AED 90 per person.</description></item><item><title>Makani numbers in Dubai assist taxi drivers in locating their customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/makani-numbers-in-dubai-assist-taxi-drivers-in-locating-their-customers/</guid><description>Source: RTA. Dubai taxis are now connected to the city through the Makani system.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) Public Transport Agency has successfully connected 4,500 taxis operated by franchise companies to the Dubai Municipality&amp;rsquo;s Makani System. This system utilizes unique coordinates, known as Makani numbers, for precise building location.
Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems at RTA&amp;rsquo;s Public Transport Agency, highlighted the significant role of the Makani System.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval.</description></item><item><title>Bee'ah and Chinook Sciences have announced the first waste-to-hydrogen project in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bee-ah-and-chinook-sciences-have-announced-the-first-waste-to-hydrogen-project-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 12:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bee-ah-and-chinook-sciences-have-announced-the-first-waste-to-hydrogen-project-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Dedicated to zero-waste cities and clean energy, Bee&amp;rsquo;ah, a leader in sustainability, revealed its plan for the UAE&amp;rsquo;s first waste-to-hydrogen project.
Source: PRNewsfoto/Chinook Sciences, Bee’ah. The decision to move forward with the waste-to-hydrogen project was reached during a signing ceremony attended by Chinook Sciences Chairman and CEO, Dr Rifat Chalabi (front left), HE Salim Al Owais (front right), Chairman of Bee&amp;rsquo;ah, and representatives from both organizations.
This project, a collaboration with UK-based industrial renewable fuel and environmental technology firm Chinook Sciences, encompasses a green hydrogen production facility and a hydrogen vehicle refueling station.</description></item><item><title>Atlantis Dubai offers a diverse selection of options for iftar dining</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</guid><description>This Ramadan, Atlantis is offering three unique dining experiences for iftar and suhoor: Asateer, Nobu, and Kaleidoscope, each providing a taste of Arabian culture.
Asateer, meaning &amp;ldquo;legends&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, provides a traditional tent setting overlooking the Arabian Sea, accommodating up to 900 guests. A customary iftar buffet is available at sunset for AED195, featuring Ramadan juices and followed by an à la carte suhoor menu starting at 9:30 pm.
During iftar, guests can enjoy classic dishes like foul moudammas and balila, complemented by a variety of Ramadan beverages such as jallab, laban, kamr al deen, and karkadeh.</description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally.</description></item><item><title>Cirque de Cuisine: The Festive Edition returns to Atlantis, The Palm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</guid><description>Source: Atlantis, The Palm. Cirque de Cuisine.
The Cirque de Cuisine event will launch Dubai&amp;rsquo;s holiday season with a Winter Wonderland theme. Held on December 6th at The Avenues in Atlantis, The Palm, this all-you-can-eat-and-drink event offers early bird tickets starting at AED495 for four hours of holiday festivities.
Cirque de Cuisine gives diners the opportunity to sample signature dishes, live cooking stations, buffets, drinks, and live entertainment at a variety of restaurants.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates</description></item><item><title>Bayara excels in creating engaging digital activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</guid><description>Bayara, a Middle Eastern brand famous for dried fruits, nuts, and spices, hosted a unique iftar (Ramadan fast-breaking meal) at The Oberoi in Dubai. The buffet featured recipes submitted by their social media followers.
Source: Bayara. Jean-Marc Lourau, CEO of Bayara, congratulated the winners whose dishes were featured at the buffet and also shared the progress that Bayara has made over the last 25 years that they have been in the market.</description></item><item><title>A white paper by the Dubai Chamber examines the funding landscape for startups in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-by-the-dubai-chamber-examines-the-funding-landscape-for-startups-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Cover for the white paper.
A recent report highlights the need for a simplified guide to help UAE startups navigate the funding landscape and connect with eager investors. The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, in partnership with Roland Berger, published this white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Helping Startups Access Funding,&amp;rdquo; during the March edition of Dubai Startup Hub&amp;rsquo;s Entrepreneurship Advocacy Series. Dubai Startup Hub, the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s entrepreneurial arm, offers guidance and clarity to new businesses through various programs and workshops.</description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal.</description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world.</description></item><item><title>Emirates NBD observes improvement in Dubai's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</guid><description>Source: Emirates NBD. Emirates NBD Dubai Economy Tracker Index: Sector
summary. Seasonally adjusted, 50 = no-change.
Data from April shows a continuing upswing in private sector output. Compared to March, all three major sub-sectors reported greater new business growth. Employment figures are increasing again, but at a slower rate than the survey average. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s private sector companies reported continued recovery and growth momentum since the survey&amp;rsquo;s record low in February.</description></item><item><title>Booking.com has recognized Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments as a top performer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 06:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</guid><description>Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments, managed by Flora Hospitality Dubai, has received recognition for its exceptional performance based on guest feedback on Booking.com.
Source: Booking.com website. Flora Creek Delluxe Hotel Apartments receives an 8.6 rating from guest reviews.
This award acknowledges the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to outstanding hospitality. The overall scores reflect a blend of factors such as cleanliness, comfort, location, amenities, staff service, value, and the quality of complimentary Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>The guidelines for using YouTube have been published by the UAE's Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</guid><description>The Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA) of the UAE has introduced guidelines for using YouTube as part of its UAE Social Media White Papers series.
The TRA highlights the immense popularity of YouTube, with over a billion unique monthly users and over 100 hours of video uploaded every minute. They emphasize that UAE law forbids publishing content that violates public morals, Islamic principles, and the social and moral well-being of the UAE.</description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established a new office in Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 10:37:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</guid><description>To capitalize on promising markets and solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s position as a global business hub, the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established its seventh international office in Shanghai, China.
His Excellency Hisham Al Shirawi, Second Vice-Chairman of Dubai Chamber, emphasized China&amp;rsquo;s significance as Dubai&amp;rsquo;s top trading partner and highlighted the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s decade-long dedication to fostering strong trade relations. The Shanghai office, Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s first in China, reflects this commitment and aligns with the Dubai Plan 2021&amp;rsquo;s goal of bolstering Dubai&amp;rsquo;s status as a leading business and investment destination.</description></item><item><title>The UAE GDP forecasts have been released by the Dubai Chamber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-gdp-forecasts-have-been-released-by-the-dubai-chamber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:57:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-gdp-forecasts-have-been-released-by-the-dubai-chamber/</guid><description>The United Arab Emirates&amp;rsquo; (UAE) real GDP is predicted to grow by an average of 3.8% between 2019 and 2023. This growth will be driven by increased investment and private consumption, according to an analysis by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.
The Dubai Chamber UAE Macroeconomic Model forecasts a resurgence in private spending and sales of consumer goods, particularly in categories like vehicles, furniture, appliances, and medical devices. This growth will be supported by robust investment bolstered by government fiscal measures.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA has entered into a partnership with Careem for ride-hailing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</guid><description>Source: RTA. HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of RTA and Mudassir Sheikha, Founder and Managing Director of Careem, signed the agreement on behalf of the two respective entities. RTA executives attending the signing included Mohammed Obaid Al Mulla, Member of Board of Executive Directors, Abdullah Yousef Al Ali, CEO of Public Transport Agency, and Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems. Bassel Al Nahlaoui, VP of Business Development &amp;amp; Government Relations attended on behalf of Careem.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists.</description></item><item><title>Fikra Labs aims to speed up innovation in the travel and tourism industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fikra-labs-aims-to-speed-up-innovation-in-the-travel-and-tourism-industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fikra-labs-aims-to-speed-up-innovation-in-the-travel-and-tourism-industry/</guid><description>In February, during UAE Innovation Month, which promotes the country&amp;rsquo;s global innovation hub status and recognizes innovators, four Abu Dhabi groups are collaborating with Wamda, an entrepreneurship platform, to launch the Fikra Labs acceleration program. The partners, including the Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi, Miral Asset Management, Etihad Aviation Group, and Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company (ADNEC), with support from Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), aim to boost innovation and entrepreneurship in Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s travel and tourism industry.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a concentrated ultra high net worth population in Abu Dhabi and Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-concentrated-ultra-high-net-worth-population-in-abu-dhabi-and-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-concentrated-ultra-high-net-worth-population-in-abu-dhabi-and-dubai/</guid><description>The UAE is home to 1,275 ultra wealthy individuals, comprising 20% of the ultra wealthy population in the Middle East, according to Wealth-X. These individuals hold a combined wealth of US$255 billion.
The study also found that 57% of the UAE&amp;rsquo;s ultra high net worth (UHNW*) population built their wealth through entrepreneurship. Inheritance was a less significant factor, with only 8% inheriting their entire fortune and 35% partially inheriting and subsequently growing their wealth.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's tourism numbers have increased thanks to MICE travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</guid><description>During the first six months of 2014, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s hotels received a record-breaking 5.8 million guests, as reported by Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
DTCM attributes this surge in tourism to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s prominent position as a regional center for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events (MICE). A prime example was the incentive trip in April that brought in over 14,500 delegates from China alone. Significant business events hosted in the first half of 2014 included Gulfood, the Arabian Travel Market, and Intersec, a major trade show for safety, security, and fire protection in the region.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is using Dreamliners on the route between the UAE and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched daily Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flights between the UAE and Singapore, setting a new standard for luxury travel on this route. Passengers can choose from First Suites, Business Studios, and Economy Smart Seats on the Abu Dhabi-Singapore route. The flight schedule is designed for smooth connections to 35 destinations within Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; network.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and Chief Executive Officer, stated that the Dreamliner&amp;rsquo;s deployment on the Singapore route demonstrates the route&amp;rsquo;s significance and the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a top-tier travel experience.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads.</description></item><item><title>AFOCH invites businesses to gather for iftar during Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: AFOCH website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is hosting Iftar celebrations ideal for gatherings with business associates.
Peter Freeman, the Deputy Director General of the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, highlighted that the hotel&amp;rsquo;s leading chefs will once again prepare a grand Iftar buffet. The buffet will feature exquisite Arabic delicacies alongside international dishes.
&amp;ldquo;Here at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, we provide the most authentic Arabic cuisine, meticulously crafted with the freshest ingredients by our highly skilled culinary team,&amp;rdquo; Freeman stated.</description></item><item><title>The Unified Electronic Contract will come into effect in January 2018 in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-unified-electronic-contract-will-come-into-effect-in-january-2018-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 17:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-unified-electronic-contract-will-come-into-effect-in-january-2018-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: DED. Al Zaabi.
Dubai Economy&amp;rsquo;s Commercial Compliance &amp;amp; Consumer Protection (CCCP) sector held a workshop for electronics businesses. The goal was to clarify the rules of the unified contract. Starting in 2018, this contract is required for selling or servicing electronic devices and components in the UAE.
This Unified Electronic Contract combines sales, warranty, maintenance, and spare parts agreements into a single document. It became mandatory in early January 2018 and must detail the product, serial number, and purchase date.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person.</description></item><item><title>The highlight of the Downtown Dubai New Year's Eve Gala is the Burj Khalifa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</guid><description>To celebrate the arrival of 2015, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Khalifa will showcase a dazzling LED display across its 828-meter height, synchronized with a spectacular fireworks show, according to a report from the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
Emaar Properties, the developer behind Downtown Dubai, is orchestrating a six-part extravaganza for their New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Gala. The event will feature a captivating blend of fireworks, laser displays, and a light show. A highlight of the celebration will be a special tribute to Dubai, its leaders, and the UAE&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments over the past 43 years, projected onto the specially designed LED screen.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Food Festival guarantees a February full of foodie fun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-food-festival-guarantees-a-february-full-of-foodie-fun/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-food-festival-guarantees-a-february-full-of-foodie-fun/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Food Festival website.
The second Dubai Food Festival (DFF) will showcase celebrity chefs and new events in addition to popular experiences from the previous year, according to the Dubai Festivals and Retails Establishment (DFRE), a branch of Dubai Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
New additions include Dubai Food &amp;amp; Film, the first foodie film event in the area, and Fatafeat Kitchen, a new program for 2015 and a first in the Middle East, featuring nine consecutive celebrity chef cooking events.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life.</description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new Home Check-in service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. The Home Check-in service utilizes a newly acquired fleet of vans and has been undergoing rigorous testing since October of the previous year.
Emirates has launched its &amp;ldquo;Home Check-in&amp;rdquo; service, allowing passengers departing from Dubai, UAE, to check in for their flights from any location. This service is offered to all Emirates passengers, regardless of their travel class, and demonstrates the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to delivering exceptional service and convenience.</description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base.</description></item><item><title>Etihad plans to increase the number of flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, will begin offering daily A380 flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne starting June 1, 2016. This will affect flight numbers EY460/461, one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily trips between the cities. This change replaces one of the three-class Boeing 777-300ER aircraft currently used. Passengers can now enjoy The Residence by Etihad, a luxurious private three-room suite, and other cutting-edge products and services across all cabins.</description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes.</description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich.</description></item><item><title>Group discounts are available for the iftar buffet at Coral Beach Resort Sharjah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 12:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</guid><description>Source: Coral Beach Resort Sharjah website.
The Coral Beach Resort Sharjah, having just finished a full update of its rooms and amenities, is offering an iftar buffet at its Al Bahar Restaurant. The buffet will feature a variety of traditional Arabic and international dishes, with options like mixed grills, shawarma, hot and cold mezze, stews and biryani, in addition to soups, salads, snacks, and customary Ramadan beverages.
Jean Pierre Simon, the Regional General Manager for Northern Emirates at Coral Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, highlighted Al Bahar restaurant as the perfect location for gatherings to break the fast, suggesting guests round off their dining experience with classic Ramadan sweets like the ever-popular umm Ali and mouhalabia.</description></item><item><title>Big discounts on Honda vehicles in the UAE during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Honda cars are on Ramadan offer in the UAE.
This Ramadan, Al-Futtaim Honda, the exclusive distributor of Honda vehicles, motorcycles, marine engines, and power products in the UAE, is offering reduced starting prices and complimentary service and warranty coverage across their car lineup. Ramadan is typically a popular time for purchasing new vehicles in the GCC region, and various brands offer promotions during this period.
Honda Civic</description></item><item><title>Emirates is set to introduce a third daily service to Brisbane</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates will begin offering a third daily flight to Brisbane, Australia starting December 1, 2017, adding to their current two daily flights.
This direct flight will utilize a Boeing 777-200LR, which boasts eight First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 216 Economy Class seats. This will increase the route&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3,724 seats weekly, both to and from Brisbane and Emirates&amp;rsquo; Dubai hub.</description></item><item><title>The Emirates Literature Foundation introduces a new digital discussion series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</guid><description>The Emirates Literature Foundation has launched a new project, Literary Conversations Across Borders. This digital initiative aims to promote global cultural understanding by connecting Emirati writers and thinkers with internationally recognized experts for live discussions on significant issues.
The series commences on May 30, 2020, with Indian politician and writer Shashi Tharoor and HE Zaki Nusseibeh, UAE Minister of State for the Office of Cultural Diplomacy. They will examine how the events of 2020 will shape the future, both positively and negatively.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian.</description></item><item><title>Submit your entries for the Zayed Sustainability Prize now!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 17:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</guid><description>The Zayed Sustainability Prize, a prominent global sustainability award based in the UAE, is calling for submissions for its 13th annual edition. Winners in each category will receive US$600,000 to further develop their sustainability solutions and create global impact.
Dr. Sultan Ahmed Al Jaber, UAE Minister of State and Director General of the Zayed Sustainability Prize, expressed confidence that the Prize will continue to draw in top innovators worldwide, tackling pressing global sustainability issues.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways has implemented improvements to its baggage policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Starting September 14, 2015, Etihad Airways will launch its new Fare Choices tariff program, which includes changes to its baggage policy. The airline claims these updates will benefit travelers, particularly those enrolled in the Etihad Guest loyalty program.
This new policy aims to provide more flexibility and align Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; baggage policies with partner airlines by catering to individual customer needs. Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, states: “This is about offering a fair and transparent baggage concept that is an industry best practice.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is increasing the number of weekly flights between Abu Dhabi and Manila</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2016, Etihad Airways will increase its Abu Dhabi to Manila route from 14 to 17 roundtrip flights per week. This provides convenient connections from Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s hub to popular destinations for Philippine travelers, including Bahrain, Kuwait, Dammam, Doha, Jeddah, and Riyadh.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, highlighted the Abu Dhabi-Manila route&amp;rsquo;s high demand and limited capacity in recent years. The added flights will increase capacity by nearly 2,500 seats weekly, improving travel options between the UAE and the Philippines.</description></item><item><title>Al-Futtaim Automall at Dubai Festival City is offering a selection of used cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-futtaim-automall-at-dubai-festival-city-is-offering-a-selection-of-used-cars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 15:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-futtaim-automall-at-dubai-festival-city-is-offering-a-selection-of-used-cars/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Used cars on offer at the Al-Futtaim Automall at Dubai Festival City.
A new destination for used car shoppers in the UAE is coming soon with the launch of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest site at Dubai Festival City (DFC).
Al-Futtaim Automall, the leading pre-owned vehicle retailer in the UAE, will inaugurate a spacious 12,000 sq m facility in June 2017. Situated opposite IKEA and adjacent to ACE, this new location will feature an inventory of over 400 vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Dubai welcomes the opening of a new Chinese Business Hub</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 23:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-welcomes-the-opening-of-a-new-chinese-business-hub/</guid><description>Source: CBH. Pictured at the Business Centre opening ceremony are (from left to right) Justin Wilshaw, SVP Commercial, Dubai South; Shoaib Alrahimi, VP, Business Park, Dubai South; Mohsen Ahmad, VP, Logistics District, Dubai South; alongside other senior officials and association representatives. The UAE&amp;rsquo;s first dedicated business center specifically designed for new and expanding Chinese startups and SMEs, known as the Chinese Business Hub (CBH), has officially opened its main office in Dubai South Business Park.</description></item><item><title>Dubai is optimistic about its FDI prospects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-is-optimistic-about-its-fdi-prospects/</guid><description>His Highness Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai and Chairman of The Executive Council, stated that the increase in foreign direct investment (FDI) inflows demonstrates growing investor confidence in Dubai, UAE.
His Highness reported that FDI into Dubai reached US$4.84 billion, a 26% increase compared to the first half of last year, during the first half of 2018. The number of FDI projects also rose significantly to 248, a 40% increase over the same period last year.</description></item><item><title>Emirates is adding another daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates has launched an additional daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka. Starting August 1, 2016, the airline will offer five daily flights between the two cities, except on Wednesdays, when four flights will be available. This new flight will provide an extra 2,520 seats and boost cargo capacity by 161 tonnes weekly in both directions, increasing the total weekly services on this route to 34.</description></item><item><title>Commemorative stamp marks 34 years of diplomatic relations between the UAE and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commemorative-stamp-marks-34-years-of-diplomatic-relations-between-the-uae-and-china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 21:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commemorative-stamp-marks-34-years-of-diplomatic-relations-between-the-uae-and-china/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Post Group. Commemorative stamps for 34 years of diplomatic relations between the UAE and China.
In honor of Chinese President Xi Jinping&amp;rsquo;s visit to the UAE, Emirates Post Group (EPG), working with the UAE Ministry of Foreign Affairs and International Cooperation, has introduced commemorative stamps. These stamps celebrate 34 years of diplomatic ties between the two nations.
The stamps showcase three distinct designs: one featuring a portrait of UAE President HH Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan, another with a portrait of the Chinese President, and the third displaying both countries&amp;rsquo; flags.</description></item><item><title>Five Asian hotels are ranked in the top 25 of Expedia Insiders' Select 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</guid><description>Expedia unveiled its 2014 Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select list in early July. This list highlights the best hotels globally, as determined by almost two million verified customer reviews and Expedia&amp;rsquo;s own travel experts.
Source: Blue Karma Resort website.
Out of over 290,000 bookable properties on Expedia&amp;rsquo;s global websites, 650 hotels received the Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select designation in 2014.
Here are a few of the top 25 hotels from this year&amp;rsquo;s list:
2. Blue Karma Resort - Seminyak, Bali</description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers.</description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE.</description></item><item><title>The Great Women Connect Series begins with Great Women Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-women-connect-series-begins-with-great-women-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Great Women Malaysia. Puan Nadira Yusoff.
The Great Women Connect Series debuted today in Malaysia. This new program seeks to provide a space for women in business worldwide to connect and exchange ideas and experiences related to trade. It also aims to foster international partnerships, helping women, especially those in Malaysia, build networks and realize their full potential.
Great Women Malaysia (GMW) is an initiative that strives to empower Malaysian women, particularly those in underserved and rural areas.</description></item><item><title>DAMAC Properties has revealed plans for three new serviced hotels in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 05:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-properties-has-revealed-plans-for-three-new-serviced-hotels-in-dubai/</guid><description>High-end real estate company DAMAC Properties is expanding its presence in the hospitality sector with the addition of three new serviced hotels in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area.
Two of these hotels, Cour Jardin and Capital Bay, are scheduled to open within the next few months, while Canal Views is already operational and receiving guests. This initiative is part of DAMAC Properties&amp;rsquo; goal to become the leading provider of serviced hotel apartments in the Middle East by 2018.</description></item><item><title>Cebu Pacific has been approved for more international routes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</guid><description>The Philippine Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB) has granted Cebu Pacific (CEB) additional flight entitlements for international routes. These include flights from Manila to the UAE and routes connecting various Philippine cities to Taipei and Kaohsiung in Taiwan.
CEB received approval to operate seven more weekly flights between Manila and the UAE. This allows the airline to offer service to any destination within the UAE, expanding upon its current daily flights between Manila and Dubai.</description></item><item><title>The winners of the SME Exporter of the Month award were honored by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently acknowledged member companies for their exceptional export achievements during the first nine months of 2016.
Nine trading companies received recognition at the &amp;ldquo;SME Exporter of the Month&amp;rdquo; ceremony: Universal International, Moon Flor General Trading, Signature Snacks, Al Khoud Trading, Raheeq Alasal Trading, Rais Hassan Saadi Logistics, Orient Links Co, Mohamed Abdulrahman Al Bahar, and Rayhan Al Sharq General Trading.
These companies were celebrated for excelling in categories such as highest export value, most export markets served, highest number of certificates of origin issued, and highest export value achieved by a start-up within a specific month.</description></item><item><title>ADIB introduces the Spice credit card specifically for Non-Resident Indians and Non-Resident Pakistanis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</guid><description>Source: ADIB. The new Spice Card offers a range of cashbacks if the owner hits a minimum spend.
Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) has introduced the Spice Card, a new product designed specifically for non-resident Indians (NRIs) and non-resident Pakistanis (NRPs) living in the UAE.
The ADIB Spice Card provides NRIs and NRPs with opportunities to save money through a variety of competitive offers and discounts. These include cashback rewards of 9% on dining, 7% on supermarket purchases, 4% on fuel, and 1% on utility bills.</description></item><item><title>The award ceremony for the Zayed Sustainability Prize 2019 took place</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 02:25:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</guid><description>Source: PRNewsfoto/Zayed Sustainability Prize. The 2019 Zayed Sustainability Prize ceremony took place during Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week (ADSW). His Highness Sheikh Mohamed presented awards to 10 winners across categories such as Health, Food, Energy, Water, and Global High Schools. The ceremony was attended by prominent figures including HH Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of Abu Dhabi Executive Council; HH Lt General Sheikh Saif bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of the Interior; HH Sheikh Mansour bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy PM and Minister of Presidential Affairs; HH Sheikh Hamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Chief of the Abu Dhabi Crown Prince&amp;rsquo;s Court; and HH Sheikh Omar bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of the Board of Trustees of Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan Charitable and Humanitarian Foundation; Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan, Minister of Tolerance; and other high-ranking ministers and officials.</description></item></channel></rss>