<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Network Technology on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:36:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>XO Offering Ethernet to the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</guid><description>Global telecommunications companies now have a unique opportunity: access to 4 million commercial buildings across the U.S. for offering Ethernet services. This is made possible by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; new Ethernet Hub service.
While this might seem irrelevant to businesses unless they&amp;rsquo;re looking to cut costs on voice and data services, the potential savings hidden within XO&amp;rsquo;s recent press release are significant.
XO Communications is a competitive carrier, meaning they weren&amp;rsquo;t part of the traditional Bell Telephone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telexplainer Expectations For 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</guid><description>As we begin a promising new year for business and technology, let&amp;rsquo;s explore some key trends for 2011 and how to leverage them.
Bandwidth demands will continue to escalate this year, as they do annually. The economic recovery will likely generate increased internet traffic as more individuals return to work. Expect bandwidth demand to surge proportionally with employment, if not more. During the recession, businesses learned to enhance individual productivity by investing in technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Communications Ups the Ante on Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</guid><description>A major telecommunications provider is expanding its Metro Ethernet services, offering businesses more options for high-bandwidth connectivity. This provider leverages its vast fiber optic network, numerous points of presence, and advanced Ethernet over Copper technology to make Ethernet an even more attractive option for Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.
Why is Ethernet so important? It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a natural progression for network technology that businesses of all sizes already rely on. This means Metro Ethernet provides a nearly effortless solution for connecting various locations, effectively unifying them under a single network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is DS-3 Bandwidth An Endangered Species?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</guid><description>For a long time, businesses needing a moderate amount of bandwidth have relied on DS-3 telecom services for dedicated internet access, file transfers, and video transport. While the price of DS-3 has been steadily decreasing due to increased competition, it might be approaching obsolescence. But why?
The shift began when data packets replaced digitized voice as the dominant traffic on global networks, and now video demands a significant portion of available bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Beefs Up Last Mile Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</guid><description>The main obstacle for companies aiming to boost their WAN (Wide Area Network) bandwidth is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; access problem. Although network bandwidth has become more affordable and easier to access, the final connection between a business and the carrier&amp;rsquo;s network often poses a significant challenge.
Think of it this way: a superhighway might be close to your company, but if the only route to your facility is a rough, narrow road, transportation will be slow and limited...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Content Delivery Networks Need More Capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</guid><description>A significant media shift is underway, marked by a technological revolution since the days of broadcast dominance. Concerns about antenna reception have been replaced by anxieties over 3G and 4G coverage for accessing videos on mobile devices. Cable and satellite TV, which succeeded over-the-air broadcasting, now face competition from the internet as the preferred medium for audio and video content. As over-the-air delivery declines, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) are emerging as its replacement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is VPLS Bringing to MPLS Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous branches have embraced MPLS networks for their affordability and high performance in connecting multiple locations. However, they may be overlooking a superior connectivity solution: Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS).
Essentially, VPLS is an Ethernet transport service operating over existing MPLS networks, enhancing rather than replacing them.
What sets VPLS apart is its ability to unify all your individual LANs into a single, company-wide network. This network transcends geographical limitations, enabling international connections for globally distributed businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>