<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Great Recession on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/great-recession/</link><description>Recent content in Great Recession on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:34:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/great-recession/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clod Computing Challenges The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing is gaining popularity as a cost-effective alternative to traditional data centers. However, a new competitor called &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; computing is emerging, boasting even lower costs.
](http://www.sysnito.com/?crid=11591&amp;linkID=145&amp;refid=Telexplainer-Clod)Clod computing minimizes infrastructure expenses by utilizing readily available, discarded computers. Chip-On-A-Shingle, a clod computing startup, defines a &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; as a network of interconnected old computers and devices that collectively provide impressive processing power.
This approach is viable due to the abundance of still functional computers being discarded simply because they are outdated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Jobs Come Calling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</guid><description>Although the Great Recession continues, the impact varies across industries. In fact, the technology sector is performing quite well in terms of employment. From November to December of last year, while 85,000 jobs were lost overall, the tech industry actually added 5,200 new positions. This suggests that technology might be a promising field.
However, having technological skills doesn&amp;rsquo;t guarantee employment. Many factory workers, for instance, would likely agree. The manufacturing sector was already moving overseas even before the recession...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-jobs-come-calling/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>