<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SN1303006 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sn1303006/</link><description>Recent content in SN1303006 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:47:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sn1303006/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Capacitor Replacement on Unit #2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</guid><description>The first Beomaster 1900 receiver is fully operational and undergoing testing in a listening room. However, the second unit still requires restoration.
Initial assessment of the second Beomaster 1900 has already been completed, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to begin replacing capacitors on the main circuit board.
The main circuit board houses most of the capacitors that need replacing. Unfortunately, it cannot be removed for servicing and must remain connected to the wire harness.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Wrap Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-wrap-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-wrap-up/</guid><description>The second Beomaster 1900 restoration project is finished.
After a night of playing music, the Beomaster 1900 was ready for the cabinet to be put back together.
The Bass, Treble, and Balance indicator masks were reattached to their slide controls.
The touch control panel was then placed onto the cabinet frame, carefully aligning the button actuators with the sensor posts.
All touch buttons were tested to ensure functionality before continuing the reassembly.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Capacitor Replacement and Slider Controls on Unit #2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-and-slider-controls-on-unit-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-and-slider-controls-on-unit-2/</guid><description>The second Beomaster 1900 unit is prepped for reassembly after completing the capacitor replacements and slider control repairs.
The Volume Control board was addressed first, requiring six capacitor replacements. Here&amp;rsquo;s the board before:
And after the replacements:
The Tone Control and FM Tuning board came next. While it only needed ten capacitors replaced, the Bass, Treble, and Balance sliders needed attention. This involved cleaning and repairing the Bass and Treble controls, which had broken slider bridges impacting the switch contacts.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Reassembly and Power Supply Checks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-reassembly-and-power-supply-checks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-reassembly-and-power-supply-checks/</guid><description>This Beomaster 1900 is almost ready for final testing after reassembly and initial power supply checks.
The power transistor heatsinks, crucial for cooling, have been reinstalled using Sil-Pad insulators for thermal protection. This process started with the power transistors in their original state before any capacitor replacements. After restoration and the addition of new thermal insulation, they were carefully mounted back onto the unit.
To prepare for the upcoming No-Load Current adjustments, test leads were soldered onto the board.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Initial Assessment of the Second One</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-initial-assessment-of-the-second-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 07:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-initial-assessment-of-the-second-one/</guid><description>This is the second Beomaster 1900 receiver that needs restoration.
Similar to the first receiver, I started by inspecting the indicator lamps when powered on.
[Images of indicator lamps]
All the indicator lamps on this Beomaster are working.
Cosmetically, it&amp;rsquo;s missing the cabinet feet, a common issue with these models.
[Image of missing cabinet feet]
The control panel lid&amp;rsquo;s rubber bumpers have degraded.
[Image of deteriorated lid bumpers]
The cabinet trim veneer isn&amp;rsquo;t peeling, but the finish is quite dull.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Performance Testing and a Volume Control LDR Problem</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-performance-testing-and-a-volume-control-ldr-problem/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 21:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-performance-testing-and-a-volume-control-ldr-problem/</guid><description>Today, I completed some service manual adjustments on the Beomaster 1900 and started evaluating its performance by measuring THD and Frequency Response.
The first adjustments involved setting the tuning voltage for FM 1 and FM 5 according to the Beomaster 1900 service manual. The procedure involves setting the FM 1 tuning potentiometer (4R3) to the 88MHz dial position and adjusting trimmer 4R2 to achieve a reading of 4.5 VDC at test point 4TP1 with FM 1 selected as the audio source.</description></item></channel></rss>