<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT Management on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-management/</link><description>Recent content in IT Management on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in.</description></item><item><title>How To Deal With Sudden Massive Bandwidth Demands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</guid><description>For years, you experience consistent, though gradually increasing, network bandwidth needs. Then, unexpectedly, you&amp;rsquo;re hit with a demand to increase your WAN bandwidth by 10x or even 100x. How does this happen, and how can you handle such unpredictable situations?
It&amp;rsquo;s unlikely everyone in the company suddenly started downloading HD movies, right? While that would certainly max out your bandwidth, it&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic scenario. Bandwidth demands don&amp;rsquo;t surge without reason.</description></item></channel></rss>