<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIP Trunks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-trunks/</link><description>Recent content in SIP Trunks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-trunks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Telephone Systems Hosted VoIP Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes have various choices for their telephone systems. Small businesses can buy systems from local stores, while medium-sized businesses often work with contractors for key telephone systems or small PBXs. Larger companies may have internal teams that handle complex telephone systems. Nowadays, hosted VoIP is a cost-effective option for companies of all sizes.
How can one solution meet the needs of different-sized businesses affordably? It&amp;rsquo;s not a one-size-fits-all solution but a scalable technology adaptable to different demands—hosted VoIP, also known as hosted PBX or cloud telephone systems.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider.</description></item><item><title>High Reliability VoIP Phone Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-reliability-voip-phone-service-providers/</guid><description>The days of traditional phone lines, even ISDN PRI, are fading. Cloud-based systems and computer networks offer more adaptable, feature-rich, and cost-effective voice communication solutions. To tap into these advantages, adopting packet-based phone service, also known as VoIP, is key.
People&amp;rsquo;s feelings about VoIP as a replacement for traditional phone service are mixed, ranging from enthusiastic support to staunch opposition. This spectrum of opinions stems from individual experiences with the technology and when they first used it.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs ISDN PRI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses have moved past analog phone lines, embracing PBX systems and ISDN PRI for their communication needs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: SIP Trunking. This technology offers potential cost and performance benefits for companies looking to enhance their voice services. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SIP Trunks with ISDN PRI to understand the best choice for your organization.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that both technologies rely on digital telephony, eliminating analog transmission.</description></item><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price.</description></item><item><title>Dynamically Allocate T1 Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dynamically-allocate-t1-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a reliable choice for transmitting voice and data for many years. Traditionally, it was believed that the purpose of the line (voice or data) needed to be determined before installation. For voice communication, a channelized T1 line or ISDN PRI configuration was used, with each of the 23 or 24 channels dedicated to a single phone call. Conversely, a clear channel T1 line was used for point-to-point data transmission or dedicated internet access, allowing for the full 1.</description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand.</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>Should You Buy VoIP as a Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</guid><description>Cloud-based services, including Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), have been around for a while. What&amp;rsquo;s becoming more popular now is the trend of large businesses connecting their different locations using SIP Trunks and all sizes of businesses choosing to outsource their PBX functionality. This can be considered VoIP as a Service.
Many home and small business users adopted cloud-based VoIP early on to cut costs. They did this by replacing their traditional phone lines and using their broadband internet connection for both high-speed internet and phone service.</description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>What is Cloud Computing For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is gaining popularity, but what does it mean for businesses beyond giants like Amazon and Google? Essentially, the cloud isn&amp;rsquo;t a new invention. It&amp;rsquo;s a way of structuring technology, similar to the public telephone system, where a central provider manages the complex infrastructure (&amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo;), and users access services through simple devices (&amp;ldquo;thin clients&amp;rdquo;).
This centralized system, known as multi-tenancy, allows numerous users to access resources seemingly simultaneously while remaining isolated.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Networking Services Extend Business Footprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 20:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</guid><description>For businesses with a single office in one city, cloud computing or hosted PBX might suffice, as their communication needs are primarily about connecting to a provider&amp;rsquo;s cloud. However, companies with multiple locations require cloud networking services to link these sites seamlessly.
Cloud networking utilizes public or private networks to connect geographically dispersed locations in various configurations. Examples include the internet, privately managed MPLS networks, and even custom-built networks using leased lines.</description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Can Improve Telephone Reliability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</guid><description>Many businesses, even large ones, hold onto their own phone systems believing it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to guarantee reliable communication. But is this true, or is it time to reconsider this assumption?
The phone service industry has experienced a significant shift with the emergence of hosted PBX (HPBX), also called hosted VoIP or cloud communications. Like other cloud-based technologies, this is a game-changer. In the future, we&amp;rsquo;ll wonder why we didn&amp;rsquo;t switch sooner.</description></item></channel></rss>