<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Benefit Tourism on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/benefit-tourism/</link><description>Recent content in Benefit Tourism on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 12:18:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/benefit-tourism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The historical context of the Dano judgment: Free movement and social benefits for economically inactive EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 12:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-historical-context-of-the-dano-judgment-free-movement-and-social-benefits-for-economically-inactive-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Géraldine Renaudière, Trainee at the CJEU, within the cabinet of the Court Vice-President, Koen Lenaerts. (This post reflects the author&amp;rsquo;s view only).
The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s recent ruling in Elisabeta Dano and Florin Dano v Jobcenter Leipzig revisits the sensitive issue of national laws that prevent economically inactive EU citizens from receiving special non-contributory benefits, even though those benefits are available to nationals in similar situations. Issued a year after the controversial Brey decision, this judgment aims to clarify the connection between Directive 2004/38, which concerns the free movement of EU citizens, and Regulation 883/2004, which deals with coordinating social security systems.</description></item><item><title>Following the Dano ruling, under what circumstances can unemployed EU citizens be deported?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Dano case focused on benefit applications, not deportation. Therefore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly affect deportation. However, due to the Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the EU citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive, it might indirectly impact deportation.
Earlier this year, I published a blog post about when unemployment could justify deporting or banning EU citizens. This post expands on that analysis, considering the Dano judgment.</description></item><item><title>Is CJEU case law on EU citizenship normatively consistent? Unlikely! - An answer to Davies' 'Has the Court evolved, or have the cases?'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 02:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cjeu-case-law-on-eu-citizenship-normatively-consistent-unlikely-an-answer-to-davies-has-the-court-evolved-or-have-the-cases/</guid><description>Alexander Hoogenboom, PhD, MSc. LL.M. Senior Policy Officer at the Dutch Healthcare Authority and associate researcher at the Institute for Transnational and Euregional cross border cooperation and Mobility, Faculty of law, Maastricht University. The opinions presented in this paper are solely those of the author.
Introduction
Some have interpreted recent Court of Justice rulings on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits as a restrictive shift compared to earlier decisions, possibly influenced by rising populism.</description></item><item><title>Disregard the children! CJEU supports automatic exclusions from family benefits in Case C-308/14 Commission v UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</guid><description>Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School The Court of Justice is increasingly distancing itself from the social welfare systems of Member States. Although the Court once suggested that citizenship is paramount and forms the basis for financial solidarity, guaranteeing some support from a host state for EU citizens facing temporary hardship, this stance is changing.
With the Court moving away from the concept of citizenship, the idea of a reasonable burden may be disappearing.</description></item></channel></rss>