<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecommunications Marketing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecommunications-marketing/</link><description>Recent content in Telecommunications Marketing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:45:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecommunications-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telarus, the New Face of Telecom Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a massive transformation thanks to disruptive technology. Wireless technology is shaking up the century-old wireline business, VoIP is changing the landscape of the digital voice trunking business, competitive fiber optic carriers are challenging the dominance of established phone companies, and Ethernet and IP networks are blurring the lines between local and wide area networks.
Despite these technological advancements, the sales and marketing processes for business telecommunications services have remained largely unchanged.</description></item><item><title>Audio Interview With Adam Edwards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</guid><description>Telarus, Inc. is considered a leading innovator in telecommunications marketing since the major telecom expansion of the 1990s. The company has transformed how businesses purchase services like T1, Ethernet, and other high-speed internet options.
I recently spoke with Adam Edwards, Telarus&amp;rsquo;s president, to understand the company&amp;rsquo;s success as a top master agency. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share an MP3 recording of our conversation so you can hear directly from Adam instead of reading a transcript.</description></item></channel></rss>