<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Motorola on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/motorola/</link><description>Recent content in Motorola on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/motorola/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>DROID vs DROID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:58:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</guid><description>The DROID phone, running Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system, actually has two versions produced by different companies with distinct specifications. So, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between the two.
The first DROID, manufactured by Motorola for Verizon Wireless, is a touchscreen QWERTY smartphone utilizing the Android 2.0 operating system. This innovative device was recognized as Time.com&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Top Gadget of 2009&amp;rdquo;.
This top-tier DROID boasts a 5.0-megapixel camera, doubling as a camcorder, with features like geo-tagging, auto-stabilization, flash, and built-in editing tools.</description></item><item><title>DROID 2 Global is a World Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 03:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</guid><description>The DROID 2 Global is a smartphone with a 1.2 GHz processor capable of making and receiving calls in over 200 countries. This Verizon phone works internationally through its unique ability to utilize both GSM and CDMA networks.
While Verizon primarily uses CDMA, incompatible with most global networks, the DROID 2 Global incorporates multiple network support. This includes WCDMA, GSM, HSDPA, CDMA EV-DO, EDGE, GPRS, and HSUPA, encompassing various forms of communication.</description></item><item><title>Cheap Used Cell Phones For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 12:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheap-used-cell-phones-for-sale/</guid><description>Need a new cell phone but dread dealing with carriers and contracts? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Carrier stores are notorious for expensive phones and restrictive contracts. They might offer a &amp;ldquo;cheap&amp;rdquo; phone, but it comes with strings attached – usually a pricey new contract and limited model options.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been with your carrier long enough for an upgrade or prefer not to sign a new contract, carriers will charge full retail price for a new phone.</description></item></channel></rss>