<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>67SSBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/67ssbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 67SSBG4000 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/67ssbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning of the Tone Arm Carriage Position Switches and a Non-Returning Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</guid><description>As a preliminary step in the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I chose to verify the functionality of its control system. Prior testing had shown that the arm carriage would not return to its home position when moved across the platter without a record in place. Instead, it would travel to the center of the platter and stop. Ideally, the carriage should trigger the End Switch (ES) at this point and subsequently return to its home position on the right, turning off the turntable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-of-the-tone-arm-carriage-position-switches-and-a-non-returning-carriage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and one of the challenges is finding modern replacements for the large capacitors used in the 1970s. I received a 3D-printed adapter that allows me to neatly install smaller, current-generation capacitors.
These photos show the adapter with the new capacitors in place:
For reliability, I used two 300uF capacitors wired together to replace the original 150uF motor capacitor. The remaining capacitors are high-quality Rubycon, Panasonic, and Multicomp components chosen for their longevity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adding a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adding-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adding-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a significant hum became apparent when connected to a Beomaster 6000 amplifier. This was unexpected, as a Beogram 4002 with the same grounding design showed no such issue. The only identifiable difference between the two models was the unshielded mains transformer in the 4000, unlike the shielded transformers in later models. While the relevance of this difference was unclear, it appeared to be the only variable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adding-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adding-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the AC Motor Voltage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 turntable restoration, I observed a noisy motor, especially at 45 RPM. Replacing the electrolytic capacitors helped but didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem completely. To investigate further, I examined the motor voltage and the signal waveform from the Wien bridge oscillator, a clever design that uses an incandescent light bulb as a variable resistor for amplitude control. I measured the AC waveform amplitude at one of the motor leads relative to ground...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustment of the Tonearm Height and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and with the major tasks complete, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the finer points. One detail that caught my eye was the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s resting position, which was noticeably higher than the sensor arm when lifted.
[Image]
Although this doesn&amp;rsquo;t impact sound quality, it was aesthetically displeasing. After consulting the manual, which recommended aligning the tonearm height with the sensor arm, I made the adjustment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:11:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>As a final step in restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, the author polished its dust cover. This is a multi-step process that can take several hours, especially since this cover had significant damage.
The author began by protecting the Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen logo with layers of insulation tape to prevent accidental sanding. They then used 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the deep scratches, leaving a surface that resembled wood.
To restore the shine, they progressed through approximately ten grades of sandpaper and micro-mesh polishing cloths, finishing with a polishing liquid...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Slow Slide Transport Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem was encountered where the tonearm carriage would continue moving after attempting to move it in reverse. This issue stemmed from a damaged keypad switch, specifically a bent contact terminal that prevented a clean shut-off connection. This damage was likely caused by a previous repair attempt.
To address this, the control panel and circuit board were removed to access and extract the switch terminals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter and the Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/</guid><description>Having completed the restoration of the Beogram 4000, I noticed the platter wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly within its aluminum panel. It needed adjustments to align it properly. The service manual suggests adjusting the platter in relation to the chassis first, and then aligning the chassis within the enclosure. This ensures the platter sits flush and centered within the panel, achieving that desirable &amp;ldquo;Beoloving&amp;rdquo; aesthetic.
To illustrate the process, I created two videos...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Recapping the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 restoration, I replaced all electrolytic capacitors as a preventative measure, opting for durable 105C types from reputable Japanese brands. Tantalum capacitors, particularly in older equipment, can fail dramatically, even catching fire.
On the power supply board, I discovered a missing screw and a loose one, potentially creating a dangerous short circuit scenario. Thankfully, no damage was evident. I replaced the tantalum capacitors and secured the board with a new stainless steel M3 screw...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Solenoid and the Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-solenoid-and-the-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:44:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-solenoid-and-the-switches/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration I&amp;rsquo;m working on requires some final adjustments. A key part of any complete restoration is calibrating the solenoid and its associated switches. This solenoid is critical as it manages the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s up/down movement and activates three important switches: audio muting, solenoid power control, and carriage transport. The audio muting switches are crucial for silencing the cartridge coils until the stylus makes contact with the record, preventing unwanted noise...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-solenoid-and-the-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-solenoid-and-the-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: First Contact</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-first-contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 20:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-first-contact/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a joyous occasion! A Beogram 4000 (5215) turntable has arrived for some care and restoration. Although these models are rare in the US, the opportunity to work on one is the next best thing to owning one, especially considering its fascinating diode-transistor-logic (DTL) control system crafted from early NAND/NOR gates and diode arrays.
Upon unboxing and setting it up for testing, it became apparent that while mechanically restored and mostly functional, the cabinet had been painted black - a tragedy for vintage audiophiles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-first-contact/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-first-contact/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulb of the Tracking Sensor with a Drop-In LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 11:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 400x turntable, it&amp;rsquo;s common to replace the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s incandescent bulb with a more durable LED assembly. A drop-in replacement for the Beogram 4002 and 4004 models has been created and documented, while the Beogram 4000 version incorporates a Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen-specified intensity trimmer for fine-tuning the tracking feedback system&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to recalibrate the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s position after any light source replacement to maintain accurate tracking sensitivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>