<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Entry on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entry/</link><description>Recent content in Entry on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor outlines four key pillars for a successful expansion into emerging markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-outlines-four-key-pillars-for-a-successful-expansion-into-emerging-markets/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, has published an e-book titled &amp;ldquo;Succeed in Emerging Markets: Selection, Strategy and First Steps&amp;rdquo;. This e-book presents a four-pillar model designed to guide businesses entering emerging markets.
The first pillar, &amp;ldquo;market,&amp;rdquo; examines macroeconomic stability, consumer market size, growth, and openness.
The second pillar, &amp;ldquo;population,&amp;rdquo; delves into demographics to help businesses assess how their products or services align with the competitive landscape.
The third pillar, &amp;ldquo;access,&amp;rdquo; evaluates the ease of market entry.</description></item><item><title>Compass Offices has launched a new business center at Oberoi Centre in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</guid><description>Compass Offices, a leading provider of serviced offices in the Asia Pacific region, is expanding its presence to the United Arab Emirates with the inauguration of its first business center in Dubai in July 2014. This strategic move comes on the heels of the company&amp;rsquo;s recent expansion into Australia and Kazakhstan, as well as the establishment of new business centers in Hong Kong.
Alexander Passler, Vice President of Business Development at Compass Offices, highlighted Dubai&amp;rsquo;s growing appeal for businesses, stating, &amp;ldquo;Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation for economic stability and its thriving financial hub status are attracting a growing number of companies.</description></item><item><title>71 SG introduces international market access programs for startups based in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/71-sg-introduces-international-market-access-programs-for-startups-based-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/71-sg-introduces-international-market-access-programs-for-startups-based-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore-based startup, 71 SG, has introduced programs designed to assist other local startups in expanding into the Chinese market. These programs are supported by International Enterprise (IE) Singapore. One such program, the Start-up Development &amp;amp; Learning Programme (SDL), aims to facilitate a smooth market entry for startups by connecting them with potential customers, partners, and investors.
The SDL offers Singaporean startups a five-day tech and business workshop that provides access to overseas markets, market intelligence, networking opportunities, and funding prospects.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the Desire 616 dual SIM smartphone for entry-level users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</guid><description>HTC, a company known for mobile innovation and design, has introduced the HTC Desire 616 dual sim phone. This new phone offers high-end features at an affordable price. Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;The HTC Desire 616 dual sim is a powerful phone with a great price tag,&amp;rdquo; says Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;This new phone in the popular HTC Desire line offers an eight-core processor, fast processing speeds, and top-tier features at an accessible price, giving users a best-in-class experience.</description></item></channel></rss>