<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beogram 4004 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beogram-4004/</link><description>Recent content in Beogram 4004 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beogram-4004/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Prematurely Activating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is progressing well. Rebuilding the deck led to a successful initial power-up where the carriage moved to the correct position, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower. A visual inspection showed a disconnected thin grey wire from the SK3054 NPN power transistor (0TR4).
Tracing the wiring and consulting the schematic revealed that the grey wire connected to the transistor&amp;rsquo;s emitter, responsible for bypassing a current-limiting resistor (7R1) during the arm&amp;rsquo;s initial descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 (type 5215): replacing sensor arm photo cell with modern one</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</guid><description>I recently had two Beogram turntables (a BG4000 and a BG4002) in my workshop with malfunctioning photocells in the detector arm. Usually, these photocells have a long lifespan, but the light bulbs can experience broken wires. While a pre-existing LED replacement for these bulbs exists (see sensor arm light bulb replacement), in this instance, the photocells themselves had broken wires and even a fractured cell, rendering repair impossible. Finding replacements proved futile as well.</description></item><item><title>Another Surprise Addition To The Workshop Beogram 4004</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/another-surprise-addition-to-the-workshop-beogram-4004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/another-surprise-addition-to-the-workshop-beogram-4004/</guid><description>In 2021, I refurbished my Beogram 4004 turntable, which I call the &amp;ldquo;Workshop Beogram 4004&amp;rdquo;. Later that year, I added the Beolover Remote Commander and have enjoyed using it to play records.
This year, I made another enhancement to my Beogram 4004: a Beolover SyncDrive Platter Motor. I was eager to try it out after reading about it on the Beolover Blog.
My Beogram 4004 was already restored and in regular use, with a perfectly functional DC platter motor restored by Beolover in 2021.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently arrived from a UK seller for restoration. This report outlines its pre-restoration condition.
Upon arrival, the unit was quite dirty but in good overall shape. The dust cover showed typical scratches from storage, many deep enough to feel with a fingernail. However, it can be polished back to good condition. Positively, the dust cover features an aluminum strip instead of the less durable plastic type, and the hinges appear to be intact.</description></item></channel></rss>