<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carbon on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carbon/</link><description>Recent content in Carbon on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carbon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discover the most environmentally friendly hotels worldwide with GreenHotelWorld</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</guid><description>Source: GreenHotelWorld website.
GreenHotelWorld, in collaboration with TripAdvisor, now boasts the largest selection of verified eco-friendly hotels on a single platform. This was achieved by incorporating hotels from TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s GreenLeaders Program.
With a global reach, GreenHotelWorld curates over 8,000 hotels recognized for their demonstrably sustainable practices. Their categorization process utilizes standards from the Global Sustainable Tourism Council (GSTC), a respected international body that sets benchmarks for sustainable tourism and accredits green hotel certifications.</description></item><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin.</description></item><item><title>Eight multilateral development banks (MDBs) working together to speed up efforts to reduce transportation emissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eight-multilateral-development-banks-mdbs-working-together-to-speed-up-efforts-to-reduce-transportation-emissions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eight-multilateral-development-banks-mdbs-working-together-to-speed-up-efforts-to-reduce-transportation-emissions/</guid><description>Eight major development banks have come together to address the significant impact of transportation on climate change. These institutions acknowledge that the transportation sector, responsible for a considerable portion of global energy consumption and emissions, needs more action to minimize its environmental footprint and enhance its resilience to climate change.
The African Development Bank, Asian Development Bank (ADB), CAF-Development Bank of Latin America, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, European Investment Bank, Inter-American Development Bank, Islamic Development Bank (ISDB), and the World Bank (WB) have pledged to expedite their efforts in several key areas.</description></item></channel></rss>