<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lounge on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lounge/</link><description>Recent content in Lounge on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:52:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lounge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport Terminal 1 has been reopened by Etihad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has officially reopened its First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport’s Terminal 1 after a complete renovation.
The improved lounge, open around the clock, spans over 1,044 square meters and can accommodate 134 guests. This updated space in Terminal 1 provides a variety of amenities to meet the needs of modern business and leisure travelers. Mirroring the lounge in Terminal 3, the refurbished facility features comfortable seating, a designated dining area, modern business facilities, complimentary Wi-Fi, USB charging ports, restrooms with shower facilities, and a children&amp;rsquo;s play area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>