<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shangri-La on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shangri-la/</link><description>Recent content in Shangri-La on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 07:26:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shangri-la/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Traders Hotel in Yangon has been rebranded as the Sule Shangri-La, Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-traders-hotel-in-yangon-has-been-rebranded-as-the-sule-shangri-la-yangon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 07:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-traders-hotel-in-yangon-has-been-rebranded-as-the-sule-shangri-la-yangon/</guid><description>After a comprehensive two-and-a-half-year renovation, Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts has rebranded the Traders Hotel, Yangon in Myanmar to the Sule Shangri-La, Yangon.
Situated on Sule Pagoda Road near its 2,000-year-old namesake, the 484-room hotel has been a prominent landmark in the city&amp;rsquo;s central business district since 1996, remaining a popular hub for business gatherings.
Source: Shangri-la. Service staff in the Peacock Lounge.
While the building&amp;rsquo;s exterior is modern, the lobby of the Sule Shangri-La, Yangon evokes a sense of a bygone colonial era with its white columns and grand staircase leading to an open balcony.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person.</description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers.</description></item></channel></rss>