<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Audio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/audio/</link><description>Recent content in Audio on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/audio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bose's Bluetooth speakers and headphones simplify the process of making connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</guid><description>Bose has expanded its SoundLink mobile audio lineup with two new products: the SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker, their most budget-friendly SoundLink speaker yet, and the SoundLink Bluetooth on-ear headphones, Bose&amp;rsquo;s first foray into on-ear Bluetooth headphones.
The SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker features a brand new design. Weighing in at 1.25 pounds (567g), it measures 5 inches wide, 2.1 inches deep, and 5.3 inches high. Bose has engineered the speaker with dual-opposing passive radiators and two high-efficiency transducers to deliver powerful, full-range sound, including impressive bass performance.</description></item><item><title>The Altec Lansing Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds come with noise isolation and GPS tracking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>Source: Altec Lansing. The Freedom True Wireless
Bluetooth Earbuds have rechargeable lithium
ion batteries.
Altec Lansing&amp;rsquo;s new Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds offer a truly wireless experience, featuring rechargeable lithium-ion batteries integrated into the earbud housings.
These innovative earbuds boast a six-hour battery life, IPX7-rated waterproof construction for sweat resistance, and Bluetooth-based GPS tracking to easily locate misplaced earbuds.
Expected to launch in the second quarter of 2016 with a manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s suggested retail price of US$149.</description></item><item><title>ACCA will be hosting a virtual conference called Accounting for the Future from September 15 to 18</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</guid><description>Source: ACCA website.
The sixth annual Accounting for the Future virtual conference, hosted by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), will focus on important topics impacting the future of accounting. These topics include corporate culture, sustainability, and global business service models.
The conference, taking place from September 15th to 18th, 2014, will feature four days of live and on-demand video and audio webcasts covering various subjects related to the accounting profession.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces music services that do not use data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</guid><description>Singtel debuted its Singtel Music service, a first-of-its-kind offering in Singapore. For a fixed monthly price, subscribers gain access to music from Spotify, KKBOX, AMPed, and MeRadio without incurring data charges.
Representatives from Singtel Music at the launch event.
Singtel Music provides premium accounts from Spotify, KKBOX, or AMPed, enabling users to stream an extensive library of songs without data usage concerns. Additionally, they can enjoy 13 MeRadio stations without impacting their data allowance.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra Halo Smart is designed to enhance both your calling and music experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</guid><description>Jabra Halo Smart headphones are designed for users who prioritize call quality but also enjoy listening to music. Research indicates that 79% of consumers desire headphones suitable for both calls and music, yet find most music headphones lacking in call performance.
These headphones prioritize calls with features like high-quality microphones, wind-noise reduction, and a dedicated button for Google Now or Siri. At the same time, they offer great audio quality for music with 10mm speakers.</description></item><item><title>The Air by crazybaby (NANO) is now offered in 10 different colors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-air-by-crazybaby-nano-is-now-offered-in-10-different-colors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-air-by-crazybaby-nano-is-now-offered-in-10-different-colors/</guid><description>Source: Hwee Seng Electronics. Air by crazybaby (NANO) is available in 10 colours.
Hwee Seng Electronics, a Singaporean distributor specializing in audio electronics, has become the official distributor for Crazybaby, a provider of high-quality audio devices. Their product, Air by crazybaby (NANO), also called Nano, is now available in Singapore through Hwee Seng Electronics.
Nano earbuds combine Crazybaby&amp;rsquo;s modern and stylish look with a water-resistant build. These earbuds utilize carbon nanotube technology, which produces sound differently than traditional methods and generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t need moving parts.</description></item><item><title>The BeoPlay H8 wireless headphones have made their debut in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beoplay-h8-wireless-headphones-have-made-their-debut-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 09:59:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beoplay-h8-wireless-headphones-have-made-their-debut-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Beoplay H8 headphones, in argilla bright.
BANG &amp;amp; OLUFSEN introduces their wireless headphones: elegant and with a long battery life. The B&amp;amp;O PLAY headphones provide up to 14 hours of battery life with active noise cancellation. Their lightweight design features a sleek aluminum touch interface.
Controlling the B&amp;amp;O PLAY Beoplay H8 on-ear headphones is done through gestures on the aluminum ear cup. Tapping and swiping can control various activities, like answering calls, adjusting the volume, selecting tracks, and activating or deactivating noise cancellation.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra SPEAK 810 can detect and track people speaking from several meters away</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-speak-810-can-detect-and-track-people-speaking-from-several-meters-away/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-speak-810-can-detect-and-track-people-speaking-from-several-meters-away/</guid><description>Fragment.in, a Swiss design interaction studio, created a computer orchestra controlled by gestures. Hand movements are recognized by a Kinect, which then controls audio from multiple computers. The sound is emitted through Jabra SPEAK 810 devices.
Jabra, a company specializing in audio and communications technology, has launched the SPEAK 810. This new conference speakerphone offers high-quality call experiences to enhance meeting collaboration.
Retailing at US$599, the Jabra SPEAK 810 addresses common obstacles to effective collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Experience all-day flexibility with the Plantronics BackBeat 100 Series Wireless Headphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</guid><description>Plantronics, a company known for its audio and wearable technology, has introduced the BackBeat 100 Series. These headphones are the newest addition to their BackBeat stereo product line and offer a unique hybrid neckband design for wireless calls and music.
The BackBeat 100 and BackBeat 105 are designed for comfort throughout the day with an ultra-lightweight build. They provide full-range sound with enhanced bass, making them ideal for listening to music and watching videos on the move.</description></item><item><title>Jabra is unveiling three new additions to its Elite series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</guid><description>Jabra introduces the Elite Active 65t (right), Elite 65e (left), and Elite 45e (middle) to the Singapore market.
Jabra is releasing three new products: the Elite Active 65t, Elite 65e, and Elite 45e in Singapore. These devices belong to the Elite family of headphones and earbuds, known for superior music quality and excellent voice capabilities.
The Elite family encompasses various styles like true wireless, headband, neckband, and soft neckband. The suffix &amp;ldquo;e&amp;rdquo; signifies an earbud design, while &amp;ldquo;t&amp;rdquo; indicates true wireless.</description></item><item><title>Cisco has launched new personal hardware to improve collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-launched-new-personal-hardware-to-improve-collaboration/</guid><description>At Cisco Live! 2014 in the US, Cisco unveiled new personal collaboration tools. The company recognizes that teamwork often spans continents, demanding tools that enable seamless and immediate collaboration, regardless of location.
Source: Cisco. The Cisco DX80 in action.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution comes in the form of the DX70 and DX80 desktop collaboration devices. These Android-based devices act as hubs for collaboration tools and applications. Featuring large touch screens, the DX70 and DX80 combine Cisco&amp;rsquo;s expertise in HD video, high-quality audio, and web conferencing with integrated business applications and web browsing.</description></item><item><title>Singtel Music is excited to announce the addition of TIDAL to its portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</guid><description>Singtel Music now offers its customers access to the global music and entertainment platform, TIDAL.
TIDAL differentiates itself as the sole music app providing high-fidelity, lossless audio quality and exclusive content from top global artists. Singtel Music users can enjoy both TIDAL Premium and TIDAL HIFI without impacting their data plans.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its music streaming options. Following the addition of Saavn in October, TIDAL further solidifies Singtel Music&amp;rsquo;s goal of providing the best music streaming experience with diverse content, attractive pricing, and no data charges.</description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization recommends restricting the use of personal audio devices to less than one hour per day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</guid><description>Source: WHO.
The World Health Organization (WHO) cautions that over a billion adolescents and young adults risk noise-induced hearing loss. This danger stems from unsafe listening practices with personal audio devices like smartphones and exposure to high sound levels at entertainment venues, including sporting events.
WHO analysis of data from developed and developing nations reveals that nearly half of teenagers and young adults aged 12-35 experience unsafe sound levels from personal audio devices.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time.</description></item><item><title>JVC introduces new sports in-ear headphones that are waterproof and washable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 03:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</guid><description>Source: JVC.
JVC introduces four new sports headphone options designed to stay securely in place during physical activity, with some models offering waterproof and washable features.
The lineup includes two models in both the JVC Gumy Sport and Extreme Fitness series. The Gumy Sport headphones, HA-EN10 and HA-ENR15, utilize a Nozzle Fit earpiece constructed from soft silicone. This unique shape ensures a secure and comfortable fit, preventing the headphones from falling out during workouts.</description></item><item><title>The LinkBuds S from Sony provide an immersive audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The LinkBuds S.
Sony has expanded its LinkBuds series with the new LinkBuds S. This model offers a new audio experience by utilizing Sony&amp;rsquo;s sensor technology and collaborations, while still providing a seamless &amp;ldquo;always-on&amp;rdquo; experience.
The LinkBuds S boast both noise cancellation and high-resolution audio capabilities. These headphones allow users to stay connected to their surroundings with the LinkBuds&amp;rsquo; ambient sound feature or minimize distractions with high-quality noise cancellation, letting them fully enjoy their preferred content.</description></item><item><title>HTC has launched the HTC Desire 826 dual sim, promising an exceptional mobile audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The Blue Lagoon version.
HTC is enhancing the mobile audio experience with its Desire 826 dual sim phone, featuring HTC BoomSound and Dolby Audio surround sound. This makes HTC the first smartphone manufacturer to integrate dual front-facing stereo speakers, a precisely adjusted sound profile, and Dolby&amp;rsquo;s decoding technology for a comprehensive multi-channel audio solution.
This combination provides listeners with a level of audio depth and range not typically found in mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>The Beats Decade Collection features the Defiant Black-Red colorway for Beats by Dr. Dre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:28:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</guid><description>Source: Beats. The Beats Decade Collection.
To commemorate its 10th anniversary, Beats by Dr Dre has unveiled the Beats Decade Collection, a special edition line of products in a striking black and red colorway. This bold design choice pays homage to the brand&amp;rsquo;s origins and the intense emotions evoked by music.
The Defiant Black-Red color scheme is showcased in these models:
Source: Beats. The Beats Studio3 wireless headphones, in folded mode.</description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry.</description></item><item><title>Jabra introduces the Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company known for creating intelligent audio devices, has introduced the Jabra Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset. This new headset is a unified communication (UC) upgrade from their original Jabra Stealth and is designed specifically for professionals who are often on the go.
Weighing in at a mere 0.24 ounces (approximately 6.8 grams), the Jabra Stealth UC is remarkably lightweight, making it both inconspicuous and incredibly easy to carry around.</description></item><item><title>X-mini expands its audio portfolio with the addition of earbuds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/x-mini-expands-its-audio-portfolio-with-the-addition-of-earbuds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/x-mini-expands-its-audio-portfolio-with-the-addition-of-earbuds/</guid><description>X-mini, a company known for its portable audio devices, is expanding its product line in Singapore with the introduction of four new wired earbud series: NOVA, XYRIUS, XTLAS, and RAY. These additions aim to provide audio lovers with a variety of choices to suit their preferences and needs.
Each earbud series is crafted with X-mini&amp;rsquo;s audio expertise, incorporating carefully chosen sound drivers to deliver their signature sound quality. All earbuds come equipped with microphones, allowing users to seamlessly switch between music and calls.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new smartphones and audio-visual solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications (Sony Mobile) has introduced new consumer experiences centered around innovation.
“Xperia Touch represents a groundbreaking interface,&amp;quot; stated Hiroki Totoki, President and CEO of Sony Mobile Communications. &amp;ldquo;A year after revealing our updated brand direction and vision for the future of communications, we are not only introducing the Xperia XZ Premium, packed with cutting-edge technologies to improve core smartphone features, but also creating entirely new interactive communication experiences with our Xperia Smart Products.</description></item></channel></rss>