<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GCC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gcc/</link><description>Recent content in GCC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:55:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gcc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Kobo eReader ecosystem is now accessible in the GCC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</guid><description>Source: Kobo. The Kobo
Aura H2O eReader.
Kobo, the eBook retailer, and distributor Lionfish have announced that Kobo&amp;rsquo;s digital reading platform is launching in the GCC region. This will give readers access to Kobo&amp;rsquo;s eBookstore, which offers over 4.2 million titles. They will also be able to purchase eReaders and apps compatible with iOS, Android, Microsoft, and BlackBerry platforms.
Kobo products will be sold in 34 stores throughout the region.</description></item><item><title>Hyundai introduces the Grand i10 in the GCC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyundai-introduces-the-grand-i10-in-the-gcc-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyundai-introduces-the-grand-i10-in-the-gcc-region/</guid><description>Source: Hyundai Motor Company.
Hyundai Motor Company has introduced the Grand i10 to the GCC market. Targeting young adults in their 20s and 30s seeking comfort, practicality, and safety, the car is offered in both hatchback and sedan styles. Two trim levels, GL and GLS, are available, with a starting price of US$10,000.
Hyundai reports strong early sales figures for the Grand i10, with over 5,400 units sold within the first six months following its April 2014 launch in Lebanon.</description></item><item><title>Bahrain becomes a member of the Cruise Arabia Alliance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bahrain-becomes-a-member-of-the-cruise-arabia-alliance/</guid><description>Bahrain has joined the Cruise Arabia Alliance, solidifying the organization&amp;rsquo;s presence in the region. Other members include Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Sharjah, Qatar, and Oman. The alliance promotes collaboration among its members to maintain high standards of service for cruise lines and their passengers.
This announcement took place at the Seatrade Middle East Cruise Forum in Doha, Qatar, hosted by the Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA). Alongside this news, Bahrain also shared that the 2015/2016 cruise season will include 68,000 passengers and 32 visits from major cruise lines.</description></item><item><title>Expatstoday provides important advice for expatriates living in the Gulf region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</guid><description>Source: Expatstoday
A new online platform, Expatstoday, aims to attract individuals considering a move to Bahrain, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, or the UAE. The website provides insights into living conditions in these Gulf countries.
The company behind the platform emphasizes its commitment to providing accurate, current, and trustworthy information. While the sections dedicated to Gulf countries appear well-established, suggesting an active user base, pages for other countries seem relatively new, often lacking listings in various categories.</description></item><item><title>The TINA ERP system is compatible with GCC VAT calculations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tina-erp-system-is-compatible-with-gcc-vat-calculations/</guid><description>Source: dcs plus. Graphic for the TINA travel ERP software.
dcs plus, a Romanian company with a Dubai office, has announced that its TINA web-based travel ERP system now supports value-added tax (VAT) calculations for businesses operating in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) region. This development comes as GCC member states prepare to fully implement VAT based on a framework agreement from 2016.
TINA streamlines business operations by collecting booking details from various sales channels and organizing them into standardized, automated workflows.</description></item></channel></rss>