<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FIOS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fios/</link><description>Recent content in FIOS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas.</description></item><item><title>Is 1 Tbps The Next Optical Network Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</guid><description>While everyday users are getting used to 100 Mbps speeds, network providers are already looking ahead to Terabit per second speeds, debating whether 400 Gbps or 1 Tbps will be the next standard.
This push for higher speeds is a natural progression, similar to the advancement from Kbps to Mbps and Gbps. Just like previous upgrades, the proposed standards represent a tenfold increase.
This speed increase mirrors Moore&amp;rsquo;s Law, which predicted the doubling of transistors on integrated circuits yearly.</description></item><item><title>The Fiber Gold Rush Is On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</guid><description>The transition from copper wires to fiber optic strands has been recognized as a necessity for some time. This shift is driven by the growing need for bandwidth as technology progresses. Over the past few decades, various sectors, including internet service providers, cable companies, healthcare facilities, and large enterprises, have progressively adopted fiber optic connections. Services like Metro Ethernet have made this transition feasible even for mid-sized businesses. Now, small businesses and individual consumers are poised to benefit from this technology.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic ISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-isp/</guid><description>Internet service used to rely on dial-up connections, but it has advanced significantly since then. Today, medium-sized businesses are now transitioning to fiber optic internet service providers, a technology already embraced by larger corporations.
Residential fiber optic internet, like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS, offers high speeds, with Google soon to introduce even faster Gigabit service. Business broadband connections, however, have already surpassed Gigabit speeds, with 10 Gbps becoming increasingly common. The technology is well-established, leaving businesses to determine their bandwidth needs and locations.</description></item></channel></rss>