<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Integrated Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integrated-access/</link><description>Recent content in Integrated Access on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integrated-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best VoIP Providers For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</guid><description>Thinking about switching from traditional phone lines to VoIP, but unsure about its effectiveness? This guide provides insights and advice for a smooth transition.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, is also known as “network voice” because it operates on computer networks, unlike traditional phone systems. Essentially, voice becomes another service on your network, alongside data, video, and audio streaming. Each service transmits packets routed through the network.
This setup offers significant cost savings for larger businesses by consolidating telephone and data networks.</description></item><item><title>Integrated Access Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>T1 lines can be used for broadband data or digital phone lines. However, needing separate lines for voice and data was expensive for smaller businesses. Integrated T1 offered a solution by combining voice and data on a single line, proving cost-effective for a while. But now, Integrated Access using Ethernet over Copper is an even better option.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a strong competitor to T1 lines. Both use existing copper telephone wiring, offering reliability and dedicated bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>