<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Q416 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/q416/</link><description>Recent content in Q416 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 11:18:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/q416/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mergers and acquisitions in the early stages are decelerating in Southeast Asia and Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 11:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mergers-and-acquisitions-in-the-early-stages-are-decelerating-in-southeast-asia-and-korea/</guid><description>Announcements for early-stage mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in Q4 2016 are predicted to be similar to the same period last year. This is attributed to reduced early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity in Southeast Asia and South Korea, as per the latest Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor (DFP) report released by Intralinks Holdings. Intralinks provides software and services, including virtual data rooms (VDRs), for managing M&amp;amp;A transactions.
Southeast Asia, encompassing Singapore, Malaysia, and Indonesia, is experiencing a significant 47.</description></item><item><title>There was a significant increase in early-stage M&amp;A activity in the APAC region during the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>The Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor, which forecasts future merger and acquisition (M&amp;amp;A) announcements, anticipates a 6% rise in the total number of global M&amp;amp;A deals announced in the first half of 2017 compared to the same period in 2016. This would establish a new record for global announced deals in the first six months of a year.
The Asia Pacific (APAC) region leads in early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity, demonstrating 44% year-over-year growth in the fourth quarter of 2016, and is positioned to significantly contribute to the projected record deal count in the first half of 2017.</description></item></channel></rss>