<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>5503 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5503/</link><description>Recent content in 5503 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5503/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Awesome Refurbished Keypads in the House!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</guid><description>I received two refurbished Beogram 4002 keypads from Denmark today. My friend, who did the repainting, said the weather conditions were perfect for the job, and he was right! The picture shows how fantastic they look.
He&amp;rsquo;s incredibly talented! The keypads look brand new, as if they were just made in 1975. He did a phenomenal job. I had sent him a worn-out keypad from a Beogram 4002 I recently restored, and he even found another one!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Restoration of the Carriage Position Sensor - Development of a New Beolover Part</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) being restored had a broken carriage position sensor photo resistor housing with damaged mounting tabs. After removing the housing and extracting the photo resistor, a replacement housing was designed and 3D printed.
The new housing consists of two parts. The photo resistor is placed on the insert part after straightening its leads. The main housing is then slid over the insert, sandwiching the photo resistor. This assembly is then inserted into the existing mounting cutouts and soldered to the PCB...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Full Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 22:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable originating from California. The restoration process commenced with the reconstruction of the carriage and arm lowering mechanisms, encompassing meticulous cleaning and lubrication of components like the solenoid and damper.
Following the mechanism restoration, focus shifted to the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm. This involved addressing a common issue: a detached copper pad on the sensor arm assembly. The pad was reattached using epoxy to ensure smooth operation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Newly Adapted Beolover RIAA Pre-Amp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</guid><description>Following the recent redesign of the Beolover internal RIAA pre-amplifier for DC-motor Beogram 4002/4 turntables and its adaptation for the Beogram 4000, the final stage of the design process involved adjusting the circuit for the AC-motor Beogram 4002. The owner of a recently restored 4002 (5504) requested the RIAA installation, making his Beogram the first AC-motor 4002 to feature a Beolover RIAA.
The new board features an input jack that connects to a replicated Beogram-style plug through a multi-lead wiring harness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival From Oklahoma - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 11:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in good condition.
While the dust cover is intact, it does have some scratches and might need polishing or replacement. The turntable itself is in good shape, with only minor blemishes on the aluminum surfaces and minimal wear on the keypad. Using a soft cloth to operate the keypad or installing a remote control module would help preserve its condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Unit Switches Immediately to 45 RPM After Pressing Start</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable being restored exhibited a peculiar issue during initial testing. Upon starting, the tonearm moved as expected but the speed immediately switched to 45 RPM. Pressing the 33 RPM button temporarily resolved the issue, but the speed reverted back upon release.
This unusual behavior pointed to a potential problem with transistors TR3 or TR2. Examining the circuit diagram, we can see how speed selection operates:
The speed control mechanism utilizes a flip-flop circuit with transistors TR3 and TR4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Signal Path between DIN5 Plug and Cartridge, Plug Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</guid><description>I recently decided to update my Beogram 4002 turntable for the 21st century. While it was functional, the DIN 5 plug was noticeably worn and corroded. To address this, I swapped it out with a modern, high-quality Neutrik AG Rean NYS 322G plug featuring gold-plated pins, aiming for a reliable, long-lasting connection with my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s auxiliary input. The old plug was in rough shape, leaving me curious about its past...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>