<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ASEAN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asean/</link><description>Recent content in ASEAN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (IBFC) is initiating roadshows across the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-international-business-and-financial-centre-ibfc-is-initiating-roadshows-across-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 15:46:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-international-business-and-financial-centre-ibfc-is-initiating-roadshows-across-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Labuan IBFC, a prominent international business and financial hub in the Asia Pacific region, has initiated a series of roadshows throughout ASEAN.
The 2016 Labuan IBFC ASEAN Roadshow will cover major ASEAN countries and, for the first time, will include both events and private briefings in the developing markets of Cambodia, Laos, Vietnam, and Myanmar. The roadshows, which began in Jakarta, Indonesia, will run until the end of July.
Danial Mah Abdullah, Chief Executive Officer of Labuan IBFC, stated, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s roadshow is unique in that we are focusing on regional businesses seeking to internationalize or expand regionally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-international-business-and-financial-centre-ibfc-is-initiating-roadshows-across-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-international-business-and-financial-centre-ibfc-is-initiating-roadshows-across-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Economic Community has the potential to be a goldmine for B2C businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, has published a white paper outlining a strategic framework for marketing to ASEAN consumers.
The establishment of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in December 2015 will unify the ten ASEAN member states into a single market and production hub. This development is anticipated to draw significant attention from multinational corporations that have traditionally focused on China and India. Euromonitor suggests that the AEC is on track to become a global economic powerhouse due to its projected robust economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IdeaLab gives power to startups in ASEAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</guid><description>IdeaLab 2016, a focused two-day startup conference, will highlight ASEAN startup collaboration and the Malaysian startup scene. It also features the Malaysian Business Angels Network (MBAN) Summit, attracting investors globally. The organizers aim to bring together 500 top startups, investors, and corporations from the ASEAN ecosystem.
Attendees can participate in various stages. The Ideation Stage features industry leaders discussing critical issues faced by startups in ASEAN. At the IdeaPad Stage, the best ASEAN startups compete before a panel of judges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new executive board of the EU-ASEAN Business Council has been elected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (EU-ABC), the leading advocate for European companies in the ASEAN region, recently selected its Executive Board for the next two years. The election took place at their annual general meeting in Hanoi, Vietnam, on June 1st.
The new board members are:
François Guibert, Executive Vice-President, President, Greater China and South Asia Region, STMicroelectronics (Chairman) Donald Kanak, Chairman, Prudential Corporation Asia (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Theodoor Bakker, Partner, ABNR Law, Indonesia; Executive Board Member, European Chamber of Commerce, Indonesia (Chamber Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Martin Hayes, President, Robert Bosch SEA (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Treasurer), and Jan B...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB discusses its regional strategies for participating in the ASEAN Economic Community</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. Chairman of CIMB Group, YBhg Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Nazir Razak (right) and Director, Southeast Asia of The Economist Intelligence Unit Justin Wood showcasing the special report Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia.
CIMB partnered with the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) to publish a report titled Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia. This independent management brief, co-sponsored by CIMB and Baker McKenzie, aims to equip companies for the upcoming launch of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) on December 31, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EY identifies obstacles that are impeding the effectiveness of the AEC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</guid><description>Political, legal, and organizational difficulties, regulatory burdens, and a lack of standardized trade regulations among ASEAN nations are hindering the progress of the 2007 ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) Blueprint. This plan aims to achieve regional economic integration by 2015, according to EY.
A recent EY report, &amp;ldquo;Trade Secrets: ASEAN economic community and inward investment,&amp;rdquo; examines the AEC&amp;rsquo;s development from a business standpoint, specifically focusing on obstacles to conducting business within ASEAN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 has been met with an enthusiastic and positive reception</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</guid><description>Source: 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. The 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, was officially opened by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah.
Source: _1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. _Pictured from left to right (back row): Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah, Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, alongside Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Bin Abdullah, Secretary General of Treasury, Malaysia. They are joined by 10 children, each representing a different ASEAN nation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shangri-La and Singapore Airlines campaign offers packaged deals for ASEAN destinations and hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</guid><description>To commemorate the 50th anniversary of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts and Singapore Airlines have teamed up to launch a travel campaign called &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore.&amp;rdquo;
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjJuZK2IwJjPxRmvmq0DT-MS7ZPDl5douabN-yaRNI7kSFX1RAg5n8m2LHrg030pnJcr68_qz-IujmANOlf3NTbWGRF887wfkPbFQPAn168XsbqGeH8wP90CW2_M3muXU8ABKS6E9PwtOA/s1600/Shangri+La+SIA+ASEAN+is+More.JPG)
Source: Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts. Banner for the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore&amp;rdquo; campaign.
This campaign highlights Southeast Asia as a travel destination through special offers on curated leisure trips. Flight and hotel packages are available for various properties in Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Myanmar, and Thailand, including Shangri-La hotels and resorts, Hotel Jen properties, and Traders Hotel, Kuala Lumpur...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Direct your attention to the ASEAN approach: Prime Minister of Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 06:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
During his opening speech at the 27th ASEAN Summit and other related meetings in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysian Prime Minister Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Mohd Najib Tun Abdul Razak urged members to embrace the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN way.&amp;rdquo;
He emphasized the importance of prioritizing community and collaborative solutions over individual pursuits and self-serving goals. This approach, he stated, favors non-violent resolutions, moderation over extreme viewpoints, and respect for all, including adversaries. He stressed that true strength lies in pursuing peace and building bridges instead of fueling conflicts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>INTA: Companies that invest in trademarks make a significant contribution to the economies of ASEAN countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 22:15:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</guid><description>A new report from the International Trademark Association (INTA) reveals that industries heavily reliant on trademarks play a substantial role in the economies of five key ASEAN nations: Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, Singapore, and Thailand. The report, titled The Economic Contribution of Trademark-Intensive Industries in Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, Singapore, and Thailand, shows that these industries stimulate job growth across sectors and significantly contribute to international trade. Industries classified as &amp;ldquo;trademark-intensive&amp;rdquo; are those that file a higher number of trademarks compared to others, adjusted for the total employment within each industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, ASEAN received the highest amount of foreign direct investment (FDI) among developing countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The latest ASEAN Investment Report examines the growth of foreign direct investment (FDI) into the ASEAN region, particularly the influence of corporations on infrastructure expansion and regional integration.
In 2014, ASEAN emerged as the top recipient of FDI among developing nations. FDI inflows to the region experienced a third consecutive year of growth, reaching US$136.2 billion, a rise from US$117.7 billion in 2013. This achievement occurred despite a 16% global decline in FDI and inconsistent global economic progress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A group of business representatives travels to Singapore to showcase the "Made In Italy" brand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-group-of-business-representatives-travels-to-singapore-to-showcase-the-made-in-italy-brand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 16:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-group-of-business-representatives-travels-to-singapore-to-showcase-the-made-in-italy-brand/</guid><description>Leading Italian industry groups have revealed their collaborative strategy with local organizations for an upcoming visit to Singapore to champion the &amp;ldquo;Made in Italy&amp;rdquo; brand. They emphasized Italy&amp;rsquo;s top-tier capabilities, aligning perfectly with the needs of a rapidly developing ASEAN region, and highlighted how ASEAN can utilize this success to accelerate its own progress.
The year 2018 marks two decades of formal economic collaboration and trade between Singapore and Italy. Recognizing innovation as a key driver of economic and societal transformation, both nations agreed to strengthen their long-term cooperation across diverse sectors, ranging from fashion and healthcare to furniture and technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-group-of-business-representatives-travels-to-singapore-to-showcase-the-made-in-italy-brand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-group-of-business-representatives-travels-to-singapore-to-showcase-the-made-in-italy-brand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GetResponse introduces its email marketing platform in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>GetResponse, an email marketing platform, has officially launched in the ASEAN region. The company enhanced its cloud-based platform earlier this year to include support for Chinese, Malay, and Thai languages. This move has contributed to a significant 41.6% surge in new account registrations. GetResponse has observed a 35.8% year-over-year growth in email marketing activities within ASEAN.
Source: GetResponse website.
Simon Grabowski, CEO of GetResponse, emphasized the significance of email marketing, especially for small and medium-sized businesses working with limited budgets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>