<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Communications on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Telephone Systems Hosted VoIP Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes have various choices for their telephone systems. Small businesses can buy systems from local stores, while medium-sized businesses often work with contractors for key telephone systems or small PBXs. Larger companies may have internal teams that handle complex telephone systems. Nowadays, hosted VoIP is a cost-effective option for companies of all sizes.
How can one solution meet the needs of different-sized businesses affordably? It&amp;rsquo;s not a one-size-fits-all solution but a scalable technology adaptable to different demands—hosted VoIP, also known as hosted PBX or cloud telephone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-telephone-systems-hosted-voip-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted PBX Adds Video Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems, also known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, are gaining popularity with businesses of all sizes. This technology offers advanced features without requiring a large upfront investment. Now, these systems are evolving to incorporate video services as well.
MegaPath, a leading network and cloud service provider, is enhancing its hosted PBX offerings by including cloud-based unified communications video services.
A new generation of business phones makes voice and video integration possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SIP Trunking Supplant ISDN PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses that require multiple phone lines can benefit from digital trunks. While previously only large companies with numerous lines saw advantages with digital trunks, advancements in technology now make them a viable option for businesses with just a few lines and internet access.
What exactly constitutes a telephone trunk? Essentially, it is a collection of phone lines bundled together. Unlike individual analog lines, which consist of a twisted pair of copper wires, a trunk combines multiple lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best VoIP Providers For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</guid><description>Thinking about switching from traditional phone lines to VoIP, but unsure about its effectiveness? This guide provides insights and advice for a smooth transition.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, is also known as “network voice” because it operates on computer networks, unlike traditional phone systems. Essentially, voice becomes another service on your network, alongside data, video, and audio streaming. Each service transmits packets routed through the network.
This setup offers significant cost savings for larger businesses by consolidating telephone and data networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Communications Advantages Explained</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</guid><description>Many businesses are unsure if switching their communications to the cloud is a good idea. XO Communications, a large networking and telecom provider, explains why this change is beneficial. Their short video illustrates why this might be the right choice for your business.
XO&amp;rsquo;s Enterprise Cloud Communications provides large businesses with services similar to what hosted PBX systems offer smaller companies. Essentially, it transitions a company from managing its own phone system to simply using a sophisticated service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone Offers Awareness In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The traditional office phone, once a large and stationary fixture on every desk, is becoming a relic of the past. Modern business communication has evolved into a dynamic and multifaceted process, incorporating instant messaging, online collaboration tools, file sharing, and web-based applications alongside traditional voice calls and conferencing. This evolution begs the question: are conventional PBX systems still equipped to handle the demands of today&amp;rsquo;s business environment?
As outdated phone systems increasingly hinder productivity, many companies are turning to cloud-based solutions for a more modern approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should You Buy VoIP as a Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</guid><description>Cloud-based services, including Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), have been around for a while. What&amp;rsquo;s becoming more popular now is the trend of large businesses connecting their different locations using SIP Trunks and all sizes of businesses choosing to outsource their PBX functionality. This can be considered VoIP as a Service.
Many home and small business users adopted cloud-based VoIP early on to cut costs. They did this by replacing their traditional phone lines and using their broadband internet connection for both high-speed internet and phone service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center On Demand in the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The sophistication of cloud communications services is constantly increasing, representing a logical progression in the cloud computing revolution. With data servers already transitioned to the cloud, numerous businesses are questioning the necessity of maintaining costly and aging PBX phone systems.
Transitioning business phone systems to the cloud is becoming increasingly practical. Beginning with Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, this shift eliminates the need for substantial hardware and traditional phone lines. Instead, handsets connect to the company network and a high-bandwidth WAN connection links to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Can Improve Telephone Reliability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</guid><description>Many businesses, even large ones, hold onto their own phone systems believing it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to guarantee reliable communication. But is this true, or is it time to reconsider this assumption?
The phone service industry has experienced a significant shift with the emergence of hosted PBX (HPBX), also called hosted VoIP or cloud communications. Like other cloud-based technologies, this is a game-changer. In the future, we&amp;rsquo;ll wonder why we didn&amp;rsquo;t switch sooner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber WAN is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that your business needs the speed of fiber optic WAN service to ensure cloud-based applications are responsive and your team stays productive. However, you may have struggled to find this service in the past. It&amp;rsquo;s time to try again.
Why Is Fiber More Accessible Now?
Fiber optic used to be a rare and costly option limited to large corporations. You had to rely on the telephone company and hope they serviced your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>