<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monster on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/monster/</link><description>Recent content in Monster on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 06:17:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/monster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The uptrend in online hiring in Singapore is being led by the IT, BFSI, and advertising industries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uptrend-in-online-hiring-in-singapore-is-being-led-by-the-it-bfsi-and-advertising-industries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 06:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uptrend-in-online-hiring-in-singapore-is-being-led-by-the-it-bfsi-and-advertising-industries/</guid><description>Singapore saw an increase in online recruitment in November 2018, with a 5% rise in job postings compared to the same period in 2017, as reported by the Monster Employment Index (MEI). This represents a significant jump from the 1% growth recorded in October 2018.
The IT, telecom, BPO/ITES sector experienced the most substantial growth, surging by 22% year-on-year, marking its highest point since March 2018. BFSI and advertising also demonstrated positive trends, rising by 16% and 15% respectively compared to the previous year.</description></item><item><title>The demand for HR and admin professionals is increasing in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-hr-and-admin-professionals-is-increasing-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-hr-and-admin-professionals-is-increasing-in-malaysia/</guid><description>For the first time since March 2018, HR and administrative (admin) jobs in Malaysia experienced a 2% year-over-year increase in December.
This job category also saw recent positive short-term growth, with a 4% rise month-over-month and a 2% increase over three months. The Philippines echoed this positive trend, with online hiring demand for HR and admin professionals surging by 22% year-on-year.
Demand for HR and admin interns remained strong in Malaysia and the Philippines, representing the highest demand among all surveyed occupations at 13% and 5%, respectively.</description></item><item><title>TalentBin by Monster searches through social networks to find potential candidates for recruitment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 16:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</guid><description>Source: Monster website.
Monster recently launched its TalentBin platform across multiple regions to help businesses locate and engage skilled professionals. Functioning as a specialized search engine for talent, the software grants recruiters access to a pool of potential candidates who might not be easily discoverable through traditional methods. This is achieved by analyzing and leveraging professional information individuals share on various social media platforms.
TalentBin not only automates and simplifies the process of identifying potential candidates through site monitoring, data interpretation, and profile matching but also makes hiring more efficient, allowing recruiters to achieve more in less time.</description></item></channel></rss>