<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pack on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pack/</link><description>Recent content in Pack on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Altec Lansing introduces durable mobile accessories at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</guid><description>Altec Lansing is launching new lines of durable chargers, power banks, cables, and cases for smartphones and tablets. Expected to be available around the second quarter of 2016, these accessories will have rugged features like IP67-rated, military-grade construction for waterproof, dustproof, and shock-resistant functionality and device protection.
The new products will include:
Altec Lansing Everything Proof Power Packs (3,000, 6,000, and 10,000 mAh): These power banks are designed for smartphones, tablets, and MP3 players, offering up to 100 hours of talk time, 75 hours of music, 50 hours of video, or 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CruCycle brings a fresh perspective to the fitness scene in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</guid><description>Krewfit recently introduced CruCycle, a new spin studio concept in Singapore, to fitness and fun enthusiasts. The studio&amp;rsquo;s classes operate on the principle of &amp;ldquo;Riding with the Pack,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing group workouts, teamwork, and camaraderie. This makes CruCycle&amp;rsquo;s workouts perfect for corporate team-building events.
Source: Crucycle.
The Ding siblings – Valerie, Calvin, and Beatrice – founded, own, and operate CruCycle. The inspiration for the studio came from their upbringing in Los Angeles, California...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces new Stan Smith designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</guid><description>This summer, the Stan Smith shoe gets a bold update with the Wrapped Animal Pack. Available in three color combinations, the pack keeps the Stan Smith&amp;rsquo;s famous shape while incorporating textured snake, alligator, and crocodile leather around the outsole.
Source: adidas.
Complementary heel tab accents in green, red, and black add a fashionable touch to this classic preppy sneaker. The Adidas Originals Stan Smith, originally a tennis shoe, has become a timeless classic thanks to its all-leather design and simple aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>