<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hotline on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hotline/</link><description>Recent content in Hotline on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hotline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The MyNumber service from Hashtag assists businesses in reducing their hotline expenses in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 11:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mynumber-service-from-hashtag-assists-businesses-in-reducing-their-hotline-expenses-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>PLDT, through its corporate business group PLDT ALPHA Enterprise, has launched the PLDT #MyNumber service. This service streamlines a business&amp;rsquo;s hotline system into a memorable four to eight-digit contact number that starts with the &amp;ldquo;#&amp;rdquo; symbol (for example, #8888). This single number can be reached by consumers nationwide using PLDT landlines, Smart, Talk N’ Text, and Sun mobile phones.
This service is designed for businesses that currently advertise different hotline numbers for different regions.</description></item><item><title>India has implemented measures to prepare for Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</guid><description>India is actively monitoring the situation to prevent the Ebola virus disease (EVD) from entering the country. Three dedicated helplines (2306 3205, 2306 1469, and 2306 1302) were set up at the Health Ministry on August 9th to address public inquiries.
While India has no confirmed or suspected Ebola cases, the World Health Organization (WHO) alerted the government about an Indian passenger who shared a flight with an Ebola patient traveling from Monrovia (Liberia) to Lagos (Nigeria), both experiencing outbreaks.</description></item></channel></rss>