<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gadgets on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gadgets/</link><description>Recent content in Gadgets on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:51:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gadgets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Solstice Before The Solstice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait for the winter solstice to experience the Samsung Solstice, a touchscreen phone designed for social networking. This sleek phone boasts a vibrant 3-inch color touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable app widgets for easy access to platforms like Facebook and MySpace.
Staying connected is effortless with the Solstice&amp;rsquo;s virtual keyboard and high-resolution screen, perfect for messaging. Its slim, half-inch profile, achieved through advanced virtual technology, surpasses bulkier models with slide-out keyboards.</description></item><item><title>Poken Enhances Face to Face Social Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</guid><description>Is jotting down contact information on scraps of paper your go-to method? Do you find yourself hoping your hand-written notes survive the journey home? Perhaps you rely on traditional business cards?
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, those methods are outdated.
Just like Facebook, MySpace, LinkedIn, and Twitter revolutionized online networking, Poken is ushering in a new era for in-person connections with a device aptly named &amp;ldquo;Poken.&amp;rdquo; Think of it as a modern-day amulet, powered by cutting-edge technology.</description></item><item><title>Cash For Clunker Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</guid><description>While the government&amp;rsquo;s Cash for Clunkers program for cars might be ending, there&amp;rsquo;s a similar concept for old electronics. You can get cash for your unwanted devices, including cell phones, laptops, and more!
You might not have heard about this, but it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to earn money from your unused gadgets. From cell phones and laptops to gaming consoles and cameras, many devices have value. Don&amp;rsquo;t let them sit around collecting dust – see how much they&amp;rsquo;re worth!</description></item><item><title>Samsung Reclaim is Green and Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-reclaim-is-green-and-free/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-reclaim-is-green-and-free/</guid><description>Contrary to what some might believe, being environmentally conscious doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to break the bank. The Samsung Reclaim M560 for Sprint is a prime example of affordable, eco-friendly technology.
This slider phone boasts a full QWERTY keyboard and a vibrant 2.6-inch color display with a resolution of 320 x 240 pixels, capable of displaying over 262,000 colors. Its 2.0-megapixel camera captures high-quality photos and videos suitable for sharing.
The Reclaim offers swift 3G connectivity on Sprint&amp;rsquo;s network, enabling access to services like Sprint TV, Sprint Music Store, and Sprint Video.</description></item><item><title>Recycle Video Games and Gaming Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-video-games-and-gaming-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-video-games-and-gaming-systems/</guid><description>Think about all the video games and gaming systems you have in your home, even the ones tucked away. You probably have quite a collection!
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to turn those unused games and consoles into cash? Instead of letting them gather dust, you could use the money to buy whatever you want, including the newest games and systems.
Selling your old gaming stuff can be a hassle, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be.</description></item><item><title>iPhone Getting its Video in a Sling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</guid><description>The mobile video landscape is seeing growth in various forms, including carrier-specific services like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s VCAST and Sprint TV, and dedicated channels such as MediaFLO. Sling Media&amp;rsquo;s introduction of a SlingPlayer for iPhone has the potential to disrupt the market by giving control of content back to the user.
Sling Media is known for its Slingbox, a device that connects to your television source (satellite receiver, DVR, or cable box) and a broadband connection.</description></item><item><title>Green Your Cell Phone For St. Patrick's Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</guid><description>On this St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day, let&amp;rsquo;s think about being green in more ways than one! Before the festivities begin, take a few moments to consider how you can help the environment.
You might be surprised to learn that millions of old cell phones are discarded yearly. They contain valuable resources like gold – enough to create a significant treasure if they were all collected. Instead of letting these resources go to waste, retrieve that old phone you have lying around, and let&amp;rsquo;s discover how it can benefit you and the planet.</description></item><item><title>Year of the Tiger Poken</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/year-of-the-tiger-poken/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 07:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/year-of-the-tiger-poken/</guid><description>February 14th was a significant date, marking not only Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day but also the beginning of the Chinese New Year. In the Chinese Zodiac, a 12-animal cycle is used to name the years, including the tiger. The year 2010 is designated as the &amp;ldquo;Year of the Tiger&amp;rdquo;.
Beyond its association with the tiger, 2010 is poised to be recognized as the &amp;ldquo;Year of the Poken&amp;rdquo;. Introduced late last year, the Poken, a social networking device originating in Switzerland, has gained popularity in America.</description></item><item><title>Cisco Steps In Front Of The Video Parade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-steps-in-front-of-the-video-parade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 19:52:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-steps-in-front-of-the-video-parade/</guid><description>John Naisbitt, a renowned futurist, once said that true leadership involves recognizing a trend and positioning oneself at its forefront. Cisco seems to have taken this to heart by acquiring Flip Video, the company behind the wildly popular camcorder line. It appears Cisco sees consumer-generated video as a growing trend and intends to lead the charge. But what exactly are their plans?
To understand Cisco&amp;rsquo;s strategy, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to examine the Flip video camera&amp;rsquo;s impact on the camcorder market.</description></item><item><title>The Impressive Samsung Impression Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impressive-samsung-impression-phone/</guid><description>Get ready to be amazed by a groundbreaking cell phone display technology called AMOLED, short for Active Matrix Organic Light Emitting Diode. This technology delivers a sharper, more vibrant display that is also slimmer, lighter, and more energy-efficient. While it will soon be widely used in various mobile devices, you can currently experience AMOLED technology in the Samsung Impression A877 Blue cell phone.
As cell phones continue to replace laptops, the demand for larger screens has increased.</description></item><item><title>Sell Your Free Cell Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You were wise to get your new, top-of-the-line smartphone for free when you signed up for service. You understand that service plan costs are consistent, and it&amp;rsquo;s the phone&amp;rsquo;s price that fluctuates.
Now that your contract is up, it&amp;rsquo;s a great opportunity to upgrade. As you search for another discounted or free phone, you might wonder what to do with your old one.
Many people keep their old phones, thinking they might be helpful someday.</description></item><item><title>Recycle Your Cell Phone To Save A Gorilla</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:36:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</guid><description>Recycling old cell phones is beneficial for many reasons, with one significant reason being the protection of the Eastern Lowland Mountain Gorilla in the Democratic Republic of Congo.
You might wonder how cell phone usage impacts gorillas in Africa. The answer lies in the interconnected nature of our ecosystem. Cell phones contain various electronic components, including tantalum capacitors. Tantalum, a scarce and valuable metal, enables the miniaturization of capacitors, making them suitable for slim cell phones.</description></item><item><title>Undercover Laptop Sleeve Computer Cloaking Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a legendary product in computer security that&amp;rsquo;s not a fancy gadget but a simple, low-tech solution: a dirty old bag disguised as a laptop sleeve. This &amp;ldquo;Undercover Laptop Sleeve&amp;rdquo; from Lazybone uses clever disguise as its security mechanism.
The sleeve&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness lies in its unappealing appearance. To a potential thief, it looks like an ordinary, grubby mailing envelope, not a valuable laptop&amp;rsquo;s hiding place. This is crucial considering the potential loss of expensive hardware and sensitive data stored on most laptops.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Picking On Cyber Monday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</guid><description>Similar to how Black Friday has become a tradition for in-person shopping, Cyber Monday is now the time for finding exceptional online deals. With that in mind, let&amp;rsquo;s explore a standout product line this year: BlackBerry devices from Research in Motion.
Business users have long favored BlackBerry for mobile communication. RIM has prioritized supporting corporate IT with the performance and security needed for serious business use on the go. But how affordable are these popular BlackBerry models?</description></item><item><title>It’s a Camera and a Movie Theater</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-a-camera-and-a-movie-theater/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 12:04:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-a-camera-and-a-movie-theater/</guid><description>Nikon has created a groundbreaking product, the Coolpix S1000pj, that redefines digital cameras. What sets this pocket-sized device apart is its integrated projector, making it more than just a camera; it&amp;rsquo;s a portable theater.
This innovation allows users to capture photos and videos and project them onto any flat surface, with sizes reaching up to 40 inches. While a dim environment optimizes viewing, the ability to share visuals instantly is game-changing.</description></item><item><title>The VoSKY is the Limit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</guid><description>Skype, known for free international calls, has become a major player with over 300 million users and a growing presence in the corporate world.
While some might think Skype is just for techies, it has evolved significantly since eBay acquired it in 2005. Beyond basic computer-to-computer calls, a range of hardware now complements Skype, resembling traditional phone setups.
VoSKY, a California-based company, exemplifies this trend, catering to both home users and large companies.</description></item><item><title>There’s $$$ In E-Waste</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 06:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</guid><description>Imagine tossing a $100 bill in the trash. That&amp;rsquo;s essentially what&amp;rsquo;s happening when we discard old electronics, or e-waste. While it might not be actual cash, these devices hold significant monetary and material value that often gets overlooked.
E-waste isn&amp;rsquo;t a new issue. It&amp;rsquo;s been accumulating since the days of bulky radios and TVs. However, the sheer volume of discarded electronics has skyrocketed due to rapid technological advancements and shorter product lifecycles.</description></item><item><title>Is That A Game Or A Netbook?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</guid><description>For years, the distinction between computers and video games has been blurry. This is because modern gaming consoles are essentially powerful computers that run games as applications. So it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s latest handheld gaming system, the DSi, boasts netbook-like features such as secure WiFi connectivity, a web browser, and expandable memory.
Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear: the Nintendo DSi is designed for gamers. It&amp;rsquo;s a handheld console, powered by a battery, and runs Nintendo DS game cartridges.</description></item><item><title>It Really Knows When You Are Sleeping</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</guid><description>You might have heard this before:
It&amp;rsquo;s aware when you&amp;rsquo;re asleep, It&amp;rsquo;s aware when you&amp;rsquo;re awake. It maintains a record of it all, And informs you the next day.
But this isn&amp;rsquo;t about someone monitoring your behavior. This is about understanding your sleep patterns.
If you wake up feeling more tired than when you went to sleep, you might benefit from the Zeo Personal Sleep Coach, a new device that tracks your sleep and provides a visual representation of your sleep quality.</description></item><item><title>Chumby Kicks the Clock Radio to the Curb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</guid><description>Are traditional alarm clocks and radios truly effective ways to wake up? Imagine a more modern approach: starting your day with your favorite internet radio station, a quick weather and market update, and a glimpse at your online auctions. You could even catch up on news and sports or play a game. All of this is possible with the Chumby.
What exactly is a Chumby? It&amp;rsquo;s a wireless internet device featuring speakers, a touchscreen, and motion sensors.</description></item><item><title>The LG Versa-tile Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-versa-tile-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 07:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-versa-tile-phone/</guid><description>LG has launched the Versa VX9600, a phone that combines the benefits of a touchscreen with a physical keyboard.
The LG Versa initially resembles many popular touchscreen phones. However, it sets itself apart with a unique accessory: a detachable QWERTY keyboard. This keyboard, equal in size to the phone, comes in a case that can be easily attached or removed.
This design provides flexibility. Users can opt for the virtual keyboard in standalone mode or connect the physical keyboard for a more tactile typing experience.</description></item><item><title>T1 Rex Is On The Kindle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-rex-is-on-the-kindle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-rex-is-on-the-kindle/</guid><description>Have you experienced the joy of reading with electronic ink? More than half a million dedicated readers have transitioned from traditional books to the lightweight Amazon Kindle. Many more are eagerly anticipating the release of the larger Kindle DX later this year. Kindle represents the future of reading, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to be part of their blog collection.
Rest assured, you can still access our content on your computer whenever you like, as that&amp;rsquo;s where it&amp;rsquo;s created and stored.</description></item><item><title>Poken Pulse Business Networking Gadget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</guid><description>Traditional business networking relies heavily on exchanging physical business cards, a practice that persists despite the rise of smartphones and online networking. Poken offers a modern alternative by digitizing the process.
The Poken device, a small gadget shaped like a four-fingered hand, allows users to exchange contact information wirelessly. When two Poken devices touch, they transfer unique codes linked to the users&amp;rsquo; online profiles.
Unlike traditional business cards, Poken stores contact data in an online portal, making it easier to manage and search.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Shows its Curve in Pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</guid><description>Who says productivity can&amp;rsquo;t be stylish? Why not combine technology and beauty in the business world? It&amp;rsquo;s definitely possible!
The BlackBerry Curve 8330 Pink for Verizon Wireless is a perfect example. This device deserves a spot in a movie, maybe titled &amp;ldquo;Pretty in Pink&amp;rdquo;—although that title is already taken, it perfectly captures the essence of this phone. This classic BlackBerry delivers on productivity while boasting an elegant curved design and a lovely pink exterior.</description></item><item><title>Will Cell Phones Replace Laptop Computers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</guid><description>Laptops have taken over as the primary mobile work tool, but their days may be numbered. They are bulky, heavy, and require constant charging. A simple legal pad is starting to look more appealing in comparison. The search is on for a mobile device that offers the right balance of power and portability. Could the answer be cell phones?
The idea of an all-in-one cell phone is appealing because most people carry one anyway.</description></item><item><title>I Heard What You Wrote Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-heard-what-you-wrote-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-heard-what-you-wrote-last-summer/</guid><description>Ever been stuck in a class or meeting, diligently taking notes but unsure if you&amp;rsquo;re capturing everything accurately? Recording the session with a digital recorder alongside note-taking could help, but then syncing the audio and text becomes a nightmare. What if there was a single device that could automatically synchronize your notes and audio? Thankfully, there is!
The Livescribe Pulse(tm) smartpen records audio as you write. Yes, you read that right—you write, it records.</description></item><item><title>Can The Big Amazon Kindle DX Save The Newspapers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-big-amazon-kindle-dx-save-the-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 03:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-big-amazon-kindle-dx-save-the-newspapers/</guid><description>The recent debut of the larger Amazon Kindle DX has been hailed by some as a potential savior for the struggling newspaper industry. However, this nearly $500 device, while innovative, is unlikely to reverse the decline of print newspapers.
It&amp;rsquo;s simply too late and too expensive a solution for an industry facing dire financial straits. Had newspapers embraced electronic delivery methods a decade ago, the outcome might have been different. Now, many are on the brink of collapse, and technology alone cannot salvage them.</description></item><item><title>Red, Red, LG Vu Wine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 22:49:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</guid><description>Everyone enjoys a nice wine with dinner, but what about in business or on the go? It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly acceptable when that &amp;ldquo;wine&amp;rdquo; is the new touchscreen phone available from AT&amp;amp;T.
This &amp;ldquo;red wine&amp;rdquo; phone boasts more features than a full-bodied Cabernet. Its compact size of 4.3 x 2.1 x 0.5 inches makes it easy to carry in your pocket or bag. You read that correctly – this device is only half an inch thin!</description></item></channel></rss>