<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Immigration Detention on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/immigration-detention/</link><description>Recent content in Immigration Detention on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/immigration-detention/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice's initial decision on detaining asylum-seekers within the Dublin system and its implications for the rule of law in immigration detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</guid><description>Tommaso Poli, LL.M. candidate in Human Rights and Humanitarian Law at the University of Essex, School of Law.
The detention of those seeking asylum is a contentious issue within immigration law. While not initially covered by the European Common Asylum System (CEAS), it is now addressed in several of the second-phase CEAS measures. These measures include the Asylum Procedures Directive, the Reception Conditions Directive, the Qualification Directive, the Dublin Regulation, and the EURODAC Regulation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Europe's Immigration Detention: Uncovering the Truth - A Recent Study by the European Migration Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
In November, the European Migration Network (EMN) published a Focused Study entitled “The use of detention and alternatives to detention in the context of immigration policies.” The study is a synthesis report drawn from national reports from 26 countries, compiled by the EMN National Contact Points (NCPs)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Utilization of Prisons for Detaining Migrants in Europe and the EU Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, a researcher at the Global Detention Project and the Global Migration Centre, and a PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies in Geneva, examines a legal question: can immigration detainees be held in prisons alongside ordinary prisoners?
On July 17, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this question in its decisions regarding the combined cases of Bero and Bouzalmate and the separate case of Pham...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing Celaj and Vélez Loor: The implications of Latin American immigrants' detention in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</guid><description>Dr Andrea Romano, Research assistant, “Sapienza” University of Rome
Introduction
The recent Celaj judgment and its debatable connection to past rulings of the Court of Justice concerning the Returns Directive has been the subject of much discussion. This analysis will provide a concise comparison between this judgment and the Vélez Loor case, which was decided by the Inter-American Court of Human Rights (IACtHR) in 2010.
The Court of Justice of the European Union’s judgment in the Celaj case stemmed from various preliminary rulings brought forth by Italian judicial bodies regarding the Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comments on the outcomes of the most recent European Council meeting regarding EU migration policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU faces another crisis alongside &amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;: a surge in immigration. Initial EU responses culminated in an emergency summit in April. I previously discussed the outcomes of that summit. Subsequently, the Commission released its EU migration &amp;ldquo;Agenda&amp;rdquo; in mid-May, followed by detailed proposals. Last week, the European Council revisited immigration, reaching several conclusions. This post outlines those conclusions and offers my commentary. The third part of the conclusions, which vaguely promises increased cooperation with third countries, is omitted...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The decision in Celaj by the CJEU: Implications of criminal penalties, entry bans, and the Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</guid><description>By Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a decision on October 1, 2015, in the case of Skerdjan Celaj (C-290/14) that once again addressed the relationship between immigration and criminal law. Specifically, the court examined whether national criminal penalties for unlawful migration align with the EU Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-decision-in-celaj-by-the-cjeu-implications-of-criminal-penalties-entry-bans-and-the-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the judicial oversight of detention a misleading disruption?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III
Member of the Institut Universitaire de France
On June 5, 2014, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) issued a decision in the Mahdi case, providing further interpretation of the Return Directive. This directive, formally known as Directive 2008/115/EC, establishes common standards for EU Member States regarding the return of illegally staying third-country nationals. The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s judgment builds upon its prior rulings concerning this directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Migration in Europe and the Challenges of Insufficient Criminalization</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/</guid><description>By Amanda Spalding, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
Photo credit: Gzen92, via wikicommons media
Introduction
With a large influx of Ukrainian refugees into Europe, alongside policies like offshore asylum processing in Denmark and the UK, and increasing irregular entries reported by Frontex, the landscape of migration laws and policies is constantly shifting. Amidst these changes, it&amp;rsquo;s vital to examine the legal context, especially the human rights framework meant to safeguard individuals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/migration-in-europe-and-the-challenges-of-insufficient-criminalization/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is establishing procedural requirements in EU law the key to better safeguarding fundamental rights in migration?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/</guid><description>Opinion of Advocate General de la Tour in Joined Cases C, B (C‑704/20) and X (C‑39/21)
Alicja Słowik, Research Assistant, Centre for European Legal Studies (CEJE), University of Geneva
Photo credit: Abouttt, via Wikimedia commons
Finding a balance between a country&amp;rsquo;s right to manage its own legal processes and the need to protect rights granted by EU law has always been challenging for the European Court of Justice (ECJ or the Court)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-establishing-procedural-requirements-in-eu-law-the-key-to-better-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-in-migration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Imprison them: the suggestion to revise the EU's Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, established to manage irregular migration by non-EU citizens, mandates that Member States issue return decisions to unauthorized individuals and enforce their removal. While the Directive allows for voluntary departure periods, it also outlines rules for detention and entry bans. Initially considered lenient by migrant support groups, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has since interpreted the Directive more broadly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>