<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Freedom of Religion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freedom-of-religion/</link><description>Recent content in Freedom of Religion on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freedom-of-religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church).</description></item><item><title>Could Data Protection be Returning Home? The CJEU's Ruling on Data Protection Law in Relation to Jehovah's Witnesses and Political Canvassing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re showering when the doorbell unexpectedly interrupts. Hoping it&amp;rsquo;s the anticipated Amazon delivery with a birthday gift for your daughter, you rush downstairs, only to find a pair of Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witnesses.
After dismissing their pleas, you close the door, putting the encounter out of your mind. However, they haven&amp;rsquo;t forgotten you. To maintain their focus on potential converts, they keep records of visited homes, categorizing residents as &amp;ldquo;Believer,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Unbeliever,&amp;rdquo; or perhaps even &amp;ldquo;Satanist,&amp;rdquo; depending on your towel situation.</description></item><item><title>Balancing religious tolerance with freedom of expression in ECHR case law: Is there a right to insult?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights has reignited the debate about whether freedom of speech should have limitations, particularly when it comes to potentially offensive remarks targeting religious beliefs, such as those of the Muslim faith. This presents an opportunity to analyze the case&amp;rsquo;s background and determine what, if any, restrictions on free speech are justifiable in such instances.</description></item><item><title>Expanding the margin of appreciation: France's prohibition on public face-veiling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 05:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</guid><description>The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) has ruled on a highly anticipated case, SAS v France, concerning France&amp;rsquo;s 2010 law prohibiting face coverings in public. The case was brought by a French woman, represented by British lawyers, who argued that the law violated several articles of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), including the right to freedom of religion, expression, and association, as well as protection from discrimination.</description></item><item><title>Faith in action: the CJEU's decisions on headscarves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer, UCL Faculty of Laws and author of Religion and the Public Order of the Euorpean Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’ordre juridique de l’Union européenne (Bruylant 2013).
Nearly two decades after the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment was implemented, the Court of Justice issued its first significant decisions regarding workplace discrimination based on religion. These rulings placed the Court in a politically sensitive area, presenting considerable risk for an international judicial body like the CJEU.</description></item><item><title>What approach should the CJEU take in addressing religious discrimination in the workplace?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer at the Faculty of Laws at UCL and the author of Religion and the Public Order of the European Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’Ordre juridique de l’Union Europeenne (Bruylant 2013).
Recent weeks have seen two opinions from Advocates General of the Court of Justice of the European Union concerning religious expression in the workplace. This follows a period where religious issues were largely absent from Luxembourg case law.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides clarification on when employers can prohibit headscarves in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Ronan McCrea, University College London
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s initial significant decisions concerning workplace policies limiting religious symbols were issued four years ago in the G4S and Micropole cases. These rulings addressed the compatibility of these policies with the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment (Directive 2000/78).
In these decisions, the Court&amp;rsquo;s Grand Chamber determined that requiring employees to maintain visible religious neutrality constituted indirect rather than direct discrimination, provided this policy was uniformly applied to all religions or beliefs.</description></item></channel></rss>