<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Burstable Ds3 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/burstable-ds3/</link><description>Recent content in Burstable Ds3 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/burstable-ds3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Burstable Bandwidth Offers Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</guid><description>Most businesses purchase dedicated WAN bandwidth to support their voice and data services. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a more cost-effective option called burstable bandwidth.
Take business broadband service as an example. A dedicated DS3 connection provides a constant 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads. This full capacity is always available, whether you&amp;rsquo;re sending a large file or backing up data. When not fully utilized, the line remains idle.
The recent drop in DS3 prices has made it a common choice for medium to large businesses.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Deals for MSPs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</guid><description>Managed Service Providers (MSPs) can provide more value to their clients by helping them find better deals on WAN bandwidth, in addition to their existing IT services. Many companies are unaware of the changes in the telecommunications market and the cheaper options now available.
A basic bandwidth service that businesses should consider is T1, which offers reliable voice and/or data services with a service level agreement. T1 prices have significantly decreased this decade, often by 50% or even 67%.</description></item></channel></rss>