<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DBS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dbs/</link><description>Recent content in DBS on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises and consumers will reap the rewards as banks increase their focus on innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</guid><description>Several financial institutions in the Asia Pacific region were honored at the Asian Financial Services (AFS) Congress 2014 in Singapore for their innovative banking solutions.
AllianceBank Malaysia received the &amp;ldquo;Asia&amp;rsquo;s Most Customer Friendly Bank&amp;rdquo; award for its BizSmart Academy initiative, which supports young SMEs through business education, coaching, and seed funding. The program is open to both existing and new customers.
The bank provides participants with a year-long curriculum covering management, business, and finance topics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DBS Marina Regatta is filled with exciting activities spread out over two weekends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest water sports festival, the DBS Marina Regatta, returns for its fifth year with an expanded format spanning two weekends, May 28-29 and June 4-5. The event, which drew over 24,000 attendees last year, will feature regional dragon boat races set against the Marina Bay skyline, the return of Singapore’s only pop-up urban beach, and the debut of Southeast Asia’s tallest inflatable water slide.
This year&amp;rsquo;s regatta will premiere several new features, including themed dragon boat races and competitive kayak races...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore residents are being targeted by a phone-based phishing campaign, according to DBS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</guid><description>DBS Bank has issued a warning to residents of Singapore about a phishing scam making use of automated phone calls. Given their customer base of over 4 million in Singapore alone, it is highly likely that scammers will connect with a DBS account holder.
The scam, as reported on the DBS website, begins with an automated voice message in either English or Mandarin. The recipient is told they have an urgent message from DBS Bank and instructed to press either &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS introduces the first mobile-only bank in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</guid><description>Source: DBS. From left: Sachin Tendulkar, Cricketer, digor
the digibank mascot, DBS CEO Piyush Gupta.
Introducing a pioneering Virtual Assistant powered by artificial intelligence. Account creation utilizes Aadhaar, the largest biometric identification system globally. DBS Bank, headquartered in Singapore and a prominent financial institution in Asia, has introduced digibank, India&amp;rsquo;s inaugural mobile-centric bank. This innovative banking platform harnesses advanced technologies, including biometrics and artificial intelligence (AI), to offer customers a novel banking experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS launches improved paternity leave program in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-launches-improved-paternity-leave-program-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 01:19:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-launches-improved-paternity-leave-program-in-singapore/</guid><description>DBS Bank will enhance its paternity leave policy in Singapore, following Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong&amp;rsquo;s call to extend such leave during the National Day Rally on August 23. This new policy, announced on August 26, allows fathers employed by the bank to take two weeks of paternity leave, retroactive to January 2015.
Cheong Meng Foong, DBS Group Head of Rewards, emphasized the bank&amp;rsquo;s commitment to its employees&amp;rsquo; well-being: &amp;ldquo;At DBS, people are our most important resource, and we consistently seek to support them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-launches-improved-paternity-leave-program-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-launches-improved-paternity-leave-program-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS introduces an integrated health management portal to assist employees in maintaining their well-being</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/</guid><description>Source: DBS. To introduce iHealth@DBS, DBS Asia Hub employees were encouraged to participate in a large group workout.
DBS Bank introduced iHealth@DBS, a comprehensive health management platform, to further cultivate a culture of well-being for its employees. The goal of this centralized platform is to promote lasting behavioral changes among staff. This will be achieved through interactive engagement on digital platforms, including mobile devices and wearable technology.
iHealth@DBS is the newest addition to a comprehensive package of wellness benefits offered to DBS employees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-an-integrated-health-management-portal-to-assist-employees-in-maintaining-their-well-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>