<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MEF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mef/</link><description>Recent content in MEF on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Business-grade Carrier Ethernet services are gaining popularity. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about Ethernet and its potential benefits, read on.
Ethernet dominates as a LAN protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable how quickly it outpaced competitors. Switched Ethernet is nearly ubiquitous. A similar shift is happening with telecom services, moving from traditional circuit-switched technologies to packet-switched networks that align better with modern devices. Ethernet is poised to become the standard for both metropolitan and long-distance networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>As companies increasingly adopt cloud services and engage in data-heavy activities like video streaming and big data analysis, the demand for greater WAN bandwidth is on the rise. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming commonplace to see requests for 1,000 Mbps connections, often fulfilled by a 1 Gbps Ethernet or GigE point-to-point connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the details and available choices for Gigabit Ethernet service.
Ethernet, the standard protocol for LANs, commonly operates at speeds of 10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1,000 Mbps, or 10 Gbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>