<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UKIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ukip/</link><description>Recent content in UKIP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 08:12:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ukip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it appropriate to question the credibility of research conducted by academics whose institutions receive funding from the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 08:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-to-question-the-credibility-of-research-conducted-by-academics-whose-institutions-receive-funding-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Some Eurosceptics suggest that research should be disregarded if the academics involved or their institutions have received EU funding, especially if that research contradicts Eurosceptic viewpoints. This tactic has been used against both recent research on the positive impacts of free movement of EU citizens and me personally. While it&amp;rsquo;s tempting to ignore these accusations, they are frequently used to discredit objective evidence supporting pro-European arguments, particularly in the context of a potential referendum on British exit from the EU.</description></item><item><title>Has UKIP completely lost its sense of humor? Another satirical story...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-ukip-completely-lost-its-sense-of-humor-another-satirical-story/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:21:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-ukip-completely-lost-its-sense-of-humor-another-satirical-story/</guid><description>By Sabine Jacques
PhD student focussing on the parody exception at the School of Law, University of Nottingham (UK)
Introduction
In September 2014, Mike Dicks created a Twitter account called ‘UKIP Trumpton’. The account bio stated ‘After the recent defection of the Mayor of Trumpton and Mr Troop the town clerk this is the new home of UKIP tweets from Trumptonshire’ and used the official UKIP logo. Dicks later explained that the account was meant to gently mock UKIP, drawing a parallel between the party&amp;rsquo;s vision and the classic children&amp;rsquo;s show &amp;ldquo;Trumpton,&amp;rdquo; which lacked diversity.</description></item><item><title>Is Nigel Farage's claim that the EU's asylum policies will allow in half a million terrorists accurate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, the UK Independence Party leader, recently asserted that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s response to the migrant crisis could unintentionally allow a large number of terrorists into the EU. He bases this on the threat by ISIS to use smuggling routes to infiltrate the EU and urges David Cameron to block the EU&amp;rsquo;s plans.
These claims lack merit. The EU&amp;rsquo;s approach essentially maintains the existing situation. The current maritime surveillance efforts, while being expanded, may not become full-scale rescue missions.</description></item></channel></rss>