<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/visas/</link><description>Recent content in Visas on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:56:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/visas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An important Irish ruling on compensation for violation of EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) affirmed the right of individuals to sue Member States for damages resulting from breaches of EU law over two decades ago in the Francovich case, most subsequent lawsuits have been initiated by businesses seeking compensation for financial losses. The CJEU has yet to address a case involving damages claims related to the free movement of EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are potential asylum-seekers entitled to a Schengen visa?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
In a recent decision concerning the Koushkaki case, the Court of Justice provided clarity on applying for a Schengen visa. The court effectively ruled that individuals have a right to a visa if they fulfill the established requirements. However, this decision also implicitly raises questions about denying visa applications from potential asylum-seekers.
The judgment
Mr. Koushkaki, an Iranian citizen residing in Iran, applied for a Schengen visa to visit Germany but was denied due to insufficient proof of financial support for his stay and return...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are the new proposals for simplifying Schengen visa applications for third-country national family members of EU citizens comprehensive enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU citizens with family members who are non-EU citizens often face obstacles to free movement, especially when those family members are from Asia, Africa, or the Caribbean. Traveling outside of the Schengen area with these family members often requires obtaining visas, adding complexity to their trips.
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent proposals on visas, if adopted, could bring some relief. One proposal focuses on revising the existing &amp;ldquo;Schengen visa&amp;rdquo; rules, which permit travel across Schengen countries for three months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's new law on travel authorization for non-EU citizens creating a brave new world?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A new European Union (EU) law regarding travel authorization for non-EU citizens visiting the EU was recently announced. This new law will impact millions of travelers annually, potentially including British citizens post-Brexit. This law, though not immediately applicable, holds significant future implications. This explanation aims to clarify its reach and functionality. (Update: the final law was officially published in September 2018).
Basics of the system..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the European Union a cause worth sacrificing for? Contemplating the future of Ukraine and the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</guid><description>There were many reasons to criticize the Yanukovych government in Ukraine, but the protests that led to its downfall were sparked by Yanukovych&amp;rsquo;s refusal to sign an agreement with the European Union. This strong desire for EU membership among some Ukrainians raises important questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s future.
The first steps after the planned elections would be straightforward. A pro-European government would likely ratify the association agreement, which connects Ukraine to EU law more closely than previous agreements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Farewell, harsh world: will there be visas for holidays post-Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Previously, I maintained that British citizens needing visas for short trips to the EU after Brexit was highly unlikely. I even disagreed with some &amp;ldquo;Remain&amp;rdquo; supporters who feared this outcome. The EU consistently lifts short-term visa requirements for wealthy nations (like the USA, Canada, and Japan) if they reciprocate for EU citizens. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t envision those on the &amp;ldquo;Leave&amp;rdquo; side supporting short-term visa requirements for EU citizens visiting the UK post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-harsh-world-will-there-be-visas-for-holidays-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Updating the visa policy of the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
In 2014, the European Commission put forward a proposal to update the EU&amp;rsquo;s visa policy for short-term visits by revising the existing Visa Code. This proposal ultimately stalled due to disagreements between the European Parliament and the Council on whether or not to incorporate &amp;ldquo;safe passage&amp;rdquo; visas for individuals requiring protection. Currently, the Commission is revisiting this issue, this time prioritizing security concerns rather than economic benefits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/updating-the-visa-policy-of-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>