<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Demand on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-demand/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Demand on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-demand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Video Kill The Internet Star?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</guid><description>The considerable growth of online video streaming and downloads has positioned them as the primary bandwidth consumers on the internet today. This begs the question: will the rapid proliferation of video packets lead to internet congestion, similar to traffic jams on physical highways?
Video content follows the same trajectory as previous &amp;ldquo;killer apps&amp;rdquo; such as email, web browsing, instant messaging, blogging, and social networking. These applications all began with a small user base, expanded quickly, and eventually became mainstream...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>