<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Speed on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-speed/</link><description>Recent content in Network Speed on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-speed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet DS3 Bandwidth Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has grown continuously since T1 lines became the norm for dedicated internet access and private point-to-point connections. If you currently use DS3 bandwidth services or are thinking about an upgrade, comparing your wide area network (WAN) bandwidth choices is essential.
DS3, a 45 Mbps service, represents the traditional high-bandwidth network connection and is equivalent in speed to a T3 line. These days, most DS3 services are delivered via fiber optic cables, with a copper handoff point at the demarcation point.</description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing.</description></item><item><title>Copper First, Then Fiber Bandwidth Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</guid><description>When your business needs a fast internet connection but fiber optic installation isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible yet, there&amp;rsquo;s a two-step solution that uses existing technology as a stopgap. This method combines the strengths of different connection types to get you online quickly and upgrade seamlessly later on.
Fiber optic connections, whether SONET or Ethernet, provide the highest bandwidth– starting from 50-100 Mbps and reaching up to 10 Gbps or even higher in some areas.</description></item></channel></rss>