<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Movement Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-law/</link><description>Recent content in Free Movement Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?</description></item><item><title>'Although you have children together, your marriage is not genuine': Marriages of convenience, UK courts, and EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/although-you-have-children-together-your-marriage-is-not-genuine-marriages-of-convenience-uk-courts-and-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Aleksandra Jolkina, PhD in Law, Queen Mary University of London
Over the last twenty years, UK authorities have become increasingly wary of marriages within the UK between mobile EU citizens and third-country nationals (TCNs) with uncertain or irregular residence status. In the current climate of Euroscepticism, such marriages are often criticized as &amp;ldquo;marriages of convenience,&amp;rdquo; intended to circumvent British immigration laws. This piece examines how UK courts interpret the concept of marriages of convenience, the potential implications for families of EU citizens residing in the UK, and the anticipated changes after Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 4 of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement focuses on the rights of citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-the-rights-of-citizens/</guid><description>This blog post examines the rights of UK and EU citizens after Brexit, focusing on the revised withdrawal agreement. This agreement aims to protect the rights of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 who moved before the transition period ended (end of 2020, possibly extendable).
The agreement safeguards these individuals better than a &amp;ldquo;no deal&amp;rdquo; scenario, where national law would primarily apply. However, it offers less protection than continued EU membership.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Complex Legal Issues from a Legal Standpoint with Partiality and Passion, or The European Union's Approval of the Istanbul Convention: Jurisdiction, Foundations, and Consensus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - @CateBriddick*
On March 11, 2021, Advocate General Hogan of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) presented his legal opinion on the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s inquiry regarding the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) potential membership in the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Istanbul Convention).</description></item><item><title>A Last-Minute Update: The CJEU has finally ruled that the NHS qualifies as a provider of 'comprehensive sickness insurance'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-last-minute-update-the-cjeu-has-finally-ruled-that-the-nhs-qualifies-as-a-provider-of-comprehensive-sickness-insurance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 01:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-last-minute-update-the-cjeu-has-finally-ruled-that-the-nhs-qualifies-as-a-provider-of-comprehensive-sickness-insurance/</guid><description>Dr Sylvia de Mars, Newcastle University*
* With many thanks to Prof Charlotte O’Brien for all the idea-swapping that preceded this blog post.
Background
A key question regarding EU nationals&amp;rsquo; rights to reside in the UK from at least 2011 onwards has been whether the NHS constitutes &amp;lsquo;comprehensive sickness insurance&amp;rsquo; (CSI). This requirement stemmed from Article 7(1)(b) of Directive 2004/38 (the ‘Citizenship Directive’), which stipulated that economically inactive EU citizens could only reside beyond three months in another Member State if they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t burden the host country&amp;rsquo;s social assistance system and possessed CSI.</description></item><item><title>The case of V.M.A. v Stolichna obshtina, rayon 'Pancharevo' and the rights of rainbow families to freedom of movement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 06:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obshtina-rayon-pancharevo-and-the-rights-of-rainbow-families-to-freedom-of-movement/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Linguist agent at the European Commission and honorary fellow European Union law at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Introduction
Advocate General Juliane Kokott, in her opinion, highlights the unfair burden placed on children of same-sex couples due to differing societal values among EU member states.</description></item></channel></rss>