<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Map on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/map/</link><description>Recent content in Map on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/map/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>World Heritage Map now for sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 01:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</guid><description>Source: UNESCO website.
The UNESCO World Heritage Centre and National Geographic Maps have released the most recent edition of the World Heritage map. This project received generous support from Turkey, and the map can be purchased on the World Heritage Centre website.
The map features an image of Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Historic Areas of Istanbul, the location of the next World Heritage Committee meeting in July 2016.
The poster-sized map displays all 1,031 World Heritage sites, along with pictures and detailed captions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>