<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Protocol on Charter on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protocol-on-charter/</link><description>Recent content in Protocol on Charter on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:45:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protocol-on-charter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU Charter of Rights post Conservative party amendments to UK human rights legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-charter-of-rights-post-conservative-party-amendments-to-uk-human-rights-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many drivers have encountered the unfortunate experience of hitting a small animal that darted across the road at the wrong moment. Reactions vary from distress to indifference, but some feel a sense of triumph, having removed an obstacle from their path.
This last reaction mirrors the Conservative party&amp;rsquo;s stance on EU law within their UK human rights law reform proposals. They aim to diminish EU law&amp;rsquo;s influence, much like a driver indifferent to roadkill.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Appeal ruling in Benkharbouche and Janah: State immunity, remedies, and rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Benkharbouche v Sudan and Janah v Libya delves into significant aspects of public international law, the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, highlighting their interplay within the current British constitutional framework. The cases involved employment law claims brought by two domestic workers against the Sudanese and Libyan embassies, respectively. The embassies invoked state immunity under a UK law based on a Council of Europe Convention.</description></item></channel></rss>