<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>201612KMBC9000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/201612kmbc9000/</link><description>Recent content in 201612KMBC9000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:30:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/201612kmbc9000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors/</guid><description>With 2017 underway and the festivities behind us, it&amp;rsquo;s time to resume the Beocord 9000 restoration. I began by replacing the electrolytic capacitors. As I&amp;rsquo;ve noted before, these Beocord 9000 units often require minimal recapping, if any. This particular unit seems to have been stored for a considerable period, and I already discovered one faulty capacitor, prompting me to replace the others.
My usual practice is to use audio-grade capacitors in the signal path and opt for high-reliability, 105°C rated, long-lasting capacitors elsewhere.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Power Supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-power-supply/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 11:40:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-power-supply/</guid><description>I began troubleshooting the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s electrical issues by examining the power supply. The power supply wasn&amp;rsquo;t functioning correctly, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t getting +24 VDC at capacitor C1. Initially, I suspected the rectifier board, so I removed it to inspect the supply capacitors (C1, C2, and C3).
Here are the readings for capacitors C1 through C3.
To further diagnose the problem, I swapped components from other Beocord 9000 units I had available.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Finishing Up The Tape Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-finishing-up-the-tape-transport/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-finishing-up-the-tape-transport/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 tape transport is now fixed and reassembled. Cleaning and lubrication were done on all moving parts, including the thrust roller assembly, even though it wasn&amp;rsquo;t being replaced.
The reassembly process involved reinstalling several components, starting with the take-up and supply reel assembly.
Next, the clutch, interconnecting mechanics, flywheel, belts, cassette holder, and opening damper assembly were put back in place.
To test the restored transport before installing it in the Beocord 9000, it was temporarily swapped into a different Beocord 9000.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Opening It Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-opening-it-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:49:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-opening-it-up/</guid><description>Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen audio devices from the early 1980s are great to repair because their components are easily accessible for service and inspection.
One of the first things to examine on Beocord 8000 through 9000 series cassette decks is the tape transport mechanism. While replacing the belts is part of regular maintenance, there are other mechanical aspects to address.
Upon opening this Beocord 9000, I immediately noticed a small broken part.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: The Tape Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-the-tape-transport/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-the-tape-transport/</guid><description>After cleaning the belt residue, the tape transport needs to be removed for disassembly. Three screws and four connectors need to be detached to free the tape transport. The image shows the Beocord tape transport ready for restoration.
The next stage involves taking the tape transport apart to clean, lubricate, and repair it, including replacing any worn rubber wheels.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: A Christmas Holiday Restoration Project</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-a-christmas-holiday-restoration-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-a-christmas-holiday-restoration-project/</guid><description>The holiday season provides me with the opportunity to work on extra audio restoration projects. A Beolover blog inspired this documentation of a Beocord 9000 restoration. Following this project is a Beomaster 8000, as the owner wants both devices in working order.
The Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s exterior is in excellent condition, except for minor damage to the rosewood veneer on the left corner.</description></item><item><title> Beomaster 8000: Ready for Some Bench Testing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-ready-for-some-bench-testing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-ready-for-some-bench-testing/</guid><description>After powering up the Beomaster and confirming its audio quality with an iPod and FM radio, I began the reassembly process. However, the remote control wasn&amp;rsquo;t working. Troubleshooting this will require investigating the power supply board, which houses the remote control receiver. For now, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to proceed with bench testing.
My initial test involved connecting the Beomaster to a previously restored Beocord 9000 using a DIN cable. The Beocord&amp;rsquo;s play button activated the Beomaster&amp;rsquo;s TP1 play mode, and the Beomaster&amp;rsquo;s standby button turned off both devices, confirming proper communication.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Pulse Found...Beocord has life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-pulse-foundbeocord-has-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 16:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-pulse-foundbeocord-has-life/</guid><description>My examination of the Beocord power system continued with the regulator and power supply boards.
The regulator board houses the +5 VDC and ±15 VDC regulators, all situated on the large rear heatsink. I always inspect the heatsink compound and mica insulators for dryness, and thankfully, this Beocord appears to be in good condition.
I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered instances where these components showed deterioration, but not in this case.
With the regulator board cleared, I shifted focus to the power supply board&amp;rsquo;s voltages.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Ready for Bench Testing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-ready-for-bench-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-ready-for-bench-testing/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I finished the seven-segment display repair. The LEDs performed without issue during a 24-hour burn-in test. I double-checked the LEDs after reassembling the display using my specialized test equipment. My test setup has two parts for evaluating the Beocord display. The left side tests all LEDs illuminated simultaneously, while the right side allows me to test each LED channel or individual LED by adjusting jumpers.
During individual LED testing, I observed some light bleed from the middle &amp;ldquo;dot&amp;rdquo; LEDs into the neighboring segments.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Seven Segment Display Board Reworked</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-seven-segment-display-board-reworked/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-seven-segment-display-board-reworked/</guid><description>Setting up the Beosystem display board rework station took a bit longer than anticipated, but it&amp;rsquo;s finally ready for LED display repairs and testing. A working Beocord display helped confirm the test setup&amp;rsquo;s functionality.
The display board, with its front and back sides visible, now features markings indicating segment numbers and polarities.
Thirty-one LEDs comprise the display. The image provides a close-up view of the original LED lights.
Here, the original LED is juxtaposed with the replacement SMD LED.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Displays and Lamps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-displays-and-lamps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 20:56:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-displays-and-lamps/</guid><description>This Beocord 9000 project was on hold until new Beolover displays arrived. In the meantime, basic functionality was confirmed - the Beocord can record and play cassettes. With the displays here, the next steps are to install them, conduct thorough cassette operation tests, and share the outcome.
The display work can be done without removing the Microcomputer and Display board. This image provides a top view of the display setup, highlighting the PPM scale lamp.</description></item><item><title> Beomaster 8000: Updating the Displays - Completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-updating-the-displays-completed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:44:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-updating-the-displays-completed/</guid><description>I successfully replaced a set of Beomaster 8000 display LEDs with SMD LEDs today. This set was in dire need of repair due to numerous malfunctioning display segments.
Initially, I attempted to use my SMD work station for this task, hoping to refine the method I used for the Beocord 9000 display restoration, which had worked well. However, the SMD work station technique proved less effective this time, requiring more rework and resulting in wasted SMD LEDs.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing Capacitors Wrapped Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors-wrapped-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 16:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-capacitors-wrapped-up/</guid><description>The capacitor replacement on the Beocord 9000 cassette deck is complete, although it took a bit longer than anticipated. While most capacitors were within specification, a few were not, including two that had completely failed. Notably, a 220uF capacitor (C56) on the Microcomputer/Display board was the culprit behind the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inability to power on. Another failed 220uF capacitor (C7) of the same brand was discovered on the Dolby board. This highlights the importance of checking all electrolytic capacitors in such situations.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Belt Deterioration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-belt-deterioration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 13:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-belt-deterioration/</guid><description>Replacing rubber belts is a standard restoration procedure for old audio equipment. However, Beocord 8000 and 9000 tape decks often require an extra step: cleaning up the mess left behind by deteriorated belts.
Most Beocords I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered have belts degraded into a sticky, gooey substance, probably due to prolonged storage in warm conditions. Like cars, these devices suffer from lack of regular use.
This picture shows the residue found in this Beocord, a common sight.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Identifying Repairs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-identifying-repairs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-identifying-repairs/</guid><description>Taking apart the tape transport allows for thorough cleaning and reveals hidden areas that require attention. While this approach makes sense for restoration, disassembling most of the transport is necessary anyway for replacing the rubber wheels.
NOTE: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to avoid disturbing the tape head assembly. It&amp;rsquo;s likely still properly aligned, or very close to it. Unless you&amp;rsquo;re certain they&amp;rsquo;re faulty, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to remove the tape heads at this stage.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Reassembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-reassembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 06:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-reassembly/</guid><description>After recapping, cleaning, and maintenance, today was the day to begin reassembling the Beocord. Starting with an empty shell, the process began. While this Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen model has some unique disassembly quirks, the internal components are readily accessible.
The reassembly process mirrored the disassembly: the last boards removed were the first ones back in.
A complete reassembly wasn&amp;rsquo;t done at this stage as the displays still needed work. Removing the transformer simplified moving and positioning the Beocord due to the reduced weight.</description></item></channel></rss>