<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TV on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tv/</link><description>Recent content in TV on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guvera introduces support for Apple TV and updates its product</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</guid><description>Source: Guvera.
Guvera, a music streaming service supported by brand funding, has announced significant upgrades to its product and compatibility with Apple TV.
The updated Guvera 3.0 app introduces music channels and a variety of new editorial features. These include artist interviews, news articles, reviews, photo galleries, brand competitions, and product promotions.
Hazel Savage, Head of Marketing and Operations for Guvera Asia, stated that the company recognizes that music is more than just individual tracks; it represents a whole culture and way of life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In January, StarHub will be featuring high-definition Korean movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</guid><description>StarHub TV customers will be the first in Asia to enjoy the latest and greatest Korean films in high definition (HD), 24 hours a day. The company announced that tvN Movies HD, Asia’s first channel dedicated to Korean films, will launch on StarHub TV (channel 818) on January 11, 2017. For added convenience, the channel will also be available on demand as tvN Movies VOD HD. Customers can watch it anytime on StarHub TV Channel 819, or stream it via StarHub Go, StarHub&amp;rsquo;s online streaming service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the hallyu wave with Viator tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</guid><description>Viator, a popular tour booking platform, has noticed a surge in demand for tours featuring filming locations from the hit Korean drama &amp;ldquo;Descendants of the Sun.&amp;rdquo;
Besides tours to Greece, Viator offers the &amp;ldquo;Yongin MBC Dramia TV Set Tour&amp;rdquo; in Korea. This half-day tour takes fans behind the scenes at Yongin MBC TV studios, showcasing sets used in Korea&amp;rsquo;s most popular historical dramas.
For K-drama music enthusiasts, Viator has curated the &amp;ldquo;K Pop Tour&amp;rdquo; in Seoul...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HALCYON VR murder mystery from Syfy will soon be accessible on the Samsung Gear VR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</guid><description>Source: Syfy. HALCYON investigates a VR murder.
Syfy, known for its imaginative entertainment, will debut its unique hybrid virtual reality (VR) series, HALCYON, on September 22nd at 10 pm. The series is a creation of Secret Location, a multi-award-winning content studio specializing in cutting-edge platforms.
Set in 2040, HALCYON centers on Julie Dover, a detective in the Virtual Reality Crimes Unit. She tackles the first-ever murder within virtual reality, a seemingly impossible crime, and unravels the hidden conspiracy behind it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IndianMoney.com is creating additional financial education content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</guid><description>IndianMoney.com, a leading financial education company in India, partnered with Kannada news channel Suddi TV to create Money Maathu (Money Talk), an educational series about personal finance. The series features short episodes, typically eight to ten minutes long, that cover a wide range of financial topics. With 35 episodes already released, the goal is to empower viewers with the knowledge to make informed financial choices.
CS Sudheer, founder and CEO of IndianMoney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV set top boxes will now include the Netflix app for seamless integration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</guid><description>Singtel is integrating the Netflix app into their TV set-top boxes. This means customers can easily access Netflix content directly on their TVs.
Subscribers with set-top boxes connected to Singtel Fibre Broadband can find Netflix on Channel 404 or by using the Quick Access Button on their remote. This feature will be rolled out gradually and should be available to all customers by the end of April.
Through an exclusive partnership, Singtel is offering customers up to nine free months of Netflix when they re-contract or sign up for eligible mobile, fiber broadband, and Singtel TV plans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultra-HD 4K L9450 Pro Theatre TVs from Toshiba are suitable for both living rooms and boardrooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultra-hd-4k-l9450-pro-theatre-tvs-from-toshiba-are-suitable-for-both-living-rooms-and-boardrooms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultra-hd-4k-l9450-pro-theatre-tvs-from-toshiba-are-suitable-for-both-living-rooms-and-boardrooms/</guid><description>Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s new Ultra-HD 4K L9450 series, featuring Android Pro Theatre TVs, blends exceptional picture quality with a wide array of downloadable Android apps from Google Play.
These TVs double as computer monitors, making them ideal for business conference rooms. With the convenience of Android apps, presentations can be downloaded directly to the TV&amp;rsquo;s memory and displayed on screen, eliminating the need for separate presentation equipment. Additionally, wireless mice, keyboards, and gamepads can be used for control, supplementing the standard remote*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultra-hd-4k-l9450-pro-theatre-tvs-from-toshiba-are-suitable-for-both-living-rooms-and-boardrooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultra-hd-4k-l9450-pro-theatre-tvs-from-toshiba-are-suitable-for-both-living-rooms-and-boardrooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The B8S 4K OLED TV has been launched by LG Electronics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-b8s-4k-oled-tv-has-been-launched-by-lg-electronics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-b8s-4k-oled-tv-has-been-launched-by-lg-electronics/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s New B8S 4K OLED TV Offers High-End Features at an Accessible Price LG Electronics, a top OLED TV brand, is strengthening its market position with the new LG B8S 4K OLED TV. This Korean-made TV joins the 2018 4K OLED lineup, boasting impressive features like the α (Alpha) 7 processor, 4K Cinema HDR, and LG&amp;rsquo;s ThinQ Artificial Intelligence (AI).
The α7 processor delivers lifelike images characterized by rich colors, sharp details, and impressive depth, enhancing realism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-b8s-4k-oled-tv-has-been-launched-by-lg-electronics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-b8s-4k-oled-tv-has-been-launched-by-lg-electronics/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celcom users now have the option to subscribe to iflix</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</guid><description>iflix, a Southeast Asian internet TV provider, has teamed up with Malaysian mobile network operator Celcom Axiata to offer TV series, movies, and other content to Celcom&amp;rsquo;s over 12 million subscribers in Malaysia.
Starting March 15, 2016, all Celcom subscribers will get two free months of iflix, allowing them to stream content seamlessly on Celcom&amp;rsquo;s 4G network (a value of RM20). After the two-month promotional period, customers can continue enjoying iflix for a discounted rate of RM9 per month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fans in Singapore of Song Seung Heon may have the opportunity to meet him</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for Saimdang featuring Song.
To kick off the new year, Singtel is bringing South Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon to Singapore on January 7, 2017. Song&amp;rsquo;s visit will promote the drama Saimdang (师任堂), which premieres on Singtel TV&amp;rsquo;s Oh!K channel (channel 525/611) on January 25, 2017, at 9 pm.
Singtel TV subscribers can enter to win 20 pairs of tickets to a meet-and-greet and autograph session with Song...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing a football package that includes both Copa America and UEFA Euro 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 12:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Singtel will broadcast the Copa America Centenario USA 2016. This competition is the oldest international tournament for nations in the Americas and features top players like Alexis Sanchez, Lionel Messi, and Luis Suárez. This year, for the first time, the tournament will be hosted outside of South America.
Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director, Home, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, stated that combining Copa America 2016 and UEFA Euro 2016 broadcasts allows Singtel to provide fans with two of the most exciting football events globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-a-football-package-that-includes-both-copa-america-and-uefa-euro-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you ask LG ThinQ AI TVs, Google Assistant will respond</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</guid><description>LG Electronics has integrated the recently launched Google Assistant into their OLED and SUPER UHD TVs.
This feature, available on all LG ThinQ AI TV models, enables users to search for information, check weather forecasts, and more using voice commands, all without interrupting their TV viewing.
Previously, voice commands were limited to basic functions like changing channels or adjusting volume. Now, users can search for specific content using the TV remote, for example, &amp;ldquo;show me romantic comedy movies on Netflix&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;show me yoga videos&amp;rdquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HOOQ is launching new original content produced by Globe Studios</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 10:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</guid><description>Globe Studios and HOOQ are launching the first episode of their original series, &amp;ldquo;OTJ: The Missing 8,&amp;rdquo; in early 2017. This series promises a cinematic experience that&amp;rsquo;s different from typical television, mirroring the gritty and fast-paced style of the original movie, which premiered at the 2013 Cannes Film Festival. This six-part series, based on Erik Matti&amp;rsquo;s award-winning film &amp;ldquo;OTJ&amp;rdquo; (or &amp;ldquo;On The Job&amp;rdquo;), is the first major production made specifically for an online video service in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson reveals insights on video consumption habits of consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Looking for effective ways to invest your marketing budget? The recent Ericsson ConsumerLab TV &amp;amp; Media Report might offer some valuable insights.
Now in its fifth year, the study surveyed 1,000 individuals in Singapore for the first time. The results reveal that 80% of Singaporeans engage in streaming TV or video content at least once a week, while 72% continue to watch traditional broadcast programs. Globally, 75% of consumers stream content multiple times weekly, compared to 77% who watch scheduled broadcast TV programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>