<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Server on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/server/</link><description>Recent content in Server on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:45:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VyprVPN from Golden Frog now includes a server in Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Golden Frog, a company dedicated to online privacy and internet accessibility, has expanded its services to India. This new server, located in Mumbai, marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 14th in Asia and aims to provide Indian internet users with a secure and unrestricted online experience through their VyprVPN service.
&amp;ldquo;India, with its vast population and rapidly growing tech sector, will benefit greatly from this new server location,&amp;rdquo; says Sunday Yokubaitis, President of Golden Frog.</description></item><item><title>HP creates servers specifically for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced new ProLiant Gen9 Tower servers to its Compute portfolio. These servers are designed to give small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) a cost-effective solution with a good mix of performance, efficiency, and manageability.
These servers are designed to handle a variety of general-purpose workloads and critical applications, including IT infrastructure, collaboration, web, and business applications. This support is intended to meet both current and future business needs.
“Small businesses must not only address immediate business challenges but also establish a foundation for rapid business expansion,” stated Peter Schrady, VP and GM of Rack and Tower Servers at HP.</description></item></channel></rss>