<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Transformation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-transformation/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Transformation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Metro and Long Haul Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies with multiple locations and many employees may find that standard internet and private lines are insufficient for their needs. At a certain point, having complete control over your network becomes desirable, allowing you to establish performance benchmarks and implement upgrades as needed.
This sounds great, but how can you maintain the same level of control over a network that extends beyond your physical premises? Should you become your own network provider and install fiber optic cable to all your locations?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>