<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airlines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airlines/</link><description>Recent content in Airlines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Internet to Soothe the Savage Flyer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</guid><description>Is there anything more frustrating than squeezing into the last seat on a long flight, stuck between grumpy passengers with hours to kill? You yearn for the distraction of emails or online games, but alas, internet access in the air seems like a distant dream.
Fear not, weary traveler! The wait for in-flight WiFi is almost over. Major airlines are preparing to offer internet access on their planes, but it comes at a price.</description></item><item><title>A trial for FAST check-in has been introduced by Changi Airport, Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</guid><description>A new Fast and Seamless Travel (FAST) check-in trial is currently underway at Changi Airport Terminal 2 for passengers flying with Singapore Airlines and SilkAir. This collaborative effort between Changi Airport Group (CAG), Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir will gradually introduce a comprehensive suite of FAST options throughout 2016. These options aim to provide passengers with more check-in choices and potentially faster processing times through automated kiosks and bag drops. Terminal 3 will also see the addition of 24 kiosks.</description></item><item><title>Shangri-La and Singapore Airlines campaign offers packaged deals for ASEAN destinations and hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shangri-la-and-singapore-airlines-campaign-offers-packaged-deals-for-asean-destinations-and-hotels/</guid><description>To commemorate the 50th anniversary of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts and Singapore Airlines have teamed up to launch a travel campaign called &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore.&amp;rdquo;
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjJuZK2IwJjPxRmvmq0DT-MS7ZPDl5douabN-yaRNI7kSFX1RAg5n8m2LHrg030pnJcr68_qz-IujmANOlf3NTbWGRF887wfkPbFQPAn168XsbqGeH8wP90CW2_M3muXU8ABKS6E9PwtOA/s1600/Shangri+La+SIA+ASEAN+is+More.JPG)
Source: Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts. Banner for the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN Is More - First Stop Singapore&amp;rdquo; campaign.
This campaign highlights Southeast Asia as a travel destination through special offers on curated leisure trips. Flight and hotel packages are available for various properties in Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Myanmar, and Thailand, including Shangri-La hotels and resorts, Hotel Jen properties, and Traders Hotel, Kuala Lumpur.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers.</description></item><item><title>Ghost Routers In The Sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wireless internet access on airplanes is becoming a reality. Although it had a slow start, major airlines like American, Delta, Northwest, and Virgin are now embracing in-flight Wi-Fi.
This shift is inevitable in a society increasingly reliant on technology. We might be giving up old habits, but staying connected online is non-negotiable. Just like hotels and restaurants adapted to this need, airlines are following suit. Passengers are willing to endure cramped conditions and forgo traditional amenities, but internet access is a must-have.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines increases frequency on Hong Kong-Haikou route with two additional flights per week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</guid><description>Starting December 25th, Hong Kong Airlines will offer two more weekly flights on its route between Hong Kong and Haikou, increasing the total frequency to nine flights per week. The new flights to Haikou will operate on Fridays and Sundays.
Flight no.*
Route
Departure/Arrival time*
Frequency
HX157
Hong Kong to Haikou
19:25/20:50
Every Friday
18:15/19:45
Every Sunday
HX158
Haikou to Hong Kong
21:55/23:15
Every Friday
21:15/22:35
Every Sunday
*Flight number and schedule may change without prior notice.</description></item><item><title>Garuda and Turkish Airlines have formed a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines have partnered to offer codeshare flights between Jakarta and Istanbul. This agreement is valid until October 24, 2015.
The joint flight schedule for Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines is shown below:
Source: Garuda Indonesia. CGK represents Soekarno–Hatta International Airport in Jakarta, Indonesia, while IST stands for Atatürk International Airport in Istanbul, Turkey. STD indicates departure time, and STA refers to arrival time. +1 signifies arrival on the following day.</description></item></channel></rss>