<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intermediary on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intermediary/</link><description>Recent content in Intermediary on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intermediary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Delfi restricting freedom of expression online in Estonia?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Media Law, University of Essex
Under what circumstances can online freedom of expression be restricted? The recent decision from the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber in the case of Delfi v. Estonia tackles this question, focusing on comments made in response to a news article. This ruling presents thought-provoking issues concerning both human rights and EU law, which will be examined in this analysis...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New ECHR ruling on freedom of expression and internet comment liability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 13:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) raises the question of whether internet site providers should be held accountable for comments made by users. This issue gained significance following the court&amp;rsquo;s ruling in MTE v. Hungary.
Considering the importance of intermediaries in the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth, there are arguments for not treating them like traditional publishers. Instead, they could be granted some immunity regarding content posted by others...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>