<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Boat on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/boat/</link><description>Recent content in Boat on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:03:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/boat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring the waters of Indonesia aboard Rascal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-waters-of-indonesia-aboard-rascal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:03:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-waters-of-indonesia-aboard-rascal/</guid><description>Source: Rascal.
Rascal, a refurbished traditional Indonesian Phinisi* yacht outfitted with modern engines, navigation, and entertainment systems, promises the ultimate adventure.
Guests enjoy personalized service on board, experiencing renowned Indonesian hospitality amidst chic tropical decor.
The removal of Rascal&amp;rsquo;s mast and sails allows for five ensuite double cabins across two spacious decks. Both indoor and outdoor areas are designed for relaxation.
The top deck, soaring 21 feet high, doubles as a diving platform.</description></item><item><title>Joo Chiat Kim Choo introduces halal rice dumplings at 7-Eleven Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 23:54:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Joo Chiat Kim Choo/7-Eleven.
- Halal rice dumplings from Kim Choo Kid are now sold at all 7-Eleven stores in Singapore.
- Customers can choose from two flavors: Nonya Chicken and Salted Chicken. For convenience, the leaves have been removed.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 7-Eleven stores now offer a halal version of the famous Joo Chiat Kim Choo rice dumplings. Part of the Neo Group, this top rice dumpling maker in Singapore is known for its Nonya dumplings, made with a recipe handed down through generations.</description></item><item><title>Emperor Cruises provides day cruises in Nha Trang</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</guid><description>Source: Emperor Cruises website.
Emperor Cruises is introducing day cruises departing from the coastal city of Nha Trang, with plans to offer overnight trips in the future. The company highlights Nha Trang&amp;rsquo;s expanding range of attractions, including the Vinpearl Golf Club and upscale hotels like the Intercontinental, Best Western Premier, and Amanoi.
&amp;ldquo;Emperor Cruises wants to provide tourists with the opportunity to admire the sunset, enjoy cocktails, and savor romantic dinners while cruising on one of the world&amp;rsquo;s 29 most beautiful bays,&amp;rdquo; stated Allister Esguerra, Branch Director of Emperor Cruises.</description></item></channel></rss>