<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CIMB on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cimb/</link><description>Recent content in CIMB on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cimb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises and consumers will reap the rewards as banks increase their focus on innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</guid><description>Several financial institutions in the Asia Pacific region were honored at the Asian Financial Services (AFS) Congress 2014 in Singapore for their innovative banking solutions.
AllianceBank Malaysia received the &amp;ldquo;Asia&amp;rsquo;s Most Customer Friendly Bank&amp;rdquo; award for its BizSmart Academy initiative, which supports young SMEs through business education, coaching, and seed funding. The program is open to both existing and new customers.
The bank provides participants with a year-long curriculum covering management, business, and finance topics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB Bank increases interest rates for fixed deposits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 18:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/</guid><description>CIMB Bank is marking its ninth anniversary by offering a special interest rate increase for online fixed deposits throughout September. This gesture is a thank you to customers for their ongoing support.
During this promotional period (September 1st to 30th, 2018), individuals who open a Singapore CIMB Fast Fixed Deposit account online will enjoy an extra 0.09% per annum on top of the existing online promotional rates.
These combined rates are highly competitive, positioning CIMB among the top options available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-bank-increases-interest-rates-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB discusses its regional strategies for participating in the ASEAN Economic Community</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. Chairman of CIMB Group, YBhg Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Nazir Razak (right) and Director, Southeast Asia of The Economist Intelligence Unit Justin Wood showcasing the special report Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia.
CIMB partnered with the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) to publish a report titled Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia. This independent management brief, co-sponsored by CIMB and Baker McKenzie, aims to equip companies for the upcoming launch of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) on December 31, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers of CIMB in Singapore have the option to apply for fixed deposits in Singapore dollars through the online platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 10:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/</guid><description>CIMB Bank is the first bank in Singapore to offer online applications for Singapore dollar fixed deposits.
This new service, called CIMB Fast Fixed Deposit (FD), allows new customers to apply for a Singapore dollar FD account and a CIMB FastSaver account online. The CIMB FastSaver account is used for deposits and withdrawals related to the FD account.
“In today’s fast-paced world, people want services that are convenient, quick, and efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-cimb-in-singapore-have-the-option-to-apply-for-fixed-deposits-in-singapore-dollars-through-the-online-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB introduces a program to enhance the skills of non-executive employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</guid><description>CIMB Group, the second-largest financial services provider in Malaysia, has initiated a program to enhance the skills, productivity, career advancement prospects, and earning potential of its non-executive employees. This program, known as the CIMB Accelerated Career Enhancement Programme (CIMB ACE), was officially launched by Dato’ Sri Richard Riot Anak Jaem, the Minister of Human Resources.
The CIMB ACE program aligns with PR1ME (Program Majudiri 1Malaysia), a national initiative launched by the Prime Minister of Malaysia in November 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-introduces-a-program-to-enhance-the-skills-of-non-executive-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>