<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Right to Carry on a Business on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-carry-on-a-business/</link><description>Recent content in Right to Carry on a Business on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/right-to-carry-on-a-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>AGET Iraklis Case: Balancing Economic Freedoms and Labour Rights - Can Governments Regulate Mass Layoffs by Employers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis
DPhil Candidate, University of Oxford; Researcher, Erasmus University of Rotterdam.
The AGET Iraklis case, despite its legal and political importance, has not received adequate attention from scholars or the public. Overshadowed by events like the UK referendum on EU membership and significant court rulings on data retention and trade agreements, the Grand Chamber judgment in this case, delivered on December 21, 2016, highlights the complex interplay between fundamental economic freedoms and collective labor rights.</description></item><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules.</description></item></channel></rss>