<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtualization on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtualization/</link><description>Recent content in Virtualization on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs VPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</guid><description>Virtual Private Servers (VPS) offer a hosting solution for websites that have outgrown shared hosting but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for the cost and responsibility of a fully dedicated server. However, a new option allows for flexible scaling and a pay-as-you-go model: cloud server hosting.
Discussions about cloud computing versus managing your own data center are becoming increasingly common. However, many companies haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the stage where investing in a complete in-house data center is necessary.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure as a Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</guid><description>Cloud computing is widely understood to have three main levels: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS). The most fundamental of these is IaaS, which forms the basis for the other two. IaaS essentially refers to providing basic hardware and operating system software over the internet.
Infrastructure is fairly self-explanatory: it&amp;rsquo;s the foundational hardware and software needed for computing. When considering cloud infrastructure, the comparison is often made with having your own data center.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's Unified Computing Cuts Costs and Power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-unified-computing-cuts-costs-and-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:57:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-unified-computing-cuts-costs-and-power/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Unified Computing technology aims to make data centers more efficient. Recognizing the enduring role of virtualization, Cisco fully embraces it to enhance performance and cut expenses, leading to reduced power usage.
You might be reminded of Unified Communications (UC) when hearing about Unified Computing. UC aims to combine all forms of business communication, such as phones, emails, faxes, voicemails, and instant messaging, into a single infrastructure. A good example is Kall8&amp;rsquo;s feature that sends faxes and voicemails to your email.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Storage as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-storage-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-storage-as-a-service/</guid><description>Affordable, high-bandwidth Wide Area Networks have led to the rise of almost everything as a &amp;ldquo;service.&amp;rdquo; Mainframe computers were once centralized and isolated within corporate infrastructures, while PCs functioned as standalone devices with their own software and storage. However, virtualization is changing our understanding of where computing resources should be located.
Software as a Service (SaaS) allows users to access familiar desktop tools like word processors, databases, and spreadsheets without the burden of purchasing, installing, and maintaining expensive software.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in.</description></item><item><title>Can You Benefit From New Cloud Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about cloud computing and might be wondering if it can help your small or medium-sized business (SMB). While it seems like cloud services are designed for large corporations, they offer significant potential for businesses of all sizes.
The cloud can be even more beneficial for SMBs because it levels the playing field. Large companies often have the resources to build their own private clouds, while smaller companies may struggle with the cost and staffing required for such an undertaking.</description></item><item><title>3 Types of Clouds You Should Know About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud-based IT services might leave you wondering if you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. To help you decide, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the three primary cloud types and which applications are well-suited for cloud environments.
These days, it seems everyone is offering cloud services, primarily based on three architectures: public, private, and hybrid clouds.
The most common is the public cloud, a specialized data center owned and operated by a provider serving numerous paying customers concurrently.</description></item><item><title>Cloud IT Online Backup For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-it-online-backup-for-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-it-online-backup-for-business/</guid><description>Cloud backups are gaining popularity for personal use, safeguarding against data loss. But what about businesses? Are cloud-based backup services beneficial for them too?
Independent professionals might find consumer-oriented services like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iCloud sufficient. However, businesses, especially those with multiple employees and locations, often benefit from business-specific cloud services, particularly when part of a managed IT solution.
Two primary approaches exist for cloud-based file backup. One treats the cloud as a separate repository for copies of essential business files.</description></item><item><title>The Ubiquitous Cloud of 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</guid><description>The year 2012 brings a shift in the business landscape, not towards a downturn, but rather a move towards cloud computing. This change benefits businesses facing uncertainty by offering flexibility and adaptability. Instead of struggling to predict the future, businesses can embrace the cloud and adjust their strategies as needed.
The current business environment is already in flux. While some businesses are stagnant, others experience constant change. This unpredictability leaves many longing for a more stable past.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs Dedicated Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</guid><description>There are many ways to host your emails, websites, and software applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the pros and cons of each option to help you determine the best fit for your business.
You might be tempted to manage your own hosting, which is how many companies started and how some large companies still operate. The basic requirement is a computer that functions as a file server and a bandwidth connection. Internally, this connection can be your Local Area Network (LAN).</description></item><item><title>Concentric Cloud Solutions Virtualizes Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been bombarded with information about virtualization, unsure if it can help control unpredictable business expenses. You might feel overwhelmed about the process of deploying virtualization. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry, Concentric can guide you through it.
Initially confined to local data centers, virtualization has migrated to the cloud. The fundamental concept is maximizing hardware performance. This is achieved by making a single server function as multiple servers, or transforming a cluster of smaller servers into a powerful computing unit.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting With a Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve considered cloud computing as a potential solution for your business but hesitate due to the investment and commitment. Now, a free trial for cloud hosting presents the perfect opportunity to explore its benefits.
Cloud hosting is a practical step for businesses exceeding their shared hosting capacity and considering VPS or dedicated servers. Cloud hosting surpasses these alternatives by offering flexibility and cost advantages.
VPS and dedicated servers eliminate the need for capital expenditures and infrastructure management associated with running a data center.</description></item><item><title>Top Enterprise Cloud Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-enterprise-cloud-solutions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:22:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-enterprise-cloud-solutions/</guid><description>Many businesses, both mid-sized and large, grapple with the decision of whether or not to transition to cloud computing. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine some prevalent cloud solutions and their potential benefits.
When discussing cloud computing, Amazon Web Services (AWS) often takes center stage. Launched almost a decade ago, AWS stemmed from Amazon&amp;rsquo;s realization that its extensive data centers, built for its e-commerce operations, held untapped potential. Renting out unused resources became a lucrative venture, appealing to companies hesitant to make similar large-scale investments.</description></item><item><title>A New Cloud In IT Managed Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</guid><description>Many businesses are seriously considering migrating their IT infrastructure to cloud-based managed solutions. The key question then becomes: which cloud platform is the right fit? One compelling option is the &amp;ldquo;new cloud.&amp;rdquo;
NewCloud Networks, a managed service provider established in 1988, offers comprehensive solutions ranging from voice and data services for small businesses to intricate national and international networking solutions.
NewCloud differentiates itself by providing bespoke solutions tailored to specific client needs, rather than forcing a one-size-fits-all approach.</description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then.</description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions.</description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits.</description></item><item><title>How Does Cloud Computing Work In Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is frequently used today. But what exactly is it, and how can it benefit your business by improving efficiency, speed, and affordability? Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into it.
In business, the term &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; often carries a negative connotation, implying uncertainty and unpredictability. Naturally, clarity and predictability are preferred, especially from a financial standpoint. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable why people might be skeptical when advised to transition their business to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery.</description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user.</description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting in Clouds and Colos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</guid><description>There are many hosting choices available. Shared hosting is popular among individuals and small businesses due to its affordability and acceptable performance. However, as your needs grow, you face a decision: self-hosting or a managed solution.
While setting up a website previously required technical expertise in server management, Linux and Windows hosting have become increasingly user-friendly and widely accessible. Even large enterprises accustomed to managing their servers in-house are reconsidering colocation and cloud solutions, driven by cost and resource optimization.</description></item></channel></rss>