<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rental on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rental/</link><description>Recent content in Rental on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:31:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avis inaugurates a new branch in Malacca, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:31:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</guid><description>Avis Car Rental has expanded its presence in Malaysia by opening its eighth branch at the Holiday Inn Melaka on Jalan Syed Abdul Aziz, Malacca.
The new location offers a range of recent car models, including the economical Toyota Passo, the compact Honda City, the full-size Toyota Camry, and the Nissan X-Trail SUV. In addition to vehicles, Avis provides renters with options for GPS navigation, child safety seats, and fuel services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cathay Pacific has chosen Hertz as its sole car rental service provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</guid><description>Hertz Global is now the sole car rental provider for Cathay Pacific, an international airline based in Hong Kong. To streamline the rental process, Hertz created a dedicated website for Cathay Pacific travelers, offering a wide array of vehicles and deals at approximately 10,000 global locations. Furthermore, Cathay Pacific passengers will automatically receive a 5% discount on Hertz car rentals worldwide.
This agreement expands on the existing partnership between Hertz and Asia Miles, Cathay Pacific&amp;rsquo;s frequent flyer program...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Booqed offers a selection of workspaces available for rent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</guid><description>Booqed, an online marketplace for booking meeting rooms and workspaces, has introduced its mobile app on the Apple App Store. This app offers a convenient way to find and reserve available spaces in a city, allowing users to book instantly or in advance and make payments directly from their smartphones or tablets.
Businesses can also benefit from this service by monetizing their underutilized meeting or conference rooms. Booqed provides a platform for them to list and rent out these spaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoTripy Car Rentals is now available in 11 cities across India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</guid><description>Source: GoTripy Car Rentals&amp;rsquo; website.
GoTripy Car Rentals currently operates in 11 cities across India. Their updated website makes online booking easier than ever before.
GoTripy offers a variety of budget-friendly and luxury vehicles, along with professional drivers, in cities like Mumbai, Pune, Nashik, Ahmednagar, Aurangabad, Shirdi, Kolhapur, Delhi, Gurgaon, Bangalore, and Ahmedabad. Their car rental services cater to diverse needs such as local transportation, day trips within a city, sightseeing excursions, airport and railway station transfers, inter-city travel, weekend getaways, business trips, and multi-city journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Science Park 1 will be testing a program for sharing personal mobility devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</guid><description>Ascendas-Singbridge Group, a leading provider of sustainable urban and business space solutions in Asia, has partnered with Neuron Mobility, a smart transportation solutions provider, to pilot a personal mobility device (PMD) sharing program at Singapore Science Park 1. This six-month trial reflects the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing accessibility and convenience for tenants, employees, and visitors within the park.
Starting June 14, 2017, fifty GPS-equipped e-scooters and twenty bicycles will be available for rent at six designated parking zones throughout Singapore Science Park 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>