<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gaining Entry to the EU's Financial Services Market in the Absence of a Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (Twitter: @KulpaBart)
Introduction
When Boris Johnson became British Prime Minister, a no-deal Brexit appeared increasingly possible. UK-based financial services firms were left wondering if and how they would be able to continue serving clients in the remaining 27 EU countries. These firms currently depend on &amp;ldquo;passporting rights,&amp;rdquo; which allow them to operate across borders. According to The Economist, in 2016, 5,476 British financial services firms used 336,421 European passports to offer their products across the EU.</description></item><item><title>Western Union has extended its contract to provide its services at Hong Leong Bank branches in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Western Union, a company specializing in money transfers, has extended its partnership with Hong Leong Bank (HLBB) for another three years. This agreement allows Western Union to continue providing its services across all 283 HLBB branches in Malaysia.
Chew Mei Ling, Western Union&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, highlighted the increasing demand for both inbound and outbound remittances in the country. She emphasized that the renewed partnership with HLBB will support this growth by offering customers fast, reliable, and convenient money transfer services.</description></item><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes.</description></item><item><title>Financial services companies are placing a greater emphasis on developing a strong risk culture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</guid><description>A recent study by Mercer focusing on executive compensation in the global financial services industry found that a majority of firms are prioritizing the development of robust risk cultures within their organizations. Sixty-two percent of surveyed firms reported significant efforts to penalize misconduct and non-compliance, while 60% demonstrated clear leadership commitment to ethical behavior. Furthermore, 58% have established and communicated unambiguous objectives related to risk culture.
Vicki Elliott, Senior Partner and Financial Services Talent Leader at Mercer, highlighted the importance of senior leaders setting a positive example when it comes to risk management and compliance.</description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised.</description></item><item><title>Smaller companies can benefit from Cisco's advanced firewall security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaller-companies-can-benefit-from-cisco-s-advanced-firewall-security/</guid><description>Source: Cisco website. Some members of the Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services family.
Cisco has introduced new Cisco ASA with FirePOWER Services models designed for small to mid-sized businesses and branch offices. These models offer the same advanced malware protection and threat detection used by larger organizations.
A recent study by PwC revealed a 64% increase in security breaches among mid-sized organizations in 2014. These organizations face similar security challenges as larger enterprises when safeguarding their network and data.</description></item></channel></rss>