<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Data Connections on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 13:40:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Gift of Bandwidth For Administrative Professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gift-of-bandwidth-for-administrative-professionals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gift-of-bandwidth-for-administrative-professionals/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Administrative Professionals Week, a time to show appreciation for those essential staff members who keep everything running smoothly. While thoughtful gestures like cards and lunches are always appreciated, let&amp;rsquo;s not forget about the practical tools that can truly empower administrative professionals to excel in their roles.
Beyond personal recognition, what administrative professionals truly benefit from are improved tools that enhance their productivity. These individuals are often models of efficiency, making the most of available resources.</description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing.</description></item></channel></rss>