<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changi on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/changi/</link><description>Recent content in Changi on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/changi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The groundbreaking ceremony for Jewel has been successfully completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Changi Airport.
Jewel Changi Airport Trustee (JCAT), a collaboration between Changi Airport Group (CAG) and CapitaMalls Asia (the shopping mall branch of CapitaLand), has initiated the construction of Jewel Changi Airport. This mixed-use development, situated in front of Terminal 1 (T1), will feature attractions, retail spaces, a hotel, and airport operational facilities.
Strategically placed at the airport&amp;rsquo;s core, Jewel aims to be a premier lifestyle destination enhancing Changi Airport&amp;rsquo;s global standing and solidifying Singapore&amp;rsquo;s attractiveness as a layover spot for travelers.</description></item><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport consolidates early check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Travelers departing from Singapore have increased access to early check-in services for various airlines at Changi Airport. Since the beginning of the year, shared early check-in counters have been established in Terminals 2 and 3. Terminal 1 features a dedicated early check-in lounge for added convenience.
Operational from 6 am to midnight, the counters and lounge offer a centralized service point for passengers flying with 23 participating airlines.</description></item><item><title>A trial for FAST check-in has been introduced by Changi Airport, Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</guid><description>A new Fast and Seamless Travel (FAST) check-in trial is currently underway at Changi Airport Terminal 2 for passengers flying with Singapore Airlines and SilkAir. This collaborative effort between Changi Airport Group (CAG), Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir will gradually introduce a comprehensive suite of FAST options throughout 2016. These options aim to provide passengers with more check-in choices and potentially faster processing times through automated kiosks and bag drops. Terminal 3 will also see the addition of 24 kiosks.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport introduces a new reward for the Be a Changi Millionaire campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 03:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. This year&amp;rsquo;s Be a Changi Millionaire competition offers a chance to win a Volvo sedan as well.
Changi Airport has enhanced its well-known *Be a Changi Millionaire*_ retail promotion this year by adding a new prize: a Volvo S90 T5 luxury sedan. This is in addition to the existing S$1 million cash prize. According to Changi Airport, this is the largest retail promotion at any airport globally.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers.</description></item><item><title>An open house event was held at Changi Airport's fourth terminal before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: CAG. CAG organises open house for Changi T4.
The Changi Airport Group (CAG) has invited Singapore residents to preview Terminal 4 (T4) before its official opening. From August 7th to 20th, 2017, the public can attend an Open House for a sneak peek of the new terminal.
Construction on the 195,000 square meter, two-story T4 began in early 2013 and finished in December 2016. Though only half the size of Terminal 3 (T3), it can accommodate 16 million passengers annually, roughly 70% of T3&amp;rsquo;s capacity.</description></item><item><title>JJ Lin has composed a song that was inspired by Jewel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jj-lin-has-composed-a-song-that-was-inspired-by-jewel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:32:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jj-lin-has-composed-a-song-that-was-inspired-by-jewel/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Lin&amp;rsquo;s The Right Time.
Changi Airport Group (CAG) collaborated with Singaporean singer-songwriter JJ Lin on his new song, &amp;ldquo;The Right Time.&amp;rdquo;
Inspired by the April opening of Jewel Changi Airport, Lin shared that the Rain Vortex, Jewel&amp;rsquo;s impressive waterfall centerpiece, sparked his creativity for this piece.
Lin composed the music for &amp;ldquo;The Right Time&amp;rdquo; with lyrics by Xiaohan. Filmed in July, the music video showcases Jewel&amp;rsquo;s waterfall and lush surroundings, featuring Lin alongside popular regional actor Christopher Lee.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport is offering mooncakes in a suitcase</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has launched its 2016 mooncake collection, featuring classic baked and contemporary snowskin varieties. These halal-certified treats are packaged in a stylish metal suitcase, making them a great gift for colleagues or loved ones.
For those who prefer a traditional taste, baked mooncakes are available in three flavors: White Lotus Paste with Double Egg Yolk, White Lotus Paste with Single Egg Yolk, and White Lotus Paste with Melon Seeds.</description></item><item><title>Changi Terminal 3 reveals its new Central Piazza</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. The newly opened Central Piazza at Changi Airport Terminal 3 features a Louis Vuitton duplex store and a dandelion-themed Crystal Garden.
Travelers passing through Changi Airport Terminal 3&amp;rsquo;s Transit Hall can now enjoy the revitalized Central Piazza. This area showcases the airport&amp;rsquo;s seventh featured garden, the Crystal Garden, composed of glass dandelion sculptures.
The Crystal Garden features a multi-level garden design with carefully chosen flowering plants and twelve handcrafted glass dandelion sculptures of different sizes.</description></item></channel></rss>