<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Desktop on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/desktop/</link><description>Recent content in Desktop on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:13:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/desktop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The six-port USB desktop charger solves all your charging problems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</guid><description>Poweradd, a company known for its mobile device accessories, has introduced a new six-port desktop USB charger with a 50W capacity. This charger is designed to meet the growing demand for charging multiple devices simultaneously when outlets are limited.
The compact charger measures 4&amp;quot; x 2.9&amp;quot; x 1&amp;quot; and supports voltages from 100V to 240V, making it suitable for international use. It features two ports that provide 2.4A, two ports with 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-six-port-usb-desktop-charger-solves-all-your-charging-problems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evernote is unveiling new additions to the Pfeiffer Collection of desktop accessories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</guid><description>Evernote has expanded its Pfeiffer Collection, a line of modern desktop accessories designed in collaboration with Eric Pfeiffer.
The latest additions are bent plywood platforms crafted to securely elevate laptops, tablets, and monitors on desks, while also providing extra storage space.
Source: Evernote blog.
The new products include:
Laptop platform: This stand, made of walnut bent ply, supports 13” or 15” laptops. A curved front trough can hold small items, and cables can be routed through the back...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</a></p></description></item><item><title>G.ho.st as the Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</guid><description>If you come across a platform called G.ho.st, don&amp;rsquo;t be spooked by the name. It stands for Global Hosted Operating SysTem, found at http://g.ho.st/. It&amp;rsquo;s essentially an online operating system.
Instead of being restricted to your desktop, G.ho.st allows you to access an operating system anywhere with an internet connection. I decided to try it out myself.
The website was visually appealing, so I launched the G.ho.st virtual computer (VC). Unfortunately, my old Compaq couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle it and displayed an error message...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beijing Tiertime Technology introduces the UP BOX desktop 3D printer priced at less than $2,000</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-tiertime-technology-introduces-the-up-box-desktop-3d-printer-priced-at-less-than-2-000/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 06:23:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-tiertime-technology-introduces-the-up-box-desktop-3d-printer-priced-at-less-than-2-000/</guid><description>Tiertime, a company specializing in 3D printing technology, has introduced the UP BOX, the newest addition to their UP Series of desktop 3D printers.
Source: Tiertime.
The UP BOX draws upon the strengths of its predecessors, the UP Plus 2 and UP mini. It boasts a larger build volume of 255mm x 205mm x 205mm while achieving a higher print resolution of 0.1mm. Additionally, it surpasses the UP Plus 2 in printing speed by up to 30%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-tiertime-technology-introduces-the-up-box-desktop-3d-printer-priced-at-less-than-2-000/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-tiertime-technology-introduces-the-up-box-desktop-3d-printer-priced-at-less-than-2-000/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Computer Recycling Easier Than Ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-recycling-easier-than-ever/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 02:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-recycling-easier-than-ever/</guid><description>Most people own several computers at home, but many go unused due to outdated specifications. Instead of letting them gather dust, have you considered selling or recycling them for cash?
Computer recycling is a relatively new concept. Previously, old computers were relegated to storage or landfills. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing concern about the environmental impact of discarded electronics. Many communities now organize recycling events, offering a responsible disposal method. But instead of giving away your old computers, you can sell them for profit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-recycling-easier-than-ever/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-recycling-easier-than-ever/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lenovo introduces the ThinkStation P series of desktop workstations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 15:41:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</guid><description>Lenovo has introduced the ThinkStation P Series, a new line of desktop workstations. The P900, P700, and P500 models join the entry-level P300, which was launched in May 2014, to form Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s most potent professional-grade desktop workstations.
Rob Herman, Director of Worldwide Workstation Product and Vertical Marketing at Lenovo, stated that the company listened to customer feedback regarding the need for faster, more dependable, and user-friendly workstations, and the ThinkStation P Series is their response...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>