<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Headscarf on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headscarf/</link><description>Recent content in Headscarf on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headscarf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Faith in action: the CJEU's decisions on headscarves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer, UCL Faculty of Laws and author of Religion and the Public Order of the Euorpean Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’ordre juridique de l’Union européenne (Bruylant 2013).
Nearly two decades after the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment was implemented, the Court of Justice issued its first significant decisions regarding workplace discrimination based on religion. These rulings placed the Court in a politically sensitive area, presenting considerable risk for an international judicial body like the CJEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Explaining the European Court of Justice's decisions on headscarf bans in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued rulings on whether employers can prohibit employees from wearing headscarves at work. These rulings have garnered significant attention, although some of it stems from misunderstandings. This post aims to provide a clear explanation of the rulings.
Background
The EU has established laws against discrimination based on sex, nationality, race, disability, age, sexual orientation, and religion. While the ECJ has frequently addressed cases related to the first three grounds, the recent judgments in G4S v Achbita and Bougnaoui mark the first instance where the court has been asked to interpret workplace discrimination based on religious grounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides clarification on when employers can prohibit headscarves in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Ronan McCrea, University College London
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s initial significant decisions concerning workplace policies limiting religious symbols were issued four years ago in the G4S and Micropole cases. These rulings addressed the compatibility of these policies with the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment (Directive 2000/78).
In these decisions, the Court&amp;rsquo;s Grand Chamber determined that requiring employees to maintain visible religious neutrality constituted indirect rather than direct discrimination, provided this policy was uniformly applied to all religions or beliefs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-clarification-on-when-employers-can-prohibit-headscarves-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>