<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Design on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/design/</link><description>Recent content in Design on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India is enhancing its intellectual property infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</guid><description>The Indian government has decided to continue its efforts to improve its intellectual property (IP) offices. This initiative, part of the 12th Plan (2012-2017), will cost Rs309.6 crore, with Rs258 crore allocated for the 12th Plan and Rs51.6 crore for the 13th Plan.
This decision recognizes the increasing importance of IP in a globalized economy, India&amp;rsquo;s recent membership in the Madrid Protocol (April 2013), and the Controller General of Patents, Designs, and Trademarks (CGPDTM) office&amp;rsquo;s new role as an International Searching and Preliminary Examining Authority (ISA/IPEA) under the Patent Cooperation Treaty (starting October 2013)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-disciplinary conversations are reshaping the service economy at KODW 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Pictured at the KODW 2021 opening ceremony are (from left) Lofai Lo (Director and GM, ViuTV); Dr Lay Lian Ong (Principal, Hong Kong Design Institute &amp;amp; Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education); Victor Tsang (Head of Create Hong Kong); Professor Eric Yim (Chairman of Hong Kong Design Centre); guest of honor The Honourable Edward Yau (Secretary for Commerce and Economic Development); Victor Lo (Chairman, KODW Steering Committee of Hong Kong Design Centre); Professor Kun-Pyo Lee (Dean of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Design), and Dr Edmund Lee (Executive Director of Hong Kong Design Centre)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Businesses have the opportunity to take part in the For a Golden Home charity campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</guid><description>Cromly.com, a design portal and social media platform, has launched &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home.&amp;rdquo; This online charity campaign aims to improve the lives of needy elderly individuals in Singapore this Chinese New Year. The platform allows organizations to create their own fundraising projects in support of this shared goal.
Source: Cromly.com. Participating companies can create a pledge project to raise funds. Eunice Olsen and Paul Foster are ambassadors for the &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home&amp;rdquo; campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has modified its regulations for the protection of designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Law (MinLaw) has introduced the Registered Designs (Amendment) Bill to Parliament for its first reading. The bill aims to modernize Singapore&amp;rsquo;s design protection laws by reflecting current design and technology developments. It seeks to foster growth in the design sector by streamlining the process for designers to safeguard their creations.
This bill stems from a joint review of Singapore’s registered designs system by MinLaw and the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore (IPOS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Business of Design Week 2021 is open to participants from all over the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Officiating guests join Business of Design Week 2021’s opening ceremony.
The 19th edition of Business of Design Week (BODW) 2021 has begun. This major Asian design, innovation, and brand event, organized annually by the Hong Kong Design Centre (HKDC) since 2002, will run for a week. The summit showcases a diverse range of speakers and television programs centered around the theme of Global Design Reset.
The event adopts a hybrid format this year, broadcast simultaneously online, on ViuTV, and at various partner venues such as the PMQ in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The book guarantees to save presentations from completely missing the mark</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-guarantees-to-save-presentations-from-completely-missing-the-mark/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 21:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-guarantees-to-save-presentations-from-completely-missing-the-mark/</guid><description>Presentations are a common way to share information, manage projects, and plan, taking up a significant part of the workweek. However, they often waste time and resources.
Ed Gruwez, a Belgian communications expert, believes most presentations are ineffective and poorly designed, failing to achieve their goals despite considerable preparation time. He points out their negative impact on corporate decisions and employee satisfaction.
Gruwez emphasizes the ubiquity of presentations in professional settings and the significant financial and time resources wasted on ineffective ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-guarantees-to-save-presentations-from-completely-missing-the-mark/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-guarantees-to-save-presentations-from-completely-missing-the-mark/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Buyers who prioritize design are encouraging gift and premium manufacturers to elevate their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</guid><description>Source: SGS website. SGS 2015 was well attended.
This year&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Gifts Show (SGS), taking place from June 29th to July 1st, sees exhibitors raising their game in response to increasingly design-conscious buyers. As the biggest event of its kind in Singapore, SGS is a trade show for gifts, premiums, lifestyle products, and services, targeting both regional and global markets. Established in 2006, this yearly showcase spans three days and encompasses both an exhibition and industry seminars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the thoughts of a designer who has won awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 02:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/</guid><description>Dr. Cingoli recently gave a presentation at the National Design Centre.
Dr. Andrea Cingoli, the driving force behind ConceptIcon, has been making a name for his team at Zo_loft architecture &amp;amp; design, and more recently, for himself through ConceptIcon. He sees design awards as a reliable measure of quality and believes that sharing designs is crucial for growth and inspiration within the design community.
Dr. Cingoli finds inspiration in his personal experiences and surroundings, aiming to create designs that are both meaningful and thought-provoking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-thoughts-of-a-designer-who-has-won-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>With Lavotre, you have the ability to create your own custom watch design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-lavotre-you-have-the-ability-to-create-your-own-custom-watch-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-lavotre-you-have-the-ability-to-create-your-own-custom-watch-design/</guid><description>Source: Lavotre. Bently
Anchor, an original design
from Lavotre.
Need a special corporate gift? Consider personalized watches.
Eugene Chow, Brand Manager at Lavotre, explained that their journey started with a simple question: &amp;ldquo;What if we could create our own watches?&amp;rdquo; They noticed a gap in the market for personalized watches without minimum order requirements or limited to generic &amp;ldquo;couple&amp;rdquo; designs. Partnering with Cheryl Tan, head of sales and operations, they established Lavotre to fill this void...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-lavotre-you-have-the-ability-to-create-your-own-custom-watch-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-lavotre-you-have-the-ability-to-create-your-own-custom-watch-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the opportunity to apply for government grants to assist with their studies in infocomm, media, and design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</guid><description>Singaporeans working in Infocomm, Media, and Design can apply for the SkillsFuture Study Awards until June 14, 2016.
Announced during the Ministry of Communications and Information’s Committee of Supply Debate for 2016, the SkillsFuture Study Award encourages Singaporeans to enhance their skills in sectors crucial for future economic growth. Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, stated that 310 awards will be granted to Singaporeans in the early or middle stages of their careers who are looking to advance their skills in these sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>