<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carlson Rezidor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carlson-rezidor/</link><description>Recent content in Carlson Rezidor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:15:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carlson-rezidor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Carlson Rezidor has revealed plans for new hotel developments in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</guid><description>The Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group has announced new deals and hotel openings in strategic locations within India, further solidifying its position as a leading international hotel group in the country.
Thorsten Kirschke, President for Asia Pacific at Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments, stating that building upon a successful 2013, the first four months of this year have shown strong results in India and Thailand. He added that with 95 hotels currently operational, they anticipate exceeding 100 operating hotels in the Asia Pacific region by year-end.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group is celebrating the expansion of its Radisson Blu brand with the debut of its first Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok.
The Radisson Blu Plaza Hotel Bangkok, boasting 290 rooms, is strategically situated in Sukhumvit, a vibrant area known for its numerous offices, corporate headquarters, and retail outlets. This property marks Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s first Radisson Blu establishment in the city and is owned by G&amp;amp;P Asset Holding Company.</description></item><item><title>Club Carlson celebrates reaching one million members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s international hotel rewards program, Club Carlson, celebrated a milestone by awarding its one millionth member in the Asia Pacific region with one million Club Carlson Gold Points.
The lucky recipient, Rong Weiji, is a Sales and Marketing Division Manager at Santen Pharmaceutical. He became the millionth member upon checking in at the Radisson Blu Shanghai New World on August 22, 2014.
When asked about his hotel preferences, Mr. Weiji explained that he values brand recognition, quality, service, and location.</description></item></channel></rss>