<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economic and Monetary Union on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic-and-monetary-union/</link><description>Recent content in Economic and Monetary Union on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic-and-monetary-union/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions.</description></item><item><title>Battle of the Legal Giants: Can the Euro endure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The German Federal Constitutional Court (BVerfG) has finally submitted a legal question to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on a critically important issue: the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) policy. This policy is widely credited with saving the EU&amp;rsquo;s single currency. If either court finds the policy unlawful, the euro&amp;rsquo;s continued existence could be in jeopardy.
In simple terms, the OMT is a 2012 commitment by the ECB to buy government bonds from struggling eurozone countries on secondary markets (from banks and financial institutions).</description></item><item><title>Preserving the euro: Gauweiler's challenge to the legality of the OMT program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
On June 16th, the Court of Justice ruled in the Gauweiler case, declaring the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program legal under EU law. This decision has significant implications for the ECB&amp;rsquo;s authority, the EU Economic and Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s constitutional structure, and the relationship between the Court of Justice and the referring court, the German Federal Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>Is there a role for the Court of Justice of the European Union in ensuring the accountability and independence of the Governors of National Banks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-role-for-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-ensuring-the-accountability-and-independence-of-the-governors-of-national-banks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 10:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-role-for-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-ensuring-the-accountability-and-independence-of-the-governors-of-national-banks/</guid><description>Dr. Marios Costa, Senior Lecturer, City, University of London
The European Union (EU) has faced criticism for administrative and structural shortcomings, with reports and discussions pointing to political irregularities within its system. Similarly, concerns about alleged corruption, maladministration, and money laundering at the national governance level raise anxieties for both citizens and the Union.
On February 26, 2019, the Court of Justice (Grand Chamber) issued a significant judgment on two combined cases.</description></item><item><title>Judicial review of monetary policy and banking supervision by the European Central Bank.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</guid><description>Introduction
The European Union has experienced widespread political and economic consequences due to the financial crisis. These effects extend to the legal realm, leading to the European Central Bank (ECB) not only creating debatable new methods for involvement in monetary policy but also acquiring new authority in banking supervision. Additionally, the ECB, alongside the European Commission and the International Monetary Fund (forming the &amp;lsquo;Troika&amp;rsquo;), has become engaged in austerity measures within Member States requiring financial support.</description></item><item><title>Should legitimacy be prioritized in the further development of the EMU, or should it be considered as a secondary concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</guid><description>Päivi Leino-Sandberg: Adjunct Professor of EU Law, Academy of Finland Research Fellow, University of Helsinki
In June 2012, the European Council outlined &amp;ldquo;four essential building blocks&amp;rdquo; for the future of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU): integrated frameworks for finance, budget, and economic policy, and enhanced democratic legitimacy and accountability. The European Council emphasized ensuring democratic legitimacy and accountability at all levels of decision-making and implementation, stating that stronger economic governance requires stronger legitimacy and accountability.</description></item><item><title>What are the legal implications of leaving the economic and monetary union according to EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-legal-implications-of-leaving-the-economic-and-monetary-union-according-to-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-legal-implications-of-leaving-the-economic-and-monetary-union-according-to-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Greece&amp;rsquo;s upcoming referendum on accepting its creditors&amp;rsquo; offer brings uncertainty. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear if rejecting the offer means Greece automatically leaves the EU or EMU, or defaults on its debt. Accepting the offer doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide clarity either, as negotiations were ongoing during the referendum announcement, potentially making the offer outdated.
Given the range of possibilities, examining the legal framework for departing economic and monetary union (EMU) is crucial. A key question is whether Greece must leave the EU if it exits the single currency.</description></item><item><title>What lies ahead for Greece and the Eurozone: catharsis or catastrophe?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent victory of the anti-austerity party Syriza in the Greek elections raises questions about its potential effects on the EU&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union. Syriza&amp;rsquo;s objective is not to withdraw from the EU or the single currency but to renegotiate Greece&amp;rsquo;s debt and austerity measures. Their goal is to secure debt forgiveness and renegotiate terms, including the removal of austerity demands associated with previous bailouts.
However, this program might encounter legal obstacles due to limitations on debt forgiveness and ending austerity outlined in EU Treaties and Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Greece to be expelled from the eurozone? How will the ECB's actions in limiting funding options for Greece impact Target2?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</guid><description>Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster https://iglinavos.wordpress.com/
The European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) actions regarding Greece, particularly since Syriza&amp;rsquo;s political victory, have drawn considerable criticism. This piece examines the gradual tightening of Greece&amp;rsquo;s financial situation within the framework of ECB regulations and considers potential outcomes if a resolution for Greece&amp;rsquo;s urgent funding requirements isn&amp;rsquo;t reached by June 2015.
ECB Halts Greek Government Bonds as Collateral
Since accepting its initial bailout in 2010, Greece has largely been unable to secure funding from markets except through domestic T-Bill issuances.</description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the Euro's downfall? EU regulations on exiting EMU or defaulting on debts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The stability of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) is once again in question after a period of relative calm. This follows the announcement of early elections in Greece. Should the anti-austerity party, Syriza, gain control of the government, the consequences could be significant.
It is crucial to note that such an outcome is not guaranteed. Syriza holds a small lead in the polls, and even if they become the leading party, they might not secure enough seats to hold a majority.</description></item><item><title>After the Steinhoff case, the ECB has an increased responsibility to uphold and advocate for the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Diane Fromage, Maastricht University*
* I am grateful to Menelaos Markakis for his insightful feedback.
On March 12, 2020, the Court of Justice dismissed an appeal concerning the Steinhoff case (T-107/17), previously decided by the General Court in May 2019. This case, though not widely discussed, holds significant weight as it clarifies and broadens the European Central Bank (ECB)&amp;rsquo;s obligation to &amp;lsquo;respect the rights [of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (ECFR)], [to] observe the principles and [to] promote the application thereof&amp;rsquo; as stated in Article 51 ECFR, specifically concerning its advisory role.</description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention.</description></item><item><title>National legislatures and the "Five Presidents' Report": The extensive journey towards the democratization of Economic and Monetary Union (EMU)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legislatures-and-the-five-presidents-report-the-extensive-journey-towards-the-democratization-of-economic-and-monetary-union-emu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 13:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legislatures-and-the-five-presidents-report-the-extensive-journey-towards-the-democratization-of-economic-and-monetary-union-emu/</guid><description>Ton van den Brink, Associate Professor, University of Utrecht
The &amp;lsquo;Five Presidents&amp;rsquo; Report&amp;rsquo; proposes significant changes to the EU&amp;rsquo;s Economic and Monetary Union (EMU), aiming to deepen its integration. These proposals have substantial implications for national parliaments. A more democratic EMU requires giving these parliaments more authority, going beyond the suggested increased &amp;ldquo;dialogues.&amp;rdquo;
The report advocates for a &amp;ldquo;system of further sovereignty sharing within common institutions,&amp;rdquo; impacting national parliaments by centralizing economic policy coordination within the EU.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Thomas Piketty to bring about reform in both capitalism and democracy within the European Union?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</guid><description>Steve Peers
French economist Thomas Piketty unexpectedly became a prominent intellectual figure, especially in the UK and US, with his book &amp;ldquo;Capital,&amp;rdquo; which presents a new perspective on the relationship between capitalism and democracy.
Maintaining his engagement with current issues, Piketty has contributed to a proposal for EU reform, connecting his academic work to practical solutions.
The EU, once adept at managing capitalism but less so democracy, now struggles with both.</description></item><item><title>Can a temporary Grexit be legally feasible? EMU like the Hotel California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-temporary-grexit-be-legally-feasible-emu-like-the-hotel-california/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 19:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-temporary-grexit-be-legally-feasible-emu-like-the-hotel-california/</guid><description>Steve Peers
News sources report that during the recent Eurogroup meeting about a potential new bailout plan for Greece, the German government was privately proposing a plan for a temporary Greek exit from the eurozone (&amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo;). Putting aside any political or economic arguments, the most pressing question is whether this is even legally feasible. The short answer: It&amp;rsquo;s not.
A temporary Grexit isn&amp;rsquo;t possible because a permanent one isn&amp;rsquo;t allowed under the current treaties.</description></item><item><title>Mario's feet were pulled out from under him by the BVerfG and the ECB's OMT programme.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mario-s-feet-were-pulled-out-from-under-him-by-the-bverfg-and-the-ecb-s-omt-programme/</guid><description>By Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster
The German Constitutional Court (BVerfG) is set to make a significant decision on the European Union&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union on June 21st. The court will rule on the Gauweiler case, which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. This program, designed to stabilize struggling Eurozone economies, was challenged by plaintiffs questioning its legal foundation.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule.</description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the ECB's OMT program in question? The Advocate-General's opinion in Gauweiler suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 01:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective (OUP)
On January 14th, Advocate General Cruz Villalon presented his legal opinion on the Gauweiler case (C-62/14), which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. He believes the OMT program generally complies with EU treaties, provided certain conditions are met if it&amp;rsquo;s activated in the future. This case has significant implications for the European Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s (EMU) constitutional framework, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s role, and the relationship between the German Constitutional Court (Bundesverfassungsgericht) and the Court of Justice of the EU.</description></item><item><title>Challenging the legality of ECB restrictions on Greek bank accounts – and ways you can support the cause</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:08:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many citizens across the EU have observed the plight of Greeks limited to €60 withdrawals per day with sympathy and apprehension. This situation stems from the European Central Bank (ECB) restricting emergency funds for Greek banks.
Beyond the human cost, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s actions raise serious legal, political, and economic concerns. A core function of any central bank is acting as a last-resort lender for banks, a role the ECB is demonstrably failing to fulfill in this case.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Europe: A Preview of the Five Presidents' Report on EMU Completion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-europe-a-preview-of-the-five-presidents-report-on-emu-completion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 14:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-europe-a-preview-of-the-five-presidents-report-on-emu-completion/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis, DPhil student at University of Oxford, Academy of Athens scholar
In June 2015, the leaders of the EU and Euro area institutions released a report outlining a plan for strengthening and finalizing the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU). This report, based on crisis-combatting measures, offers numerous suggestions for improving the EMU&amp;rsquo;s governance and deepening economic integration within the Euro area. The EU Presidents suggest advancing towards a unified economic, financial, fiscal, and political system.</description></item><item><title>Legal Challenges of Implementing the Digital Euro by the Central Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:21:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</guid><description>Dr. (Annelieke) Anne Marieke Mooij, Tilburg University
The European Central Bank (ECB) is preparing to introduce a digital euro, a central bank digital currency (CBDC). The ECB has explored several design options, ranging from restricted access for financial institutions to broad accessibility for all consumers via national central banks. While a final design hasn&amp;rsquo;t been chosen, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s statements suggest a preference for broader accessibility. This blog post will examine the primary legal hurdles associated with each design option.</description></item></channel></rss>