<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/open/</link><description>Recent content in Open on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/open/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encouraging an open workplace culture: the role of leaders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</guid><description>Open communication and strong relationships are essential for a thriving workplace. UK-based sales and marketing firm Forrest Bell emphasizes that openness involves respectful and constructive dialogue about needs, opinions, and concerns. It also means actively listening to and considering new ideas, questions, and feedback.
Forrest Bell believes that a culture of openness fosters trust and facilitates collaboration on projects. It also promotes transparency and streamlines processes in dynamic business environments.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75.</description></item><item><title>An open house event was held at Changi Airport's fourth terminal before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: CAG. CAG organises open house for Changi T4.
The Changi Airport Group (CAG) has invited Singapore residents to preview Terminal 4 (T4) before its official opening. From August 7th to 20th, 2017, the public can attend an Open House for a sneak peek of the new terminal.
Construction on the 195,000 square meter, two-story T4 began in early 2013 and finished in December 2016. Though only half the size of Terminal 3 (T3), it can accommodate 16 million passengers annually, roughly 70% of T3&amp;rsquo;s capacity.</description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway.</description></item></channel></rss>