<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Insert on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insert/</link><description>Recent content in Insert on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/insert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Arrives From UK! Solenoid Oscillates!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</guid><description>I recently acquired another Beogram 4000 from the UK. The unit is in fair shape; importantly, the MMC cartridge mount is undamaged and the sensor arm insert is present. The control panel for the cueing and tonearm lift detached during shipping, highlighting the wisdom of securing such parts. Thankfully, the seller had protected the turntable with a durable plastic sheet, preventing any damage. Reattaching the panel should be simple.
Internally, all parts appear to be present:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Arrival from Italy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-arrival-from-italy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 20:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-arrival-from-italy/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to be working on another Beogram 4000 restoration. The unit arrived from overseas in just three days and was packaged very well, ensuring its safe arrival.
The exterior looks good overall. The wood veneer is undamaged and the dust cover can be polished back to its original shine.
The aluminum trim on the back of the dust cover needs to be reattached, which should be a simple fix. Inside, the aluminum plates need a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Arrives! First Impressions!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-first-impressions-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 07:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-first-impressions-/</guid><description>I was lucky enough to get a Beogram 4000 turntable today! It needs a little work, but it came with a perfect MMC20EN cartridge – I&amp;rsquo;m listening to Miles Davis on it right now and it sounds incredible!
The outside and dust cover are in great shape, and the platter looks really good too. Here are my initial thoughts:
The control panel is nice (ignore the Sharpie marks under the position indicator for now&amp;hellip;):</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Incandescent Light Bulbs in Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, all four incandescent bulbs in the control panel were found to be non-functional. This highlighted the fragility of these bulbs and emphasized the need for a more durable solution. To address this, the original bulbs were replaced with custom-designed LED replacements.
Specifically, the two position indicator bulbs were replaced with surface-mounted LED (SMD LED) units. The two bulbs responsible for illuminating the RPM trimmers were replaced with high-intensity red LEDs.</description></item></channel></rss>