<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Broadband Internet Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband-internet-access/</link><description>Recent content in Broadband Internet Access on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband-internet-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional ISDN PRI For Telephone Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</guid><description>ISDN PRI is a great option for businesses that need a robust phone system. It provides 23 digital lines with features like fast call switching and Caller ID on a single, cost-effective line. However, not all businesses need that many lines.
Smaller businesses or those with lower call volumes can opt for Fractional ISDN PRI, which offers the same features but with fewer lines. This option allows businesses to customize the number of lines they need, typically around 12, leading to significant cost savings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>