<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/work/</link><description>Recent content in Work on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Most Singaporean women believe they are compensated fairly and that their employers value their opinions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/most-singaporean-women-believe-they-are-compensated-fairly-and-that-their-employers-value-their-opinions/</guid><description>Milieu Insight, a Southeast Asian consumer research firm, recently surveyed women in Singapore, Indonesia, and the Philippines to gauge their perceptions of workplace support, opportunities, and rewards.
Concept art featuring a woman
generated by dream by WOMBO.
Some key takeaways include:
While 67% of Singaporean women feel adequately compensated for their work, only half believe they are appropriately rewarded for exceeding expectations.
Although 65% believe their employers welcome their input, only 50% feel that feedback is acted upon.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is implementing measures to ensure that esports becomes a profitable industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</guid><description>Source: SCOGA. From left: Matthias Beyer, Partnerships Lead, Southeast Asia at Twitch, Dennis Ooi, Honorary Secretary of (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA), Kelvin Tan, President and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Nicholas Khoo, Chairman and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Raiford Cockfield III, Director of APAC Partnerships at Twitch, and Dr Charles Ling, COO, Informatics Education.
As esports&amp;rsquo; popularity explodes globally, the (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA) has established new partnerships to cultivate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s esports landscape.</description></item><item><title>60% of employed Singaporeans report feeling burned out</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/60-of-employed-singaporeans-report-feeling-burned-out/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic has led 49% of Singaporeans to reevaluate their priorities, with their careers no longer holding the same level of importance. A new study by Employment Hero highlights the significant role employers can play in employee well-being to attract and keep talent, particularly given that 62% of Singaporean employees report experiencing burnout and 57% feel they have an inadequate work-life balance.
Employment Hero, a company specializing in payroll, HR, and people management solutions, suggests that burnout stems from multiple factors.</description></item><item><title>According to Accenture, gaining digital skills could help reduce the gender gap by up to 40 years faster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</guid><description>Source: Accenture. Closing the gender gap at work.
According to Accenture research, digital skills and technologies are empowering women in Singapore to secure and progress in their careers. However, a wage disparity persists, with men earning more. Ranked 5th out of 31 countries in Accenture&amp;rsquo;s research, Singaporean women demonstrate significant progress in digital fluency, reflecting their adoption and utilization of digital tools for knowledge acquisition, networking, and enhanced efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness.</description></item><item><title>IWG: The Transformation of the World of Work in 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 19:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</guid><description>This image, created using the AI tool Dream by WOMBO, depicts a concept of modern office work.
As the leading global provider of flexible workspaces, IWG, known for brands like Regus and Spaces, has identified ten significant workplace trends anticipated to influence global work dynamics in 2024. The company predicts the continuation of hybrid work models, citing ongoing research by institutions like Stanford University that suggests a significant portion of white-collar workers will maintain this approach.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Dell EMC was recognized as one of the top companies to work for in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</guid><description>Dell EMC Singapore has been recognized as the 8th best company to work for in Singapore in 2016. This ranking comes from a comprehensive study conducted by the Great Place to Work Institute Singapore, which evaluates workplace culture.
The study utilizes 58 metrics from employee surveys and company audits to measure the factors that contribute to a positive and successful work environment. Only organizations where a majority of employees consider it a great place to work are eligible for inclusion.</description></item><item><title>Increase your productivity by installing a treadmill at your desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</guid><description>A recent study featured in the journal Plos One found that using a treadmill desk could lead to higher productivity compared to a traditional desk setup.
[Image of a treadmill desk]
Source: Plos One
This study, titled &amp;ldquo;Treadmill Workstations: The Effects of Walking while Working on Physical Activity and Work Performance&amp;rdquo;, was conducted by researchers from the University of Minnesota-Twin Cities, University of Texas-Arlington, Mayo Clinic, and Arizona State University. Over 12 months, they observed the impact of treadmill desks on physical activity and work output at a financial services company.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Herbalife has found that women in Singapore who work are less active than men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</guid><description>Herbalife, a worldwide nutrition company, has found some differences in the health outlooks and routines of working men and women in Singapore. Their Nutrition at Work survey showed that, compared to men, women in Singapore tend to stay at their desks longer, eat lunch at their desks more, and have more difficulty being active during a typical workday.
“Our aim as a global nutrition company is to provide members and customers with high-quality nutrition products that support healthy eating and active lifestyles,” said Dr.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An improved chair designed to alleviate back discomfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</guid><description>Simon Hong, a neuroscientist, is seeking funding for his invention, the Chairbot. This robotic chair aims to eliminate back pain by suggesting new positions to the user based on their current posture.
Source: Kickstarter page
The Chairbot&amp;rsquo;s unique design features a split seat that encourages users to alternate between sitting and standing, reducing strain on the spine. Hong explains on the Kickstarter page that this constant shifting prevents the spinal trauma associated with maintaining a single posture for long periods.</description></item><item><title>Skills and challenges for global citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</guid><description>A new book by an INSEAD professor explores the unique skills and challenges faced by &amp;ldquo;citizens of the world&amp;rdquo; – individuals who hold multiple passports or live outside their home country. These individuals often come from diverse backgrounds, navigating multiple cultures and languages, which has driven their success. Author Linda Brimm, an Emeritus Professor of Organisational Behaviour at INSEAD, emphasizes the importance of a global mindset in international business and problem-solving, stating that these individuals offer valuable insights for addressing today&amp;rsquo;s complex challenges.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>Cisco: The adoption of hybrid work has enhanced the quality of life for many individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-the-adoption-of-hybrid-work-has-enhanced-the-quality-of-life-for-many-individuals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-the-adoption-of-hybrid-work-has-enhanced-the-quality-of-life-for-many-individuals/</guid><description>A recent global Cisco study indicates that hybrid work arrangements in Singapore have led to improvements in overall employee well-being, work-life balance, and performance. While companies have seen gains in employee productivity, there&amp;rsquo;s room for improvement in fostering an inclusive work environment and fully implementing hybrid work models to enhance employee experience and preparedness.
Cisco&amp;rsquo;s study, titled &amp;ldquo;Employees are ready for hybrid work, are you?&amp;rdquo;, revealed that 56% of Singaporean employees believe their work quality has risen, and 60% reported increased productivity.</description></item><item><title>The future of work revolves around extracting valuable business insights from data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 01:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</guid><description>The rise of robotics and artificial intelligence (AI) is a significant development for the workforce. The shortage of skilled professionals across industries has made automation increasingly appealing to employers. It is evident that automation and AI have the potential to replace a considerable portion of tasks currently performed by humans.
Reactions to this trend are varied, ranging from optimism to apprehension. An Oracle study reveals that 93% of individuals would readily follow instructions from robots in the workplace, demonstrating a high level of trust in automation.</description></item><item><title>Part 12: 2023's Work Trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</guid><description>Source: Deel playbook. 12 work
trends for 2023.
Deel, a provider of payroll and compliance solutions for global teams, has identified twelve emerging workplace trends for 2023:
Overemployed
Deel found that remote workers are increasingly taking on multiple jobs simultaneously, leveraging flexible schedules and asynchronous communication tools.
The Chief Remote Officer (CRO)
The role of CRO is gaining traction, with companies seeking individuals to oversee all aspects of remote work, including in-person events, time-zone management, compensation, and communication tools.</description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure.</description></item><item><title>Balancing work and play on your smartphone: Four helpful tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. View the full infographic.
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming harder to separate our work and personal lives with smartphones being used for both. For instance, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Lumia 640 and 640 XL come with an Office 365 subscription.
Dr. Mark Batey, an Organizational Psychologist at Manchester Business School in the UK, collaborated with Microsoft to offer advice on finding a good balance:
1. Capture inspiration immediately.
He says, &amp;ldquo;Make use of note-taking apps on your phone to jot down brilliant ideas as they come, anytime and anywhere.</description></item><item><title>How Technology Enables The 4-Hour Workweek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</guid><description>Timothy Ferriss&amp;rsquo; book, &amp;ldquo;The 4-Hour Workweek,&amp;rdquo; captivated my attention with its intriguing title and concept. It challenges the conventional 40-hour workweek and suggests a lifestyle where individuals can achieve personal and financial freedom by working less.
Ferriss, who identifies as a &amp;ldquo;vagabond,&amp;rdquo; emphasizes embracing technology and shifting perspectives to design a fulfilling life filled with travel and adventure. He challenges the traditional notion of working tirelessly for decades before retirement, proposing instead a series of &amp;ldquo;mini-retirements&amp;rdquo; interspersed with periods of work.</description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action.</description></item><item><title>Helping individuals with disabilities transition from training programs to meaningful employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Individuals with disabilities should be placed in jobs where they can acquire skills on the job, rather than receiving training without a clear path to employment. Christy Lynch, CEO of KARE Ireland, an organization supporting individuals with intellectual disabilities and their families, emphasized the importance of collaborating with both individuals with disabilities and employers to create truly empowering opportunities. He spoke at the &amp;ldquo;Towards an Inclusive Workforce 2015&amp;rdquo; event, co-organized by SPD and supported by SG Enable and the Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA).</description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway.</description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant outlines three key strategies for remaining employed in the coming decade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-outlines-three-key-strategies-for-remaining-employed-in-the-coming-decade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 02:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-outlines-three-key-strategies-for-remaining-employed-in-the-coming-decade/</guid><description>Cognizant&amp;rsquo;s Jobs of the Future Report highlights a three-part theme, Coaching, Caring, and Connecting, which prioritizes human skills and predicts their importance in the future job market, regardless of technological advancements.
Coaching Coaches can transform work by making it more engaging, humane, and meaningful. Individuals with a knack for mentoring and helping others improve in areas like finance or personal well-being should focus on developing these skills further.
Caring Future-oriented organizations will prioritize employee well-being alongside technological advancement.</description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date.</description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future.</description></item><item><title>Emirates provides LinkedIn Learning courses during flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates will offer LinkedIn courses inflight.
Emirates has teamed up with LinkedIn to offer a selection of LinkedIn Learning courses on its inflight entertainment system, ice. This makes Emirates the first international airline to provide these courses during flights.
This new addition to the ice system will launch in November and reflects Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to offering passengers fresh and diverse entertainment options. The free LinkedIn Learning courses, led by experts, range from 20 minutes to over two hours in length.</description></item><item><title>Workaholic and Proud of IT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 22:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re deeply involved in technology, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you might identify as a workaholic. Did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a day specifically for acknowledging workaholics? It&amp;rsquo;s not an official holiday, of course, as that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t align with the workaholic spirit. Workaholics Day falls on July 5th, the day after most people are recovering from their Fourth of July festivities.
While others are recovering from fireworks or tending to minor burns, you might find yourself busy with crucial hardware upgrades in a server room.</description></item></channel></rss>