<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hard Brexit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hard-brexit/</link><description>Recent content in Hard Brexit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hard-brexit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Benefits of a Hard Brexit? Transforming Britain's £24 billion worth of unicorns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The pro-Brexit group &amp;ldquo;Change Britain&amp;rdquo; recently released a statement claiming significant financial benefits for the UK following a &amp;ldquo;hard Brexit,&amp;rdquo; where the UK leaves both the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market and customs union. This claim was widely circulated in the media despite being fundamentally flawed.
While the report attempts to offer a thorough analysis, it highlights the poor quality of the overall Brexit debate. The report&amp;rsquo;s claim of a £24 billion benefit originates from three key areas: ending contributions to the EU budget, potential savings from reduced regulation, and the anticipated benefits of new trade agreements.</description></item><item><title>The Failed Gamble: Brexit Election aftermath and the future steps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-failed-gamble-brexit-election-aftermath-and-the-future-steps/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent UK election concluded with an unexpected &amp;lsquo;hung Parliament,&amp;rsquo; where no single party secured a majority in the House of Commons. This raises questions about the future of Brexit.
Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s Conservative party undeniably faced a major setback. The Prime Minister called for this election three years ahead of schedule, seeking a stronger majority to solidify her Brexit plan. Instead, voters reduced her majority, resulting in a minority government.</description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures.</description></item></channel></rss>