<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recap on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recap/</link><description>Recent content in Recap on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Lubrication of Platter Motor Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the DC motor was lubricated. This particular motor uses brushes and has simple sleeve bearings.
To access the bearings for lubrication, the pulley and outer housing were removed. The pulley is attached to the shaft with glue, allowing for easy removal. After taking out two small screws, the housing can be opened and the motor taken out.
Next, the black rubber vibration insulation boot was removed, revealing the circuit board connected to the brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Main PCB and Installation of a Biasing Trimmer for TR3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</guid><description>After getting the Beogram 4002 (5513) operational again, I focused on fully restoring the main PCB. This involved installing a trimmer to correctly calibrate TR3, the transistor responsible for amplifying the signal from the record detection sensor. The board&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown below:
The RPM relay and trimmers had already been replaced by the owner. I finished the restoration by replacing all electrolytic capacitors
and adding a trimmer to enable bias adjustment at the base of TR3.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: New power supply capacitors and belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-new-power-supply-capacitors-and-belts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-new-power-supply-capacitors-and-belts/</guid><description>In the last update on this Beocord 5000 (Type 4923), I was about to install new belts and replace the power supply&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors.
This post covers the completion of those tasks.
The original power supply capacitors are shown below.
&amp;hellip;and the replacement capacitors are here.
Next up are the belts.
First is the tape counter belt.
Now for the clutch wheel and flywheel belts. Replacing these requires disassembling some brackets.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration and Test Drive with Cal Tjader and Claus Ogerman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable for an Australian customer who purchased it on eBay. The turntable arrived in poor condition.
My initial evaluation is documented here.
This post details the unit&amp;rsquo;s restoration, excluding the dust cover, which will be covered separately.
I began with the DC platter motor, as is customary, since the bearing lubrication process requires a few days. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable. Initial assessment of the unit can be found on a separate blog post.
The restoration began with the platter motor, as its bearings require a lengthy oil treatment. The motor was extracted, disassembled, and its bearings were submerged in oil under a vacuum to allow for optimal oil diffusion.
Concurrently, the carriage assembly was cleaned. All &amp;ldquo;motion critical&amp;rdquo; parts, including the arm and its associated mechanisms, were removed, ultrasonically cleaned, and reassembled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration Including a Refurbished Keypad and Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This unit is currently for sale. Please, see here.
This post details the complete restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) from Arizona, which I first inspected as shown here. The unit&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is pictured below:
My first step, as always, was to initiate oil infusion for the platter motor bearings. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:
I took it apart to extract the bearings (two small rings on the black pad):</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This blog post details the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a client in Florida. A previous post documented the initial assessment of the unit.
Upon beginning the restoration, the turntable was in relatively original condition. However, the platter motor showed signs of prior work, evidenced by an incorrectly installed pulley.
To address this, the motor was removed and disassembled to extract and lubricate the bearings. This involved immersing them in motor oil under vacuum until air bubbles ceased to appear, indicating the bearings were properly saturated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and one of the challenges is finding modern replacements for the large capacitors used in the 1970s. I received a 3D-printed adapter that allows me to neatly install smaller, current-generation capacitors.
These photos show the adapter with the new capacitors in place:
For reliability, I used two 300uF capacitors wired together to replace the original 150uF motor capacitor. The remaining capacitors are high-quality Rubycon, Panasonic, and Multicomp components chosen for their longevity.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Power Supply and Replacing the Reservoir Capacitors with a 3D Printed Fixture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</guid><description>It seems Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen made two versions of the Beogram 4002 (5513) with different power supply setups, both designed with a possible CD4 upgrade in mind. The output board could be swapped for one with a pre-amplifier and CD4 decoder. One version powers the CD4 board directly from the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s 30V rail and uses a single 4000uF capacitor.
My Beogram 4002 uses a separate power supply for the CD4 board, with its own transformer winding, bridge rectifier, and 1000uF capacitor.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Total Recap - Replacement of all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 10:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>This article revisits a complete restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, focusing on the replacement of electrolytic capacitors for improved long-term reliability. While not as crucial as with amplifiers due to lower operating temperatures, capacitor replacement is recommended for optimal performance.
The Beocord 9000, designed for serviceability, allows access to its numerous electrolytic capacitors. Unlike its predecessors, it offers easier access by removing the front and back panels instead of extracting the main circuit boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Too Early Arm Lowering and RPM Change During START</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5524) turntables I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing had a recurring issue: during the start-up sequence, the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consistently lower at the 30 cm mark. Occasionally, the RPM would unexpectedly switch to 45 right after pressing start.
Troubleshooting was challenging because the problem was intermittent. I replaced all the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay, and trimmers, as detailed on my blog. To test, I installed the boards in my own Beogram 4002 (5513).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors on the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</guid><description>I began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) by replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards with high-quality 105C capacitors. I made sure to use components from reputable Japanese brands like Nichicon and Rubycon, sourcing them through trusted distributors like Newark and Mouser. The process was straightforward, aside from uncovering a spider web (and its architect) beneath the main PCB. This restoration project also highlighted the existence of at least two different solenoid control circuits within the 5513 series.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>Some time ago, a customer in Texas purchased a Beogram 4000 turntable on eBay from a seller in New York. The turntable was in fair condition, as detailed on the blog (see hyperlink). To address a cracked corner on the dust cover, the decision was made to acquire a second Beogram 4000, allowing the creation of one flawless unit from the two. With the arrival of the second turntable, the restoration began.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a Plug-In Ready SMD LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I installed the latest iteration of my SMD LED light source for the tracking sensor.
Previously, I designed a drop-in SMD LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb fixture, which worked well. However, it still relied on the original, cumbersome tracking sensor sensitivity adjustment process. This process involves carefully positioning the light sensors relative to the light source, a task made difficult by the mechanism&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and the adjustment mechanism&amp;rsquo;s coarseness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Rebuilding the Main and Output PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</guid><description>I recently got the main circuit board, output circuit board, and DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5524) turntable. A customer in the UK sent them to me to fix because the platter&amp;rsquo;s RPM wasn&amp;rsquo;t consistent and the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower to the correct position when starting.
My usual process for these is to replace the electrolytic capacitors, install a new relay, and swap the single-turn RPM adjustment knobs with 25-turn ones for more precise control.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the AC Motor Voltage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 turntable restoration, I observed a noisy motor, especially at 45 RPM. Replacing the electrolytic capacitors helped but didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem completely. To investigate further, I examined the motor voltage and the signal waveform from the Wien bridge oscillator, a clever design that uses an incandescent light bulb as a variable resistor for amplitude control. I measured the AC waveform amplitude at one of the motor leads relative to ground.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of New Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 and it was time to replace the large capacitors. This is a process I enjoy, made easier with a 3D printed adapter I designed. This adapter allows for the use of smaller, modern capacitors while maintaining a neat and organized appearance. I have a previous post detailing the connections for anyone who might find it helpful, as there are several jumpers that require re-soldering.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration involved replacing the motor phase capacitor and reservoir. I used a 3D-printed adapter I designed, which allows for secure mounting of modern, smaller capacitors in the original location using the factory bracket. This post provides a closer look at the replacement process and includes a comprehensive wiring diagram for the capacitors. This can be particularly helpful for those tackling this task for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Full Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 22:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable originating from California. The restoration process commenced with the reconstruction of the carriage and arm lowering mechanisms, encompassing meticulous cleaning and lubrication of components like the solenoid and damper.
Following the mechanism restoration, focus shifted to the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm. This involved addressing a common issue: a detached copper pad on the sensor arm assembly. The pad was reattached using epoxy to ensure smooth operation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the carriage transport and arm lowering mechanisms, the electrolytic capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration project required attention. Replacing the original reservoir and motor capacitors in AC motor Beograms is always satisfying, and the 4000 boasts an impressive collection of large capacitors.
The initial step involved removing the outdated capacitors. A quick assessment using a BK LCR tester identified two faulty capacitors. One of the 2200uF capacitors registered a meager 7.</description></item><item><title> Beogram 8000 Type 5613: Finishing the floating chassis components, transformer C1 replacement &amp; cleaning the control panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-finishing-the-floating-chassis-components-transformer-c1-replacement-cleaning-the-control-panel/</guid><description>Last night, I completed work on the floating chassis parts.
I reassembled the cleaned tangential drive parts, including the spindle, spindle nut, rails, and new bracket, and installed them on the floating chassis.
Following the service manual&amp;rsquo;s instructions, I lubricated the spindle. The lubricants are very similar to those used in the Beogram 400x, which is logical given that both turntable series have comparable tangential drive systems. The Beogram 8000 lubrication chart had one intriguing item that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t previously considered: an entry for lid damping grease.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This article details the refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5504) turntable. An initial assessment of the unit is documented in a previous post here.
The turntable, stripped of its panels and platter, appeared relatively untouched. However, evidence of previous work emerged later.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly, which was quite dirty. After disassembling and cleaning the parts, the platter motor and capacitors were removed for thorough cleaning. The motor housing, including the bearings, underwent an oil infusion process under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all switch terminals on a Beogram 4000 restoration project, the next step involved addressing the electronics. The restoration typically begins by replacing outdated reservoir and motor capacitors, as they are frequently out of specification and nearing failure. The image provided showcases these original components.
To ensure proper fitment of the (smaller) modern replacement capacitors, a custom 3D-printed fixture was designed and utilized. This fixture secures the capacitors in the correct position.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and Rebuilding of the Platter RPM Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</guid><description>During the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable, the electrolytic capacitors were replaced and new relays were installed to enhance RPM stability. The aging tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail catastrophically, were replaced as a precautionary measure. The main board was refurbished, replacing the electrolytic capacitors and installing new relays, including a custom-designed replacement for the Siemens relay that ensures precise RPM control.
The original reservoir capacitor, a dual-capacitor unit no longer in production, was replaced with a 3D-printed fixture housing two modern capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5501 from Sweden: Full Technical Restoration and Some Interesting Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 turntable (Type 5501 with optical carriage position detection) for a complete technical restoration. The unit arrived without a dust cover. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the Beogram right after unpacking:
Besides a number of loose parts that fell out when I opened the box, I was surprised to see that the cartridge was still mounted on the tonearm:
Fortunately, the MMC4000 cartridge had a small plexiglass guard in place, preventing any damage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the AC Motor and Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s printed circuit boards, attention shifted to the capacitors associated with the reservoir and motor, as well as the AC motor itself. The capacitor and motor section appeared as shown before any servicing.
Visual inspection revealed leakage from the larger capacitors, indicating a critical need for replacement. The extent of the capacitor bay&amp;rsquo;s condition was evident upon their removal.
The AC motor was extracted for servicing, taking advantage of its disconnected state from the capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>This article details the comprehensive restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The initial evaluation of this unit is detailed in a separate post.
The turntable was first disassembled, revealing the need for bearing lubrication in the platter motor, a common issue in these models. This process typically takes a few days.
While the bearings were being re-lubricated, the intricate carriage mechanism, responsible for raising and lowering the tonearm, was addressed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Recapping the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 restoration, I replaced all electrolytic capacitors as a preventative measure, opting for durable 105C types from reputable Japanese brands. Tantalum capacitors, particularly in older equipment, can fail dramatically, even catching fire.
On the power supply board, I discovered a missing screw and a loose one, potentially creating a dangerous short circuit scenario. Thankfully, no damage was evident. I replaced the tantalum capacitors and secured the board with a new stainless steel M3 screw.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with Stanley Turrentine and Milt Jackson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Kentucky. The unit, pictured below, was in excellent condition, making it ideal for a complete refurbishment.
As is typical with DC motor Beograms, the platter motor was the starting point. These motors commonly suffer from dried-out bearings, leading to speed instability. The extracted motor is shown here:
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings:
The bearings, visible as two small rings on the black pad, were then submerged in motor oil under a vacuum:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Complete Functional Restoration and a Spin with the Cal Tjader Quartet!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The restoration began with addressing the motor, a common procedure for these models. After removing and disassembling the motor, the Oilite bearings were submerged in oil and placed under a vacuum for several days to replenish lubrication.
Next, the carriage and arm mechanisms were disassembled, cleaned, and re-lubricated. This included taking apart and servicing the damper. The main PCB was removed, and both power transistors were replaced.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and Reservoir Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the tonearm and drive carriage mechanisms on this Beogram 4002 (5513), attention turned to the electronics. The initial phase involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, RPM trimmers, and the relay to guarantee smooth operation for years to come.
The main PCB in its original state is shown here.
The same PCB is pictured here after component replacement.
This image provides a detailed view of the RPM control section.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Exchanging all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>After finishing most of the mechanical work, it was time to start repairing the electronics on a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable. Replacing all electrolytic capacitors is recommended, as their internal fluid often leaks or dries up. I use high-quality Japanese capacitors to ensure my repairs last as long as possible. Tantalum capacitors, in particular, must be replaced because they can fail dramatically if a short circuit occurs, potentially damaging the circuit board.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Completing the Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 10:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</guid><description>During the summer of 2019, I had the opportunity to work on a Beogram 4002 turntable from Virginia, specifically restoring its DC platter motor. I recently received the entire unit for a complete overhaul. The arm lowering mechanism had been previously restored and was in excellent condition. My attention turned to the remaining areas needing restoration.
To begin, I tackled the main PCB. The first photo illustrates its original condition:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, RPM Relay and Trimmers on the Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild on this Beogram 4002 (5513), the main PCB was addressed. All electrolytic capacitors were swapped with high-quality, Japanese-made, 105C-rated capacitors. The existing Tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail dramatically, were preemptively replaced with modern equivalents to avoid any potential issues. Images illustrate the original board and the sections targeted for capacitor replacement.
The author designed a replacement for the original Siemens relay using a modern, fully encapsulated SMD relay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Restoration and a Test Spin with Oscar Peterson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable from Sweden in very corroded condition. To address the extensive corrosion, I chose to use another 4000 unit as a donor for parts. The donor unit, while missing some components, was free of corrosion.
My restoration process started with the carriage. I disassembled and cleaned the arm lowering system, damper, carriage rods, and spindle in an ultrasonic bath. Additionally, the sensor arm assembly was removed to lubricate the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs - New Capacitors, RPM Trimmers and RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the motor and reservoir capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step involved rebuilding the PCBs. This typically involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM trimmers, and the RPM relay. The main PCB, which is difficult to remove due to its hardwiring, was &amp;lsquo;flipped&amp;rsquo; for component replacement.
After replacing the components, the rebuilt board was ready for installation. A new relay was used, as the original Siemens relays often experience oxidation, hindering proper RPM switching.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board and Adding a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-and-adding-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>During the Beogram 4002 restoration, I took the opportunity to rebuild the output board while cleaning the keypad contacts. A common issue with these units is low or absent volume in one or both channels, often caused by the output relay. To address this, I replaced it with a modern, durable Japanese relay designed to last for many years. The original output board is shown here:
The old Siemens relay was swapped out for a custom-designed SMD relay assembly, pictured below:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs and Restoring the 33 RPM Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</guid><description>Typically, my restoration process for Beogram 4002 turntables begins with the arm lowering and tracking systems. However, this particular Beogram 4002 (5513) required a different approach. The control system needed attention, so I opted to address the PCBs first.
Upon unpacking the turntable, I discovered that the platter motor would power on as soon as it was plugged in. This unusual behavior was caused by the seller connecting the motor to the standby LED header on the circuit board  a connection point rarely used on the 5513 boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with the Bill Evans Trio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable from a Massachusetts customer. The initial evaluation can be found here.
The restoration began by addressing the carriage system. This involved cleaning hardened lubricants from various parts like the arm lowering mechanism, rods, spindle, linkages, and damper, and applying modern synthetic lubricants.
A key aspect of the Beogram 4000 is its solenoid-activated switches, which frequently experience oxidation and require attention. The contact terminals were removed and re-plated with nickel and gold-cobalt alloy for optimal performance and corrosion resistance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of Main and Output Printed Circuit Boards, and a New Reservoir Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the PCBs after addressing the decayed transport lock bushings. The main PCB was first, as shown below:
In addition to replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay and trimmers were targeted due to their susceptibility to corrosion and impact on RPM stability. The following image highlights the RPM section in its initial condition:
Modern, encapsulated 25-turn trimmers replaced the old ones, and a new relay was installed (interested enthusiasts can obtain a replacement relay by email or through the contact form).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Original Dual Main Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</guid><description>While restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513), I had the chance to improve my design for a replacement part for the reservoir capacitor. This part lets me use two modern, high-temperature Japanese capacitors in place of the original dual-capacitor unit, which is no longer available. My previous design worked, but this new version is more robust and easier to 3D print. I&amp;rsquo;m getting better at designing for 3D printing; for instance, I learned to minimize overhangs.</description></item></channel></rss>