<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech Support on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tech-support/</link><description>Recent content in Tech Support on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tech-support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dual Core, Quad Core, Up to 64 Core Managed Dedicated Servers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</guid><description>The race for faster processors has shifted its focus. Instead of increasing clock speeds, the industry is now prioritizing multi-core and multi-processor designs to improve performance.
The good news is that there are affordable options for powerful processing, including managed dedicated servers with excellent support.
Entry-level systems typically feature dual-core processors. For increased power, users can opt for quad-core or hexa-core (6 cores) configurations. For even greater performance, dual or quad-processor dedicated servers are available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Website Hosting Services A Bovine Beyond The Cow of Duty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/website-hosting-services-a-bovine-beyond-the-cow-of-duty/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 19:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/website-hosting-services-a-bovine-beyond-the-cow-of-duty/</guid><description>Considering a new website or a change for your existing one? Look no further than FatCow, where affordable web hosting meets exceptional service.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let the name fool you; FatCow is anything but cheesy. Unlike other website hosting companies, FatCow provides excellent service without inflated prices, hidden fees, or complicated setups. They are also environmentally conscious, utilizing 100% wind energy. Starting at $3.67 per month with a 30-day money-back guarantee, FatCow offers a free domain name, unlimited disk space and bandwidth, unlimited POP mailboxes, MySQL Databases, and the ability to host multiple domains on one account...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/website-hosting-services-a-bovine-beyond-the-cow-of-duty/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/website-hosting-services-a-bovine-beyond-the-cow-of-duty/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Have Your Computer Repaired Online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-your-computer-repaired-online/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 03:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-your-computer-repaired-online/</guid><description>Experiencing computer problems but unsure what to do? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve waiting weeks for repairs. Online tech support services like BluePhone offer expert help remotely.
BluePhone employs skilled technicians who provide personalized support. Unlike typical corporate help desks, BluePhone is available to anyone via subscription. Subscribers enjoy unlimited access and assistance with any tech issue, big or small.
Telephone troubleshooting is a common help desk service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-your-computer-repaired-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-your-computer-repaired-online/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>