<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General Court Case Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-court-case-law/</link><description>Recent content in General Court Case Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/general-court-case-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Standing of a Third Country before the CJEU: AG Hogan's Opinion in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council in Relation to State Immunity and Comity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
In a legal opinion issued on February 20, 2021, Advocate General Hogan addressed a crucial procedural issue: Can a non-EU country legally challenge EU actions before the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)? This question holds significance because the Court has never directly ruled on it within the context of sanctions, and it delves into the principles governing the relationship between EU law and other international law subjects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dalli Saga: A Story of Accountability and Defenestration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City University
The forced resignation of the Santer Commission in 1999 due to accusations of fraud, maladministration, and mismanagement remains a relevant topic even after nearly two decades. The European Commission has faced ongoing criticism for its administrative shortcomings and the structural flaws within the Union&amp;rsquo;s accountability system. Numerous reports have portrayed the Commission as an institution grappling with systemic and political irregularities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Council v H: Another Court victory in the Common Foreign and Security Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</guid><description>Graham Butler, PhD Fellow at the Centre for Comparative and European Constitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen, Denmark
Introduction
This summer, the Court of Justice (the Court) issued two significant decisions influencing the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) legal landscape. Despite the Treaty of Lisbon&amp;rsquo;s integration of this largely intergovernmental area (previously the Second Pillar) into the unified ‘EU’, its legacy persists. Enduring evidence of CFSP as a distinct yet incorporated legal domain allows it to be termed ‘CFSP law’...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New discoveries in the "Mellifera" case shed light on access to environmental justice under the Aarhus Regulation, but the underlying issues remain unchanged.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</guid><description>Mario Pagano, PhD candidate in EU environmental law, European University Institute
Background
The Aarhus Convention is a crucial piece of international law concerning environmental democracy rights. Established in 1998, this UN Convention lays out three procedural rights directly connected to environmental protection: the right to environmental information, the right to participate in environmental decision-making, and the right to legal recourse on environmental issues (the three Aarhus &amp;ldquo;pillars&amp;rdquo;).
The Aarhus Convention Compliance Committee (ACCC), formed in Geneva in 2002, ensures that the legislation of the Convention&amp;rsquo;s Parties aligns with the Convention itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU General Court has declared Adidas' three-stripe trademark to be invalid.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:20:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/</guid><description>Alexandros Antoniou, a legal expert from the University of Essex, analyzes a June 19, 2019, ruling by the EU General Court (GC) that invalidated Adidas&amp;rsquo;s trademark of three parallel stripes. The court upheld the EU Intellectual Property Office&amp;rsquo;s decision, which found the trademark too simplistic and lacking distinctiveness, both inherently and through use.
Adidas&amp;rsquo;s trademark, registered on May 21, 2014, for apparel, footwear, and headgear, was challenged by Shoe Branding Europe BVBA in December 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Judicial review of monetary policy and banking supervision by the European Central Bank.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</guid><description>Introduction
The European Union has experienced widespread political and economic consequences due to the financial crisis. These effects extend to the legal realm, leading to the European Central Bank (ECB) not only creating debatable new methods for involvement in monetary policy but also acquiring new authority in banking supervision. Additionally, the ECB, alongside the European Commission and the International Monetary Fund (forming the &amp;lsquo;Troika&amp;rsquo;), has become engaged in austerity measures within Member States requiring financial support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The General Court has made a ruling on the European Citizens' Initiative, stating that the Commission must provide reasons for refusing to register proposals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 16:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/</guid><description>Anastasia Karatzia, Assistant Professor in EU law, Erasmus School of Law
Introduction
On February 3rd, the General Court (GC) overturned a European Commission decision for the first time, determining that the Commission failed to provide sufficient justification when it denied registration to a proposed European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). This concise judgment in the Minority SafePack case concerns procedural matters within the relatively new ECI, which was established in 2012. The judgment offers valuable insight to those interested in the ECI and, more broadly, in opportunities for citizens to participate in EU lawmaking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-general-court-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-european-citizens-initiative-stating-that-the-commission-must-provide-reasons-for-refusing-to-register-proposals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In search of the Babel-fish: Addressing language discrimination in EU law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-search-of-the-babel-fish-addressing-language-discrimination-in-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-search-of-the-babel-fish-addressing-language-discrimination-in-eu-law/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano
Introduction: Language Differentiation in the EU
The EU already faces a considerable language challenge with 24 official languages recognized by Regulation n. 1/1958. While the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights allows citizens to communicate with EU institutions in their chosen language, the primary working languages are English, French, and German. However, all official EU documents necessitate translation into all 24 recognized languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-search-of-the-babel-fish-addressing-language-discrimination-in-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-search-of-the-babel-fish-addressing-language-discrimination-in-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>