<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Third Pillar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/third-pillar/</link><description>Recent content in Third Pillar on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/third-pillar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period.</description></item><item><title>Do crime victims now have additional rights under EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
*This analysis is taken from the upcoming 4th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Victims of crime are often disheartened not just by the crime itself but also by the criminal justice system&amp;rsquo;s indifference to their needs. To tackle this issue, the EU introduced a Directive on crime victims’ rights in 2012 that Member States were required to implement by November 16, 2015. This law supersedes an earlier Framework Decision on this matter from 2001.</description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013.</description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues.</description></item><item><title>The EU Data Retention Directive provides the context for the background.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</guid><description>By Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
As the Snowden leaks continue to make waves, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) is set to rule on a case (Digital Rights Ireland, Seitlinger and Others) that could potentially invalidate the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive in its present form. This directive mandates that private companies retain large amounts of their users&amp;rsquo; telecommunications data, just in case law enforcement needs it for criminal or terrorism investigations.</description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>How committed are Member States to safeguarding fundamental rights through the EU's common rules on detention?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</guid><description>By Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
In early February 2014, the Commission released a concerning report regarding &amp;ldquo;common rules on detention.&amp;rdquo; The report revealed that a mere 18 out of 28 EU member states had implemented any of the intended instruments. This study was purely quantitative and did not assess the effectiveness of the rules or their impact on individuals.
The inadequate implementation of these fundamental commitments to enhance detainee rights is worrisome.</description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state.</description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro.</description></item><item><title>The argument for the UK to remain in the European Arrest Warrant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Maria Fletcher, Senior Lecturer in Law at the University of Glasgow, and Steve Peers, Professor of Law at the University of Essex, collaborated on this piece.
As of December 1, 2014, the UK government will have to decide which pre-December 2009 EU laws on criminal law and policing to potentially rejoin. One of the most contentious issues is whether to opt back into the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. This article presents the argument for rejoining this legal framework.</description></item><item><title>What's all the fuss about the draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</guid><description>Cian C. Murphy, The Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London
The transnational public sphere continues to be gradually suppressed. The European Union&amp;rsquo;s initial legislative response to recent killings by Islamic State militants in Europe and elsewhere is a draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism, which was published last month. The Directive, which seeks to expand the scope of EU law in national criminal law regarding terrorism, will replace the Framework Decision on Combating Terrorism, which was initially approved in 2002 and revised in 2008.</description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion.</description></item></channel></rss>