<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Maker on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/maker/</link><description>Recent content in Maker on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:57:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/maker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>De’Longhi introduces the La Specialista Prestigio, a high-end pump espresso coffee machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/de-longhi-introduces-the-la-specialista-prestigio-a-high-end-pump-espresso-coffee-machine/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/de-longhi-introduces-the-la-specialista-prestigio-a-high-end-pump-espresso-coffee-machine/</guid><description>De&amp;rsquo;Longhi recently unveiled its new La Specialista Prestigio espresso machine with a global campaign titled &amp;ldquo;Perfetto.&amp;rdquo; This campaign, directed by Damien Chazelle and starring Brad Pitt, offers a glimpse into Pitt&amp;rsquo;s daily routine, emphasizing how De&amp;rsquo;Longhi&amp;rsquo;s products seamlessly integrate into a refined lifestyle. The advertisement showcases a world where achieving the perfect cup of coffee is as simple as pressing a button, providing a luxurious bean-to-cup experience. The campaign can be viewed on YouTube.</description></item><item><title>Tech Saturday at Suntec will demonstrate the future direction of consumer technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</guid><description>Source: Smart Nation website.
Tech Saturday is a public carnival presented by the Infocomm Development Authority of Singapore to demonstrate the power of technology. In addition to tech exhibitions, visitors can participate in interactive &amp;ldquo;Worksheds.&amp;rdquo;
Located throughout the carnival, these booths provide hands-on technology workshops. With options ranging from circuits to 3D printing, all workshops are free. While pre-registration is closed, same-day registration is available at counters near the Worksheds.</description></item></channel></rss>