<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Refugee Quotas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/refugee-quotas/</link><description>Recent content in Refugee Quotas on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/refugee-quotas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections.</description></item><item><title>EU Law and Policy on the Relocation of Asylum-Seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers recently discussed the legal aspects of the refugee crisis, focusing on international law. This post will examine the relocation of asylum-seekers within the EU, a topic that has sparked considerable debate. The EU recently passed a second decision on this matter, facing opposition from several member states. This decision follows an earlier one from September. Both are temporary measures, effective for two years, but there is a proposal for a permanent system.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries.</description></item><item><title>Preserving the Formal Rule of Law in the EU's Asylum Policy: The CJEU's Ruling on the Asylum Relocation Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, Ph.D. Researcher in European Union Law at the School of Law and Government of Dublin City University*
*Reblogged from the Bridge Network blog
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling found Poland, Hungary, and the Czech Republic to be in violation of European Union (EU) law. The violation stems from their failure to implement two Council Decisions outlining the relocation of asylum seekers.</description></item><item><title>Comments on the outcomes of the most recent European Council meeting regarding EU migration policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU faces another crisis alongside &amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;: a surge in immigration. Initial EU responses culminated in an emergency summit in April. I previously discussed the outcomes of that summit. Subsequently, the Commission released its EU migration &amp;ldquo;Agenda&amp;rdquo; in mid-May, followed by detailed proposals. Last week, the European Council revisited immigration, reaching several conclusions. This post outlines those conclusions and offers my commentary. The third part of the conclusions, which vaguely promises increased cooperation with third countries, is omitted.</description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly.</description></item></channel></rss>