<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Credit Card on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/credit-card/</link><description>Recent content in Credit Card on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/credit-card/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival.</description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally.</description></item><item><title>Card-not-present fraud is on the rise, leaving two-thirds of credit card issuers in the Asia-Pacific region vulnerable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 11:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</guid><description>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing a surge in e-commerce, but this growth is accompanied by an increase in online fraud. A survey of fraud professionals in the region, conducted by predictive analytics firm FICO, revealed that card-not-present (CNP) fraud is the fastest-growing type of fraud. Nearly all (94%) of the survey respondents reported an increase in CNP fraud.
eMarketer, a research firm, projects that B2C e-commerce sales in the Asia Pacific region will reach US$525.</description></item></channel></rss>