<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>App on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/app/</link><description>Recent content in App on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:42:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Bleisure app emerged as the winner of the Sabre hackathon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</guid><description>Source: Sabre. From left: Isolda Josy and Pranay Roy, Moments; Mendis from Sabre Travel Network Asia Pacific; and Marco Angeles, Moments.
A team from Singapore won the 24-hour Destination Hack: Singapore, Sabre&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Asia Pacific hackathon. Participants were tasked with designing a new technology app that could revolutionize travel – from planning and booking to the overall experience.
The winning app, Moments, caters to the increasing demand for &amp;ldquo;bleisure&amp;rdquo; travel in the Asia Pacific region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bleisure-app-emerged-as-the-winner-of-the-sabre-hackathon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Styletag is known for identifying the latest fashion trends globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</guid><description>Want to stay stylish at work? South Korea&amp;rsquo;s SK Planet has refreshed its Styletag mobile app using trends from New York Fashion Week, which wrapped up on February 13th.
Source: Styletag page at the Play Store
Styletag gathers and organizes user-submitted fashion content worldwide, offering both style inspiration and shopping details. The app includes contributions from professional photographers, amateur enthusiasts, and invited fashion experts.
This free app is compatible with iOS 7 (iPad, iPhone, and iPod) via iTunes and Android devices through the Google Play store...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/styletag-is-known-for-identifying-the-latest-fashion-trends-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The FastGig app has been released to connect flexible workers with job opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</guid><description>FastCo, the company known for its Asian non-executive job platform FastJobs, has launched FastGig, an app designed for the expanding gig economy. FastCo claims this is one of the first apps specifically for gig workers in Southeast Asia.
FastGig, operating as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first workforce-as-a-service (WaaS) platform, connects skilled flexible workers with companies facing staffing shortages, particularly during peak seasons.
Julian Tan, FastCo&amp;rsquo;s Founder &amp;amp; CEO, highlights FastGig as a solution to a significant market gap, providing flexibility for both workers and businesses and transforming Singapore&amp;rsquo;s gig economy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The handbag app reveals the newest handbag options available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 15:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</guid><description>Source: Google Play Store.
Swipe Boutique has launched a new fashion app for Android devices called &amp;ldquo;handbag swipe.&amp;rdquo;
The app allows users to explore thousands of the latest handbag designs from over a hundred popular brands, including Topshop, New Look, and Michael Kors.
With a browsing experience resembling Tinder, shoppers can swipe through various handbag options. The app enables users to curate personal wish lists, purchase desired products instantly, or save handbag details for future reference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers of Credit Suisse in Hong Kong now have access to a new digital private banking app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse e-brochure.
Credit Suisse has introduced its digital private banking platform in Hong Kong, launching an improved Private Banking Asia Pacific app.
This digital platform offers a new way to serve clients, blending digital and in-person experiences. Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s first digital private banking platform debuted in Singapore in March 2015. After analyzing client usage and conducting usability tests for over a year, the bank has introduced an enhanced app in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guvera introduces support for Apple TV and updates its product</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</guid><description>Source: Guvera.
Guvera, a music streaming service supported by brand funding, has announced significant upgrades to its product and compatibility with Apple TV.
The updated Guvera 3.0 app introduces music channels and a variety of new editorial features. These include artist interviews, news articles, reviews, photo galleries, brand competitions, and product promotions.
Hazel Savage, Head of Marketing and Operations for Guvera Asia, stated that the company recognizes that music is more than just individual tracks; it represents a whole culture and way of life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Atari guarantees a fitness app that incorporates gamification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atari-guarantees-a-fitness-app-that-incorporates-gamification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 07:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atari-guarantees-a-fitness-app-that-incorporates-gamification/</guid><description>Atari, a company known for interactive entertainment, is launching Atari Fit™, a fitness app with gaming elements, in early 2015.
Atari collaborated with certified personal trainer Michael Porter to create over 150 exercises for the app, including circuit training, running programs, and personalized routines. Users can earn points by exercising alone or with friends to unlock classic Atari games such as Pong, Centipede, and Super Breakout.
Porter highlights that all exercise routines within Atari Fit are certified, ensuring their safety and effectiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atari-guarantees-a-fitness-app-that-incorporates-gamification/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atari-guarantees-a-fitness-app-that-incorporates-gamification/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces three new exclusive routes with a 20% discount on all flights until February 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</guid><description>AirAsia is the sole airline offering flights for three new routes: Johor Bahru to Tawau, Singapore to Kota Bharu, and Singapore to Terengganu. The airline is currently promoting these routes with fares as low as RM69* for travel between Johor Bahru and Tawau. This offer is valid for bookings made before February 16th, 2014, for travel dates between April 18th, 2014 and January 31st, 2015.
Welcome banners at Changi Airport..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Nanu, the free calling app, provides a fresh approach to connecting with customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</guid><description>Source: nanu website.
Nanu, the first entirely free mobile calling app, is experiencing rapid growth in its monthly and daily active users. Based in Singapore, the startup claims its app&amp;rsquo;s active user rates are almost twice the industry standard, with 56% monthly active users and 19% daily active users.
CEO Martin Nygate points out that many tech startups avoid disclosing these figures due to poor performance. He&amp;rsquo;s pleased to share nanu&amp;rsquo;s positive data, reflecting both strong download numbers and increasing app usage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nanu-the-free-calling-app-provides-a-fresh-approach-to-connecting-with-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips from Akamai for optimizing app engagement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</guid><description>A report from Akamai highlights that 95% of gamers quit playing a game within the first month. The company states that slow loading times are a major factor, causing 40% of players to abandon games. Additionally, 20% of gamers expect instant page loads.
To enhance user retention, Akamai suggests strategies applicable to any app:
Anticipate Large-Scale Success: Be prepared for a global player base. Utilize a robust content delivery network to handle high traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Activpass provides discounted rates for wellness activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</guid><description>Source: Activpass. Activpass is a mobile-based marketplace for booking lifestyle activities.
The team behind Activpass, a platform designed for businesses and professionals in fitness, wellness, and beauty, believes in living life to the fullest. Their mobile platform gives users access to over 1,000 services like yoga, training sessions, golf, massages, and beauty treatments, all without requiring a long-term commitment.
Users can easily book and pay for services on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China's unicorn company has revealed the top 10 rankings in the Google Play store for its Wi-Fi crowdsourcing app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</guid><description>Source: Play Store.
The free app WiFi Master Key, which helps users find and connect to crowdsourced Wi-Fi hotspots, is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia. It helps people access the internet in a region where connectivity is rapidly expanding.
The app lets users share Wi-Fi hotspot information with the community. While this information allows others to connect for free, the app prioritizes privacy and security by encrypting and storing shared Wi-Fi passwords in its cloud database instead of revealing them directly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Facebook enhances the Messenger chat platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
During Facebook&amp;rsquo;s F8 conference, the company launched Messenger Platform. With over 40 apps available for download, users can enhance their conversations through GIFs, photos, videos, audio clips, and more.
Source: Facebook. Users will be prompted to install new apps.
Source: Facebook. Messenger will allow businesses and customers to communicate directly, replacing traditional methods like email or phone calls.
Facebook also provided a sneak peek of Businesses on Messenger...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aptugo develops customized web software without requiring any training</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 03:31:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</guid><description>Aptugo, a software tool designed to help individuals without coding experience build websites, is currently in beta testing. Developed by the company Aptugo, the software is expected to launch in 2015.
&amp;ldquo;Aptugo has the potential to bridge the gap between large and small businesses. Users don&amp;rsquo;t need any programming knowledge to use it,&amp;rdquo; stated Gaston Gorosterrazu, Head of Aptugo. &amp;ldquo;However, those with coding experience can further enhance what Aptugo can do, as it is designed to empower users and expand their capabilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aptugo-develops-customized-web-software-without-requiring-any-training/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DIB Mobile app has been enhanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</guid><description>Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has launched an upgraded version of its mobile banking app for iOS and Android devices. This enhanced app offers access to over 60 services, including features designed to help users manage their personal finances effectively.
With smartphone usage on the rise and Nielsen reporting that 78% of the UAE population owns at least one such device, DIB&amp;rsquo;s mobile app caters to this growing trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox and Microsoft collaborating more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Dropbox and Microsoft are joining forces to make it easier for their users to work together. This collaboration will allow users to seamlessly work with Dropbox and Microsoft Office on their phones, tablets, and computers. Given that over 1.2 billion people use Microsoft Office and 35 billion Office files are stored in Dropbox, this partnership has the potential to benefit a lot of users.
This integration will enable users to edit their Dropbox documents directly in the relevant Office application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HandySpeech app, which converts handwriting to speech, is now available on Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</guid><description>iSpeak4U, a company known for developing mobile apps for individuals with speech and hearing impairments, has launched an Android version of their app HandySpeech. This app offers a simple and efficient communication tool for those with speech difficulties.
Source: iSpeak4U. HandySpeech running on various devices.
With HandySpeech, users can input text on a device screen using their finger or a stylus, and the device will then vocalize the written words. The app is designed to store frequently used phrases and adapt to the user&amp;rsquo;s handwriting style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the ability to hail a cab using Hailo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</guid><description>Hailo, a highly-rated taxi app boasting more five-star reviews than any other similar service, launched in Singapore on October 29th. With a global network of over 60,000 drivers and a strong user base exceeding 1.4 million, Hailo reports a ride request every two seconds somewhere in the world.
Source: Hailo. From left: Benny Lim, Managing Director, SMRT Road Holdings; Ron Zeghibe, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Executive Chairman, Hailo Global, and Yu Hsiang Wong, General Manager, Hailo Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zap Delivery in Singapore guarantees fast and reliable couriered deliveries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</guid><description>Source: Zap Delivery.
Zap Delivery, an on-demand courier service, promises quick, safe, and dependable deliveries of packages and documents within Singapore in two hours or less using their new mobile app. This app utilizes advanced authentication and real-time tracking to provide peace of mind for those awaiting deliveries.
“We’ve experienced our fair share of delivery issues, so we created a user-friendly app that fosters trust,&amp;quot; explained Michael Tan, Zap Delivery Co-founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zap-delivery-in-singapore-guarantees-fast-and-reliable-couriered-deliveries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recharge your prepaid mobile accounts using du's mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</guid><description>For the first time in the UAE, du customers can now top up their prepaid mobile phones using mPay. This new service was unveiled today at GITEX Technology Week 2015.
Fahad Al Hassawi, Chief Commercial Officer at du, stated, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to be the first operator offering prepaid recharge via mPay, making it easier for our customers to top up their prepaid du lines conveniently. We believe this will be highly popular among our users...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor simplifies the process of capturing important moments during a trip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the biggest travel website globally as of July 2015 according to comScore Media Metrix, has introduced a &amp;ldquo;Travel Timeline&amp;rdquo; feature for its mobile app. This feature allows users to record and share their travel experiences. When turned on, it automatically generates a timeline of the places visited and photos taken at each location. This timeline can be viewed chronologically or as a route on a map.
Adam Medros, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s SVP of Global Product, highlights the feature&amp;rsquo;s value in documenting and sharing travel memories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Someline Apple Tree app will produce apples for charity as long as you refrain from using your phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</guid><description>Source: Google Play.
Libern Lin, a student entrepreneur attending Republic Polytechnic in Singapore, has expanded his app, Someline Apple Tree, with financial support from the Singapore Computer Society (SCS).
The app incentivizes real-life interactions by rewarding users with digital apples for reducing phone usage. Lin, the app&amp;rsquo;s creator, explained that they wanted to use the app&amp;rsquo;s concept for a good cause. So, they used the S$30,000 grant from SCS to add a charitable component to the app in line with IDA&amp;rsquo;s Code for Charity*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New visa services for Dubai are now available through VFS Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</guid><description>VFS Global, a company that provides outsourcing and technology services for governments and diplomatic missions globally, has announced expanded visa services at its 33 Dubai Visa Processing Centres (DVPCs) across 16 countries. These services cater to all types of travelers, including those on business or attending MICE events.
Planning to launch UAE visa applications through DVPC mobile apps this summer (June to August), VFS Global will offer a device-compatible online platform via www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-visa-services-for-dubai-are-now-available-through-vfs-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi cab booking app is now available in Kuala Lumpur and will soon be expanding to more countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a cab booking app, has expanded its reach to Malaysia and will be pre-installed on Celkon phones in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal.
Developed by India-based On Time Technologies, TaxiPixi launched in Malaysia this week. Celkon, a mobile phone manufacturer, will pre-install the app on its devices in several countries. Pradeep Yerraguntla, Celkon&amp;rsquo;s Head of Digital, stated that Celkon will promote the app through its app store and website, targeting consumers in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new NYNJA app allows you to communicate, make purchases, and utilize cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: NYNJA Group. Screen captures of the NYNJA app, currently in beta.
NYNJA Group, a Hong Kong-based communications and mobile technology firm, has introduced NYNJA, a new communications app with a built-in digital marketplace and cryptocurrency wallet.
The NYNJA app works across multiple platforms and integrates voice, text, and visual messaging with business management and e-commerce tools. Its features are powered by its own financial ecosystem and cryptocurrency, NYNJACoin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singdaptive has released a new app for asynchronous vocal coaching</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singdaptive-has-released-a-new-app-for-asynchronous-vocal-coaching/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:21:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singdaptive-has-released-a-new-app-for-asynchronous-vocal-coaching/</guid><description>Singdaptive, a vocal training platform, has introduced Exchangely, a mobile application designed for vocal coaching.
Source: Singdaptive. With Exchangely, students can submit recordings to Singdaptive&amp;rsquo;s instructors for feedback at a later time, rather than receiving live, immediate feedback.
Exchangely allows singers and Singdaptive vocal coaches to exchange videos, enabling instructors to offer personalized feedback, exercises, and assignments tailored to each singer’s objectives. This method empowers singers to learn at their preferred pace within a platform that connects them with Singdaptive&amp;rsquo;s team, provides quizzes, and monitors their advancement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singdaptive-has-released-a-new-app-for-asynchronous-vocal-coaching/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singdaptive-has-released-a-new-app-for-asynchronous-vocal-coaching/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Airtel to launch hi!India plans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:05:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</guid><description>Singtel and Airtel have partnered to provide Singtel prepaid mobile customers with access to high-quality calls to India through the Airtel Talk app. This service was previously only available to credit card holders.
Now, Singtel prepaid customers can utilize Airtel Talk by purchasing hi!India plans using their prepaid credits. Calls made through Airtel Talk are transmitted via standard IDD lines, resulting in enhanced call clarity.
Hi!India plans start at S$5 for 100 minutes (S$0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ANA has developed an app to assist passengers in relaxing and diverting their attention away from takeoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</guid><description>Source: App Store.
All Nippon Airways (ANA), a major Japanese airline, developed an app to alleviate stress during the most anxiety-inducing part of air travel. Based on a survey of US airline passengers revealing that takeoff causes the most anxiety (68%), ANA created &amp;ldquo;ANA Takeoff Mode.&amp;rdquo; This mobile app aims to help travelers relax and focus on something other than takeoff.
The app presents a simple puzzle accompanied by calming music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verify the authenticity of KSA sales and promotions using this app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</guid><description>Source: MCI. HE the Minister of Commerce and Investment Dr Majid bin Abdullah Al Qasabi launched the Sales app on 31 January 2017.
The Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) in Saudi Arabia has introduced a mobile application called &amp;ldquo;Sales.&amp;rdquo; This app allows the public to access the MCI&amp;rsquo;s database of authorized sales and promotional offers. The goal is to help users find genuine deals and discounts quickly.
Through the app, consumers can browse information on more than 27,000 retail locations and over 700,000 licensed products registered with the MCI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The intelligent coach for individuals with diabetes is designed to improve long-term quality of life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</guid><description>A new &amp;ldquo;smart coach&amp;rdquo; service aims to assist individuals with type 2 diabetes in developing healthier lifestyle choices for improved long-term well-being. Diabetes, particularly when poorly managed, can result in complications such as vision loss, kidney issues, and nerve damage. It has also been linked to Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease, sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;type 3 diabetes.&amp;rdquo;
The global rise of diabetes presents significant healthcare cost concerns. Holmusk, a digital health and data analytics company, highlights that over 415 million people worldwide have diabetes, a figure that continues to grow annually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If apps don't offer speed, simplicity, and security, consumers will not hesitate to abandon them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</guid><description>Source: CA Technologies infographic.
People are pickier than ever about the apps they use, so businesses that don&amp;rsquo;t offer a good app experience could lose a significant portion of their customers. A regional study* sponsored by CA Technologies shows that mobile and desktop applications in the Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) region have become key to earning customer loyalty.
Software: the New Battleground for Brand Loyalty – A survey of 1,449 consumers and 259 business decision-makers across five APJ nations pinpointed three major factors influencing the customer experience: Source: CA Technologies infographic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Booqed offers a selection of workspaces available for rent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</guid><description>Booqed, an online marketplace for booking meeting rooms and workspaces, has introduced its mobile app on the Apple App Store. This app offers a convenient way to find and reserve available spaces in a city, allowing users to book instantly or in advance and make payments directly from their smartphones or tablets.
Businesses can also benefit from this service by monetizing their underutilized meeting or conference rooms. Booqed provides a platform for them to list and rent out these spaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is encouraging subscribers to use their phones for payment at the supermarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</guid><description>A picture of a Dash payment reader at a FairPrice checkout.
Starting November 17th, shoppers can use Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash mobile payment app at over 200 NTUC FairPrice locations, including their supermarkets, Xtra hypermarkets, and standalone Cheers stores.
Gan Siok Hoon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of mCommerce, Consumer Singapore, stated that as a major fintech provider, they were excited to partner with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer, FairPrice, to offer this fast and secure payment option to their over half a million daily shoppers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Flickr App for iPad has been optimized for iOS 8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a new Flickr app designed for iPads, allowing users seamless photo management across all devices. Yahoo claims the app is optimized for iOS 8, providing an enhanced experience for capturing, editing, and browsing images.
Source: Yahoo.
Current iPad users can update their existing Flickr app, while new users can download it from the App Store. The app supports multiple languages, including English, French, Indonesian, Korean, Chinese, and Vietnamese...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flickr-app-for-ipad-has-been-optimized-for-ios-8/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AsiaKredit has introduced a consumer lending platform in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>AsiaKredit&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make financial services more accessible in the Philippines. They aim to achieve this by making credit easier to obtain and improving the approval rates for individuals with limited or no credit history.
Source: pera247 website. Screenshot of the pera247 app.
Pera247 is a completely digital platform offering short-term loans, up to 90 days, through a mobile wallet. These loans are typically small, unsecured, and target consumers with limited financial history...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiakredit-has-introduced-a-consumer-lending-platform-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at Emaar can customize their experience using the latest apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-emaar-can-customize-their-experience-using-the-latest-apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 10:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-emaar-can-customize-their-experience-using-the-latest-apps/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Emaar introduces custom-designed apps, linked with their internal systems, to improve the customer experience.
• Apps for Address Hotels + Resorts, Vida Hotels and Resorts, Palace Downtown, and Manzil Downtown are now available. These apps are personalized based on guest profiles and preferences. The Rove Hotels App will be launched soon.
• The apps connect with backend systems, providing management teams with important real-time data to improve the guest experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-emaar-can-customize-their-experience-using-the-latest-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-emaar-can-customize-their-experience-using-the-latest-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Word Lens assists travelers in translating signs instantly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</guid><description>Quest Visual, the company behind the augmented reality app Word Lens, has decided to offer the app and all of its language packs for free for a limited time. This includes languages like English, French, Italian, Portuguese, and Russian. This gesture of thanks to their users comes as the company transitions to new ownership under Google.
Source: Word Lens page on Play Store.
You can download the Glass, Android, and iOS versions of Word Lens from the Quest Visual website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fit Spotting assists users in finding hotels that have excellent gym facilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</guid><description>Fit Spotting is an iOS mobile application that helps users discover, evaluate, and read reviews about hotel gyms and fitness facilities.
Tarek Atwan, the creator of Fit Spotting, explained that as a frequent traveler and fitness enthusiast, he found it challenging to locate reliable reviews and images of hotel gyms while booking accommodations. Information was scattered across the internet, lacking a central platform where users could access consolidated feedback, ratings, and photos to accurately depict the hotel&amp;rsquo;s fitness offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fit-spotting-assists-users-in-finding-hotels-that-have-excellent-gym-facilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By 2022, consumers are projected to spend over $155 billion on apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 18:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</guid><description>Source: App Annie. App Annie predicts app trends will change by 2022. Figures are in US dollars.
A new report by App Annie, a mobile app data and insights company, projects global consumer spending on apps to reach US$156.5 billion by 2022, a 92% increase from 2017.
The App Annie Forecast 2017-2022 highlights major trends expected to shape the app economy in the coming years. Global first-time app downloads are predicted to rise by 45% between 2017 and 2022, hitting 258...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2022-consumers-are-projected-to-spend-over-155-billion-on-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Support World Vision in the Philippines by using the Gift It app to make a contribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</guid><description>World Vision, a charitable organization, has teamed up with Gift It, a crowdgifting platform. Gift It allows users to create personalized campaigns to fund gifts from various stores or support charitable causes through foundation partners.
Jun Godornes, World Vision&amp;rsquo;s Director for National Resources and Development, highlights the app&amp;rsquo;s convenience, stating it simplifies giving while raising awareness for their programs that support children through education, disaster relief, and economic development. Gift It also features a social aspect, enabling friends to contribute collaboratively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank has enhanced its mobile application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</guid><description>Source: Alizz Islamic Bank. The app.
Alizz Islamic Bank has introduced a redesigned mobile banking app and online platform to solidify its position as a customer experience frontrunner in Oman.
The dual-language app, compatible with both Android and iOS devices, boasts high-level security features and a self-registration option. Users can conveniently manage web banking logins, money transfers, bill payments, and other transactions using QR codes. The app is compatible with 3D Touch technology and is the first of its kind in Oman to provide in-app alerts for new transactions and payment reminders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates has observed that 20% of its users access the website via iPads, prompting the airline to develop an iPad app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 10:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</guid><description>Emirates airline has introduced the Emirates App for iPad, available globally through the App Store. This app allows users to easily explore destinations and manage their Emirates travel experiences.
With a simple tap, users can discover information on over 130 Emirates destinations across six continents and learn about the airline&amp;rsquo;s renowned services.
The Emirates App for iPad simplifies travel management for Emirates customers, whether they&amp;rsquo;re on the move, in flight, or at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-observed-that-20-of-its-users-access-the-website-via-ipads-prompting-the-airline-to-develop-an-ipad-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new version of McAfee Mobile Security has been launched by Intel Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</guid><description>Intel Security has released the newest version of McAfee Mobile Security (MMS) for Android devices. This updated software offers enhanced security and improved device performance.
As people increasingly rely on their mobile devices for personal and sensitive tasks, MMS provides protection and addresses the need for faster speeds, longer battery life, and secure browsing on Android phones and tablets.
This new version of MMS allows users to maximize their Android device performance with features that optimize speed and battery life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-version-of-mcafee-mobile-security-has-been-launched-by-intel-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi is working to increase the popularity of taxis in India and other countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</guid><description>A new free taxi booking app called TaxiPixi is gaining popularity in India. Available on Android, iOS, and online, this less-than-a-year-old service offers reliable options for booking cabs, motorcycles, or auto-rickshaws for point-to-point trips or hourly packages.
TaxiPixi&amp;rsquo;s online home page
Co-founder and CEO Kajal Dubey believes that the biggest obstacles to increased taxi use are the uncertainty of finding a ride and the perception that taxis are much more expensive than driving...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New touchless camera app is now accessible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:22:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/</guid><description>Source: Crunchfish.
Crunchfish, in partnership with MOMAX, has introduced MOMAX cam, a hands-free camera application for selfie sticks.
MOMAX cam allows users to take pictures using gestures, touch, and Bluetooth.
Here are some of its key features:
Snap photos with a simple V-sign gesture. Use a touchless grab gesture to set the timer for capturing photos from up to 3 meters away. Switch between the front and rear cameras, as well as zoom in and out, using the Bluetooth trigger to get the perfect shot...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-touchless-camera-app-is-now-accessible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evernote introduces a new and improved app with a redesigned interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</guid><description>Evernote has announced three updates: a brand new app, a significantly enhanced feature, and a major app redesign.
As detailed in a recent blog post, the company will introduce &amp;ldquo;Scannable,&amp;rdquo; a mobile scanning app. Scannable can transform physical items like business cards and receipts into digital content that can be easily shared and acted upon. It also integrates with the ScanSnap Evernote Edition desktop scanner, enabling shared scanning across a user&amp;rsquo;s network and essentially turning it into a shared office resource...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-introduces-a-new-and-improved-app-with-a-redesigned-interface/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks Indonesia has launched the Starbucks Mobile App</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Use the mobile app to make purchases at Starbucks.
Starbucks Indonesia has launched its mobile app, offering customers a quick and easy way to pay at over 260 stores across the country.
Expanding upon the cashless Starbucks Card system introduced in 2013, the Starbucks Indonesia mobile app (available on iPhone and Android) allows customers to pay for purchases by scanning a barcode linked to their registered Starbucks Card...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avast Wi-Fi Finder helps you find trustworthy Wi-Fi connections globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</guid><description>Avast has released Avast Wi-Fi Finder, an Android app that helps users locate trustworthy, fast, and secure Wi-Fi connections no matter where they are. The app uses a map interface to display recommended and crowdsourced hotspots.
&amp;ldquo;Many of us, whether traveling or working remotely, have struggled to find dependable and secure Wi-Fi,&amp;rdquo; said Gagan Singh, President of mobile at Avast. &amp;ldquo;With Avast Wi-Fi Finder, consumers can now easily locate a safe and fast Wi-Fi connection at the gym, hotel, airport, bus station, library, or café...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avast-wi-fi-finder-helps-you-find-trustworthy-wi-fi-connections-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Traveloka will introduce awards based on audience participation for Asia's Got Talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 13:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</guid><description>Traveloka, a popular Southeast Asian travel app, is sponsoring the second season of AXN&amp;rsquo;s Asia&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent and introducing the Traveloka Awards.
The Traveloka Awards will recognize the contestant with the most compelling background, emphasizing unique talents and strong family and friend connections.
Premiering this October, Asia’s Got Talent on AXN will feature ten episodes, including auditions, semifinals, a finale, and a results show revealing the winner of a $100,000 prize from Traveloka...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ItSeez3D has released an updated version of its 3D scanner app for iPad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</guid><description>Source: itSeez3D page on the App Store.
itSeez3D, a company that develops 3D scanning software, has released an updated version of their mobile scanning app, also named itSeez3D. This app, designed for use with the Occipital Structure Sensor 3D device, now allows iPads to generate lifelike, full-body 3D models.
This updated app serves as a valuable tool for 3D printing, enabling the scanning of a full-color figurine in under two minutes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new version of Flickr is now available for iOS 9</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 02:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s Flickr app for iOS 9 now includes features designed for the updated operating system.
Source: Yahoo.
The app utilizes 3D Touch on the latest iPhones. This allows users to preview content by pressing lightly on the screen. For example, in the Camera Roll, lightly pressing a photo shows a preview, while a harder press expands it to full screen.
Another 3D Touch feature, &amp;ldquo;Quick Actions,&amp;rdquo; lets users perform certain tasks directly from the app icon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-version-of-flickr-is-now-available-for-ios-9/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing complimentary content and data to commemorate Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 51st birthday on August 9th, Singtel is offering customers complimentary mobile data, alongside free access to Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO.
Postpaid mobile users will enjoy free data from 12:01 am to 11:59 pm on August 9th, allowing them to connect with family and friends on social media, stream music, and watch videos.
From August 5th to 9th, Singtel TV subscribers will have free access to over 140 channels, including popular options like Disney Channel, National Geographic Channel HD, FOX Movie Premium HD, KBS World HD, Astro Ria, and Sun TV...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SmartUp introduces the Digital Readiness Experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</guid><description>Source: SmartUp website.
Screen capture of the SmartUp
platform.
SmartUp, a mobile-first knowledge-sharing platform, has introduced a Digital Readiness Experience. This offering utilizes microlearning modules to educate the workforce on trending technology topics.
This multi-week Digital Readiness Experience is available for purchase by SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s corporate clients for their employees, as explained by Deborah Tan-Pink, SmartUp&amp;rsquo;s Global Head of Marketing.
&amp;ldquo;The Digital Readiness Experience is a four-to-six-week program designed to shift attitudes and knowledge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartup-introduces-the-digital-readiness-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The language learning app HelloTalk has reached 1 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</guid><description>Source: HelloTalk app page at the Play Store.
The mobile language learning app HelloTalk has reached over one million registered users globally, according to its developer, HelloTalk.
The HelloTalk app allows users to teach each other their native languages using their mobile devices. Users can communicate in real-time with native speakers through various features, helping them practice their target language.
Over one million HelloTalk users, representing over 200 countries, use the app to learn various languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Subscribe to Grabz for exclusive insider privileges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</guid><description>Source: Grabz website.
Grabz is a subscription service that provides its members with exclusive benefits and special offers. Using location-based alerts and a wide range of affiliated businesses, the app connects its subscribers with exclusive deals and privileges in their city.
For a monthly fee of S$15.98, premium members enjoy invitations to events and promotions such as discounted business class airfare and exclusive access to limited-edition luxury watches.
Premium members also get access to the Grabz Concierge, a personalized booking service that assists members with securing reservations at clubs and getting on guest lists for exclusive parties in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>