<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dwdm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dwdm/</link><description>Recent content in Dwdm on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dwdm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Metropolitan and wide area networks are getting faster. Undersea cables are moving from 10 to 40 and even 100 Gbps, and land-based fiber lines are already at 100 Gbps. This means large companies, healthcare organizations, and video producers are starting to find their networks inadequate. The good news is that there are more affordable options than ever before.
There are several practical ways to boost your MAN or WAN bandwidth beyond one Gigabit per second, up to 10 Gbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Wavelengths to Serve You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</guid><description>When your network reaches its maximum capacity, you typically need to upgrade to a faster network with faster components. Upgrading your entire network infrastructure can be extremely expensive. However, with fiber optic networks, you can significantly increase bandwidth within the same cables using a technique called Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM).
WDM allows multiple light beams to transmit data simultaneously over a single fiber optic cable. Each beam operates on a different wavelength, increasing capacity proportionally to the number of beams...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (EoDWDM)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</guid><description>Large organizations with high bandwidth needs, such as financial institutions and research labs, often require more capacity than standard telecom services offer. Building a custom fiber network by installing owned or leased dark fiber is one solution. Another is leasing wavelengths on existing fiber infrastructure.
Your Own Fiber Installing fiber optic cable on your own property provides control over both the physical space and network assets. However, construction costs increase significantly beyond your premises, especially when obtaining right-of-way permissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic DWDM Up to 100 Gbps Per Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 09:44:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth keeps increasing, even during economic slowdowns. The main reason is the huge popularity of video, especially high-definition video, which needs a lot of bandwidth on all types of networks. Now, fiber optic systems using DWDM (Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing) can handle 100 Gbps per wavelength.
It seems like just yesterday we were excited about moving from 10 Gbps to 40 Gbps channels. Now, Alcatel-Lucent offers an upgrade that handles both 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps on a single optical carrier for their 1830 Photonic Service Switch (PSS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services For The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</guid><description>Initially only utilized by telecom companies, wavelength services are now accessible to large organizations. These high-bandwidth fiber optic services are necessary for entities like hospitals, financial institutions, government service providers, video production companies, content delivery networks, and research facilities. The demand for faster data transfer solutions is constantly increasing. But are wavelength services the answer?
A wavelength, or lambda, is light at a specific frequency, similar to a distinct color. It is usually measured in nanometers (wavelength) rather than terabits per second (frequency)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-for-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</a></p></description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zayo Lights Denver With Expanded Fiber Optic Network Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</guid><description>Zayo Group, a prominent fiber optic bandwidth infrastructure provider, is expanding its existing metro fiber network coverage in Denver and Colorado Springs. The expansion project will add 521 miles of fiber along the Colorado Front Range, encompassing cities like Boulder, Longmont, Loveland, Greeley, and Fort Collins. This increase brings Zayo&amp;rsquo;s total fiber optic network in the Denver area to 900 route miles, supporting industries such as research, technology, education, and energy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber - Dark, Lit and Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve decided that a fiber optic connection is no longer optional for your business; it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for productivity. The next step is determining which type of fiber to get. You might be surprised to learn there&amp;rsquo;s more than one option.
One Strand, Multiple Options
The foundation of all fiber optic connections is the transmission of information through modulated light waves within a glass strand. The fiber cable entering your building will appear the same regardless of the type...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Networks Need Denser Wavelength Multiplexing To Meet Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</guid><description>Despite the economic downturn, fiber optic network providers are experiencing a surge in demand. However, instead of widespread digging, they are leveraging technology to boost capacity on existing infrastructure.
XO Communications, a leading fiber optic network provider, recently revealed plans to double its capacity per fiber strand using Infinera&amp;rsquo;s optical line equipment. The Infinera Line System 2 increases the channel count for C-band fiber optic systems from 80 to 160, resulting in an extra 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eastern Tennessee Gets Lit for Business Fiber Optic Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 09:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</guid><description>Nashville, Tennessee, is known for its robust fiber optic network infrastructure. The city&amp;rsquo;s thriving business sector, particularly in healthcare, publishing, banking, transportation, and music, demands high bandwidth, a need that extends across the state.
EarthLink, a leading bandwidth provider, has recently expanded its fiber optic network in eastern Tennessee. The project includes a 343-mile route connecting Nashville to Knoxville, with additional routes linking Knoxville to Chattanooga and Bristol. This network offers connection points in multiple cities, including Cookeville, Oak Ridge, and Cleveland, and major Points of Presence (PoPs) in Knoxville, Morristown, Johnson City, and Bristol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Wavelength Services for San Francisco and Silicon Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-wavelength-services-for-san-francisco-and-silicon-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-wavelength-services-for-san-francisco-and-silicon-valley/</guid><description>AboveNet is expanding its high-capacity fiber optic network services by offering new low-latency wavelength services. These services will be available in the San Francisco Bay Area and Silicon Valley, including key locations like Santa Clara and San Jose, California.
AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave solutions utilize ROADM (Reconfigurable Optical Add/Drop Multiplexer) technology, enabling dynamic wavelength add/drops for various protocols such as Ethernet, TDM, storage, and video transport. This results in flexible service options, scalability, and fast provisioning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-wavelength-services-for-san-francisco-and-silicon-valley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-wavelength-services-for-san-francisco-and-silicon-valley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>600 Mbps Ethernet vs OC12 SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</guid><description>Companies that need bandwidth in the fractional Gigabit range have often relied on OC12 SONET fiber optic service. While it remains a solid high-speed choice, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering 600 Mbps Ethernet as well. Comparing these two options might yield some surprising results.
OC-12 (622 Mbps) is the next tier up from OC-3 (155 Mbps) in the SONET optical carrier hierarchy. This service is widely available in Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and as a dedicated internet access connection for mid-sized internet service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Lit Buildings and Near Net Fiber Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic internet service is becoming increasingly essential for modern businesses, but not everyone has access to it. Some businesses don&amp;rsquo;t need the high speeds fiber offers and are content with slower options. Others might have outdated perceptions of fiber&amp;rsquo;s affordability. Many are unaware that fiber might already be available in their building or nearby.
Fiber optic internet isn&amp;rsquo;t the niche product it once was. Even consumers are demanding fiber to their homes for streaming and entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Services to 400 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</guid><description>Bandwidth requirements are clearly increasing. Small companies are upgrading from 1.5 Mbps T1 lines to 10 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, while medium-sized companies are moving towards 50 or 100 Mbps connections. Large companies are continuously seeking even faster Gigabit connections.
While bandwidth typically peaks at 5 or 10 Gbps, some providers offer up to 40 Gbps as they transition to 100 Gbps. However, one provider is setting a new standard with 400 Gbps availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>