<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Comcast on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/comcast/</link><description>Recent content in Comcast on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/comcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comcast’s 100 Gbps Core Network Supports Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</guid><description>Over the past year, major telecom companies have been upgrading their core networks from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. Comcast recently joined this trend by incorporating Ciena&amp;rsquo;s Wave Logic 3 interfaces into their existing Ciena 6500 packet optical platforms. This begs the question: why would a cable company make this change, and how can it benefit your business?
Comcast is widely recognized as a Cable TV provider, or MSO (Multi-System Operator)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cable vs FTTH Bandwidth Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</guid><description>The competition for superior internet speed is underway. Fiber to the Home (FTTH), is perceived as the frontrunner, while Cable Broadband is the contender. It&amp;rsquo;s still uncertain who will come out on top, but one thing is for sure: users with substantial bandwidth requirements will be the ultimate victors.
This clash is unfolding in Washington state, where Comcast, the Cable behemoth, is introducing a 50 Mbps internet service to rival Verizon, the telecommunications giant, and its 50 Mbps FiOS internet service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-vs-ftth-bandwidth-throwdown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pricing Slashed For Michigan 100 Mbps Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</guid><description>Michigan businesses are facing a common problem: the need for faster internet speeds. Traditional options like T1 lines are no longer sufficient for handling increased data demands from video conferencing, cloud-based applications, and automation. While fiber optic services offer the necessary bandwidth, their high cost often makes them inaccessible.
Comcast Business Class emerges as a potential solution, delivering 100 Mbps download and 10 Mbps upload speeds at a price comparable to T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PRI over Cable Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 01:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</guid><description>Many businesses use ISDN PRI, a technology that bundles multiple phone lines onto a single digital cable, for cost-effective phone service. While initially implemented with T1 lines, offering 23 usable voice channels after reserving one for signaling, ISDN PRI can now be delivered over cable networks.
Modern phone systems, including PBX and key systems, typically support ISDN PRI, allowing businesses to scale their phone lines up to 46, 69, 92, or more...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>