<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Evening on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/evening/</link><description>Recent content in Evening on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/evening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During this Ramadan, the Corp Amman will offer Iftar dining and entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Corp Amman Hotel website.
The 4-star Corp Amman Hotel has put together a special offering for iftar and suhoor during Ramadan, showcasing traditional Jordanian hospitality. Guests can enjoy evenings filled with food and music for JD18 per person, not including services and taxes.
The celebration starts with an iftar menu at the Boulevard Restaurant &amp;amp; Poolside Terrace, available all day. The menu features Ramadan favorites such as juices, dried fruits, Arabic breads, soups, salads, pickles, and mezze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>