<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regulation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation/</link><description>Recent content in Regulation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Investing in corporate bonds will be made more accessible for Singaporean investors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has launched two new regulations aimed at making it easier for retail investors – individuals who purchase securities for personal investment purposes – to participate in corporate bond offerings. These changes are part of MAS&amp;rsquo;s broader strategy to expand retail investors&amp;rsquo; investment choices by providing access to simpler, lower-risk investment products.
Corporate issuers typically rely on the wholesale bond market for funding due to the higher expenses associated with reaching retail investors.</description></item><item><title>ERGA and the Audiovisual and Media Services Directive 2.0: A European Regulators Group without Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
In 2014, the European Commission created ERGA to help implement the Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) and support a unified European market. This built upon the existing High Level Group of Regulatory Authorities, established in 2003, which brought national enforcement bodies together twice a year. The goal was to improve collaboration between these authorities to ensure the AVMSD was applied consistently across Europe. This reflects a broader EU trend of forming networks, sometimes including member states, to promote harmonization.</description></item><item><title>Proposed changes to the tenure of independent board directors in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/proposed-changes-to-the-tenure-of-independent-board-directors-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 03:51:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/proposed-changes-to-the-tenure-of-independent-board-directors-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Singapore Exchange Regulation (SGX RegCo) is asking for public opinion on its suggestion to implement a strict nine-year limit for independent board directors (IDs) and end the two-tier voting system for long-serving IDs.
The consultation document states that if directors wish to stay on after the limit, they must be reclassified as non-independent, even if their appointment was previously approved by a two-tier vote.
They are also seeking feedback on making it mandatory for companies to disclose the exact amount and breakdown of board directors&amp;rsquo; and the CEO&amp;rsquo;s pay in their annual report, identifying them by name.</description></item></channel></rss>