<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IoT on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iot/</link><description>Recent content in IoT on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Now, you have the ability to answer calls directly on your Apple Watch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple Watch 3 includes phone capabilities.
Apple has launched the Apple Watch Series 3, a smartwatch with built-in cellular capabilities. With this new feature, users can make and receive calls and texts, and stay connected even when they don&amp;rsquo;t have their iPhone nearby.
This third-generation Apple Watch is designed for health and fitness, offering smart coaching features, water resistance up to 50 meters, and a new barometric altimeter for measuring elevation changes.</description></item><item><title>Actxa Spur makes training in your heart rate zone easier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</guid><description>Actxa has launched the Spur, a wearable fitness tracker that continuously monitors heart rate and provides zone indication. The Spur aims to make heart rate zone training accessible to everyone, not just athletes, by offering a user-friendly alternative to chest straps.
For years, fitness enthusiasts and athletes have used heart rate as a measure of workout intensity. A higher heart rate generally indicates a more intense workout.
The Spur uses a wrist-based sensor to measure resting heart rate and track different heart rate zones: Warm Up, Fat Burning, Cardio, Intense, and Maximum.</description></item><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?</description></item><item><title>Intel Security has released a list of the holiday gifts that are most vulnerable to hacking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</guid><description>· A survey indicates that 80% of shoppers are anticipated to make purchases online this year.
· While 85% of consumers begin utilizing connected devices within a day of obtaining them, a mere 45% report taking the appropriate security precautions.
· Despite acknowledging the significance of device security, nearly half of consumers (46%) are unsure if they are implementing adequate protective measures.
Intel Security has released its second yearly McAfee Most Hackable Holiday Gifts list, aiming to spotlight potential security vulnerabilities linked to popular gift items this holiday season.</description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence.</description></item><item><title>The potential marketing opportunities presented by a customizable wearable device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</guid><description>Source: Broadcast Wear website. Control the shirt&amp;rsquo;s display with an app.
Broadcast Wear, an innovative company from Hyderabad, has introduced a programmable t-shirt with touch-sensitive technology, opening up exciting possibilities for marketing.
Their invention incorporates a flexible, washable LED screen directly into the fabric. Users can pair the shirt with the Broadcast Wear smartphone app to instantly show any text or image. A simple tap turns the screen on and another tap switches it off.</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>Smart mirror launched by FRED Technologies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-mirror-launched-by-fred-technologies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 07:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-mirror-launched-by-fred-technologies/</guid><description>FRED Technologies has introduced &amp;ldquo;Mirror,&amp;rdquo; a waterproof smart mirror designed as a modern-day butler. This Android-powered device displays news and interacts with various lifestyle apps and devices.
Equipped with speakers in a sleek, champagne gold frame, Mirror plays music and responds to voice commands. Its smart display activates when approached and reverts to a standard mirror when not in use. The built-in air purifying technology keeps the surrounding environment fresh.</description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras.</description></item></channel></rss>