<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cyprus on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cyprus/</link><description>Recent content in Cyprus on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:47:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cyprus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Deceptive Client: The case that confused the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
John Grisham&amp;rsquo;s novels often feature a recurring theme: a determined but outmatched lawyer battling a powerful corporation that exploits the legal system, a vulnerable client harmed by the corporation, a polished corporate law firm doing the company&amp;rsquo;s bidding, and an eccentric judge striving for courtroom order. This formula has been a mainstay of his books for over two decades. However, the settings rarely venture beyond the Southern United States, except for occasional plot-driven trips to Caribbean islands.</description></item><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions.</description></item></channel></rss>