<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Common Agricultural Policy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/common-agricultural-policy/</link><description>Recent content in Common Agricultural Policy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/common-agricultural-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Farewell and gratitude for the fish: CJEU provides clarity on international law and institutional matters related to fisheries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s fisheries policy generates disagreement both within and outside the EU because of its effects on fish populations and the economic well-being of fishing communities. Prior to the Treaty of Lisbon, its implementation was essentially under the sole authority of the Council. Although the European Parliament (EP) attempted to gain shared control over some of the policy&amp;rsquo;s external aspects by asserting its consent was required for international fisheries agreements that significantly impacted the EU budget, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) dismissed this claim.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU once again reinforces the EU's external role with In Vino Veritas ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While only a handful of EU countries excel in wine production, it&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed throughout the Union. This simple truth underpins the recent Germany v Council ruling, where the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) bolstered the EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign relations authority, aligning with several previous decisions.
Background
This case centers on instances where Member States act as &amp;rsquo;trustees&amp;rsquo; of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external competence. This situation arises when the EU, despite having authority over a subject, cannot join a treaty or international organization dealing with it (a frequent occurrence).</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General considers the intersection of public health, trade, and competition in setting minimum alcohol pricing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-considers-the-intersection-of-public-health-trade-and-competition-in-setting-minimum-alcohol-pricing/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School Background to the Opinion Advocate General (AG) Bot provided his opinion on September 3rd, 2015, regarding Case C-333/14, which involved the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to establish a minimum price per unit (£0.50) on alcohol sales. This Minimum Unit Pricing (MUP) faced legal challenges from the Scotch Whisky Association, leading to the case reaching the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The CJEU was asked to determine whether the MUP aligned with the single Common Market Organisation (CMO) and the free movement principles of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item></channel></rss>