<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gaming on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gaming/</link><description>Recent content in Gaming on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:27:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore is implementing measures to ensure that esports becomes a profitable industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</guid><description>Source: SCOGA. From left: Matthias Beyer, Partnerships Lead, Southeast Asia at Twitch, Dennis Ooi, Honorary Secretary of (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA), Kelvin Tan, President and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Nicholas Khoo, Chairman and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Raiford Cockfield III, Director of APAC Partnerships at Twitch, and Dr Charles Ling, COO, Informatics Education.
As esports&amp;rsquo; popularity explodes globally, the (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA) has established new partnerships to cultivate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s esports landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel has declared the champions of Season 1 for the PVP Esports Corporate Championship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</guid><description>Teams from Singapore and Indonesia emerged victorious in the corporate category of Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 2020 PVP Esports Community Championships (Season 1).
Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s team, DeloitteOne, and DBS&amp;rsquo;s team, TurretHeist, secured the top spots in the Dota 2 and Mobile Legends: Bang Bang Corporate Championships, respectively. The Indonesian team, HZL Legion (RM Djamiah Putra), claimed victory in PlayerUnknown&amp;rsquo;s Battlegrounds (PUBG): Mobile.
Each winning team received over S$5,000 in cash and prizes. The grand finals, held online from September 5th to 6th due to the COVID-19 pandemic, saw teams competing remotely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience personalized lighting effects with Philips Hue Play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-personalized-lighting-effects-with-philips-hue-play/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 03:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-personalized-lighting-effects-with-philips-hue-play/</guid><description>Source: Signify. Philips Hue Play light effects now available in Singapore.
Signify, a company specializing in lighting solutions, has introduced the Philips Hue Play to the Singapore market. This compact light bar is designed to create an immersive atmosphere with its adaptable placement options.
The Philips Hue Play can function independently as an indirect light source, serving as backlighting or accent lighting.
Using Philips Hue Sync, a software available for both PC and Mac computers, users can synchronize the Hue Play with on-screen content, such as movies, video games, or music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-personalized-lighting-effects-with-philips-hue-play/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-personalized-lighting-effects-with-philips-hue-play/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Promotions for Dell at CEE 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</guid><description>Dell is promoting several products at the Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) 2017. These products, equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors, are designed for an excellent visual experience and enhanced gameplay.
Here are some of the featured products:
Inspiron 13 5000 2-in-1
Original Price: Starting from S$1,699 Show Price: Starting from S$1,299 Features:
Latest 7th Gen Intel Core processor 13.3&amp;quot; FHD (1,920 x 1,080) IPS Truelife LED-backlit touchscreen with wide viewing angles and an infrared (IR) camera Four versatile modes: tent, stand, laptop, and tablet XPS 13 2-in-1..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Basilisk V3 Pro is Razer's most sophisticated mouse yet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:32:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/</guid><description>Razer, a leading brand in gaming lifestyle products, has introduced the Basilisk V3 Pro, a wireless gaming mouse designed for high performance and extensive customization. The mouse boasts features like a Razer HyperScroll Tilt Wheel, Razer Optical Mouse Switches Gen-3, more than 10 programmable buttons, a Razer Focus Pro 30K Optical Sensor, and wireless charging capabilities.
Chris Mitchell, the Head of Razer&amp;rsquo;s PC Gaming Division, highlighted the Basilisk V3 Pro as their most feature-packed gaming mouse yet, packed with everything needed to outperform the competition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CEE is ready to showcase gadgets and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 02:31:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</guid><description>The 4th Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) will be held from May 23rd to 26th, 2019, at Suntec Singapore Convention Centre. The event is organized by Exhibits Inc., a subsidiary of Sphere Exhibits, which is the events and exhibitions branch of Singapore Press Holdings.
Some of the featured events include:
Singapore Robo Fight 2019 (Level 4, Gamex Booth 8601)
Attendees can use smartphones to control miniature battle robots and engage in virtual combat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new smart gaming projector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 01:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the EH-TW6250 Smart Gaming Projector, the most budget-friendly option in their 4K PRO-UHD lineup. This projector delivers an impressive home theater experience with a screen size up to 500&amp;quot;, brightness up to 2,800 lumens, and an input lag* under 20 ms, making it ideal for movie nights and casual gaming.
This all-inclusive entertainment solution features scene-adaptive gamma correction, frame interpolation, HDR10/HLG support, and 3LCD technology. These features combine to provide smooth, color-accurate, high-resolution images with balanced white and color light output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AMD has launched a new bundle featuring the Radeon RX 590</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amd-has-launched-a-new-bundle-featuring-the-radeon-rx-590/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 10:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amd-has-launched-a-new-bundle-featuring-the-radeon-rx-590/</guid><description>Source: AMD website. The AMD Raise the Game bundle comes with free PC versions of three games.
AMD is dedicated to making exceptional gaming experiences accessible to everyone. That&amp;rsquo;s why they&amp;rsquo;re promoting their Radeon RX 590 as a budget-friendly yet powerful 1080p graphics card that can deliver impressive visuals at over 60 frames per second (FPS).
Utilizing the redesigned Polaris architecture, the 8 GB Radeon RX 590 offers the memory capacity needed to provide lifelike visuals and high performance for HD gaming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amd-has-launched-a-new-bundle-featuring-the-radeon-rx-590/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amd-has-launched-a-new-bundle-featuring-the-radeon-rx-590/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>